yo yo yo welcome to another episode
before we start the episode I have some
killer news forly those who are
interested in building for web 3 it is
hackathon season Once Again the Solana
Renaissance hackathon is around the
corner and this time the best projects
and developers stand a chance to win up
to half a million in prize money and
there's $150,000 in prize money for all
the sidetracks as well this includes
deepin payments consumer apps gaming
infrastructure and all the selected
Winners Get accept into the colosium
accelerator where you get a $250,000
check along with mentorship from other
web3 Founders so if you have a killer
startup idea this is your special chance
and if you don't have an idea and you're
looking for an idea go to build.up team.
fun 200 plus ideas on what you can
potentially build at the hackathon all
right there or if you're just looking to
join a team that's participating in the
hackathon you can do that as well join
colosium use their team finder over a,
Indian developers have already joined it
so you can find a team there or if you
have a team and you have an idea and
you're looking to build check out super
team India on Twitter they're doing in
real life build stations across the
country so you can meet other people who
are participating in the hackathon and
get whatever help you need by the way
this time especially for India onc has a
special track onc is basically UPI but
for e-commerce and they want to find
startups that can increase order volume
on the network so maybe you can build an
interoperable product like an ads
exchange a negotiation engine coupon
system there's $10,000 in additional
prices for all submissions to the onc
track previous winners from this
hackathon have gone on to raise about
$600 million in funding so what are you
waiting for think of an idea and go sign
up or go to colosium find a team and
make your startup idea come true all the
links are in the description all the
best if you're participating let's start
the video yo yo yo welcome to the
episode the OG gang is here with us we
got priser op writer op Banker op and
making his debut on the show we got
rapper op AKA jasm baa why you called
rapper op
because passionately everyday rap sun
and I have a name also MC Jizzy and MC
is for middle class that's how it roll
and I don't want to know what Jizzy is
for yeah
[Laughter]
bro okay
hard
[Music]
hello I don't know how to say this
without sounding
rude reminds me of my
ex hello hello
[Laughter]
hi
already
funny
yes now I can't wait to see like a
slightly older Child Called Elvish and
then basically like a fetus yelling
El and a gynecologist named
Raj
isolated G
at they teaching Y in how to say [ __ ]
why are they teaching y' how to say
[ __ ] in India that's not physics how
the hell is a [ __ ] how am I physics how
am I
science your name is literally
speed
smooth R by
[Laughter]
Smooths has done engineering from MBA
college of Commerce
[Laughter]
physics Spiderman crash oh my
God okay this was like ra F Khan on the
bike oh my God man I will make weap for
you
man I will for you
manad sper Al
[Laughter]
[Music]
jok I did man I did oh my God R's
entertainment 21st half Century
[Laughter]
Fox
unbre
[Laughter]
my last
relationship Max turn after meeting
[Laughter]
[Music]
Elish masan
ending please box
office
[Laughter]
guys thank you for bringing my
[Music]
[Laughter]
father
pap
today we announce liberalization of
Indian
[Music]
[Laughter]
economy by the way and
okay
[Laughter]
this uh flute version of Titanic music
in a meme has never disappointed no yes
such
Titanic it would have been a
[Laughter]
comedy
sunk by priad jahaj
Masala
h no get down get
[Music]
down
infant that's amazing always wanted to
go to a g to Table
Restaurant when zato plans to deliver in
10 minutes
[Music]
not a toothbrush it's
a brush I love that you did
theit
commit
oral bee or vaginal
be not worth you know what I want to
change that to you know guys over each
other
over brush you have
[Laughter]
[Music]
toate
[Laughter]
find the seconds in
which
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes customer has been delivered to
delivery
boy your location has reached you your
location has reached
you it blink it
blink your delivery partner has picked
up
you notification have you been
delivered shaal is no longer driving
safely to your location you're deliv
dely boy has been
[Music]
delivered going from Oral B to vaginal
B when I order power bank from China
your charger is now fully
[Laughter]
charged
working model in fifth
class game guy who made the
charger technical shishu
ging
after I'm imagining steepen haing going
around around like
this
[Laughter]
think
[Music]
soan sh first
d
um thanks
to thanks too thanks Lord thank
you thanks to everyone for all the
[Laughter]
[Music]
wishes
you become so free when you know you're
going to fail an
exam why should only College reject me
yeah situation in heaven
[Music]
yeah
me trying to jell at ran by's house
[Laughter]
party I've never seen someone be so
despasito to sing despasito
[Music]
bro
[Laughter]
he's a true
[Music]
Swifty why they put a flute in his mouth
bro or
Chia wow you really took 20 seconds with
that one I took my
[Laughter]
time the big yawn yeah okay wake up wake
up have a glass of water the cricket's
getting interesting
wake up old
boy yeah yeah yeah yeah Steve Smith in
South Africa you a ball
boy balls pampering balls balls
pampering sorry
[Music]
sorry
yeah this was Co
[Laughter]
the Nika
3350 iPhone
filters MAC Cosmetics
oh
wow
[Music]
imagine cancelling cement bro
like [ __ ] cement man
[Music]
[Laughter]
like
all right that for today's episode if
you enjoy that hit that like button
follow the panel on Instagram and before
we go by rapper op Nam so you know what
you need to
do see you the
[Music]
[Laughter]
next middle class first
[Music]
CL middle
CL middle class drip
sh middle class DP freestyle
he