[Music]
this is the S podcast outfit it's the
same when we did that pod the jacket
isck the jacket is the same yes is the
perfect jacket to travel between Bombay
and Delhi it is it is bro otherwise the
climate change issue that happens Midway
from Delhi to
huh
DJ I'm a opera singer yeah I can hit
high octane notes I'm a Firefox
[Music]
singer I just got
it oper a
browser and he slow as Internet Explorer
rip
juile Hills this is the most fancy
area why can't we sit in the ambulance
sorry you can sit in the
[Music]
ambulance this basically like this you
have to take like wa
I don't know why I'm holding
the I'm holding a
stomach so today we are going to this
Red Bull Soap Box
event and Rohan is alone as per
usual okay which is
easier
Hill Comedians and me we've been doing
leg day since morning yeah yeah this is
third leg day of the day I was also
doing leg day in different airports of
the hello oh my God we've come back
down what was the point
put your hand inside put your hand
inside I'm
scared oh
my wow that was shocking I've never seen
a lift hack and we guys like you guys
are from Bombay to like you should know
these hand
no oh here we go again if you know
me you know I'm a huge fan of Junior NTR
this is his
grandpa I think his father
grandpa
no they all gas okay so go go back
little bit no these are red
athletes no dead bull people oh right
now filling oh okay he's chewing a gum
all can't be any more relaxed than this
oh almost hit the hair look at him look
at the attitude he's not he's left the
steering wheel also so now he's finished
easy easyy now at this point basically
you guys stop
[Music]
talking
big boss oh let's pretend we talking to
Big Boss can you be big boss for me
start with God I can be H pretend you're
big
boss I just said on the system pretend
to be big
Bo Pia sounds like a
restaurant
Pia
yeah you want to join the team you're
matching us you could be a Lind fellow
L you want to drive the car also you can
take that a big beautiful turd you guys
look like you got di need for sure you
guys look like relief this is what
relief feels like yes it's very
comforting all started with an
idea hell H this is our main god
[Laughter]
I God like
amazing will a different person after
this
race going to this race I don't think so
I'll will be person after this
race so we have finally come to another
bua area GL is so sleepy and we are uh
doing hair and makeup would you like to
introduce yourself hi
I'm she's doing my
[Music]
makeupday
thank
you guys I can feel a coming between K
and
I I don't know what relationships you've
been
[Music]
in be choosers you changed yeah I
changed that's what I thought also I was
told my knees are too vulgar yeah yeah
cover them they Inspire impure thoughts
in and ankles and my ankles and ankles
don't want people to get impure thoughts
yeah sa how you feeling about today it's
my first race ever any kind of race it's
my first race ever so I'm really really
excited okay fantastic good to see that
you skipped the rat face and do you know
what a soap box is and I tell you right
now is a
clue what is the Soap Box R
guys you package it
yourself
good more excited about the races cuz
they seem
insane
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God that was a huge leap same leap
you'll take when you marry me what oh my
God
me going on a date representation in a
race format yeah you were a little shaky
last Rob has made this so I'm going to
be very
biased
I I think it's brilliant without seeing
it I can just say it's brilliant cuz it
is Rob and he has robbed us out of a lot
of artistic oh my God
seconds construction drinking
R what a great car I love it slow and
steady V look
at look at oh my God looking so cute do
ittle on the
planet
performance andani both of them it's a
very controversial question
you for saying that hour and we were
just because of
guys that was a very fruitful but
extremely exhausting day K is also
coming uh he's ditching me for dinner
he's going some with someone else for
dinner oh
[Music]
yeah it's
okay but Rohan Rohan is my new favorite
cuz now he's coming for dinner what do
you mean new that
means sorry but he's really into nonv
stuff so only my jokes are nonv yeah and
habits yeah otherwise he's vegetarian
and Pious and pure but thank you see you
bye so
please
okay thank you