Hello, friends!
On the morning of November 12, 2023,
while we were preparing for Diwali,
in a tunnel in Uttarkashi
41 workers were working
on building a highway project.
Around 5:30 in the morning
this tunnel collapsed suddenly.
The workers were trapped in the tunnel.
With no way out.
The collapsed wall of stones and mud
standing between them and their way out,
was 60 meters long.
Soon, a concerned group of people
gathered in this small city in Uttarakhand.
The next day, on November 13th,
the rescue mission began officially,
involving over 200 individuals.
It took 17 days of intensive efforts to
successfully extricate the trapped workers.
How did they achieve this feat?
Let's understand the entire rescue operation
in today's video, with 3D animations.
Furthermore, let's answer the biggest question.
What is the underlying cause of the incident?
The root cause is the same that is faced by Joshimath,
a situation often overlooked
by mainstream news channels.
Let's begin.
The incident unfolded in Uttarkashi district in Uttarakhand,
specifically in the Barkot-Silkyara tunnel,
this map shows its location.
This is a two-lane bi-directional tunnel
being constructed as a part of the Modi
Government's ₹120 billion Char Dham project.
Let's talk about the details of the project later in the video,
but broadly speaking,
this is a highway project connecting 4 North Indian Dhams.
Badrinath, Kedarnath,
Yamunotri, and Gangotri.
Roads will be built connecting these four dhams,
to reduce the travelling distance between them.
PM Modi laid the foundation stone
of this project in December 2016.
This particular tunnel was announced in February 2018.
under the Brahmakhal-Yamunotri National Highway section.
The purpose of this tunnel was to reduce
the distance between Gangotri and Yamnotri
by approximately 20 km and
45 minutes of travel time.
The estimated cost of the project is ₹13.83 billion,
overseen by Navyug Engineering Company Limited
under the guidance of
the National Highways and Infrastructure Development Corporation Limited.
From the Silkyara side, 2,340 meters
of construction was nearly over.
And from Barkot, 1,600 meters was constructed.
The collapsed tunnel section was situated
270 meters from the Silkyara entrance,
the debris from the collapse formed a 60 meters thick wall.
Fortunately, since 2,000 meters of the tunnel was already constructed,
the trapped labourers
had a space of 2,000 meters to stretch their legs.
Fortunately, they weren't trapped in a small space.
The height of the enclosure they were trapped in was 8.5 meters.
Typically, incidents of this nature are
classified as "Act of God,"
signifying that it was a natural disaster.
However, the degree to which these events are
influenced by natural and human factors
is a subject of ongoing discussion.
As per the government's press release,
the workers were engaged in reprofiling work,
a process involving adjustments to the tunnel structure.
This activity becomes necessary when
the surrounding rocks exhibit unexpected
behaviours that went unnoticed previously.
The exact cause of the collapse will
remains unknown until further research.
However, preliminary findings suggest
this collapse was due to a potential geological fault
known as the Shear Zone.
This refers to a thinner or weaker part of the Earth's crust,
The construction would have put
a strain on the surrounding rocks,
leading to a landslide.
Another consideration as stated by
ML Sharma, a professor from IIT Roorkee,
is the presence of undetected cavities in the rocks,
gaps between these mountain rocks.
These cavities naturally weaken such areas,
increasing the risk of landslides.
These are 2 possible causes,
but we can only speculate right now
and the definitive reason will be established
only after the completion of investigation reports.
There are two main approaches to constructing
a tunnel construction in mountainous terrain,
the first is the drill and blast method (DBM),
and the second is by using a tunnel boring machine (TBM).
The former involves drilling holes in stones,
placing explosives,
and literally blasting the rocks.
It's as if a small bomb is detonated from inside the rocks.
It is the simple and traditional approach.
Using the tunnel boring machine is a more expensive
but safer alternative.
The machine creates a hole in the rocks with a rotating head,
and precast concrete segments are then installed.
Unfortunately, in the Himalayan mountains,
we cannot use these machines.
Due to the extreme geological conditions.
As you have studied in school,
the Himalayas are the youngest mountain ranges in the world.
At only 40-50 million years old,
they continue to grow,
resulting in highly sensitive
and unpredictable conditions.
Consequently, accidents in these areas
resulting from extensive construction
cannot be solely attributed to 'Act of God.'
Nevertheless, even in challenging situations,
people often seek a divine explanation.
Consider this article,
where a local resident claims that there
was a Baba Baukh Nath's temple on the site
which was removed to make way
for the highway construction.
He claims that this was the cause of the incident.
Attempts to find a divine cause behind
natural or man-made disasters
are not unprecedented.
In the case of the 2013 Kedarnath floods,
some locals attributed the calamity to
the relocation of Dhari Devi's shrine
during the construction of
the Alaknanda Hydroelectric Project.
During the rescue efforts in the tunnel,
where over 200 people were involved,
a small temple was constructed at the
entrance of the tunnel on November 18th,
and rituals were conducted.
Interestingly, this initiative wasn't
undertaken by the locals
but by NHIDCL,
the same company overseeing the tunnel construction.
However, neither the temple
nor the subsequent rescue operation
would have been needed
had an emergency escape passage
been incorporated as per the original plan.
When the Government sanctioned this project,
they had clearly stipulated the necessity of an escape passage,
a way out in case of emergency was mandatory.
as per government guidelines,
such emergency exits
are recommended for every tunnel
exceeding 1.5 km in length.
PC Nawani, the former director of the
Geological Survey of India, emphasizes that
managing projects of this nature
without escape routes is impractical.
The entire incident could have been
averted had proper precautions been taken.
But anyhow, let's get back to the incident,
the truth was, the workers were trapped indeed.
How could they be rescued?
This marked the beginning of "Operation Zindagi"
[Operation Life]
Uttarakhand government formed a five-option rescue plan
to be carried out by five distinct agencies:
Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC),
Satluj Jal Vidyut Nigam (SJVNL),
Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL),
National Highways and Infrastructure Development Corporation Ltd (NHIDCL),
and Tehri Hydro Development Corporation (THDCL).
Additionally, the Border Roads Organisation (BRO)
and the National Disaster Response Force (NDRF)
stood ready on the sidelines,
offering assistance whenever required.
The first step in the rescue operation focused on
ensuring a continuous oxygen supply to the trapped individuals
so that they could breathe properly.
A compressed air pipe was manoeuvred
between the debris for this.
Simultaneously, a separate 4-inch pipe was passed through the debris
to deliver snacks and dry fruits.
These measures were implemented
on the first day, November 12th.
Notably, electricity was being supplied in the tunnel,
so the trapped individuals weren't in complete darkness.
There was some light.
The following day, a rescue plan was devised,
involving horizontal drilling to create a passage
and passing a pipe through it,
that would be big enough for people
to crawl through and escape.
They had planned for horizontal drilling.
Using an auger machine.
This is how the machine looks.
Since the first pipe had been passed on the first day,
it was possible to communicate with the trapped workers
allowing constant interaction and
encouragement from the people outside.
THDC operated from the other side of the tunnel,
using micro-tunneling techniques.
Additionally, SJVN and ONGC were
gearing up for vertical drilling if necessary.
Vertical drilling meant drilling a passage
from the top of the mountain to the tunnel.
However, geologists expressed reservations about vertical drilling
due to potential complications with weak stones,
which could lead to further issues or even a landslide.
If it wasn't executed perfectly.
On 14th November, horizontal drilling commenced,
but the slow progress of the machine being used
and the additional debris caused by the drilling
led to the wall of debris becoming longer.
by now if you liked the animations
in the video and the general editing,
I would recommend that you consider
a career option in video editing.
With the surge in YouTube channels, emerging YouTubers,
podcasts by CEOs,
and businesses creating videos,
video editing presents itself as a legitimate
and viable long-term career option,
where degrees or qualifications are not crucial.
Only your skills matters.
If you want to seriously consider a career in video editing,
check out AevyTV's video editing course.
Over 1200 editors have been trained here,
and many are now working with renowned
YouTubers like Tanmay Bhatt and Ali Abdaal.
AevyTV boasts a large recruiter network,
and in recent cohorts, the placement rate exceeded 80%.
Yes, you heard it right,
80% of those opting for placement
at the end of their course
secured a job.
The average salary for these placed individuals
is ₹400,000 per annum,
this after completing just a 3-month course.
Even if you're a beginner in video editing,
they promise to equip you with the
necessary skills in just three months,
that you can score a job.
If you are interested, they have
a free masterclass especially for you.
For the viewers of the Dhruv Rathee channel,
the link to this free masterclass is
provided in the description below.
Even if you don't plan to join the cohort,
do attend the free masterclass
you'll learn something for free.
And it might open up
a new career option for you.
Returning to our main topic,
on November 15th,
a decision was made to bring in
a new, powerful machine.
This machine, transported from Delhi
via millitary aircraft in 3 parts
had to be assembled.
It took a day.
So by November 16th,
the machine was ready for digging,
with the capability to excavate
5 meters of debris per hour.
While the initial day went smoothly,
operations had to be halted the following day
due to a concerning cracking sound from the tunnel.
The fear arose – could continued drilling
lead to further sinking of the tunnel?
A day was dedicated to thorough inspection,
by then five days had passed,
with no visible progress.
The frustration among the workers' relatives
and rescue officials escalated,
resulting in a heated confrontation.
One distressed person cried out about
his brother who was trapped for seven days.
People were so angry and agitated that
to pacify the growing anger,
Uttarkashi District Officer D.P. Baluni proposed
the idea of vertical drilling.
"People are agitated,
so it was decided to
provide vertical openings
in addition to horizontal openings
for the rescue operation."
The plan with respect to vertical drilling involved
digging a passage for 90 to 105 meters.
Here, the BRO played a crucial role
in constructing temporary roads
so that the drilling machines
could be transported to the top.
This was being done simultaneously,
preparations for vertical drilling began
along with the ongoing horizontal drilling from below.
A significant development occurred on 20th November
when Arnold Dix, a tunneling expert
and the president of the International Tunneling
and Underground Space Association,
joined the rescue operation.
Leveraging his expertise,
Dix provided valuable suggestions
about what should be done next.
On the same evening,
rescuers successfully inserted a pipe of
6-inch diameter through the wall of debris.
This development expanded possibilities,
since this pipe was wider,
proper food could be delivered
to the trapped individuals.
The workers received their first hot meal since they were trapped,
a serving of hot khichdi.
An endoscopic camera was passed
through the pipe to film the workers,
This was the first video where we could see them.
Beyond food, the pipe became a conduit for medicines,
mobile phones, chargers, and walkie-talkies,
The walkie-talkies enabled direct
communication with the workers.
On the same day, it was decided to dig two additional tunnels
to create additional escape routes.
By 21st November,
four 900 mm pipes had been
successfully inserted through the debris.
However, the rescue operation was
still far from being successful,
with the pipes interfering with the drilling.
This interference led to a slight delay on November 22.
Further setbacks occurred on November 23
when the platform upon which
the drilling machine was placed,
had weakened,
that night was spent repairing that structure.
By November 24, the drilling machine had to be reassembled,
and the sequence of challenges persisted.
Once something was set right
something other broke down.
On November 25, a significant setback unfolded
as the auger machine completely broke down
and was lodged in the tunnel.
Arnold Dix informed reporters that
the drilling machine had already broken
down thrice during the rescue operations
and was now completely destroyed.
"The Auger is broken.
-Broken?
-Yeah, broken.
Yeah, the machine is busted.
It's irreparable.
It is destructed.
No more work from Auger."
On November 26, authorities announced
their intention to attempt vertical drilling again.
By then, 20 meters had been drilled vertically,
but the primary focus remained on horizontal drilling,
with only 12 meters of drilling left.
Recognizing the machine's irreparable state,
on November 27, a decision was made
to resort to manual drilling,
by bringing in rat hole miners.
Rat hole mining, an old and
hazardous coal extraction method,
was used in the past.
It involved creating vertical passages by hand.
The passage would be barely big
enough for a person to pass through it.
Despite being banned in India by the National Green Tribunal,
due to its adverse environmental impact
and the unsafe conditions for the miners,
in this situation, it was deemed the
best option for this rescue operation.
A team of 12 rat hole mining experts worked diligently,
and by the evening of November 28,
it was reported that only 2 meters of digging remained.
Everyone waited for the good news with bated breaths,
and finally, around 8 in the evening
the first worker was successfully
brought out on a stretcher.
Subsequently, one by one, all 41 workers
were rescued from this tunnel.
"After 17 days of being trapped in
the collapsed tunnel in Northern India,
rescuers have now freed all 41 workers."
Munna Qureshi was one of these 12 rat-hole mining expert,
he said that it was an emotional moment.
He was the one who removed the last piece of debris.
He could see them once he removed the last piece.
He said that those workers hugged them
and thanked them once they were safely outside.
They worked incessantly for 24 hours to rescue the workers.
Qureshi said that his happiness knew no bounds,
and that he did it for his country.
Ambulances and helicopters stood ready outside,
the rescued workers were adorned with garlands,
and a freshly cooked meal awaited them.
Potatoes and cauliflower stew, roti, lentil soup, and rice
were served to them as they emerged.
The entire nation celebrated the safe rescue of these 41 workers,
and praises poured in for the rescuers.
However, amidst the celebration for
this happy ending, it is crucial not to forget
the underlying cause of the incident
and the need to address its root cause.
Waiting for an official investigation may not be necessary,
as the actual reasons behind the incident are already known.
The answer to the question lies within
the Char Dham Highway project,
The same reason that is contributing
to the sinking of Joshimath.
This so-called development in Uttarakhand,
exemplified by projects like Char Dham,
adversely impacting the environment,
escalating the risk of landslides and related accidents.
I am not making this up,
look at this article
"Tunnel collapse in Uttarakhand is a part
of a bigger problem in the Himalayas"
In the construction of roads, there was inadequate slope analysis.
There is extreme slope cutting at some places,
slopes have been cut up to 45 degrees to construct the roads.
This can cause landslides easily.
In fact, the region has witnessed an average
of one landslide per day over the past 2 years.
According to this article.
Environmental activists have
raised concerns about this project.
In February 2018,
Citizens for Green Doon, an NGO based in Dehradun,
lodged a complaint with the National Green Tribunal (NGT),
highlighting the catastrophic impact of
this project on the Himalayan ecology.
They pointed out that, at that time, 25,000 trees
had already been felled for the project,
violating the Forest Conservation Act.
Furthermore, the NGO emphasized that,
according to Indian environmental laws,
every highway project exceeding 100 km
requires an environmental impact assessment.
However, the government
unabashedly circumvented this regulation
they said that this wasn't a mega project
of thousands of kilometers of highways,
they claimed to undertake 53 smaller projects,
each highway with a length of
less than 100 kilometers.
This mega project was presented as a cluster of small projects
simply to bypass this law.
Consequently, in September 2018, the NGT ruled that
the project did not need an environmental clearance.
This order was later contested in the
Supreme Court of India in August 2019,
leading to the appointment of a
26-member High-Powered Committee,
led by environmentalist Ravi Chopra.
The committee had to investigate the potential
environmental and social ramifications
of this project in Uttarakhand
and provide recommendations based on their findings.
In July 2020, the 4 members of this committee, including Ravi Chopra,
took note of the government's guidelines from March 2018,
issued by the Ministry of Road and Transport Highways.
These guidelines specified that highways constructed on mountains
should not exceed a total width of 7 meters.
However, the government aimed for
12-meters-wide highways on these mountains.
The other 21 committee members
supported the government's plan.
In response, Ravi Chopra directly wrote to
the Environment Ministry in August 2020,
expressing concern beyond tree felling.
He emphasized that, in addition to cutting down trees and mountains,
the waste generated during road construction
was being indiscriminately dumped into rivers,
particularly in eco-sensitive zones
such as Kedarnath Wildlife Sanctuary,
Valley of Flowers National Park,
and Rajaji National Park.
Waste was being dumped at such places.
The following month, in September 2020,
the Supreme Court considered
Ravi Chopra's recommendation
and ruled that the highway's width
should not exceed 7 meters.
This made sense as
wider roads would necessitate
more slope cutting, tree removal,
and more waste being dumped,
which could destabilise the Himalayan terrain
and increase the chances of
landslides and flash floods.
"We observed unanimously
that the road width was the key factor
which determines the extent of hill-cutting
and the subsequent environmental damage."
However, instead of adhering to the Supreme Court's decision, the government
employed a new masterstroke
to circumvent the Supreme Court's direction.
In November 2020, the Ministry of Defence entered the scene,
appealing to the Supreme Court for
the construction of a double-lane road,
citing it as a necessity for the Army.
The Char Dham project was reframed,
asserting that it was essential for
the country's benefit and the Army.
That's why the roads had to be so wide.
While the public had been initially informed
that the road construction was for the
Char Dham Yatra and religious pilgrimage,
the project's purpose was suddenly recast
as a strategic imperative.
Rooted in national interest,
specifically facilitating the movement
of Indian troops to the Chinese border.
The new reason was that since China
was constructing roads on its side of the border,
India needed to do the same.
However, a major difference is the terrain.
China's territory lies on the Tibetan Plateau,
characterized by fewer mountains,
a relatively stable landscape,
building roads is easier there
with fewer adverse ecological impacts.
Following this appeal by the Ministry of Defence,
the Ministry of Highways modified its
2018 directives the subsequent month,
stating that the 7-meter guideline
could be expanded to 10 meters
if a project holds strategic importance.
A year later, on December 14, 2021,
the Supreme Court reluctantly approved
the continuation of the Char Dham project as it is.
Consequently, the highways in the
Char Dham project are 12 meters wide.
Looking at how unabashedly the government
has disregarded rules and guidelines for this project,
Ravi Chopra resigned from the committee.
As of today, the Char Dham project has
resulted in the clearance of 600 hectares of forest,
the felling of over 56,000 trees,
and the widening of 75% of the Char Dham highway.
The Ministry of Highways acknowledged
200 landslides in the area in 2021,
And in November 2021, they admitted to the Supreme Court that
125 landslides were triggered around
the route of the Char Dham project
attributed to the construction work.
Do you recall what I said in the video on Bhopal Gas Tragedy?
Before the incident, journalists, activists, and experts,
gave repeated warnings that
disaster may strike at any moment.
Similarly, experts and activists are giving warning repeatedly now.
Look at these headlines;
17th May, 2023:
"Unchecked pilgrimage, construction in Uttarakhand
spell disaster for fragile Himalayas, warn experts"
A mountain crumbled near Joshimath
on 4th May during road widening.
August 23, 2023:
"The Recipe for Disaster That Is
Causing Destruction in Himalayan States"
19th January, 2023:
"Joshimath crisis is a warning from the Himalayas"
25th July, 2023:
"Landslide washes away Char Dham
road stretch in Uttarakhand"
"Uttarakhand's Char Dham project:
Why some call it 'A Road to Disaster'?"
15th November, 2023:
"Another warning in the Himalayas"
23rd August, 2023:
"Badrinath highway collapse is a warning"
"The Char Dham road project is a Freeway to Disaster"
This was acknowledged by the Supreme Court 5 years ago.
Look at this article from 2018.
"Frequent landslides in Uttarakhand on
Char Dham yatra marg raises questions"
In light of this data and warnings,
there are no indications of the plan being modified.
The government is celebrating the rescue of the tunnel workers.
There are indications that tunnel work will resume.
What's unfortunate is that,
in the coming years, we might get more news
of more such incidents in Uttarakhand.
The link to AevyTV's free masterclass
is in the description below.
If you found this video insightful,
you can also watch the Joshi Math video
by clicking here.
Thank you very much!