Now its Guttu turn
Now kids of people who make pickle will debate with our kids
Again this nightmare,I need to do something
This mother will go to the skies to make her guttu perfect, if you think your mother made you perfect too please watch the video and share too
The study is alright but one must know English and its weak for guttu, that's whats is in the trend
You said it right Sarita, 100 percent true
All this nonsense in social media is crazier, people are nude, I was thinking there shall be a time when old people like us will walk in bikini
Haa you said right now give me tea ,its so cold
Just go straight then right
Hey what happened?
We looking for english speaking classes
Cant you see consulting hour its 11am to 1pm
I can see everything, I just visited an eye doctor but with English its get hazy
If you are weak with english please go away
Where ?  to the classes ??
Ohh God NO, classes are full
Take some extra money and get us seats,adjust a little bit
What Sarita such an embrassement ?
With all those house chores we got no idea what English language hold such importance,but this should not happen with our kids
What all vulgur songs you kids are listening? All of the sudden you need to become adult,One nice slap and you will get your senses back
Now you will only listen english songs,wait let me play some for you
What nasty song mumma played, feeling so awkward
Ohh wow how magical this song is
True aunty why dont you play this song in your kitty party
Guttu it was fun though
I don't get Jazz but whatever she says in English is legit gold
Oh my GOD she so pretty and how well she speaks English
Haven't you seen any beautiful girl
She complimented me I think
Why are you doing all this while being sick mummy ,maid will take care of it!
Beta all this is for your future,dont worry
What mummy???
You get ready ,I will be ok
She is still stuck with cheap snacks,achaar pappad
And see the crockery it looks so sarojini types
Everything smells like pickle
Rima, how are you? Hello Jazz. Jazz goes to that English tuition please make reference for guttu too
Arey sarita you keep up with this pickle a why you want guttu to learn english
All this is alright but i got some vintage pickle just for you, if you want!!
Haa sure send all of that, I will talk with the tuition classes right now
I had talk go tomorrow for admission
Thanks Rima
What a lady babe? I must say she is so village type how will she make guttu learn english
Mummy you must give one nice lesson to that rima,she speaks such nonsense
You keep quiet i will handle her, don't utter a word to her
Mom why all of these?
Rima does her job,now this pickle will work
Rima referred us
Whats this delicious smell?
50 years old recipe it is ,its famous pickle handmade it is
Amazing.
Well I came for guttu english classes I want you to teach her and make her best
Yes sure i will
Wow Im so proud of you my kid,how nicely you spoke english
Really you understood mom!!
Yes a bit but if you explain to me that would be the cherry on top
What mummy how innocent you are!!
That to I'm no doubt
English might want of current generation but it can never be your necessity, have you also judged someone's capability by his or her English speaking skills, Please like & share our video.