[tense music]
'Surbhi! Sister!'
'Surbhi, stop! Sister!'
'Surbhi!'
'Sister!'
'Surbhi! Sister!'
[dramatic music]
'Surbhi!'
[tense music]
'Sister!'
[dramatic music]
'No!'
[sad music]
Sister!
Sister, please forgive me.
I couldn't save you years ago.
I couldn't save
your memories, either.
Your farm and well
are going to be auctioned off.
Sister, this farm and well
is like a mother to our Nandu.
[crying]
What do I tell her, sister,
when she will ask me
where is her mother?
[sobbing]
[mellow music]
[happy music]
[music playing]
[song playing]
[intense music]
Nandini!
Yes, tell me, Mehul.
Come quickly! Emergency!
- Nandini!
- I am coming.
You make them practice. I am coming.
Nandini, hurry up.
Nandini!
[intense music]
What happened, Mehul?
Nandini! The farm
is being auctioned off.
Uncle is in the bank. Think of
something quickly. What do we do?
Let's go home.
The auction is being
held in the bank.
Let's go home.
Yes, let's go.
- What?
- Helmet.
I have worn it. Let's go.
Hey!
[intense music]
Rs. 2,02,500.
Tell me if you want to give it.
Okay, let's go. Is there anyone?
Three lakh rupees!
Very good. Anyone else?
- Three lakh, fifty thousand rupees!
Four lakh, fifty thousand rupees!
Very good.
It was the land of our ancestors.
I couldn't save it.
Aunt, I am sorry. Did you get hurt?
Get down.
The hay has also finished.
There is no one to look
after the house except me.
No one is concerned
about anything except me.
What is going on?
Surbhi, you have been
ringing the bell since morning.
There is no one in
this house except me.
Did someone give you grass?
No one does anything.
No one helps me.
No one does anything
in this house except Mani.
- I do all the work.
- Aunt!
What is this?
Where have you been since morning?
Forget all that. Put this aside.
One minute. Take this off.
[chuckles]
You have such a photogenic face.
Come here. I will show you
how beautiful you are.
Don't flatter me.
I am not flattering you.
I am telling the truth.
Wait a minute. Here.
Stand like this. Yes.
Here... Yes!
- Hey!
- Aunt!
Yes!
Aunt, do you know?
In Upleta, they put up big posters
of the pictures I click.
[sad music]
'Uncle.'
'All these ornaments...'
'Are they all ours?'
'Nandu, these are the ornaments'
'that my mother gave your mother.'
'And these are the ornaments
of my mother that I got.'
'I saved all these
for your wedding.'
'Why do we need so many ornaments?'
'What else does a bride
need except a nuptial chain?'
'Nandu, this is your dowry.'
[sad music]
[suspenseful music]
Very good, Aunt. Very good.
Yes.
Okay.
Come on.
This is the last auction of the day.
Ishwar Tambariya's farm.
Six acres of land.
There is a well on the farm.
There is a fence as well.
And there is an electric pump too.
And the base price for this
is nine lakh rupees.
[intense music]
Thank you, Uncle.
Nine lakh rupees.
Tell me. Is there anyone?
Nine lakh and twenty-five
thousand rupees.
Nine lakh and fifty thousand rupees.
One.
[intense music]
- Nine lakh and fifty thousand
rupees. Two. - Ten lakh rupees!
Ten lakh rupees.
Ten lakh rupees. One.
- Ten lakh rupees! Two. Ten lakh...
- Hold on!
[intense music]
Sorry
to stop your auction like this.
Sir. Here's the loan amount of ten
lakh rupees taken by Uncle Ishwar
and the interest in it.
You can take it.
It's twelve lakh fifty
thousand rupees.
Please don't auction
my uncle's farm.
Okay. You...
You wait for a while.
I will tell you.
Okay.
[intense music]
Mr Ishwar owes eleven lakh and
seventy-five thousand to the bank.
You have paid for it.
So the auction can stop.
[intense music]
Sir, give me the file.
Come in, Mr Ishwar.
Mr Ishwar, you are so lucky.
Now, there is no interest or loan.
Now your farm will be with you.
Take this.
Sign on this.
Get it signed by the registrar too.
And take the receipt
of your money from outside.
Leave the money here.
The rest of the money
will be returned to you.
Uncle, I have seen
all these papers.
I will get the
registrar's sign on this.
- Mehul, you sit with Uncle
and make him drink tea. - Yes.
I'll be back. Come on, Mitesh.
It's hot. We'll drink
buttermilk instead of tea.
- Ms Nandini.
- Yes.
I believe that
you have saved the land
of the farm with great difficulty.
Sorry. I am Parag Kanhabar.
I work for the politician and MLA
Mr Arjan Khimji here.
As a well-wisher,
I have an offer for you.
If we offer you 20 lakh rupees
in return for your land
can you tell your uncle
to transfer your land to us?
Thank you for your offer.
But we don't want
to sell this farm.
Come on, Mitesh.
[intense music]
Yes, sir.
Sir,
the man's niece came
and stopped the auction.
What did you do, Nandu?
Have you gone mad?
You sold the ornaments.
Do you know what your aunt
will do if she finds out?
She will create havoc.
Uncle, you don't have to
tell Aunt anything right now.
It's wrong to hide the truth.
You hid it from us.
And from Aunt Mani.
Did you tell anyone
that you have mortgaged the farm?
Don't ask me questions.
The ornaments were
for your wedding.
You sold them for my land.
Uncle, the gold will
remain in the safe.
The gold will grow on the farm.
But you can't risk your land
for the ornaments.
Uncle, your daughter will leave
what will be left with you,
if you lose the farm as well?
It's good that Mitesh
told me everything.
You come in the rickshaw with Mehul.
Uncle, come with me.
[happy music]
Uncle!
Uncle,
don't tell Aunt about the ornaments.
She will get worried.
I will explain it to Aunt later.
Dear, I am worried
about what I will offer
for your wedding.
Uncle, why are you worried?
I told you. A nuptial chain
is enough for a bride.
And my groom will bring
my nuptial chain.
Uncle, am I so shameless
that I will sell your land
and wear ornaments?
Uncle, after mom left,
you have brought us up.
You brought us up.
You made us worthy.
You have given me
twice the love of a mother.
Oh no!
- Uncle, mom.
- Mom?
- Mom!
- What mom?
Oh! I forgot the sweets!
[happy music]
- Why are you running?
- Sweets!
Where have you been since morning?
Later. I want to go to the farm.
What are you doing?
Oh God! This girl
is so troublesome.
I don't know
what will happen to her.
Enough.
I don't have to go to Rajkot.
- Box?
- Sweets.
Sweets?
Hey, give me some money.
- Me?
- Give it to me.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
- I will tell you later. Hey!
- Sorry.
He is a strange man.
- Uncle.
- Yes.
Where did she go to feed sweets
to in such a hurry?
- The one whose birthday is today.
- Birthday?
Didn't you understand?
[dramatic music]
Who is calling?
Mr Naren Ratan Singh.
Tell me, Mr Naren. Greetings.
Mr Mehul. I have left from Upleta.
I am coming to see the girl today.
Today? You were supposed
to come tomorrow, Mr Naren.
Yes. The work in the factory
got over before time.
So, I thought of completing
this program as soon as possible.
You are great, Mr Naren.
No problem. Come here.
Hey! Sir.
The boy who was supposed to come
to see the girl is coming today.
- What?
- Yes.
Go inside and tell
your aunt. Come on. Quick.
- Aunt Mani.
- Yes.
The boy who was supposed to come
to see the girl is coming today.
What?
He is supposed to reach
Upleta in some time.
Oh, God! How is that possible?
When will I get ready?
Mani. The boy is coming
to see the girl.
He is not coming to see you.
Yes. But I have to get dressed up.
You should get the girl dressed up.
Why are you getting dressed up?
Okay, forget about me.
But won't he give the girl
a chance to get ready?
Her eyebrows, bleach, facial are
pending. She is yet to get ready.
- And, Mehul.
- Yes.
First, call Sheetal.
Tell her that I am sending
the sweets with you.
And then call Nandini.
And tell her that the boy is coming
today instead of tomorrow.
Yes.
[soft music]
Sweets for you, Mom.
Happy birthday, Mom.
[song playing]
[phone ringing]
Yes, Mehul. Tell me.
'Aunt, the boy is coming
to see the girl today.'
What? Is he coming today?
Yes.
Did you tell Nandini?
I am calling Nandini.
I thought I would call you first.
I will send Nandini to your house.
And that I am coming
there as well with the sweets.
Oh, God!
Yes. Nandini.
[phone ringing]
Yes, Mehul.
Nandini, come home soon.
Mr Hemraj's son from Rajkot,
Naren Ratan Singh
who was supposed to come
tomorrow is coming today.
What? When will I get ready?
And when will I prepare everything?
That's why I am telling
you to come home, Sister.
[happy music]
Greetings, Uncle!
I am sorry! Aunt. I got late.
It's okay.
The boy hasn't turned up yet.
So make some 'Khandvi' quickly.
I have kept the flour
and curd there.
What is this Aunt?
Aunt, why did you order
so many things from the market?
You could have
ordered 'Khandvi' as well.
You can't get 'Khandvi'
like this, in the market.
And you should serve
something homemade, too.
Forget it, Aunt.
I understand everything.
You are going to serve
homemade 'Khandvi'
as 'Khandvi' made by Vishakha
in front of the boy's family.
Everyone does this.
A little white lie isn't a sin.
[soft music]
Aunt, Uncle says that no matter
how trivial the lies are
relationships are not based on lies.
You will serve this 'Khandvi'
saying it's prepared by Vishakha.
After marriage, her in-laws
will ask her to prepare 'Khandvi'.
What will she do then?
Her lies will be exposed
in front of Naren.
You ask too many questions, girl.
Just make the 'Khandvi' quickly.
And teach Vishakha
before her marriage.
Make it quickly so that the
moment they eat 'Khandvi'
Vishakha's wedding gets fixed.
Hurry up.
The boy will be here any moment.
Mr Hitesh, Naren Kumar is here.
Welcome.
Greetings!
- Greetings!
Come. Sit.
How are you all?
- We are fine.
- Please sit.
Please sit.
Uh...
I am sorry.
I got a little late.
What? You didn't get late.
You are early by an entire day.
[laughter]
Aunt Sheetal keeps cracking jokes.
Mr Naren, he is Uncle Hitesh,
Vishakha's father.
And she is Vishakha's mother,
Mrs Sheetal.
And he is Mr Hemraj's son,
Mr Naren from Rajkot.
So, I have introduced you to all.
Vishakha, get the drinks.
Vishakha.
- I hope there was no problem
in coming here. - No problem.
Vishakha is here.
She is Vishakha,
- my daughter.
- Greetings.
Greetings.
Have a drink.
Yes. Thank you so much.
- Where is 'Khandvi'?
- Oh yes.
Where is 'Khandvi'?
Give me 'Khandvi'.
Wow! Everything is amazing.
Taste 'Khandvi'.
Vishakha has made it.
She has come third in the
inter-district
Master Chef competition.
Wow! It's really nice.
Wow! Vishakha's 'Khandvi'
has passed the test.
Now, it's best if Vishakha
passes the test as well.
Yes. Naren Kumar.
If you want to talk to Vishakha,
- you can talk to her.
- Actually...
Vishakha, take him
to the garden outside.
You go. Yes. Calmly.
- Talk to her calmly.
- Yes.
Please. After you...
[soft music]
He looks good.
I don't know if Vishakha
will get along with him.
Come in.
Mr Naren, wow! Vishakha...
Hey...
[intense music]
Vishakha, what happened?
Why were you crying?
What did he say?
Tell me. What happened?
What happened? Vishakha...
Did you like Vishakha?
Yes. She is a nice girl.
Very nice.
Wow! So...
Mr Naren likes Vishakha. Wow!
Thank God!
- Mehul, call the priest.
- Yes.
We want to figure out
an auspicious day.
We need an auspicious day.
Yes. Hold on.
Mr Mehul...
It's a matter of marriage.
Before we move ahead
let's talk about the dowry.
[tense music]
Greedy man!
He looks so modern
but talks about dowry.
Dowry?
Tell me, Mr Naren.
Look, my parents
will make you understand
about the basic dowry.
But...
Actually, Hitesh.
I need something as well.
I just need two things.
First,
I need a fancy
automatic car.
[tense music]
And second,
I just need around 1 kg of gold.
[tense music]
Is he here to marry Vishakha
or make a deal?
[sobbing]
You were crying because of this?
Huh?
Vishakha?
[sobbing]
Mr Naren Kumar, but...
This is too much.
- Uncle Hitesh...
- Mr Hitesh...
We don't
bargain in marriages.
It's considered inauspicious.
[sobbing]
Hold on and stop crying.
I'll deal with him.
You were talking about a car.
That depreciates, you know?
The value of property increases.
A mansion
or 100 to 150 acres
of agricultural land.
Isn't that a better investment?
You're right.
If...
we get the value, then...
I mean, it's fine.
And gold is fine.
But don't you think
diamonds are forever?
I love diamonds.
Even better.
Me too. Okay, fine.
We'll give you the car
and gold you asked for.
And the land and diamonds
that I asked for,
you'll give them to us.
[tense music]
So shall I consider it done
between you and Vishakha?
Mehul,
when did the groom's
family start giving dowry?
It's the age of equality.
So, the exchange will also be equal.
[tense music]
What happened?
Why are you staring at me?
Did I say something wrong?
Nandini. You go inside.
- I will talk to him.
- No, Mehul.
The wrong customs that
are being followed for ages
we cannot insult
our traditions in its name.
Nandini. You go inside.
Let me talk to him.
Mr Mehul, did you invite
me for insulting me?
I am not capable
of insulting anybody
neither is it my upbringing.
You said so much despite that.
I disagree with the alliance.
We disagree with the alliance.
Relationships are
not made out of greed,
but by respect.
And the one who asks for money,
we should donate money to them.
Not get our daughters
married to them.
[tense music]
[song playing]