- [Mark Rober] Today I helped MrBeast
conquer his fear of heights.
It all started when I gave him
a tour of my secret lair CrunchLabs,
and after I showed him what
I call the fireman's piston,
he started to reveal his true colors.
- [MrBeast] Oh no.
Bro, I'm terrified.
How high is this?
- [Mark Rober] Turns out the dude
who spent 50 hours buried alive
was wimping out over an eight foot drop.
- I'm scared.
- [Mark Rober] But if
he just had more trust
in the laws of physics,
he wouldn't need to worry,
'cause when you step off,
you pull down on the rope,
and it pulls up on this plate,
but all the air in the chamber here
has to get squeezed out of
this tiny hole at the top,
and that creates a traffic jam.
And just like traffic jams in
real life slow down your car,
this one will slow you down
to a nice easy landing.
- You just reminded me that
I'm deathly scared of heights.
- [Mark Rober] At this point, I could have
put him at ease by telling him
just how many five year olds
had already made the jump,
but then again, watching
him suffer was way more fun.
(Mark Rober laughs)
(MrBeast sighs)
- Bro, I hate this.
(triumphant music)
(crowd cheers and applauds)
I'm never doing that again.
There you go. You got your freaking video.