Hello, friends!
On 4th January, 2024,
on his social media handles,
Prime Minister Modi
posted some pictures from Lakshadweep.
Although there was no
mention of Maldives in these pictures,
some politicians in the Maldivian government
reacted to these pictures in a way
that led to years of friendship
between the two countries
being in danger today.
In a few days, the situation becomes so serious that
#BoycottMaldives started trending on social media.
The 3 ministers of the Maldivian government,
who caused the controversy are
Mariyam Shiuna,
Malsha Shareef and
Abdullah Mahzoom Majid.
Their comments on India and the Indian Prime Minister,
look to be born out of insecurity.
They believed that PM Modi's agenda
was to make Lakshadweep and Maldives compete.
But these comments included some personal attacks too
On Twitter, Mariyam called PM Modi,
"a puppet of Israel."
Her colleagues said that these photos from Lakshadweep
aimed at challenging the tourism industry in the Maldives.
And Mahzoom Majid stereotyped Indians
and made hateful comments against India.
Sharing photos of open urination he said that
it is a part of Indian culture.
These led to an outright conflict on social media.
When the Indians started posting that they
are cancelling their flight and hotel bookings,
the Maldivian government understood the seriousness
and the Maldivian Foreign Ministry stated that
the opinions expressed by the ministers
were their personal opinions and
did not represent the views of the Maldivian government.
Later, the government suspended these 3 ministers.
But the point isn't about
Maldives versus Lakshadweep only.
Not just about this social media war.
The whole controversy was driven by hateful politics.
A geopolitical agenda which led to all of this.
Let's understand it in today's video.
One thing you all would know is that
Maldives is a small country.
The total population of this country
is only around 500,000 people.
This country is made up of numerous islands.
In fact, there are more than 1,000 islands.
But out of these 1,000 islands,
only about 200 are inhabited.
Where humans live.
And out of these 200,
more than 150 islands are resort islands.
They have been sold to private companies.
And those companies have their private resorts on it.
Obviously, the country depends heavily on tourism.
28% of Maldives' GDP depends on tourism.
And 90% of the tax revenue for the government,
comes from import duties and tourism-related taxes.
And an interesting fact is that
India is the number one country
based on the number of tourists visiting Maldives.
In 2023, more than 200,000 Indian tourists went to Maldives.
In total, approx 1.75 million tourists
went to Maldives this year.
So you can imagine a country with a population of 500,000,
hosting more than 1.7 million tourists in a year.
But the relationship between India and Maldives
is much deeper than that of tourism.
For years, India and Maldives have been strategic allies
and there has been military cooperation between the two too.
India has played a special role in initiatives like SAGAR.
SAGAR stands for
Security and Growth for All in the Region.
Around 2008, India launched its Neighbourhood First Policy,
and improved relations with Sri Lanka, Maldives,
Nepal, Afghanistan, Bangladesh,
Pakistan, and Myanmar.
About 77 Indian military officers and soldiers
are present on the Maldives islands
additionally, two Dhruv Advanced Light Helicopters
were donated by India to the Maldives in 2010 and 2015.
There are many reasons behind this
military presence and helicopter donation.
Such as helping during natural calamities,
conducting search and rescue operations,
airlifting medical patients between islands.
But apart from this, India's warships patrol the
exclusive economic zone of the Maldives too.
This is the sea area surrounding Maldives
where illegal activity is prevented.
Basically, to prevent terrorism.
Maldives had requested India to do this.
In 2009, when the Maldivian government
were concerned about potential
terrorist attacks in their country,
they had asked India for help
because they did not have the capabilities
in terms of military assets and surveillance.
But this help and India's military presence
has become a major issue of controversy
in Maldives' internal politics for the last few years.
Some political parties in Maldives completely oppose this
and want India to withdraw its military.
In fact, Maldives' current President, Mohamed Muizzu
and his political party, People's National Congress,
used this issue during their election campaign
and came to power.
The issue of "India Out."
To understand this better,
we have to take a look at Maldives' internal politics.
The thing is, the country was
under dictatorship for 30 years.
It was only in 2008
that a new constitution was adopted
and a multi-party democracy system
was established in their country.
The elections that were conducted in 2008
was won by the Maldivian
Democratic Party or MDP in short
and their new President was Mohamed Nasheed.
He was a successful president for the first 4 years of his term.
He spread awareness on climate change issues,
pledged to make Maldives carbon neutral
and his foreign policy was India First.
During his term, India and Maldives became close allies.
And as I said, in 2009, on his request,
India donated military equipment to Maldives.
But in 2012, a political crisis broke out in Maldives.
And the next year, in 2013,
when elections took place,
a new party came to power.
The Progressive Party of Maldives or PPM.
The President was Abdulla Yameen Abdul Gayoom.
And with the change in the governing party,
the foreign policy of the country also changed.
This new party opposed India.
In 2016, their new government stated that
India can take back the
2 helicopters that were gifted to them.
After distancing themselves from India,
Yameen's government got closer to China.
Chinese companies were given contracts for
major infrastructure projects in the Maldivian islands.
And in the meantime,
Maldives became a part of
China's Belt and Road Initiative.
Under this initiative, China wants to spend money
on large infrastructure projects
in different countries across the world
by building roads, railways, and ports
to increase its influence in Asia, Africa, and Europe.
Most of the loan terms of Chinese contracts
were quite unsustainable.
Because of this, many countries fall into China's debt trap.
During this time, Maldives borrowed
$1.5 Billion from China.
Friends, here I'd like to say that
if you couldn't understand any part in my video,
you can use ChatGPT as an assistant.
What is China's Belt and Road Initiative?
You can simply ask this.
It can explain, in simple terms,
why many countries are deep in debt.
And not only in English, ChatGPT can
answer your questions in Hindi or Hinglish too.
Similarly, for many such tasks
ChatGPT is a useful software.
This is why I made a 4.5-hour-long
course to master ChatGPT.
This course is in Hindi with English subtitles.
In it, you can learn how ChatGPT
can help students, employees, and business owners
to increase their productivity and efficiency.
Next week, a new 1-hour long bonus
content will be added to the course.
Recently, I conducted a workshop in
Dubai's 1 Billion Summit,
it was on ChatGPT,
You can watch the entire workshop in this course.
If you have already purchased the course,
it is a free update for you.
But if you haven't,
do check it out.
For this video, use the coupon code LAK40
to get 40% off.
It is only for the first 400 users.
The link is in the description below.
Or, you can scan this QR code.
Now, let's get back to the topic.
Because of this government,
relations between India and Maldives got weaker
and India's strategic position in this area starts weakening.
After this, the next election was in 2018,
once again, the governing party changed
and so did the foreign policy of the country.
In 2018, Ibrahim Mohamed Solih from MDP
became the President.
And the first thing he did was
the Indian helicopters that Yameen wanted to send back,
Solih extended the contract of those Indian helicopters.
He wanted to keep those helicopters in Maldives.
Once again, they adopted India First strategy.
Thereafter, India helps the Maldivian government.
India provides billions of dollars to Maldives
so that they could repay the loan
taken by the previous government.
Even during the Covid pandemic,
India provided vaccines in Maldives.
One thing to note here is that
even when Maldives wasn't a democracy,
during the 30-year dictatorship,
India-Maldives relations were still strong.
Like in 1995, India built
Indira Gandhi Memorial Hospital in Maldives.
It is still the largest hospital in Maldives.
Back to 2020,
this new MDP government
was extremely enthusiastic about
the India First sentiment.
Many bilateral agreements were signed
between India and Maldives during this time.
India granted $500 million for maritime connectivity.
A Line of Credit of $800 million
was given by Export-Import Bank of India.
Due to this India First's proactive approach,
an undercurrent was spreading across the country.
The sentiment of India Out.
The politicians in the opposition had a
negative outlook towards the alliance between
the Indian government and the Maldivian government.
By 2021, many journalists had written articles about it,
numerous posts had been made on social media,
which were openly criticising India
and in many ways, degrading India.
Politicians were also giving hateful speeches
to end India's presence from their islands.
Seeing all this, the Indian High Commission in Maldives
wrote to the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Maldives
stating that the articles and social media posts
were attacking Indian dignity.
They asked the ministry to do something about them.
This letter was leaked to Maldives' media.
On 2nd July 2021, the MDP government
officially apologises to India.
And expresses concern that
some people who are spreading hatred against India
on Maldivian media and social media.
Acknowledging it as wrong.
Here, a local news publication DRS was mentioned
with their co-founder Ahmed Azaan.
Specifically, pointing out that
they are the people spreading Anti-India hate.
Regarding India Out slogans, Ahmed Azaan gave a statement
that the campaign does not mean that they
want to expel the Indians from Maldives.
They do want Indians to be safe in their country.
And that the India Out movement means that
they want to expel the Indian military from their country.
And that the people using the India Out campaign
to threaten the Indians
and to attack Indians
are in the wrong.
He called it an issue-based movement.
So the point is
if this is an issue-based movement,
then what are their issues?
The opposition politicians claim that
the agreements entered into by the MDP government with India
are very confidential
and their details are not revealed to the public.
The then Vice President of their opposition party, PPM,
Mohd Shareef said that
if the details of the agreement
are not presented to the country,
it is a violation of democracy.
The government should not hide the details
by citing the excuse of national security.
He used the example of the Harbour project
on the Uthura Thila Falhu Island in Maldives.
A joint defence action plan was signed
between India and Maldives in February 2021.
where India's job was to develop and
maintain the harbour of this coast guard.
Leaked documents suggest that
according to this agreement,
the Indian military could stay here for decades
and they would have the exclusive rights to this facility.
Many Maldivian citizens were
genuinely upset after hearing this.
Even those who were not
supporting the India Out campaign,
started supporting the opposition.
And because of this, when the next
elections were conducted in 2023,
the governing party changed again,
and the PPM party that was the opposition,
came back into power.
This time, this PPM party
formed an alliance with PNC party to be in power.
And the latest President of Maldives,
Mohamed Muizzu,
was the candidate of this right-wing party, PNC.
This happened on 30th September, 2023.
This political party, which focused on the
India Out issue during their election campaign
is in power today.
It is also worth noting that
had the previous MDP government been more transparent
and had not kept the agreements so confidential,
then perhaps the India Out sentiment
would not have gained so much traction.
And perhaps, they could have remained in power.
But now, since this PPM party came into power,
they took this India Out issue
even more seriously than last time.
Their new president Mohamed Muizzu,
openly stated, four days after winning the election
that Indian forces in Maldives
will have to leave the country.
On 17th November 2023,
he became the President officially,
and only a week later,
on 23rd November,
he met Indian Union Minister Kiren Rijiju.
He repeated the same points in the meeting
that India withdraw its military personnel from Maldives.
And it was only a month and a half later
that the Muizzu's ministers
openly started insulting PM Modi and India
on public platform.
When this happened, the ex-Presidents of Maldives
and the MDP party,
obviously, stood up in favour of India.
Mohamed Nasheed and Ibrahim Mohamed Solih
both condemned this hateful language against India.
Now that you know these, you can understand
that it was never about Lakshadweep.
This was entirely about Maldives' internal politics.
This India Out sentiment
is a way for some Maldivian politicians
to incite their citizens
and to score more votes with their hateful speeches.
In 2021, when the MDP government was in power
and India Out slogans were raised,
then one of the MDP ministers Ali Azim had said that
this anti-India movement was
happening because some people
enjoy making hateful speeches.
Today, this is a great example of how
hateful politics can be harmful to a country.
You will find such politicians not only in Maldives
but in every country in the world.
They either spread hatred against a community,
against a religion
or against another country.
What's unfortunate is that,
many people get misled by such
hateful speeches and the fear they create.
If we look at the foreign policy of the new Maldivian government,
it is once again leaning towards China.
Maybe it's just a coincidence that
this entire controversy started just a day before
the Maldivian President's visit to China.
His trip to China was from 8th to 12th January.
The Chinese state-sponsored media
praised this situation stating that
"it demonstrates that Muizzu is treating
India with a normal mindset
and steering the relationship between Maldives and India
to a normal state-state relationship."
It is also historic that
Muizzu chose China for his first foreign trip.
All the Maldivian presidents before him,
came to India on their first foreign trip.
Just two days ago, on 10th January,
after this controversy began,
President Muizzu extended an
invitation to Chinese tourists
to visit Maldives.
Since Indians started boycotting the country,
he is openly inviting Chinese tourists to his country.
So, the entire issue here
is about Maldives' internal politics.
The parties in favour of China
versus the parties in favour of India.
This also reveals that
if the governing party changes once again
in Maldives in 4-5 years,
and the pro-India party comes to power,
then India's stance towards Maldives can change again.
The boycott Maldives slogans that are trending now,
can turn into Go to Maldives slogans,
after a few years.
But regardless of what happens in Maldives' politics,
we can always promote Indian tourism.
One thing that we need to be cautious about is that
while promoting local tourism,
the local biodiversity and the local
population should also be cared for.
Tourism should not be at the cost of
environment and the livelihoods of the locals.
If you liked this video, you will
like this video on geopolitics too,
in which I have talked about how
countries all over the world
promote the weapons industry.
And why the United Nations fails in such cases.
You can click here to watch it.
Thank you very much!