Hey everybody. I am Priya and welcome back to my channel Finology Legal.
If there is an article in the whole constitution that is
Interpreted most time is article 21.
Why? Because logically speaking, a constitution has to survive
For decades but as time changes, society's thinking also changes.
That's why the meaning and purpose of article 21 have been interpreted as time passed.
From life to death,alongside food, clothing and shelter,
There are more basic necessities like freedom, dignity, pollution-free environment
And others more like these are all discussed in article 21.
So by discussing article 21, lets understand how
Meaning of life and person liberty has evolved on a case-by-case basis.
Article 21 is available to both citizens and noncitizens states that
No one shall be deprived of life and personal liberty
Except according to procedure established by law.
Article 21 has these three keywords. If we understand
With these three keywords, we will automatically understand article 21.
Let's get started with "Procedure established by law".
Article 21 is mainly inspired by American constitution.
Their provision states that no person is deprived of life and
Personal liberty except according to due process of law.
This means that courts have the power to question
To control the actions of both legislative and executive.
Meaning, those substantive laws that define what should be the laws?
Can be questioned. Alongside it, procedural laws that define
How will these laws be implemented and followed? Can also be questioned.
So, whichever countries have due process of law
Their courts have the power to ask two questions from their legislature.
First, do you have the power to create this law?
Second, do these laws comply with the principles of natural justice?
If the answer to both these questions is negative
Then the court has the power to declare that part of the law invalid.
That's why Dr. B.R Ambedkar wanted article 21 of the Indian constitution
Should use this phrase. But Sir Alladi Krishnaswamy Aiyer
Said that if we want to bring new social legislation in future
Then this part here will create problems.
That's why we used procedure established by law
Which only focuses on these. So finally, article 21 used a procedure established by law.
That's why up till 1978, we
Only got protection from arbitrary executive action. Meaning
Only those executive actions that were not just,fair or reasonable
Could be challenged.
But, arbitrary legislative action still did not grant us any protection. But all this talk
Were up till 1978. Why? Because in 1978,
Maneka Gandhi case arose. This case further elaborated
The scope of article 21. So, this was a procedure established by law.
Now, let's understand life and personal liberty.
We will understand personal liberty through two very important case laws.
First, A.K Gopalan vs State of Madras. In this case, what happened was
That A.K Gopalan was detained through preventive detention act
So he challenged the act and said that this act
Infringes personal liberty. The Supreme court said that
Personal liberty is only infringed in two cases.
First, if there is a physical restraint, and secondly, in case of coercion.
If the case is neither one of these, then your personal liberty
Is not being infringed. Isn't it a very narrow interpretation? Yes
In this case, personal liberty was very narrowly interpreted.
After this, a very important case was "Maneka Gandhi vs Union of India".
In this case, the passport of Maneka Gandhi
Was impound or ceased by the government without giving any reason.
Maneka Gandhi challenged this government action in the supreme court and said that
This is an infringement in my personal liberty.
In this case, the supreme court said that personal liberty is a very wide concept.
It is only infringed by physical restraint and coercion, which is absolutely not the case.
So in this case, A.K Gopalan's narrow view was overruled
And from here we got a wider definition of personal liberty.
Now the supreme court says that if any procedure or
Law which curtails personal liberty, that law
Should be passed by "Test of reasonable". Meaning
That procedure must have to be just, fair and reasonable.
This case is also important because after this case, due process of law
And procedure established by law had no differences remaining.
Both were being included in article 21.
Now, let's talk about "Life". In this single keyword,
There are many human rights included like environment, health, dignity
Livelihood and education. At least 14 to 15 human rights are included in life.
In today's video, we will learn about some important case laws that
Will help us understand how the supreme court interprets life?
Generally, people think that if they have the right to do a certain thing
Then they also have the right to deny it.
Meaning, if I have the right to live then I also have the right not to live.
Meaning the right to die. So, is that right? The very same question was discussed
In P. Rathinam vs union of india case.
In this case what was that petitioners were
About to be punished in IPC under section 309. Because they attempted
To commit suicide. They challenged section 309 and said that
Article 21 also gives us the right to die.
That's why section 309 should be rendered invalid.
Supreme court said that yes, article 21 gives the right to die
That's why it should be rendered invalid. But in today's date, the law being followed
Was given to us by the Gian Kaur vs State of Punjab case.
In this case, the supreme court said that the Indian constitution
Does not allow to weaver from fundamental rights.
So if you have the right to life you can not give it away.
Meaning the right to die is not protected in article 21
And section 309 will be valid.
After this comes the "Right to privacy".  This does not exist as a separate fundamental right
And we always infer it inside article 21
The first important case of this was Kharak Singh vs the State of UP.
The Supreme court said that the right to life does not merely mean animal existence.
If there is any unauthorized disturbance then it is a violation of privacy.
After this, PUCL vs union of india case arose.
It is also known as the "Telephone tapping case". The supreme court clearly said that
Right to privacy is a part of right to life
And unless there is a public emergency or a case of public safety
Then you cannot infringe anyone's right to privacy.
Next in article 21 is right to "Get pollution-free water and air".
It's a very interesting case is RLEK vs the State of UP.
What happened, in this case, was, Masoorie and Dehradun belt
Were being extensively mined illegally and unauthorized. So, RLEK
Wrote a letter to the supreme court stating all of this.
Supreme court treated this as a writ petition.
And by environment protection act ordered all of the illegal mining and excavation
To be halted at once.
After RLEK case, M.C. Mehta case and finally t Damodar Rao case,
The Supreme court finally said that right to live in a healthy environment
Is a part of article 21. Now, let's talk about the impact of emergencies on
Article 21. So listen, article 359
Gives president the power to suspend article 21.
That's why a total of three times, during Chinese attack, Pakistan attack
And internal emergency, article 21 was suspended.
In A.D.M. Jabalpur v. Shivkant Shukla case supreme court said that
During emergency, article 21 can be suspended.
But then came amendment 44th, which amended article 359.
And finally current law is that even in emergency
Article 21 can not just me suspended.
I hope this topic of article 21 is clear to you now.
Do let me know in the comment section how was my video?
For now, see you in the next video. Bye-bye.