I have seen his love story.
Quiet interesting.
- Absolutely.
If we want a twist in it...
I would need a smart man who...
who can handle any situation.
There is only one measurement
in Hyderabad...
like you said.
Battabi!
He has a brain smarter than wolf.
He is a champion when it comes
to illegal activities.
Battabi!
He is the ideal of every lawyer
in this profession.
Battabi!
Just like earthquake sinks
into the ocean...
he shifted to Bangalore
after finishing...
all the cases of Hyderabad.
His office will be opened tomorrow.
Have a seat.
- Thank you, sir.
Sir, my name is Ranjit.
And she is my wife.
Our sign of love...
our dream palace...
is Damayanthi Palace
which has been captured.
How to free it?
You are neither Ranjit
nor she is Damayanthi.
That means you guys aren't married.
That means you are acting to
get hold of that palace.
Hey, how do you know that?
Wouldn't I get to know
if you are lying?
I am not that dumb.
- Oh!
I have dealt with thousands
of such cases.
You know, everyone...
studies law after all.
I have ready every lines
of the law book.
Come on!
He is C. V. Rao.
He was the CEO of Gujarat's...
Google.
He can get you the green card
of America from here. - Oh!
He is Mr Murti.
Expert of false signatures.
He is the smartest when it comes
to preparing illegal documents.
This kid is S. N. Sharma.
It's a cup of tea for him
to find witnesses.
He is a bitch.
Here are the witnesses.
- Hello!
People believe
their lies to be the truths.
And he is...
Mathura Lal.
He has a beautiful name.
But works really hard.
Sir, your team is really good.
You can change injustice into
justice very easily.
Not for free. I charge money.
No matter if you are right,
if you claim she is your wife...
keep working till...
the operation is completed.
I'll try, sir.
- Please co-operate as well.
Act only if you feel comfortable.
Tell me clearly if...
you fall in love with me or...
you have any doubt.
And drop the topic.
There is no need of that.
I can act well.
Thank you, honey.
- Honey?
Who is honey?
Pet name of Damayanthi.
Honey!
What is this game?
Hmm? - The person
who touches it first, wins it.
Touch me, honey.
Honey! Touch me.
- Honey!
The person
who loses has to give a kiss.
Here it is. Have it.
What is this?' Upma' (Indian
food) made of Cashew.
Why so?
For our land, dear.
Have it.
That's nice.
Honey! I touched.
I was the first one.
- No, it was me.
I touched you first.
Honey, the person
who loses has to give a kiss.
Another spoon.
Honey, who is he?
Is he your relative?
Isn't he your relative?
Who are you all? How did you come
in without any permission?
You even came to have
the breakfast? - Sir...
the interior of
the house is perfect.
I became hungry while looking
at the interior...
so I started having the breakfast.
Will you rent this house?
- Hey, Pandit!
If they play like this,
the house will become a mess.
(Cross Talks)
Be careful.
- Get out!
Let's go!
- Careful!
If you have breakfast
at his place...
what else will he do
if not throw you out of the house?
We didn't go there to have
the breakfast. Take a look. - What?
Oh, no, come to the point.
We are legally going to
steal that palace.
Yes, towards right.
- What is this?
We are planning to bring
back the land...
which has been forcefully captured.
Madam will come close to me
along the process.
What if you lose?
I'll have her for
the rest of my life if I win.
If I lose,
I'll live with her memories.
The MLA is coming to meet our sir.
All the arrangements have
been made to welcome him.
MLA should be welcomed just
after he comes down from his car.
He should be praised.
You'll be paid according to
your performances. - Yes!
Let's go, sir.
- Right!
Sir, are you the MLA?
Yes, MLA.
A man with high ambition.
Victory, MLA!
I can't hear anything from the back!
Say it loudly.
There is no rhythm!
Say it together. In the sync.
Who is this MLA?
He is asking me to speak in sync.
Hey, stop!
Who is this MLA?
Take out the garland.
When is our shooting?
We will shoot tomorrow.
Get out of here.
Such an amazing feeling.
I had goosebumps.
I understood
the fun of politics now.
I hate politicians.
Victory, MLA!
Sorry, sir. I got
the respect that you deserved.
People assumed me to be the MLA.
See you soon.
Both of you are close to
the Damayanthi palace.
If you want to communicate
visually...
you have to kiss Damayanthi.
What?
- I am ready.
Roll camera!
Action!
Get inside!
Cut! Sir, I can't do
these things like this.
I'll kiss the green matt.
You are cheating...
and won't do it properly either.
Are you thinking...
that you will fall in love with him?
Do what has been said.
Cut!
How was the scene?
Oh, no!
It's really good, sir.
You got attached as if you caught
cold. Will you not leave me?
If you come to my house once...
I haven't grown up enough to go to
your home. Leave me.
I feel so sorry for Kalyan.
He loves you sincerely.
Don't be foolish, Smrita.
I can't love someone
for this sensitivity.
You know my condition.
Hmm.
Sir, stop!
Hello, sir. Please give me the bonus
of 'Diwali' (Indian festival).
Who are you?
- Sir, I sell vegetables.
You are watching it for
the last 4 years.
Okay, go!
Sir, is Mrs Honey not at home?
Honey is not yours but mine.
Who are you?
I press clothes.
The collar of your shirt was burnt.
That is why you stopped
giving me clothes.
Please talk to ma'am.
- Okay, I will. Leave!
"Every dots have started to match."
"All the evidence of
the crime have been found."
"The truth have been revealed."
"Nobody will be spared
in the court."
"The truth will be prevailed.
- It will be."
Your documents are ready.
"Everything will happen."
"The truth will be prevailed."
"It will happen."
Who captured here?
See, this belongs to him.
You and your wife have captured it.
That is why they filed a complaint.
This is the notice.
Who complained?
Tell me and I'll take care of him.
Honey, this is the sign of our love.
There shouldn't be
any violence in it.
We will win with honesty.
Nothing will happen with
honesty. - Hey!
No matter whatever we have captured.
This is honestly ours.
Everything is legal. We will fight
in the court. - Okay, sir.
How are you both related to each
other? - Wife and husband.
Where did you get married?
I asked where did you get married.
In the temple? In the church?
Or inside your home?
Do you have
the marriage certificate?
At least, show us
the wedding photograph.
Even if we didn't get married...
we are going to get married soon.
Did you listen to them, your honor?
They aren't married.
But they are staying together.
Live in relationship.
What do they exactly want
to convey to the society?
Objection, your honor!
Do they have any proof if...
they are married?
What does the marriage
certificate say?
What does the ration card say?
What does the adhaar card
and the passport say?
The government believe that...
they are Mister and Mrs Ranjit
Singh. - It is possible.
But I have all the original
documents of the palace.
We too have the documents.
You can check.
These are the original documents.
Sir, this is my house.
You can ask
the people living in the colony.
The people are here.
Hello, red towel!
- Yes, sir.
Third row!
Not you. Sit down.
The one sitting besides.
Yes, you two. Come here.
Do you know him?
- He lives in my colony.
One of them is a vegetable seller
and the other presses clothes.
How long do you know them?
- Since 4 years.
Oh!
Then tell me...
who owns the Damayanthi palace.
He can never be the one.
But he is the owner of
the Damayanthi palace.
Hey, why are you lying?
It was 'Diwali' (Indian festival)
when you came at my home.
I understood.
They belongs to their team.
Your honor, I never saw them.
Note this point, your honor.
He just claimed that he knows them
since 4 years.
Now he claims that
he doesn't know them.
That means you didn't
see them either.
Honey, if we agree,
we will be trapped.
We will say that we didn't see them.
No, we didn't.
Your honor...
On the 17th day of this month...
check the CCTV footage
of that place.
Did you see, your honor?
When my client was having
'Upma' (Indian food)
he kicked him out of
the palace forcefully.
Everything is a trap. They came
to ask for rent of that palace.
Does the people wanting rent
has 'Upma' (Indian food)?
Who else do you want to trick?
Your honor...
it is clear that...
every witness has been created
by Mr Bhattabi.
If he is truly
the owner of this house...
he must be having
the footage of the past as well.
Let's check.
Show us.
Huh?
"Justice will be prevailed."
How would you explain that?
Did I shoot them and changed
the CCTV footage of the palace?
Yes, you did everything.
Your honor, let me tell you...
I captured his land.
That is why they are
trying to capture...
my palace by pretending
they are married.
Oh, so, this was the actual plan.
'Now I have to save myself.'
Exactly, your honor.
Ranjit...
capture the property of
their company...
and wounded all
the people who tried to interfere.
Huh?
- Yes.
He wounded them brutally.
To tell them what it costs
to capture the property...
I made the false witnesses
say the truth...
so that my client gets the property.
So that justice is prevailed...
I had to choose the path of lie.
Did you get it?
Thank you, your honor.
Yes!
The criminal has admitted
his mistake.
And he has to return the land...
he captured.
The court decides that
the people involved in the case...
should be imprisoned for 3 years.
Battabi!