Granddad, did you start yet?
- No.
Move aside..
Brother Asha..
Get in line.
It's my turn after him.
Isn't Granddad done yet?
Try another song.
It's weird to help Granddad
by singing everyday.
Get in the line, Apu.
Granddad?
- Yes. - Come on!
Is he still having trouble?
What happened?
Tell him to get in line
for the sweets.
Dad again?
Exactly, Dad.
We spend our mornings
in helping him empty his bowel.
It's all because of him.
Because of me?
Am I stopping him from doing it?
Why can't you get a commode
for the unfinished
bathroom upstairs?
He is right, Dad.
All right,
do me a favour.
Stop being celibate
and get married.
Ask you father-in-law
for a bride, a pair of clothes
and a commode.
Don't be a miser.
Tell him that if he
wants to save money
stop feeding him so that
he doesn't come here
in the morning.
And if he is feeding him,
he should find a solution too.
Move aside.
I am going in.
Hey..
- Hey, we are waiting here.
Why did you stop singing?
It's not helping, is it?
Say that dialogue, Rana,
I will drink your blood.
That dialogue stopped working
before the 'Dussera'.
His system keeps
updating as well.
I think that we should
call a sorcerer.
He too must be squatting down
somewhere right now.
Let's strike the plates.
It helped during
the first lock-down.
The entire India did it.
Only then he did it
at five o'clock.
How will just four plates help?
How did we handle it in Shimla?
It was easy over there.
The hotel was near a cliff.
He got scared
and it became easy.
Let's sing a 'Qawwali'.
They were singing
it on the train
and he got it done
in the first verse.
That's because they were
professional singers.
Should we take him
for Bungee jumping now?
Get him out of there
or else I will
have to do it here.
What happened?
Can't the whole family
together get it done?
Punjabi!
Play a Punjabi song!
The high energy
will make it easy for him.
Are you done?
- I did it in the fourth verse.
Yes!
- Yes!
My dear child..
Feeding a hungry man
and emptying the bowel
of a constipated man
both are noble deeds.
Stay blessed.
Now go ahead.
Hey! - Dad..
- Dad..
Open it..
- Open it!
I have readied your bag
according to the schedule.
The lunch is in it too.
Don't put this water bottle
in the bag if it leaks.
Otherwise, it will ruin
the history and geography.
Where is your school uniform?
Will you go to school
wearing this?
I go to school
without doing my homework.
Today, I will go without
wearing the school uniform.
I see. You will go to school
without wearing the uniform
on your mushroom
cut anniversary? - What?
Have you forgotten?
You had mushroom cut
for the first time on this date
two years back.
You remember the date!
Yes, such small things
bring happiness in life.
Forget it.
Where is your school uniform?
I have not found
my school uniform.
You have not found!
Yesterday, I asked Aloukik
to wash your shirt.
Come with me.
Stop. Where are you going?
Stop.
I won't spare you today.
Don't do this, Mr. Hatasha.
Mr. Asha Amar.
How many times I have told you..
Don't keep your underwear
for drying on my towel.
And what's this?
You wear only red
colour underwear!
It has left colour stains.
It's perfect.
If you wear this towel,
you will look like Superman.
He is making fun of
his elder brother.
What are you doing here?
Has dad hired you to work
in the shop
or he has hired you
to come here and laugh?
He asks me to do every work
if there is any.
Okay, leave!
Aloukik, where
is Akki's uniform?
But it's still dirty.
- Impossible!
Aloukik and I washed
this together.
Wash our clothes which have
become dirty in the process.
But the backside of the
collar is still dirty.
Who looks the backside?
Kids go to school
to progress in life.
This means, you didn't
wash the entire shirt.
Brother Asha..
Brother Asha Amar suggested me
not to wash the entire shirt.
He asked me to remove
armpit stains.
Those parts become dirty
due to sweat.
Even I liked the idea.
Hence, I just removed
armpit stains.
Akki can't go to school
wearing this shirt.
Sister-in-law,
ask him to wear this.
See, I have done a great job.
Thank God!
This shirt is clean.
Wear this. - Okay.
- Just a moment..
What's this?
- Chalk.
Chalk?
- You are surprised, right?
Even this was
Brother Asha's idea.
I just followed his suggestion.
I have been applying chalk
on stains since my childhood.
Brother-in-law,
it was a simple work.
You couldn't even do that.
Last week, I asked
to put papads for drying.
You used hair dryer.
After that, I asked to remove
spider's web from the storeroom.
You kept the stool
on the cupboard.
So that spider's web
can't be visible.
That's the main problem
if something is visible, right?
Spider's web doesn't fly
and gets stuck on things.
It's okay.
Akki, come.
- Aunt.
You give me toffees
and make me wear casual.
I will say that
today is my birthday.
Come..
Sargam, such a small problem!
Is it a small problem?
He is the first student
of the school
who celebrates his birthday
four times in a year.
He has gone to school
wearing casual even today.
Moreover, if father-in-law
gets to know
that he has distributed
toffees for no reason
I will get scolded.
Baby, relax..
It's fine.
Everything is fine.
You always ask me to relax
and say 'everything is fine'.
Stop this.
Because nothing can be fine
just like that.
Actually, 'Poha'..
Hey, today is Tuesday, right?
You must have prepared
Parathas too.
I couldn't prepare
Parathas today.
Why?
It's fine.
'Poha' is fine.
'Poha'?
But today is Tuesday.
You must have prepared
Parathas too.
Appu.
- Aloukik, my brother..
She has prepared
only 'Poha', okay?
Only 'Poha'!
It's fine, Aloukik.
See.
Everything is fine.
Are you preparing breakfast
or inventing corona vaccine?
How long will you take?
Yes, breakfast
is ready, Brother.
Sargam has prepared 'Poha'
which is very tasty.
'Poha'.
Since today is Tuesday
she must have
prepared Parathas too.
Brother-in-law, I made
arrangements for Parathas too.
But it took so long
to finish other works
that I had no time to prepare
anything else other than 'Poha'.
But I have time to
eat Parathas too.
You will have time
to eat even 56 dishes.
Dear, take time for eating
seeing the menu.
Don't ask her to prepare food
since you have time.
Nastik, someone
is very happy today.
She has saved his money.
Go to Prashant's house
and see.
Three dishes are prepared
for breakfast.
Prashant's three
brothers are married.
Sargam is managing
everything alone.
Asha Amar Awasthi,
what should I tell you?
You even broke your marriage.
Sargam takes care
of your kid too.
That's all right, Father-in-law.
You'll get 'Parathas'
for sure next Tuesday.
Very nice, Sister-in-law.
Never break the pair of 'Pohe'
and 'Parathas' every Tuesday.
You should think of your pair.
He is one more great man who
has taken the vow of celibacy!
Dad, this world is an illusion
and marriage is a disturbance.
We came alone in this world,
we will have to go alone too.
This was said by 'Guruji'!
Alaukik..
I say that you shouldn't
get married either.
Don't you dare
make him like you.
You won't understand
the happiness you get
when you throw money for
your son's marriage.
Right! You're getting your kids
in trouble for your enjoyment.
I don't want to eat 'Poha'!
Brother-in-law,
you will get 'Parathas'
next Tuesday for sure.
- Yes!
I was gathering up the
mess that you had made
so I only got the
time to make 'Poha'.
The mess that we made?
What mess did we make?
We even washed our shirts.
Yes! Everyone listen
to this carefully.
Henceforth, no one will speak
of shirts or wash shirts.
Got it?
Baby, I told them.
You all had taken the
responsibility of killing
the cockroaches using
insecticide, right?
Did anyone do it?
That day,
Alaukik was putting something
behind the refrigerator.
Yes, my 10 rupee coin
had fallen there.
I was looking for it.
Did you find it?
It was mine.
Father-in-law,
I've been cleaning all
the suitcases and
bags since morning
there are cockroaches
everywhere.
If dad gives us some
money to go travel
then people may use that bag
or else, only the cockroaches
will rest there.
Sargam..
Coming..
- Come, Dad!
For a little 'Poha', a man
has to work all day long here.
Sargam, you pour that
insecticide on me.
Yes, put it.
Yes! I'm the cockroach
of this house, right?
No, Brother-in-law,
it's not like that.
Then what is it like?
Nothing happens in this house
according to me.
I'm trying my best to see that
everything happens
here as per your wish.
Does it?
You come to our room
and cry every day.
'Brother, she made
curry today too!'
Why are you laughing?
'Cumin rice..'
What do you say? Even when
you sneeze, cumin comes out.
No one is happy with
this system, change it.
What do you mean?
- I mean, democracy.
Even our government
changes in five years.
The house should be
run according to
the person who makes
everyone happy.
And who will that be?
It can be anyone.
It can be me too.
That's very nice,
Brother-in-law.
You run the house from now on.
I don't have any problem.
No.. Or people will say that
Asha Amar Awasthi scared
his sister-in-law and took
over the reins of the house.
It should be a fair selection.
Yes.
Fair selection.
Here's a deck of cards.
You pick a card,
sister-in-law will pick one.
Whoever picks the bigger card
will run the house.
They're not deciding on
what to get for meal
Chinese or Pizza,
to choose using picking a card.
This is an important decision
of running the entire house.
And important decisions are
never made in this house.
What?
- What?
It's done by voting.
- Yes..
That means, election.
Brother Asha against
sister-in-law.
No..
I mean, my system needs
to be changed, right?
So, I can't do it.
Appu, you contest the election.
Okay..
What! Me?
Hey, they like Ms. Sonia
and Mr. Manmohan.sssss
I mean, Appu will do what
Sargam tells him to.
He got scared of losing
the election already.
I'm not scared of anyone.
That's fine then.
Our second candidate is Appu.
Yes, perfect!
Beware, Brother Asha.
Never forget what
Spiderman said.
What?
- Spiderman.
He watches Hindi dubbing.
Spiderman says
'With great power comes
great responsibility'.
What!
What?
Forget all that.
The voting will take place
tomorrow morning at 10.
You can campaign as
much as you want today.
Tomorrow onwards, the person
who wins will run the house.
Yes, absolutely.
That person will take all
the decisions of the house
like how food will be made
who will do what and
how things will be.
Inform about this
to Eklavya too.
He may be the youngest but
his vote will count too.
Here he is.
Breakfast is ready?
'Poha'?
Today is Tuesday.
There will be 'Paratha'
with 'Poha' too. right?
No!
Sargam.. Baby.. Listen..
This won't work without you.
Hey! Your name
means immense power.
But you are crumbling under
responsibilities. - Hey..
No.. That's not the case.
The thing is, if
Brother Asha wins..
He will make everyone
eat jackfruit every day.
I love jackfruit.
- No, but.. - Appu..
Relax. It's fine.
Everything is fine.
Brother Asha is not
ready to understand
at least you try to understand,
Spidey.
What..
- Look.
With power comes responsibility.
But if Brother Asha
gets powerful, he'll forget
his responsibility
and become careless.
Then he'll make such
strict rules.. - Yes..
Why are you scared?
You may win this instead of him.
I am not an expert
at running a house.
You'll become one.
I've been trying to be
one for four years now.
'Sargam, do this, do that..'
'Sargam, where is this?
Where is that..'
Where is the stapler?
Sister-in-law, I am asking you.
You are in-charge
till the elections happen.
There..
Come here.
Sit here!
Why do you want a stapler?
For what?
Distances are growing between
India and Pakistan for years now
so I thought of stapling
the countries together.
Really?
What do you mean why?
I want to staple something.
It is kept above the cupboard
containing crockery
in the left drawer.
Off you go.
Also, shut the cupboard gently.
Slam it and the crockery inside
it will come crashing down.
Saw that?
Saw that? You're teaching people
how to shut a cupboard!
I am not kidding..
Nobody here knows anything.
You know everything.
You are aware of everything.
How will they manage?
I will be here and help you out.
Passive help.
Don't just sit.
Go and campaign for votes.
Or be prepared to eat jackfruit.
My fear has come true.
I am afraid, my fears
may also come true.
Dear family members!
If I win the election,
every Sunday
you will get ice-cream twice!
Ice-cream..
- Yay..
Promise only that
which you can fulfil.
For how long will we
have tea in broken cups?
If I win the election
I'll get new crockery
from the storeroom.
Please tell him
that changing crockery
won't turn tea into cappuccino!
To have good tea,
we need to do away with
the terrible tea leaves
dad brings in wholesale.
If I win, I'll get
premium tea leaves.
Forget the tea leaves.
I'll get better rice.
We shall not have
the useless rice anymore.
Four times a week,
I'll get basmati rice for all.
Sargam, I will press
all clothes for you.
Ekalavya, I will massage
grandpa's feet for an year now.
Dad, I'll keep the accounts
and save your money.
Forget it, you fat-headed.
For how long will you rub
used soaps on your body?
I'll get you a personal soap.
What should I bathe with now?
You will be free from
washing the tank every month.
Brother, I will perform
all the asanas you teach me.
Master!
One, two, three, four, five
six, seven, eight..
The voting is complete.
Now count them..
I mean, count the votes..
Oh, I am sorry..
Only one.
Did Asha win?
Who won? Tell me.
- Brother Appu gets..
Zero votes.
Congratulations, Mr. Asha!
You won with majority.
Now the house is
in your control.
No, Sister-in-law.
That's the wrong vibe.
He has got just one vote.
What do you mean?
Mr. Asha got one.
Appu got zero.
Then he..
All the chits has your name.
- Okay..
You all have written my name
on the chits.
Great!
I thought I am the only person.
Yes, Grandpa, even I thought
it was just..
But everybody has..
What's all this?
- You won this battle.
Why did you do this?
Listen..
- Sargam..
Sargam, what's wrong?
Sister-in-law, I thought
you will be free.
Then I read a survey report.
Every year 4.5 percent of people
die in kitchen because
of gas leakage.
If they forgot to switch it off
then we are all gone.
Grandpa can't even run.
- No, I..
I can't run.
Listen, Sister-in-law.
I am a celibate.
I follow all the rules
with honesty.
But I have read a book.
All the necessary things
in this world are feminine.
For example, pen.
Books, earth
and the crops on land.
Even roti..
- That's enough.
Come to the point.
All these things
are feminine.
So how would men run this house?
Nice.
Very nice.
But I never thought so deep.
What's there to think?
It's you, Sister-in-law.
You never let us realise
our mom's absence.
Right.
These fools can become
a part of this circus.
But they can't run it.
Even you are not perfect.
But who wants perfect?
Manage what you can.
Leave the rest.
Imperfection makes a house.
Only hotels are perfect.
Like I said..
It's fine.
Everything is fine.
Come on, Brother Asha!
You voted yourself.
It was a waste.
- I didn't vote myself.
What!
It wasn't you!
We all wrote her name
then who..
Sister-in-law!
I voted him.
That means even he has
voted sister-in-law.
It wasn't intentional.
Yesterday I saw your diary.
I thought I should have a look.
I thought it would be as usual.
But I saw a list for whole week.
I looked at it carefully.
And I didn't find it usual.
There were so many little things
which are essential
for the house.
If you start reading
it will need the entire day.
Monday's list was covering
the page of tuesday.
These are the works
which we think are easy.
But today I learnt
how difficult they are.
It needs courage.
It really needs hard work.
The hard work for which
we never thank her.
You have been doing this
since four years.
But we only know
how to quarrel for food.
I don't think we could have
managed it.
But I have understood.
Sargam, nobody can do
what you do here.
About my vote.
That's not a big deal.
Yes, the lockdown taught
all the men.
There's no holiday
in the life of wives.
People say 7:30 is a bad time.
But in my case
it's the opposite.
Appu proposed me
at 7:30 p.m.
Also, before this marriage
our affair lasted
for seven and half months.
Even the circumambulations.
I mean we did extra half.
Now you all have
become my world.
It might be bad for others.
But for me it's a path
for happiness.
Aunt..
Come, dear.
Aunt, I am extremely hungry.
- Okay.
Please prepare something
within ten minutes.
What can I prepare
in such less time..
'Poha' is the only option.
- What!