imagine living in scorching heat with no
access to food water or electricity
while constantly fearing for your safety
this is a saddening reality for the
people that live in this remote Village
in Zambia where locals are forced to
rely solely on natural resources to
survive and due to isolation from any
City and no access to light during the
nights many children are left to
navigate in complete darkness making it
extremely dangerous as there is a high
crime rate in the area this only became
evident to us 6 months ago when a woman
named Dora Muno sent us this Tik Tok
pleading for our help be philanthropy
please please help me save our village
our kids need you I immediately sent
Darren there to find out what we could
do to help Dora and her
community upon his arrival Darren
received an extremely warm welcome from
the
children hi Dora how are
you I came to my papa village where we
are right now in 2019 I started to
notice that some of the kids they
experienc horrible situations just
having that constant threat on your life
is terrible I felt very cold to come
back and do something so within a year
Dora packed up her life along with her
already adopted four children and moved
from luaka to mapapa to start building a
village to rescue as many children as
possible and the first thing I did was
build a mud hut and my kids and I lived
in the mud hut the kids would use my
house as classroom during the day and
then at night we would use it at a house
but when the rainy season came it got
washed away this forced Dora to turned
to Tik Tok for help the very first day I
posted I did not get any views at all it
took one song and that small video
helped me to have my first follower
which I moved from one to close to 4.5
million this on its own is an incredible
feed especially without any access to
electricity or reliable cell reception
as you can see there's barely any
connectivity out here well there is
actually one way every time I have to
post out here I have to hold my phone up
for close to 30 minutes depends can I
track my phone I got to download some
cat videos I don't know if it's working
just a little bit longer oh can you get
a signal hold it don't move it is it
working okay good we're done to hold it
like that it is she is doing all of this
solely to generate income through
donations to expand this Village we've
rescued 350 kids we provide good
education for them we provide meals for
them just for them to experience a
different lifestyle from what they know
but the cost of maintaining this school
have become increasingly expensive and
impossible to sustain meaning it won't
be long until the school will have to
close down it became evident that the
lack of electricity was holding them
back and severely curtailing Dora's
ability to help develop this Village to
what its potential could be having to
wake up and thinking what will these
kids eat that is still very difficult to
do each and every day so we came up with
a plan to use the direct sunlight and
scorching heat to our advantage by
installing a massive solar grid that
will provide electricity to the entire
Village while we've worked on even more
ways to grow this Village and surprise
Dora with the team along with our
amazing Partners at give power spent the
next few months secretly building this
solar
plant again I want to emphasize how we
would never have been able to pull this
off in time without give power after
months of planning and a lot of hard
work I'm pading the last Bol in the
Solar Ray we're finally
done as you can see behind me the sun is
Now setting and in a little while we're
going to be turning on the lights for
the very first time and from now on the
kids will no longer experience Darkness
at
[Music]
night the moment has finally come we're
just about to turn on all the lights
Mato the electrician is waiting in the
container and I'm going to radio him and
give him the go ahead M turn on the
nice and we have
light
yeah to witness these children's
reaction to light such a simple
necessity was incredibly
humble oh it was a joy it was a sight to
behold and we're very grateful to be
philanthropy for that but we weren't
done just yet there's barely any water
in the water that they have is not
Quality Water this is one thing that
electricity just cannot solve and with
the extreme heat could be fatal as they
only have one tiny pump that lasts for
30 minutes per day and 350 kids and 84
staff have to be taken care of by this
little water and that's including the
water that they need to be able to cook
fresh food so every day I will have to
then get into my car which will either
start that day or it won't start that
day then from there if it does run
she'll have to do a 2-hour round trip
just to get cold water but Darren is
about to surprise door about how this is
all going to change after to I've seen
everything that you've done here what
you're doing with these kids we decided
we're also going to do a hydrological
study and we're going to give you a
proper well a professional deep deep
well so that you're never going to have
to worry about water again we're going
to install an electric water heater in
the kitchen a commercial gas stove and
we're going to more than triple Your
Capacity in solar production okay thank
you it's been a dream come true honestly
so that is amazing so thank you so much
you're teaching all of these kids to be
empowered and stand up for themselves
and you're going to change society here
cuz they're going to grow they're going
to raise their families this way they're
going to spread the message that you're
teaching them you're planting seeds
because they love you as much as we do
but obviously doing more would incur a
much bigger expense so we reached out to
our long-term partner and sponsor of
this video electric ebik as always we
shot him a message saying hey we need
help funding this project we think it
will help a lot of people and as always
they responded no problem and then
proceeded to double Their donation for
this video because of electric ebikes
generosity we will be able to provide so
much more for Dora and these children so
make sure to go to their website or
click the link in description and buy
one of their electric ebikes right now
by purchasing their product you help
them make more money so they can sponsor
more videos and we can help more people
okay let's get back to the video and for
one final surprise before we left Darren
wanted to give the kids his favorite
treat this is the first time any are
going to get ice cream it's a very rare
treat because it needs Refrigeration
which they haven't had before who want
ice
cream awesome let's
[Applause]
go as always thank you for watching the
video by doing that you helped us make
more money so we can help more people by
giving us your eyeballs for this video
you helped us generate ad Revenue with
which goes straight into our Beast
philanthropy charity which goes straight
to easing human suffering all around the
world and when it comes to this project
we want to make sure that Dora never
needs to worry about providing for these
incredible kids again so if you want to
do even more you can click the Donate
button below or visit Beast
philanthropy. org and we'll be sure to
get all the money to Dora and obviously
it's not possible without you guys so
thank you for continuing the show up and
subscribe if you haven't already or I'll
be very
madany oh