Welcome to Techno Ruhez, this
is the first video of our in MWC.
There is a lot of noise,
I apologize for that.
But here we have come to the Infinix booth and we have got to witness two big technologies.
The first thing is that
I have this phone.
This is Infinix's eColorShift
technology smartphone.
It has Prism 3 technology.
If you look at the back,
it glows in different colors.
And it reacts according
to the design you want.
That is, if you want to wave someone or want some other design, you can do that here.
You get 8 basic colors in this and you can
customize this color in 100 different ways.
You get to see a lot of amazing
technologies in this.
And in the future, such phones
of Infinix will come to the market,
in which we will get
ColorShift technology.
Its back panel is quite
premium than normal phones
As I was telling you, if
you look at this back panel,
you will feel that this
is a front display.
But this is not a front display,
this is a back panel.
And if you look here,
it glows like this.
It will look like there is a camera in the
display, but it is not like that.
This is a back design.
So this kind of technology will
be in the future smartphones,
where the whole back
panel will glow in different colors,
which you can customize
according to your needs.
Do tell us in the comments
how did you like this technology.
And this is our
AirCharge technology.
You will see that this phone
is getting charged here.
And this is a device of Infinix.
And in this device, you just have
to take your phone close to it.
You don't have to
connect it with a wire.
touch it wirelessly.
It's not like you put it
in a wireless charger.
As soon as I take it here, you will see
that the phone has started charging.
You can see that the
phone is charging.
I haven't done anything and
the phone is charging here.
This is AirCharge technology.
Right now, Max you can
see the charging speed of 7.5W.
It's 20cm.
It won't work from here.
I will have to take it very close.
And when I go, you will see
that the charging has started.
The distance you get
here is not much.
It's very less.
If you come up to 10cm, then
it provides you with a charging speed of 1-5W.
So this is their
AirCharge technology.
Infinix has done it here.
Which other brand....
I think Oppo has done it before.
Now Infinix has done it here.
I would like to test it again.
This is the phone.
As soon as we take it here, you
will see that the charging has started.
This is how AirCharge
technology works here.
We will get to see this in
the market very soon.
And who knows, we might get 30W, 50W,
60W fast charging through AirCharge in the future.
And before I go, I will give
you an exclusive news.
It is being said that Infinix will launch a
flagship smartphone very soon.
Many people complain that Infinix
does not launch flagship smartphones.
Why don't they do it?
So we have come to their booth.
And they have shared
this video with us.
It is being said that a very powerful
chipset is going to be installed.
And this chipset is not any else
but Mediatek Dimensity 9300.
We have also spoken
to Mediatek people here.
And they have also confirmed that this
chipset is going to be installed in Infinix phones.
And they are going to give it to you.
So it is very good news that Infinix will
launch a flagship smartphone.
In which Mediatek
Dimensity 9300 is going to be installed.
So let's hope for the best.
I hope you will like today's video.
I have shown you three technologies.
E-Colorshift technology, AirCharge
technology and a flagship smartphone from Infinix.
Subscribe to the channel for
such coverage of MWC.
So that you get the latest notifications.
Like and support.
Till then always keep smiling.