Come on, in!
- Yes, I'm here.
Just say the word.
Where are we
with the Myntra designs?
And is the meeting
with king set up?
I need these designs approved asap.
If you're going to
meet this deadline...
And we're going to meet it. Okay?
Listen, those are too many words.
And not a single one sounded good.
Well, I've sent the presentation.
Did you check?
Yeah, I saw it.
And?
- There's too many ruffles. Okay?
They're not working for me.
Neither are the...
The pleats and the patchwork...
I mean...
I need something that's a little
more ramp. - Listen, chill.
Let's go out, have a drink.
And let's discuss it over a drink.
You are young and single.
No, I'm hoping
you're single considering...
...you spend all your time here.
Yeah, I'm a loser. Okay?
But I keep my professional
and personal life separate.
Anyway, thanks.
You go, enjoy yourself,
have a drink.
I'm going to finish our work.
- Okay.
Bye. Good luck.
Okay.
I'm still here.
Thank you.
Bro, we're going to lose.
- Yes, loser.
Hey.
Oh!
- Whoa!
Crap!
Ooh! We go!
We go!
I hope you know he is not
the real Gaurav from 'Going wrong'.
He is fake.
- Yeah, actually I'm the fake one.
Yeah.
Yes, creep.
- I was kidding.
What would I have done without you?
- You would've been lame.
Well... - Hey, listen.
Your taste isn't bad.
Got it?
- Right.
You see that place, over there?
- Yes.
That's exactly where
I'm going to perform.
You won the Indian challenge!
- Hey, it's not that bad. Right?
No!
- You're glad you came, right?
Yes.
- Who wrote the pallet?
Actually, there was no ink
in the printer.
And I had to send
the designs because...
...my designs are heading
this season's evolution trunk.
It's very deep.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
You're so much nicer when you
like your clothes, you know that?
I'm always nice to you.
Okay, stop it.
Well, that depends how you
describe 'always'.
Anyway, I'll call your drinks.
So, how are you coping up with...
...Raghav's exit?
Don't look at me like that.
- I'm just asking you.
I'm fine.
- Are you?
Yes.
I knew he was going back to London.
So, I'm mentally prepared.
So, have you deleted his number?
I never dial once I'm drunk.
Okay, cool.
Give his number to me then.
Why do you want it?
- I like that guy.
He is a nice guy, he is in London
and he knows a lot of people.
You are my friend,
you cannot hang out with him.
But why? This is not fair.
- That's it.
End of discussion!
- Hey!
He is my Ex.
- So?
You can't do this.
Fine. If you have a problem...
No!
Darn it!
This was the moment...
We were waiting for this!
Oh, God!
It was such an awesome batch.
The carpet was awesome too.
Deva, are you serious?
They left because of you,
didn't they?
I'm alone... - Did you even
notice I was at home?
How does that matter?
Do you watch football?
It does matter. I was in the kitchen
cleaning after you and your friends.
Oh! Wow!
This is such a classic... It's...
Fantastic! Just because
I'm enjoying my evening...
...I'm happy watching this match
and my friends are here...
...but you have to make sure,
you put up this drama!
You can't sleep without it,
is it? - Dev.
I was in irritating meetings
since morning.
And when I come back home,
I just want to relax.
I don't want to take care of
you and your friends and...
...take care of
this house or do anything.
So, don't even talk to me about
drama right now. - What should I do?
You want me to keep
the cushions here?
Yeah?
- Please! Don't do anything.
Yeah? Something else?
- Don't do anything!
Can I watch my match now?
Thank you so much.
- You're doing that anyway.
Okay...
Do you ever wonder
what happened to 2008 batch?
Like, where are they?
How are they? - Yes.
I think about them every day.
Really?
- No.
Okay, so this might...
...interest you.
Open.
Yes? No?
Maybe?
- Uh! No.
Why?
- Why would I go?
And who goes to these things?
- I do.
Yes, you're really cool.
So are you.
- Great!
You will thank me
in a while, of course.
Yes! We're done!
You've made a group?
You added me to the group?
I love you too.
Delete me now.
- Of course.
There's a ten year school
reunion next month. Dev!
Dev.
Dev. Dev!
Dev!
What have I done now?
- Nothing.
I'm talking to you.
Anyway, there's a reunion
next month. - I'm aware.
It's mentioned in the group.
- Group?! Which one?
Here.
Where's your phone?
It's on charging.
Should we go?
I want to go.
Thank you so much
for coming with me, G.
I would've forgotten this file.
It's okay.
By the way, Piya is in
and so is Sam. And that...
Diptanshu is out! So happy.
I never liked him.
Aww...
Do you think
that Piya still has those...
Do they grow, with age?
Say yes.
I think they do grow.
Hey! I'm talking about the group.
The reunion.
- No!
I'm not coming
for the stupid reunion. - It's not!
It's not stupid.
- Yes, it is.
It's not.
Dating Raghav has just made
you this uptight person.
Hey! - You haven't
met them for 10 years!
I mean it will be fun to see if...
...people have changed
or not at all.
Just do me a favour.
Just give it a thought.
Please.
G...
If I wanted to see somebody
from school, I would have by now.
And everyone who I want in
my life is alrready in it.
Like you.
- I know.
Thanks. But that's not true.
If I tell you something,
you won't believe me.
But let me tell you something,
you still miss Deva.
Okay!
No.
I haven't thought about her
for a long time.
Ans she doesn't miss me.
Where is the pickle from Aarya?
It had fungus, so I threw it away.
What else did you throw away?
My electric shaver is missing too.
That got spoilt.
You would have got a shock.
That didn't happen with
your taunts though, right?
You know, if you didn't insist
on being this man child...
...there would have been
no need for me to taunt.
I know. I know all this lecture.
If you know everything,
you can try to change atleast.
What do you mean?
- I mean, I am fed up...
...of your childish behaviour.
I have a life and I'd really
like to go and live it...
...but I am out of such...
- Hold on.
I didn't ask you to do that.
You are doing it by yourself.
In fact, it would be
better if you don't do it.
Yes, because it's a perfect life.
You don't go to work.
You stay at home and drink.
Watching stupid...
- This is also my house.
I am paying the rent
for the last four months.
I'm chasing my dream
and it takes time.
How would you know about it?
You don't have any dreams.
You're living your
comfortable life.
Dev, I did and you know it.
Then we got married
and life happened...
...but I knew that I
have responsibilities...
...and we worked
together as a team.
I know that we are us
and we were never just I.
Was that supposed to be
an explanation? - Oh, shut up.
Okay, let's recall.
We met in school
and started dating.
And then suddenly we got married
because that was your right time.
Then you wanted to move to US
And you wanted to do
a family planning...
...because that was your
bloody right time.
Did you ever think that was
the right time for me?
Your right time?
You never wanted to marry after
being together for seven years.
You wanted me to keep
waiting around for you...
...to figure out
what your right time was?
I wish I had spent those
years in chasing my dreams.
I would've really...
- You don't know that, Dev.
You know everything.
- I do. - Wow!
So, you know very well where
the cushions have to be kept...
...because that's
how you planned it.
Wine glasses have
to be clean, right?
The bedsheets should
be clean, crisp...
...and there shouldn't
be grease on it.
As per your plan.
We'll get married at the age of 25
because that's how you planned it.
We'll plan our family at 29!
You know what?
Hell with you and your planning!
You spent your entire
life planning!
Have you ever realised?
Have you ever lived
those moments with me?
I enjoyed being with you, Dev.
I enjoyed being married to you.
I enjoyed doing up this house.
Why do we always
end up discussing this?
Because all I wanted was...
...to watch and enjoy my match,
with my friends and my beer.
Of course!
Hello!
Seeing messages from
your reunion group...
That's why I called.
Is Deva coming?
- Dev said yes. So...
...I guess, yes.
Hang on!
Woah! Good Lord!
Listen. Deva just replied.
She's coming!
Okay! Good night!
Good morning!
Yeah! Good morning!
It's 8:30 in the morning.
Why don't you take a shower?
I've already put the breakfast on.
No, it's fine. I'm okay.
You drank quite a bit. Might
be nice if you had something.
It's alright. Thank you.
Okay, let me just cut to the chase.
We're going to the reunion anyway.
They're expecting us, so...
...I was thinking whatever happens
here, should not happen there.
Can we...
...can we please be
nice to each other?
No name-calling, no sarcasm.
Let's just be nice.
Was this request for you or for me?
For both of us.
Listen, Deva.
I'll take my own time. Please.
Look, Dev. I...
I hate saying this, but we
used to be the perfect couple.
I mean, people used
to look up to us.
And we were in love
and we got married.
And I know we're...
...a little, but...
It's a rough patch
and it's just...
If we go there like
this, fighting...
...in front of everyone.
Can we please just be...
End of the day,
you are just concerned...
...about what they'll think.
Okay, fine. Let's just be...
...cordial to each other.
Okay?
Just that.
Yeah.
"What do I think about now?"
"These passing winds say it all."
"We'll meet when at leisure..."
"All of us, will meet again."
"This life is so unpredictable!"
"Where is it leading us to?"
"I wish to revisit the old...
...memories again."
G...
...when do we leave?
Hey, my brother!
Such drama!
- It's me, Kunal!
Yaay!
- Woah!
Don't make a scene
just because you...
...think you've this new
found freedom. Please!
I don't have his new found freedom?
Actually, I have it.
What's happening?
Why is he behaving like this?
I followed you because
I knew you were hurting.
It was hurting...
...10 years ago, too.
Where were you then?