In September of 2009, a critical event unfolded
in the rugged terrains of the Shuryak Valley
in Kunar province, Afghanistan.
A powerful Blackhawk helicopter, on its mission
to rescue wounded Marines, found itself under
intense fire from Taliban militiamen.
The situation on the ground was dire; the
defending forces were outnumbered, and the
Blackhawk's position became increasingly perilous
amid the escalating firefight.
In this tense moment, pilot Patrick Benson
made a sudden and unexpected appearance in
the most surprising of helicopters, barely
suited for the situation.
His Bell OH-58, typically used for light reconnaissance,
entered the fray.
Despite its compact size, the OH-58 was no
stranger to combat.
It could be armed with an array of weapons,
including Stinger air-to-air missiles, a .50-caliber
machine gun, podded 70mm Hydra rockets, and
AGM-114 Hellfire air-to-ground missiles.
It was a bold move, and Benson drew the enemy's
fire towards the small helicopter, risking
his life to protect the wounded Marines.
The OH-58 took several hits, with its nose
being punctured by small arms fire, injuring
both Benson and his co-pilot.
Despite his injuries, Benson persisted in
his efforts, ensuring the Blackhawk could
safely evacuate the area.
This act of bravery and dedication to his
fellow soldiers would later earn Benson and
his co-pilot the accolades they rightly deserved.
Moreover, this incident showcased the resilience
and dependability of the OH-58, aptly nicknamed
the Kiowa Warrior…"
The Ugly Duckling
Following the success of the American-made
helicopters deployed during the Far East campaigns
of World War 2, the military envisioned and
developed several types of rotary wing aircraft
tailored for different uses.
Besides providing transport for troops and
carrying supplies for logistical support,
such as the Korean War era Sioux, or the future
Chinook, helicopters began to be employed
for retrieving other helicopters and aircraft
and even delivering artillery and ground vehicles
across difficult terrain.
Others, such as the future Bell AH-1 Cobra,
would find their purpose as gunships armed
to the teeth, ready to provide immediate fire
support to allied ground troops and effectively
decimate the enemy.
As American involvement in Vietnam increased,
the United States Navy commenced looking for
a replacement for the Bell OH-13 Sioux and
Hiller OH-23 Raven for the reconnaissance
role.
Both helicopters had been successfully used
during the Korean War for MEDVAC or medical
evacuation.
However, they struggled with their piston
engines, offering a maximum output of 250
shaft horsepower.
On behalf of the Army, the US Navy approached
over 20 helicopter manufacturers for the submission
of proposals for a Light Observation Helicopter
or LOH.
The designs had to be powered by an Allison
250C-20B free turbine engine, and their primary
role was to be the eyes in the skies for military
intelligence.
Besides reconnaissance, the rotary-wing aircraft
had to be capable of ground attack, transport,
and medical evacuation roles.
Of the twelve helicopter manufacturers that
entered the competition, only three were shortlisted.
Bell presented the YOH-4A or Model 206, Hughes
the YOH-6A Model 369, and Hiller the YOH-5A
FH1100.
Bell produced five prototypes of its helicopter
that were tested thoroughly in 1962.
During its maiden flight, Army and Navy personnel
referred to the YOH-4A as the Ugly Duckling
when compared to the competitors.
It was not a good omen.
Ranger to the Rescue
After testing the Bell, Hiller, and Hughes
helicopters, the Army ultimately settled for
the Hughes OH-6 Cayuse “Loach” in May
1965.
Despite the Army's decision, Dave Ostrowski,
an Army aeronautical engineer in the LOH contest,
said in issue 10 of Take Off magazine that
Bell's model: (QUOTE) “Sprang off the ground
like a homesick angel.
It had power, speed, and maneuverability.
It felt good.
It was a super ship to fly.”
Nevertheless, it was not over yet for Bell.
They knew their helicopter had potential,
and the company decided to market it for civilian
use.
But first, the engineers had to redesign the
Ugly Duckling to attract customers.
The displeasing bubble face canopy and small
fuselage had to be reshaped to be easier on
the eye, provide more space for the cramped
quarters of the three passengers, and ample
cargo space.
In January 1966, Bell presented a redesigned
fuselage and dubbed the new helicopter the
Model 206A Jet Ranger.
The fuselage was more aesthetically pleasing,
added over 16 cubic feet of cargo space for
luggage, and made the passenger compartment
more pleasing, providing enough space for
up to five people.
Furthermore, the Jet Ranger was also modified
internally.
It was now powered by a 317 horsepower Allison
250-C18 engine.
The Ranger had its maiden flight the same
month and experienced no issues.
It became a best seller in the coming months,
becoming a familiar sight around the United
States.
The Jet Ranger was adopted by the government,
forest services, law enforcement, news broadcasters,
and tour companies.
Bell's Jet Ranger became so recognizable that
even Italian manufacturer Agusta acquired
the production rights to fly the Jet Ranger
over the skies of Europe.
In January 1968, Bell scored big when the
Jet Ranger was solicited by the US Navy to
come up with a modified variant for flight
training.
Over 40 TH-57 Sea Rangers were produced.
And there was more to come for Model 206.
The Kiowa
While Bell's Jet Ranger flew thousands of
people across the US without incidents, Hughes’
OH-6A Cayuse struggled in Southeast Asia.
The fighting in Vietnam had turned into a
meat grinder.
In January 1968, the North Vietnamese launched
a mass offensive during the Tet New Year festivities,
and dozens of cities were sieged by the Communist
forces.
Thanks to the effectiveness of the Ho Chi
Minh Trail, the North Vietnamese Army was
now supplied and equipped with modern Soviet
and Chinese equipment, including anti-aircraft
countermeasures that were making quick work
of the American OH-6A Cayuses.
The Cayuse was exposed to enemy fire during
scouting and artillery fire correction missions,
making it an easy target for hidden Viet Cong
or NVA troops.
Casualties for Hughes’ helicopter were piling
up, and the company could not keep up with
production and its costs.
The Army reopened the LOH competition because
Hughes could not meet production demands.
Bell submitted its upgraded Model 206 Jet
Ranger and won the contract.
It was designated OH-58A and named the Kiowa,
following the Army's tradition of honoring
Native American tribes.
The OH-59 Kiowa was delivered to Army inventories
in May 1969.
It had a length of 34 feet, a width of 35
feet, and a height of 12.9 feet.
The scout helicopter had a weight of 3,289
pounds.
Compared to its civilian variant, the Kiowa
featured military instruments, multiple radios,
Army olive drab livery, and deflecting blades
above the canopy and belove the nose to avoid
crashes with electrical wires.
The Kiowa was also powered by an Allison T63-A-700
engine rated at 315 horsepower mounted atop
and to the rear of the passenger cabin.
The cockpit was well-forward and provided
all-around visibility for the pilot and co-pilot
thanks to the large windscreens and the option
to remove hinged side doors.
Changing the Mission
Behind the cockpit, the passenger cabin featured
entry-exit doors and enough room for three
soldiers or two medical litters.
The first Kiowa variant featured a flexible
twin-bladed main rotor that would later be
replaced with a four-bladed one with the OH-58D
model.
The first batch of Kiowas arrived in Vietnam
in August 1969 to support the Hughes Cayuse
in the reconnaissance, observation, and medical
evacuation roles.
The Kiowas were lightly armed with either
an M129 40-millimeter automatic grenade launcher
or a powerful 7.62-millimeter M134 Minigun
that could fire up to 4,000 rounds per minute.
During a North Vietnamese offensive in April
1972, John Paul Vann, a US civilian advisor
who often piloted Kiowas, directly coordinated
the attack of AC130s, jet fighters, Cobras,
and Hueys to destroy enemy formations trying
to overrun Firebase Delta in the Highlands.
In his book, A Bright Shining Lie, Author
Neil Sheehan recalls that Vann, unsatisfied
with providing guidance for US aircraft, began
stocking his Kiowa with as many supplies as
the helicopter could handle to deliver them
to Firebase Delta.
Six times the brave man and his Kiowa delivered
ammunition and other supplies to the besieged
troops under enemy ground fire.
Weeks later, Vann and his Kiowa were landed
in a ravine to extract US and South Vietnamese
advisors while enemy tanks approached.
The helicopter escaped unscratched.
But Vann's luck soon ran out.
On June 9, 1972, he and his entire crew were
lost when his Kiowa crashed into a hill due
to low visibility and light rain.
Over 310 Kiowas served in Vietnam between
1969 and 1973.
More than 50 of them were combat losses.
The Warrior
Following the end of the Vietnam War, the
US and NATO prepared for a possible large-scale
Soviet Invasion of Western Europe.
The Soviets had AA defenses that were far
more effective than the highly effective Strela
2-man portable air defense system.
This led to an improved variant of the Kiowa
equipped with an AN/APR-39A Radar Warning
Receiver to inform the crew about enemy radars
and night vision goggles for night operations.
A more powerful engine made the helicopter
faster and more maneuverable.
This was the Charlie variant or OH-58C.
Nevertheless, this variant did not solve the
armament issue the Kiowa faced since Vietnam.
Meanwhile, the Army was hard at work introducing
the iconic UH-60 Blackhawk and the AH-64 Apache.
In 1981, the Army Helicopter Program upgraded
the Kiowa with sophisticated sensors, a thermal
imager, a laser designator, and the iconic
MMS or Mast Mounted Sight that made the Kiowa
easily recognizable.
The Kiowa Warrior, or the OH-58D variant,
was fitted with a Rolls-Royce T703-AD-700A
turboshaft engine providing 650 horsepower
and a top speed of 149 miles per hour.
It had a range of 345 miles and a service
ceiling of over 15,000 feet.
The Warrior packed some punch and was armed
with 12.7-millimeter machine guns in either
M296 or M3P mounts, Hellfire-guided anti-tank
missiles, Hydra 70 high-explosive unguided
rockets, and AIMS-92 Stinger air-to-air missiles.
During the 1980s and 1990s, over 400 Kiowas
were upgraded to the Warrior variant, becoming
crucial for their new armed light scout role
during the conflicts of the Middle East in
the same decade.
Iraq and Iran were engulfed in a power struggle
that resulted in US involvement in providing
escort services to merchant ships in the Persian
Gulf.
The Kiowas were bound for the Persian Gulf.
Reagan's War on Drugs
Kiowa Warriors replaced other helicopters
for Operation Prime Chance during the Iran-Iraq
War.
The objective was to escort oil tankers.
From February to September 1988, the Kiowas
patrolled the Persian Gulf but were never
engaged by the Iranian Navy.
During these operations, the Kiowas cooperated
with Task Force 118 Little Birds, locating
and evading enemy vessels.
One year later, in 1989, they returned to
the Middle East when Iraq invaded Kuwait.
As Operation Desert Shield turned into Operation
Desert Storm, over 115 Kiowas were deployed
for different combat roles.
Like in Vietnam, the Kiowas spotted Iraqi
objectives for Apache helicopters and other
attack aircraft to hunt them down.
They also provided artillery fire correction
to properly strike the enemy.
No Kiowa Warrior was lost in combat during
the war against Iraq during the Gulf War.
During this time, the Kiowas were also dispatched
to the US following Reagan's War on Drugs
Policy.
The National Guard Bureau created Reconnaissance
and Aerial Interdiction Detachments or RAIDs,
of which over 80 were Kiowas that conducted
more than 1,200 counterdrug reconnaissance
and interdiction operations.
At the dawn of the XXI century, the Kiowas
were again deployed to the Middle East as
part of the War on Terror.
The OH-58D became part of the air units participating
in Operation Iraqi Freedom and Operation Enduring
Freedom in Afghanistan.
According to Bell, the Kiowas flew over 820,000
combat hours by April 2013.
Over 35 helicopters were lost in combat operations
and accidents before American retirement from
Afghanistan.
Drawing Enemy Fire
While in Afghanistan, Chief Warrant Officer
Patrick Benson flew numerous reconnaissance
and security missions on a Kiowa, becoming
the eyes in the sky for American attack helicopters.
In September 2009, Benson and his co-pilot
were providing security and reconnaissance
for infantry attacking Taliban troops in a
mountain in what is known today as the Shuriak
Valley.
Benson left the area for a refuel, and minutes
later, the Marines left behind were ambushed.
During the fight, two Marines were hurt, and
Benson was called again to provide Medevac
security.
The Blackhawk helicopter dispatched to hoist
up the wounded Marines was immediately attacked
by the enemy, threatening the extraction.
The men on the ground did what they could
to fight off the enemy attack, but they were
outnumbered, and the Blackhawk’s safety
turned precarious with every second that passed.
It was then when Benson’s Kiowa appeared
out of nowhere and did the unbelievable for
a light reconnaissance helicopter of its class:
it began to draw enemy fire away from the
Blackhawk.
Soon, the small helicopter’s nose was punctured
by small arms fire, wounding Benson and leaving
his co-pilot unconscious.
Nevertheless, Benson did not falter and continued
to assist until the Blackhawk safely evacuated
the area.
With his aircraft failing and his best-man
Adam Stead wounded, Benson landed at the nearest
base to save his co-pilot and his Kiowa.
Due to his extreme bravery shown in combat,
Benson was awarded the American Legion Valor
Award, proving that even a small helicopter,
such as the Kiowa, can change the tide of
battle if used properly.
The Army officially retired the Kiowa from
service in July 2020 after it selected the
Bell 360 Invictus and Sikorsky's Raider X
as possible replacements for the Future Attack
Reconnaissance Aircraft program.
Nevertheless, the Kiowa remains in operation
with several allied nations across the globe,
proving that after more than 50 years of service,
it continues to excel as a reconnaissance
helicopter.
Thank you for watching our video!
Please like and subscribe to our Dark Skies
channel to watch more videos about American
helicopters during the Vietnam War.
Don't forget to hit the bell icon to be notified
of our newest videos!