[ MUSIC ]
We were first given a welcome drink
as soon as the we enter in the aircraft.
To be honest it was awsome.
Everyone does business class
travel for their own purposes,
i do because i get extra space.
I may sleep till my destination,
get a flat bed so that i can start my
work as soon as I reach my destination.
So, i don't get travel fatigue.
It has enough leg space,
this space is here to keep the stuff.
But can't keep at the
time of take off and landing.
If you don't want to watch
Tv, you can turn it back.
If you want to tookout the
table, you can took it out.
This is the standard, the
light will go on from here.
This is the seat controls.
Left,
Front, back,
Up and down.
This is the charging point.
One headset is given inside.
I travelled with Cathay, DELHI -
HONG KONG and back to Delhi.
In boeing 777 aircraft.
I find the seating arrangement
of Cathay airways amazing.
They have a configuration of 1-2-1.
Means,
1 seat on side, 2 in the
middle and then 1 in side.
Last year, when we went to U.S
So we in travelled
business class on the same
aircraft, the boeing 777
but of British Airways.
Althrough, you can lie down in
flight but i had trouble in turning.
There configuration looks like this,
It's look crowed.
And it was,
2-4-2
So, i can lie down like this,
so they don't have any option.
They will have to pass by walk my legs.
It's the worst thing while travelling.
The first thing we did when we came,
Remove the shoes.
And
Waers cabin slipers.
On every seat of Business
class there is a amenities pouch,
in which you got basic amenities,
Like an eye patch to sleep,
Body lotion,
Face mist,
Lip balm,
Brush, Toothpaste,
Mouthwash
And i don't know what was this.
But this pouch was of very
good quality and i kept this safely.
This help me to keep my
camera gadgets and accessories.
The cabin crew came and
took our order even before taxi.
If you are vegetarian then make sure
you tell them before booking otherwise,
It becomes very difficult to get veg
food in foreign flights if you don't order.
The flight was going great
and the take off was great too.
But what i realise after take-off, Oh Man!
This is the boeing 777 Aircraft.
And the one I've flown before was
an Airbus 350 from Cathay Airways,
Airbus 350 is a new aircraft
and boeing 777 is an old aircraft.
I decided to check the
sound levels on my Iphone.
Noise levels were,
Too far than 80 decimals
Amplitude which is a but noisy.
The small seat in front of
me, I can fit a small kid in it.
But whatever you say, the
space given in this aircraft,
I loved it, I love space.
I mean this space, the space
of space, not the space of space.
On the side of your
seat, there is space where
all your small things
will come, phone etc.
There is space below where
your big things will come.
There is space in front
where your shoes will come.
And above that there is space, there
is a small seat where there is leg space.
I mean people who say there is
space in life, they should come here.
In-flight entertainment, the TV screen
given to you, its size is very good.
And in-flight entertainment
is also very good.
I decided, let's play a video game today.
It's a long flight, I'll download
some Stuff on my phone and see,
I said, let's see that.
It was meal time,
And before the meal, I ordered
one red wine and some nuts.
- Thank you
As soon as my drink was over,
the crew prepared my table very well.
And my meal came.
There was a special note with the meal.
I am saying again and again that
if you are traveling internationally.
And if you are a vegetarian, please make
sure you tell them during ticket booking
That you are taking a veg
meal, it will not be a lot of trouble.
When the meal came,
I was a little shocked to see it.
I was only given salad in the meal.
And raw mushrooms were
given to me in the salad.
I thought, maybe this is healthy in
Hong Kong, people must be eating there.
But then I realized that this is an
appetizer, the meal will come later.
Then I was thinking that how
can I eat this bread with salad ?
And do you know why it was happening?
It was the wonder of a wine.
But when you go to a
new country, you think,
maybe this is the custom here.
Immediately after this, dinner was served.
It was a good dinner, it was fun to eat.
But now I started enjoying the raw mushrooms.
Finally, the meal came.
I thought I would have to eat
raw mushrooms with bread.
But no, I was wrong, obviously I was wrong.
No one can be so cruel.
But this looks good.
- Thank you
- Yes, I make travel videos on YouTube
That's what I do professionally
Whenever I travel, I share my experience, how was it.
Stuff like that.
I travel a lot
- Whenever you need food, please
call us, thank you
- Thank you so much
Dinner is done, I ordered one more wine and
cheese platter.
Cheers !
Oh man,
such a big washroom.
I have seen such a big washroom
in an aircraft for the first time, 777.
Usually,
washrooms this much in
size, cards are given here.
And this space is used in the galley.
Means this part,
Think, move this part
forward, happens here.
But this is,
Oh man.
But this is so much space.
777 is a big aircraft,
It has a lot of space but still,
Airline saves space.
But I love the space on this aircraft
The only thing I don't like is
The engines are a little noisy.
My elbows are so dry.
Why i am realizing
everything in the washroom.
Do you know why my elbows are dry?
Because I srtike people with my elbow.
Man, the whole aircraft's
lights are turned off
This is the signal to stop vlogging.
And go to sleep
Guys, in this 5-hour flight, we
spent 2.5 hours like this.
All the people around us have gone to sleep.
Now, let's put our bed sheets and get ready to sleep.
You get two things on the bed,
One to wear one,
And one to lay down.
I have never laid down bedsheet in my life.
Whether I travel in a railway,
Whether I travel in a plane,
Even if I sleep at home.
I just take it to wear.
But today,
because I am making a review.
I have to work properly.
And by the way, this
review is not sponsored at all.
I have made ready my bed, ready to sleep.
I turned off the lights.
And bbye..
The trip is over.
Time to go home and see the kids.
The trip was very comfortable.
The food was amazing.
The overall experience was
very good, Big thumbs up.