[Shikha] 'Everybody, take cover.'
[Gunshots]
Check!
Check.
[Shikha huffing]
[Shikha] There's a species of ants
found in the Amazon forest.
[Shikha] The bullet ant.
[Shikha] The bullet ant's
bite lasts for 24 hours.
[Shikha] And nothing in this
world is as painful as this bite.
[Shikha] The tribes over
there have a ritual.
[Shikha] For a boy to
become a warrior...
[Shikha]...he has to put his hands
in the bullet ant's nest.
[Shikha] If he tolerates this
pain without breaking or crying...
[Shikha]...then he
becomes a warrior.
You've always told me
that I'm your daughter..
...and I should not try to
be your son.
But I think you've forgotten
that I am YOUR daughter, Dad.
Every time, I proved the people
who discouraged me wrong.
I love you, Dad.
But it's time to put
my hand in the ant's nest.
Bring on the bullet ants.
[Title Montage]
[March past practice]
[Bus roving]
Attention.
[Foot thump]
Bend position, everybody.
- 100 pushups.
- One.
Two.
Three.
I am Naib Subedar Kripal Bhatti.
Seven...
Next few months are going to be
the toughest months of your life.
- Ten.
- Our only motive is... - Eleven.
- ...to break you from inside
and from outside. - 13.
Amongst the whole
of Indian Army...
....24 of you had the courage
to come here
Take a close look at the person
next to you.
And bid them farewell .
Because soon, either he won't be
a part of this course, or you won't.
23.
- 24.
- And the ones who are left...
...will be given an opportunity...
...to fight for the nation
and for their names.
- 46.
- She's very sexy.
- 47.
- A woman in a uniform.
48.
- Oh!
- 49!
50!
There's always a guy
in every batch...
...who thinks he is
smarter than others.
- Did you say something?
- No, sir.
I can even read your mind.
And he always has a bootlicker too.
Do you want to do 50 more pushups?
No, sir.
- 87.
- We've never had such a weak batch.
88.
89.
90.
Shall I send you back?
98.
99.
100.
Party, stop!
Here. Fall in!
We don't want you.
Let me repeat that.
We do not want you.
You all feel that you're
good enough...
...to be the elite of the elites,
don't you?
Are you capable of operating...
...without eating, drinking
and sleeping?
Are you capable of going
through the pain...
...which no one else can
even imagine?
Are you capable of keeping
the nation's respect...
...while putting yours at stake?
Are you capable of
this maroon beret?
- Yes, sir!
- Bullshit!
Bullshit!
Look at you.
- Sir, have you got the forms?
- Yes, sir.
Always.
These are your non-volunteer forms.
Please sign these and go
back to your units.
Please don't waste my time, okay?
One by one, please.
Come on.
Oh.
- So you all have guts to
prove me wrong? - Yes, sir!
- You want to enter hell?
- Yes, sir.
You want me to give
you the chance?
Yes, sir.
Until now...
...you all were from
Madras regiment...
...mechanised infantry...
...or artillery.
But henceforth,
you'll just have one identity.
You are a nobody.
- Were you winking at me?
- No, sir.
- Were you eyeballing me?
- No, sir. There was a fly, sir.
Captain Bilal Siddiqui.
I've heard that people from
Lucknow are quite sensitive.
- Is that true?
- No, sir.
Better prove me wrong.
What's written on the wall?
Read what is written on the wall.
- We make men out of boys.
What would I make out of you?
A commando, sir.
Bloody hell!
Because of this MOD meeting,
I missed my call.
And God only knows what bomb
she's going to drop on us today.
Fighting with a
politician is like...
...wrestling with a pig in the mud.
Even if you win, you lose.
What is...
- Morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
Thank you.
[Clears throat]
Thank you for coming, Generals.
Ma'am, is this meeting about...
...the seventh pay commission's
anomalies or...
It's about something else,
General Raman.
Something which is
important than all this.
As you're aware,
on February 23rd, 2016...
...President Pranab Mukherjee
had announced in the parliament...
...that women too will be inducted
in combat roles.
Ma'am,
some things are easy to announce...
...but hard to enforce.
There are already lady officers in
combat roles in the navy and the air force.
Yes, ma'am...
As far as the IAF and navy go...
...you can't compare apples
to oranges, ma'am.
A fighter pilot is only responsible
for his own life.
Be it male or female.
But in a tank, where four people
stay in such a small place...
...they eat together,
sleep together...
They... Pardon my french, ma'am.
They even piss together.
And a lady...
What are you trying to say,
General Raman?
A woman can't handle that stress?
Or she can't take those
physical conditions?
Ma'am.
On the border,
imagine, if something untoward...
...happens with a lady...
...what will we do?
Will we handle her
security or the nation's?
Why did countries like
Australia, Canada and the US...
...didn't think about this while
accepting women for combat roles?
Our serving conditions
are very different.
The background from which
our soldiers come...
They've not
interacted with any woman..
..besides their mothers,
sisters, or wives.
And ma'am,
during a combat operation...
...stress levels are already high.
So, why should we add another
layer of tension?
That's your opinion.
It's not a fact.
I'm not saying that it's
going to be easy.
No. It's going to
be tough initially.
But this is the future, Generals.
Not just the future,
run down the memory lane.
Queen Laxmi Bai,
the one who fought a battle...
...with her child tied on her back.
Ma'am, if the question is of
equality of men and women...
...I would definitely
agree with the fact.
In fact, women...
Don't patronise me, General Raman.
Don't teach me about
women's capabilities.
Fair enough, ma'am.
But there's also
the issue of capture.
If a lady officers get captured...
...are you aware of the torture...
...they'd have to go through?
You have a point.
But patriotism doesn't
come with gender.
A women can tolerate
the same pain that a man can.
What is that Harvard study?
Yes, ma'am.
Gentlemen, according to a study
by Harvard university...
...a human body can only
withstand 45 units of pain.
But while delivering a baby...
..a woman feels up to
57 units of pain.
Just like 20 bones of your body
being crushed all at once.
That's the problem.
Wikipedia's articles, WhatsApp's
forwards and the entire world...
...believes anything.
Ma'am, why are we trying
to fix what's unbroken?
Because just like every other
established organisation...
..the army too avoids changes.
And General Bedi...
...now even naxalites and
jihadis are recruiting women.
Yes. They're also recruiting
five year olds.
Shall we do that too?
General Bedi...
Ma'am..
I request you to please read
Justice Khaitan's report.
She too was quite inconclusive
regarding this.
I beg your pardon, ma'am.
But the army is not politics.
Where one can get everything
through reservations.
And the fact that we've managed
to maintain such a high standard...
...is because we've just one basis.
And that is merit.
[Turning pages]
I agree.
Captain Shikhar Sharma,
age 28, army brat...
...state 5000 meters and
10,000 meters champion.
World class triathlete.
Had achieved sword
of honour in the academy.
Serving in military intelligence,
currently...
...has volunteered for special
forces training course.
You can see all the ACRs.
What do you think?
Should we give a chance
to Captain Shikhar Sharma?
Definitely.
Good.
Because actually,
her name is not Shikhar Sharma...
...it's Shikha Sharma.
And if Captain Shikha Sharma
passes this commando course...
...of the special forces...
..then, you'll have to
open your gates, gentlemen...
...to more women.
And to battles not between
the sexes...
...but battles that
shall be fought together.
Captain Shikha Sharma
will be our test case.
This is called a surgical strike.
I can't see the army being
butchered like this...
...in the name of gender politics.
I'm putting my papers down.
Relax, Bedi.
A good golfer has the
determination to win...
...and the patience
to wait for breaks.
This is the special forces,
and not a picnic.
Your backpacks are a
part of your skin...
...and the gun is a
part of your body.
These two should always
be there with you.
It doesn't matter if you're asleep,
awake, or in the bathroom.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Louder.
Ma'am.
There's a separate
arrangement for you.
After all, you can't stay
with them.
Sir, what do you call
the rest of the officers?
Sir, ma'am.
Call me the same.
Yes, ma'am.
Sir...
[Marching]
[Indistinct voice]
[Clapping hands]
[Unloading the gun]
B*******d, look at him!
His father is a General and his
brother is an instructor here.
Didn't he get commissioned
in his father's unit?
He gives such intense looks,
he thinks he's a hero.
- Bhatti will get him on track.
- Yes.
I've heard that
he's quite hot-blooded.
Just like Nana Patekar
in the movie "Farar".
Do you always have to
use movie references?
Without films...
- Did you get parathas?
- Hey!
You're a Punjabi.
Did you bring phirnis?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Will you have it?
- Yes.
Bin.
Do you remember?
In the NDA too...
...we had beds right
next to each other.
Of course, bro.
Those were the days.
Always better in
hindsight, my friend.
Well, speaking of hind side...
...do you still have
the rash on your back?
Do you wish to scratch it?
That's a cute a*s.
Oh, bromance!
Love is in the air.
"Dostana 2".
There you said it.
Just like how a person who
got in through IMA would say.
We may be that but we
reached here on our own.
Be my guest, Tank.
I anyway liked that bed better.
Hey, Thapa,
please take the other bed.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Who named you Tank?
No, I'm sure your parents didn't
name you Tank Chauhan.
Right?
Hello, ma'am.
Porn won't save your a*s in
the battlefield, my friend.
Not porn.
- This is my good luck charm.
- Is it?
First episode, bra salesman.
First published in November 2008.
Well, Mr. Rathore
If you think entry through
IMA is a forced entry..
- ...what is getting commission called
in your father's unit? - Merit.
Merit.
Forced entry!
Well, the real forced entry
is Captain Sharma.
A single dorm for all of us.
We need to bear the shoe stink
and snores of everyone.
And special room for her.
Is this a commando
course or a honeymoon?
Wait and watch, partner.
I don't know how many more rules
are going to be broken for her.
The one who will lose to her
will have it from me.
What if you lose?
Come on.
You know me better than that.
- No f*****g way.
- I can see that.
When will they call us for lunch?
You didn't get parathas also.
Good morning, sir.
At ease.
Captain Shikha Sharma,
Military Intelligence, Delhi Cantt.
Sent here directly by
Ministry of Defence as a test case.
Father,
Subedar Major Devichand Sharma.
12th OKRA.
My unit.
Has three sons.
But he sent you.
He didn't send me, sir.
I joined the army
because I wanted to, sir.
- Jhajhar Singh.
-[Jhajhar] 'Sir?'
What is the most common thing in
the list of these officers?
- All are men, sir.
- What?
- Okay.
Captain Sharma.
I am not a misogynist.
I respect woman.
Especially the women
who reach their destination...
...not because of their gender
but because of their ability.
That's exactly the plan, sir.
I don't need any special
privileges from you.
It's too late for that, Capt.
Sharma.
You came here because of the direct
recommendation of a minister.
This is a special privilege
in its own.
You staying in an officers'
guesthouse is a special privilege.
A lady RMO being appointed
just for your sake...
Again a special privilege.
I didn't ask for any of it, sir.
Actually, I came to place
a request here, sir.
I want to stay in the dorm
along with the other officers.
Dismissed.
"- There was a beautiful girl.
- There was a beautiful girl."
"- A rifle man saw her.
- A rifle man saw her."
"- He forget to wipe the floor.
- He forget to wipe the floor."
"- Major saw him.
- Major saw him."
"- He punished him.
- He punished him."
"- The quartermaster was smart.
- The quartermaster was smart."
"- He cancelled the ration.
- He cancelled the ration."
"Badluram's body is beyond
the ground..."
- Good afternoon.
- Look who is here.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Captains,
say hello to the military Barbie.
- Hello.
- Military Barbie.
- That's a new one. Hello.
- Is it?
- Please.
- Thank you.
You'll have to excuse
Rohan, he's a chauvinistic a*s.
Sorry, ma'am.
Oh, no.
Please don't ma'am me guys.
Shikha or Shiks will be great.
I'll feel a bit better.
Okay, Shikha.
- So, Capt. Shikha...
- Yes.
Since you are a part of us now...
...you will be welcomed
in a special way.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- Shall we have something sweet?
- Of course.
- This is phirni. I saved this
last one specially for you. - Yes.
Oh, God!
Have it...
Especially for you.
No.
I won't have this phirni again.
- That's pretty lame.
- So is this.
We need to fight for our name,
salt and target.
Salt being the operative
word there.
Sure but...
This is all you guys have?
There should be something tough.
Yeah, we have, Military Barbie.
Okay, let's see.
How long can you stare at...
- ...Surjewala's balls?
- Not cool, guys.
- No... I got this.
- Come on. Get up.
That's okay.
I know where they are.
Okay.
Come on, Surje.
Go for it, boy.
Eyeballs, right?
Nice.
- Beauty with brains.
- Smart.
Well, you do have balls.
For a woman.
Actually, I could never
understand this phrase.
Why do balls represent strength?
They are the weakest part of
a man's body. Right, Captain?
It hurts a lot.
The vagina, or p***y as you guys like to
call it, denoting a coward...
...is actually the strongest
part of a woman's body.
It pushes out an entire
human being.
It pushed you out, Capt. Rathore.
She nailed you, partner.
Now that's what I call
a vagina monologue.
- That's a good one, Capt. Avinash.
- Thank you, lady.
Please call me Avi.
All right, gentlemen.
I'll take your leave on that note.
- I just stopped by to say hello.
- Sure.
- Capt. Sharma.
- Yes?
Even I know how to drop punch lines.
You are a lady officer.
I respect you.
- That's why I didn't say more.
- Respect?
I have been hearing such
sexist comments...
...in the guise of chivalry
for many years, Captain.
And I am actually used
too much worse.
In OTA and in the unit...
So, please spare me your bullshit.
I am used to blocking such
noise since childhood.
But you seem to be a little
weak in this matter.
Why don't you focus on
your work instead of me?
Did someone see Colonel Sathe?
His phone is out of reach.
- I met him at the war memorial
a while ago. - Okay.
Please inform everyone
not to come near the main building.
We have a situation.
- What happened, Captain?
- Capt. Surjan is on the roof.
The door is locked and
he has a loaded weapon.
[Slamming the door]
Open the door.
[Door opening]
- Capt. Surjan.
- Back off.
Back off.
Or else, I'll shoot. It's loaded.
I won't step ahead without
your permission.
Where the hell is Colonel Sathe?
He's on his way.
Who...
Who are you?
- I'm in the new batch. Today
is my first day here. - What?
Lady officer in special forces?
Don't lie to me.
- Who are you?
- I'm not lying. I'm the first.
- And I'm here to help you.
- How?
To understand why you want
to risk your entire career.
I broke my ankle.
- I broke my ankle.
- I understand.
You don't understand.
I have only one motive, that is...
...to be an officer
of the special forces..
...and serve this flag.
This is the motive of everyone
present here.
So, I do understand.
Have you heard about Camp Dosaq?
That is the stress test
of our course.
Everything was fine till
the last hour of the last day.
I cleared everything.
But one stupid mistake
and I broke my ankle.
I hadn't spelt for 35 hours!
It could happen, okay?
I hadn't slept for f*****g 35 hours!
And they will declare me
medically unfit and send me back.
I told everyone in my battalion...
...that I'll be back after becoming
the special forces commando.
What will I tell them now?
- Are you sure he has only a glock?
- Yes, sir.
Jai Hind, sir.
Damn, Kripal.
He was the best of his batch.
He still has the ability.
-But... - That word has no place
in the special forces.
Only the toughest of the tough get
to wear the maroon beret.
[Shikha] 'You know the rules,
Captain.'
One injury can fail
the entire mission.
I can complete my operation
with this broken ankle.
I am a...
I am a special forces commando.
Not a bloody civilian!
Do you understand that?
I understand.
You can apply again next year.
You can still earn
your maroon beret.
Nothing is lost.
Nothing.
But if you pull that trigger,
your life will be ruined, Captain.
Please think about it.
I know.
I just want to meet
Colonel Sathe...
...and beg for one more chance.
Just one more chance.
- Go upstairs with Kamat.
- Sir.
- Go this way.
- Okay.
- Kamat.
- Jhajhar Singh. - Sir.
Please hand me the weapon.
Is one more chance too much to ask?
Please hand me your weapon.
Thank you, Captain.
Thank you.
Captain Surjan.
Come down.
Immediately.
Can you hear me?
Captain.
Give up your weapon and come down.
- Captain.
- Surjan.
- If you don't come...
...I'll have to take
disciplinary action.
Drop the weapon.
Drop the weapon, Captain.
Drop it.
Your first day was quite eventful.
How did others behave with you?
Sit up, please.
Some were good,
some were a little weird.
But no one was normal.
Rotate for me.
This is a crazy way
to meet someone...
...for the first
time, Capt. Sharma.
- Please call me Shikha.
- Aparna.
You have been posted here
just for my sake.
I hope you are not
upset about that.
Of course not.
I got a chance to serve in SFTC
because of you.
Anyway,
I wanted to meet that crazy girl...
...who wants to be an example.
No pressure.
But the future of all the girls of
this country is in your hands.
Thanks.
Okay.
Just some bruising.
No broken ribs.
Okay.
Thank God.
Or else, they'd have sent me back
before the course could even start.
You can wear your shirt now.
Tell me one thing.
What were you thinking
when you went up there?
[Gunshot]
Actually, something similar
has happened before.
And I couldn't do anything
at that time.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Colonel Sathe has called you.
Afternoon, sir.
You are trying to get on my nerves
from the very first day. Isn't it?
Who gave you the permission
to go upstairs?
Are you trained to handle such
situations, Capt. Sharma?
Permission to speak freely, sir?
Granted.
At ease.
I'm very sorry, sir.
I reacted with my instinct and gut
at the time of crisis, sir.
But please correct If I'm wrong.
But SF commandoes
are trained to do the same.
You are not yet a
commando, Capt. Sharma.
You are far from it.
Do you even realise...
...that I can throw
you out of the academy...
...because of this behaviour
of yours?
Yes, sir.
But I won't do it.
It'll be too easy.
I don't have to work
too hard for that.
You will go on your own.
You won't be able to
complete the course.
I beg to differ, sir.
You really think you are a
special case, don't you?
No, sir.
Then what?
A nutcase?
- No, sir. - Then who the
hell do you think you are?
The test case, sir.
[Notification sound]
[Theme music playing]
- Good evening, sir.
- Good evening.
My apologies, Capt. Sharma.
Military Intelligence Directorate
has been on my a*s...
...to take this from you.
Sir, this will be my last job
for the MI.
It has the intel
of the terrorist sleeper cell, sir.
I hope you get the b******s, sir.
I hope so too.
Well, is your commander,
Colonel Sathe aware...
...that you are here?
- Sir, had he known...
...I would have been going home
by a Haryana Roadways bus.
And if this was not
a time sensitive handover...
...I wouldn't have risked jumping
the academy fence on the first day.
If anyone deserves to be
the first woman in combat...
...and in special forces...
...it's definitely you.
Thank you very much, sir.
Really good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
- I'll take your leave.
- Night, sir. Sir.
- Good night.
[Engine starting]
[Bhatti] 'Where the training
of the army ends...'
[Bhatti] '...the training
of the special forces begins.
Without sleep, water, or food...
...you'll fight against
your enemy and win.
From today, with every drill...
...our leader board
will be updated.
After 8 weeks, many officers
among you will pass out...
...and become entitled
to the maroon beret.
But only one of you,
who tops this course...
...will get that special
commando dagger.
- Did you get my point?
- Yes, sir...
[Whistle]
[Bhatti] 'Those who sweat
in peace...'
[Bhatti] '...do not
shed blood in war.'
[Bhatti] 'Your body will
get tired, you will lose hope...'
[Bhatti] '...you will get
out of breath...'
[Bhatti] '...but
you must not stop.'
Speed up.
Come on.
Hurry up...
This is special forces. Buck up!
Jai Hind.
Jai Hind, sir.
The cut-off of this obstacle
was 7 minutes.
Capt. Tank, you completed it
in 5 minutes and 7 seconds.
Congratulations.
You are in the first position.
Capt. Manit.
You are in the second position.
Very good.
And Capt. Sharma,
what do we do with you?
I think we have to make
a new obstacle course for you.
- No, sir. I'll do it, sir.
- When?
Your upper body strength
might be better than other girls.
But special force training doesn't
differentiate between genders.
Anyway, here in SFTC
there is a special principle.
No matter who makes the mistake...
...everybody gets punished.
Until Capt. Sharma completes
this obstacle within 7 minutes...
...everyone will get
limited ration.
Lack of food.
- Did you get it?
- Yes, sir...
F*****g told you, man.
All of us will be in trouble
because of her.
Yes, dude.
- Manit, S***e.
- Hey, Avinash.
I am from the Garuds!
What's up, my friend...
- My friend. How are you?
- Very well.
- You've impressed everyone here.
- Always, brother.
Superb, man!
By the way, have you met
the legendary Capt. Rathore?
I met him in the mess,
very briefly.
- Hi. - You hold a good reputation
in the regiment.
- Good to finally meet you.
- Pleased to meet you.
Rohan, your friend
is improving, dude.
Shikha.
I mean, Capt. Sharma.
You too, man.
You were together in NDA, right?
Yes, we were.
People’s priorities change.
- You okay?
- I hope this is not sympathy.
Because that will make me
feel like an outsider.
Not at all.
It's...
It's support.
Believe me.
I know what it feels like
to be an outsider.
My name is Bilal Siddiqui.
That is why I joined the army.
Because here,
things just don't matter.
Are you getting me?
Call me Shikha, Bilal.
I'll do that.
See you.
- See you at dinner. Bye.
- Sure.
Read what is written on the wall.
- We make men out of boys.
- We make men out of boys!
What would I make out of you?
I swear on Sunny Leone.
My stomach is growling.
I am famished.
Lack of food is killing me.
You have the solution
for your hunger.
What?
- Eat Ms. Savita.
- S***e.
It sounds so wrong.
Hey, come on.
Banta, your Santa is here.
And look what I got.
- Look.
- You thief! What is this?
I convinced the guard.
And Capt. Manit got food from CSD.
One minute...
First, repeat after me.
- I am from the Garuds.
- Say, my friend...
- Ahead.
- Always ahead..
- Victory to...
- India...
Slowly.
Everyone will get it.
Move..
- Did you finish the food?
- Yes, Dad.
Good girl.
I told your mother...
...that you won't do homework
on the weekends. Okay?
-'Love you, Dad.'
- I love you too, baby.
Bye.
You've changed a lot
after marriage.
No, dude.
I think it’s becoming a dad
that changes you.
You'll know it one day.
Your entire focus is on your kid.
I mean..
You become so protective.
Even if there is a mosquito
in the room...
...you will be worried
that it might bite your daughter.
- Dad of the year 2017.
- No, dude.
All the mosquitoes and flies
remind me of our dearest Bilal.
- Were you winking at me?
- Were you eyeballing me?
No, sir.
There was a fly, sir.
By the way, where is Bilal?
Where do you think?
15.
16.
Hey.
Hi.
- Good evening.
I thought you could use
some reinforcements.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
But I don't want
to break more rules.
I see! So, you have
already broken a rule.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Why are you...
Why are you killing yourself?
Bilal, if I don't complete
this obstacle course...
...Bhatti will throw me
out of here...
...saying,
"Carry on, Capt. Sharma."
I have to give it everything.
It's do or die, Bilal.
Is it important to prove a point
always and every time?
Always and every time.
"The motive of my life
is to protect my country."
"India is in my heart."
"I am not weak
nor less than anyone."
"I don't mind sacrificing my life."
"I am proud to say
that the tricolour is my life."
"India is in my heart."
Check.
I am hungry.
Eating a few biscuits
doesn't help at all.
No problem.
It's a matter of one day.
Tomorrow, she will fail again.
There will be no more
food shortage.
No, dude.
She is strong.
And I have a feeling
that she will do it.
- Let's bet for Rs. 2,000.
- Sure.
Even I am in.
She won't be able to do it.
- Dude.
- She will do it.
- Right?
- Let's see.
You came here because of a
minister's direct recommendation
This is a special privilege
by itself.
Say hello to the Military Barbie.
Girls cannot become
a commando in the army.
No pressure.
But the future of all the girls
of this country is in your hands.
I don't have to work
too hard for it.
You will leave willingly.
Only 20 are left.
Capt. Sharma.
We are giving you
the last chance today.
If you fail,
your exit form is ready.
But this time, the difficulties
will be doubled.
You will be carrying a load
of 10 kilograms...
...from the start.
Because the weak
have no place here.
- Did you get it?
- Yes, sir.
Dude, I think I'll lose my money.
Keep Rs. 2,000 ready.
[Whistle]
Come on, Capt. Sharma.
It's easy to go home.
But do you want to go home?
Try!
Come on...
You shouldn't stop.
Pull yourself.
Jai Hind, sir.
[Footsteps]
Done.
At ease.
7 minutes and 10 seconds.
But you completed this course
carrying a load of 10 kilograms.
So, according to our principles...
...you are given 20 seconds extra.
And because of this...
...you are safe from getting
disqualified by 10 seconds.
Congratulations, Capt. Sharma.
I think there is still time
for you to go home.
Thank you, sir.
Go and have food.
The food is served for all of you.
Well, no matter what we say...
...but she has an X-factor.
That is why she won the bet.
- What say, hero?
- For sure. Well... For sure.
Capt. Rathore.
You lost the bet.
Hand me the money.
Are we allowed to get wallet here?
I'll give it to you in the dorm.
- Good evening, boys.
- Good evening.
I heard about a bet...
...that I won't be able
to complete the obstacle course.
It's between the boys
so I don't want to interfere.
But I feel bad
for the ones who lost.
Just cut the crap, Capt. Sharma.
All right?
Capt. Rathore.
Listen to what she has to say.
Dude...
No offence to anyone.
But I just want to say
that people should stay focused.
Focus on the leader board.
Forget about betting.
- Isn't it?
- Of course.
- Won't you get me a beer?
- I made you win.
- Come on.
- Bilal, you coming?
You'll be paying the bill.
Come...
Sir.
Bar brawl with the police.
Right?
Got any explanations?
Sir, I was in Mhow.
I had completed
the Junior Command Course.
They were goons from Meerut.
They were teasing my friend.
So, I..
I just gave it back.
But what do I do
about the FIR, Capt. Avinash?
Look.
Maybe everyone does...
...what you did.
But this is SFTC.
And we go by rules.
I can't have someone in the academy
who has a police case on him.
Finish your court case.
And volunteer next year once again.
Sir, please.
Reconsider it.
Rules are rules, Capt. Avinash.
- Sir...
- All the best.
Dismissed.
One more thing, Capt. Avinash.
During the punishment
of lack of food...
...food items from CSD canteen
were taken to the dorm.
Am I right?
- Yes.
- We are watching, always.
While leaving, explain this
to your course mates.
[Ranjit] 'Who must have
named him Tank?'
- I heard his name is Tankesh.
- Tankesh?
I prefer Tankinder.
But he is good.
He remains silent
when everybody laughs.
And when everyone cries,
he laughs.
Dude, I am feeling bad for Avinash.
He was a good lad.
He had to leave for no reason.
He always gets into trouble.
I think that Military Barbie
is behind this.
Military Barbie.
We successfully maintained
our first week's record.
Four have signed exit forms.
- But she is still here.
- Yes, sir.
We have underestimated her.
She trained herself every night.
And completed
the obstacle course today.
- Sir, I wanted to ask something.
- Yes.
Do we have to be
so strict with her?
Mr. Bhatti, how long have you
been posted in SFTC?
Eight years, sir.
But you never asked me
this question in 8 years.
Regarding another officer.
One more thing.
Capt. Shikha Sharma
had requested...
...not to be given
any special treatment.
But this has never happened, sir.
That is because
a lady officer never applied...
...to become
a special forces commando.
F**k.
What kind of a joke is this?
Colonel Sathe's orders.
I just have to find myself
a bed now.
Welcome, Shikha.
By the way, we have a rule here.
You'll have to compete
with the heavy drinker here...
...in order to get a bed.
Who is that?
I am.
Okay.
Come on...
Well done.
Wonderful.
Come on, Shikha.
Come on, Rohan.
[Applauding and cheering]
You must not stop.
Wow!
Look at his style. Wow.
Wonderful!
Come on...
- Finish this.
- Rohan, come on!
Dude!
Come on, Shikha.
Come on.
How much will you drink
to prove a point?
Let it be, Capt. Sharma.
Anyway, only men and horses
can digest rum.
Where are the horses that drink rum?
- Wonderful!
- Point.
He was the only heavy drinker here
but now she has arrived.
Hey!
And I am saying this to you
with due respect, ma'am.
Okay.
Come on, Surje.
- Very good!
- Come on...
[Cheering]
Go, Rohan.
I think Capt. Sharma
is about to give up.
The game has just begun.
Capt. Sharma, come on.
You can do this.
[Man] Come on.
Come on, Shikha.
Come on...
[Applauding and cheering]
- Come on...
- Well done...
Come on...
Shikha!
[Bilal] Hey. Here.
Have some water.
As the saying goes,
a single blow of a blacksmith...
Is equivalent to a hundred blows
of a goldsmith...
- I am impressed, Rohan.
- Let's go...
Hey...
To the floor, Barbie.
Aye aye, Captain!
Cheers, boys.
Capt. Sharma has lost the battle.
[Cheering]
I think you had too much
last night.
As all of you know...
...the Krav Maga of the Israelis...
...is one of the best
martial art forms in the world.
In the special forces...
...hand to hand combat...
...is more important than weapons.
Capt. Rohan Rathore.
Brigade of the Guards,
IMA, NDA.
- Do you remember their rule?
- Yes, sir.
Then, take 20 rounds.
Buddy piggyback.
Everything will be all right.
As per the rules
of special forces...
...the commandos holding alternate
positions on the leader board...
...are buddies.
So according to that...
Capt. Manit!
- You are Capt. Rohan's buddy.
- Yes, sir.
Come on.
Fulfil your responsibility.
Rathore, don't we look like
Vikram and Betal?
F**k your PJs man, Manit.
My head is aching.
"You broke your silence,
so I'll fly away now."
Are you done
or do you have more to say?
There is more.
Eight more rounds to go.
Who asked you to show off?
You drank
one and a half bottle of liquor.
I wanted to show her, her place.
Yeah. But she showed you,
your place instead.
What the f**k are you
talking about?
- Don't you see what everyone can?
- What?
She played you, partner.
She laid a trap
and you fell into it.
Capt. Rathore,
are you tired already?
You shouldn't stop.
Come on, continue.
[Woman] "As per our sources,
a lady officer has been sent..."
"...for a commando course
in the special forces."
"And her performance..."
"...has left everyone speechless."
"After the Test Case,
the defence minister is sure..."
[Phone ringing and vibration]
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning, Colonel.
You must have heard
the breaking news.
Apparently you and I
are speechless...
...after seeing
Shikha Sharma's performance.
[Bedi] 'Anyway, how is she doing?'
In physical strength, the male
officers are better than her.
But in shooting,
Capt. Sharma is quite strong.
[Sathe] 'She thinks calmly.'
After failing in the obstacle task,
she has come back really strong.
You are praising her,
Colonel Sathe.
General Bedi,
you know me very well.
I won't praise anyone
without any reason.
And I won't criticise her...
...just because she
is a lady officer.
[Sathe] 'I am just
telling you the facts.'
The areas in which
most women would give up...
...she is doing much better
than what I expected.
[Sathe] 'However, sir.'
From next week, strategy and
tactics training is going to start.
Under Freddie, right?
Yes, sir.
Under Colonel Freddie Punawala.
[Sathe] 'You know that not
everyone can do this.'
Also Camp Dozakh is pending.
She might clear
the tactics course...
...but it won't be possible
for her...
...to clear Dozakh.
Are you sure?
The failure rate of male officers
is 40 percent, sir.
Remember, Colonel.
This is not just
about Shikha Sharma.
This is about the future
of the army.
I just want our benchmark
to be the same.
[Bedi] 'You know what I am saying.'
Push her the hardest.
Yes, sir.
"I am used to winning."
"This is the end of enemies."
"India is in my heart."
"The motive of my life
is to protect my country."
"India is in my heart."
"I am not weak
nor less than anyone."
"I don't mind sacrificing my life."
"I am proud to say
that tricolour is my life."
"India is in my heart."
Come on, Commandos.
Come on.
Well done, Officers!
Capt. Manit.
Because of your good performance...
...you are moving up
on the leader board.
Capt. Rohan.
Being disciplined is also important
apart from good performance...
...for the leader board positions.
Capt. Sharma,
keep up the good work.
That's all for today.
Good news comes without warning
in the special forces.
You can go anywhere you want
for six hours this evening.
You can do what you want.
But tomorrow morning at 5...
...be ready for the fall in.
Okay.
Dismissed.
Guys, hurry up.
[Door knocking]
How will you manage today,
Capt. Shikha?
The bus will leave in 15 minutes.
Hurry up.
[Man2] 'Hurry up.
There is poor water pressure.'
What will you do?
What is your plan?
Surje.
You are taking a bath today.
- I took a bath on Thursday.
- Is it?
- Mr. Bilal.
- Yes.
How long are you going
to bathe?
[Door knocking]
F**k it.
No...
What happened, Manit?
Hurry up.
The bus will leave in 14 minutes.
Okay.
This is good.
What happened, Surje?
What are you looking at?
- Tell me.
- No...
What?
It's the same.
Like your mother and your sister.
Your daughter would be the same.
I'm using a filmy dialogue
to explain to you.
It's just anatomy.
Get used to it.
I'll get used to it.
Sorry, I didn't want to offend you.
It's okay.
Fair enough.
Actually, everyone
has their own fantasy.
- That's why I...
- Stop it now.
Now, I might really get offended.
[Music playing]
- So, where are you from?
- From Bangalore.
- Are you army officers?
- Yeah.
Okay.
What is the matter?
Time for some cocktail?
- Nice shot.
- It was easy.
Did you talk to Avinash?
He must be fine.
I can't even connect to Tinder.
Bhatti has got it blocked, dude.
Holy f**k!
Tell me one thing.
Just very honestly...
She is always with him.
Don't worry, dude.
I too have made arrangements.
Hey.
How are you doing?
- You look gorgeous.
Thank you.
- Hi. Manit. Pleasure.
- Hi. Suzy.
- Capt. Surjewala.
- Yes.
- The most sincere captain here.
- Really?
- Yes. - Linda
- Hi.
- Suzy.
- Hey. - Suzy.
They are from Australia.
I love Shane Warne.
Bowler...
We don't follow cricket.
But you drink, right?
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
Australians love beer.
- Ranjit.
- Suzy.
Excuse me.
In Bollywood,
there's a villain named Ranjit.
And Capt. Surjewala's father
is a very big fan of Ranjit.
That is why he named
his son after him.
Well, I must say.
Manit is quite charming.
- Why? - Where did he find
such cute girls in Kolipad?
I see!
Which one do you like?
The one wearing the floral dress
or the one wearing the tan dress?
Both are hot.
But...
What's wrong with you?
I am in the army
and I fire weapons.
Does it mean I am into girls?
- What a sad stereotype...
- No...
No... Dude.
That is not what I meant.
It's just that I never saw a girl
complimenting another girl.
Here you go.
One more stereotype.
I also gave a compliment
to the man.
Yeah. And I don't think
she is into girls.
There you go.
See.
Vishnu gets me.
[Notification sound]
That's so sad.
And here I was thinking...
...that I am number one
on your personal leadership board.
- Thanks, bro.
- Hard luck, bro.
There is a lot of competition,
Bilal.
Okay.
I'll catch you guys later.
[Door knocking]
[Door opening]
Yes.
Sorry.
I'm looking for my boyfriend.
Are you sure you have
the right room number?
Let me check if he is in.
I don't have time.
You will do.
No.
My shoulder.
I've hurt it.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Perfect.
So good to see you.
By the way, I must say.
You look hot.
Thank you.
And that's a beautiful dress.
My boyfriend gifted me this.
He seems to have good taste.
- Shivi.
- What?
What is this?
No music, no candles.
How unromantic!
A star is sitting next to me.
And you are talking about candles.
- Star?
- My star.
Ouch...
Really that bad?
No. It's okay.
What happened?
- It's nothing, Shivi...
- Tell me...
Tell me.
It's just a little tough, dude.
Actually it's very tough.
So many drills. Physically,
it's very challenging, dude.
And on top of that, those two...
Bhatti and Sathe.
Harbingers of doom..
Listen.
I feel really bad...
...for them.
- Shivi.
- What are you saying?
- Very bad. - Let me cure
your shoulder pain right away.
Here you go.
It'll be fine now.
Listen.
I know you.
Do you remember the incident that
happened in the DTC bus in Delhi...
...when you had thrashed
the bus conductor?
I should have broken his teeth.
Did you see his eyes?
You would have killed him
had I not stopped you.
Here you go. Do you know what
all the officers...
...must be telling their wives
and girlfriends?
- What?
- They must be saying...
..."Baby, I got my b**t kicked
today by a lady officer."
You are the strongest girl
in the world.
And you are going to survive this.
I'm telling you.
- Shivi, you know, I really...
- I do. Yeah.
I really missed you, Shivi.
- I have a question...
- What?
What?
You won't ignore me as you are
with so many guys, right?
I'll try.
But I can't promise.
I'll take it.
[Footsteps]
Camp Chitnis, Greenhorn, Rovers...
You were a leader
wherever you went.
You were a topper in NDA.
Always been the best, bro.
Then what has happened now?
Why are you so angry?
Let it be, Bil.
Don't act like you care.
How long have you known me?
Around 13 years.
These days, it doesn't feel so.
What are you saying?
Dude, listen...
You do not understand.
She is good at heart.
She just wants to prove a point.
That's all.
- Capt. Sharma. Where were you?
- Yes.
I just went to grab a coffee.
What?
- She is blushing.
- What, dude?
- How is the food here?
- You tell us. How was it?
It would not be better
than the coffee.
I went to grab a coffee.
Come on, guys... What is this?
You seem so happy.
What happened, Bil?
Why are you quiet?
Listen. If you think there can
be something between you two...
...forget it.
She is playing you.
She is playing everyone.
[Shikha] 'Stop it.
We need to go. It's time.'
[Shikha] 'We have
to go back. Dude.'
Just like Bunty and Babli,
Neal and Nikki...
Surje and Suzy.
She was close to me
yet I couldn't do anything.
Foxy girl..
[Snores]
[Gun shots]
Good morning.
Sleep is precious, officers.
But our lives are
more precious than that.
Fall in for Dozakh in 10 minutes.
Hurry up.
What the f**k?
Dozakh!
Already?
Rohan, you had told me...
...that we'll go through
Dozakh in the eighth week.
It's a surprise, buddy.
This is the special forces.
There is a task in every
special forces' training...
...which not only checks...
...the limit of your physical
and mental strength...
...but also checks your passion,
your survival instinct...
...and your willpower
to the ultimate limit.
Israelis call it LDFX.
Americans call it Robin Sage.
And we call it...
...Camp Dozakh.
You won't forget the next 36 hours
for the rest of your life.
Because Dozakh means netherworld.
Hell.
I just have one suggestion
for all of you.
If you are going through hell...
...just keep going.
I think we are done for.
The first stage of Dozakh.
Night march for 30 kilometres...
...carrying a load of 30 kilograms
and your weapons.
Keep walking.
Come on, Commandos.
Do not stop. Keep going.
Keep walking.
Everyone, sit down.
Sit...
Sit properly.
Is there any doubt?
Lift your weapons.
Advance! Come on...
One, two...
Move...
Keep going..
No other moves.
What are you looking at?
Come on. Move ahead.
So, are you not able to do it?
Come on.
Sign this form and go back.
Sign this and go back
to your luxury posting in Delhi.
[Devichand] 'Buck up. Good...'
Try harder.
[Devichand] 'Try harder.'
Don't you want to join the army?
[Devichand] 'Don't you want
to become a commando?'
My back is hurting, Dad.
If you bear this pain now,
later you won't face any trouble.
- Lift this up.
- No, Dad. - Lift.
Even I want to become
a commando, Dad.
Dear, girls cannot
become commandos in the army.
But girls do join the army,
right?
He doesn't even
want to join the army.
- Why don't you let me do it?
- You..
- Let her do it.
- Stay quiet.
What are you laughing at?
She lifted it up.
And you are not able to lift it.
Is this how you will join the army?
Come on. Lift it up.
Try harder.
And you!
You have become too talkative.
Control your tongue.
Very good.
You have to join the army.
[Naved] 'Come on.
Sign this form and go back.'
[Siren]
[Bhatti] 'Be it right or wrong...'
[Bhatti] '...this is the future
of war, Captains.'
Chemical warfare.
[Footsteps]
[Door opening]
[Bhatti] You will find
chlorobenzylidene malononitrile...
[Bhatti] ...inside the building.
[Bhatti] In short,
it is called CS gas.
[Bhatti] Even the American army
use this in their training.
[Bhatti] You will perform
this task with your buddy.
[Bhatti] Remember one thing.
[Bhatti] If you don't complete
this task in 2 minutes...
[Bhatti] ...your buddy
might lose his life.
[Bhatti] You will get to know
the value of every breath...
[Bhatti] ...while doing this task.
[Coughing]
[Bhatti] Both the buddies
will have to breath carefully.
[Bhatti] If you
inhale more oxygen...
[Bhatti] ...your buddy might not
get enough oxygen to breathe.
You can at least share the oxygen.
[Bhatti] If the oxygen gets over
before the task ends...
[Bhatti] ...you'll fail the test.
Get up.
- Get up.
- God!
Rohan.
Buddy.
Are you all right?
Rohan, are you all right?
What is happening?
Rohan, what is happening?
Rohan, don't fall.
Are you all right?
We need help.
Guys!
Guy...
Rohan.
Are you all right, Rohan?
What happened, Rohan?
Rohan...
No...
Rohan!
Rohan...
Rohan.
Get up.
Get up, Rohan...
Rohan...
[Coughing]
F**k!
Sorry, man. Manit.
S***e, had something happened
to you or me today...
...because
of your claustrophobia...
...even your dad wouldn't
have been able to do anything.
F**k, dude.
B******d.
[Coughing]
Are you all right, buddy?
Thanks, Bilal.
I have my own buddy.
We first need to win the battle
within, Capt. Rohan.
Got it?
In this way you will put
yourself, your buddy...
...and the entire unit in danger.
Give up your dream
of becoming a commando.
Listen, dear. I know
this was your father's dream.
This isn't dad's dream.
This is my dream.
I wanted Udit to fulfil
this dream of mine.
But I know what
brother went through.
Dad, you have no idea.
Brother never wanted
to join the army.
You always forced him.
Now that I want to join the army...
...you are trying to stop me.
We all saw the impact
of your stubbornness on brother.
- Now, don't try the same
thing on me. - Shikha!
What type of girl are you?
Don't you want to get married?
And we're ready to let you
marry the guy you like.
- And you!
- Yes.
- Will you marry her?
Dad, I don't want
to get married now.
I want to finish my graduation
and then join the army, Dad.
You want to roam around
with your boyfriend...
...and join the army.
Wow!
You are my daughter. Don't try
to become equivalent to my son.
- Hasn’t Shikha Sharma quit yet?
- No, sir.
Good.
Oh, my God!
Hey.
It's a love bite, right?
What happened?
I am just asking.
You have a boyfriend, right?
Bilal, I don't want
to talk about this.
You met him last night,
didn't you?
Dude, I just said, I don't
want to talk about it.
All right.
We both are friends.
But it doesn't mean
that we share
everything about ourselves.
Why are you getting defensive?
There's no need for that.
In friendship...
...people usually share everything
with each other. Don't they?
I don't.
I need my space.
Bilal.
From now on, if you think
you shouldn't share
everything with me...
...then please don't.
Don't expect me to give you
my biodata, man.
Seems everyone is right.
- You are playing me.
- What?
What do you mean
by I'm playing you?
Because I didn't tell you
that I have a boyfriend?
He is my boyfriend.
That's my personal life.
How does it matter to you?
Did I come to you and ask you
to be my friend, my buddy...
...and to take care of me?
No.
If you are feeling bad
then please leave me alone.
Listen.
A word of advice, Shikha.
No one!
Absolutely no one
wins a battle on their own.
Got it?
One lakh, one thousand, two hundred
and eighty Indian army soldiers...
...are deployed in 16 peacekeeping
missions, worldwide.
In all these overseas operation...
...the special forces
play a special role.
The missions in which even
the toughest soldiers give up...
...we go to those missions
and operate.
That's why we put you all
such rigorous training.
[Whistle]
The one who survive this...
...can go through anything.
Come on, Capt. Rathore.
Get inside.
Are you scared, Capt. Manit?
Don't be scared.
[Bhatti] 'When the pain
becomes unbearable...'
[Bhatti] '...you stop feeling it.'
[Bhatti] 'Go ahead
and experience the pain.'
[Bhatti] 'Understand its value.'
[Bhatti] 'Your pain will
become your strength.'
[Bhatti] 'Your power to endure
will increase so much...'
[Bhatti] '...that you won't let
any kind of fear break you.'
Commando!
"I am used to winning."
"This is the end of enemies."
"- India is in my heart.
- India is in my heart."
"The motive of my life
is to protect my country."
"India is in my heart."
"I am not weak
nor less than anyone."
"I don't mind sacrificing my life."
"I am proud to say
that the tricolour is my life."
- "India is in my heart."
- Get the first aid. Hurry up.
"India is in my heart."
Commando!
As I always say...
...the weak have no place here.
The one who gets scared...
...will either go home...
...or lose his life.
We aren’t even halfway through
Dozakh yet, Captains.
Before we move ahead,
a 20 minute break.
- Let's take a nap.
- Yes, sir.
Don't take my words so seriously.
When I say break,
I mean your bones will break.
- Shall we move ahead!
- Yes, sir...
An uphill march for one hour...
...is waiting for you.
You have to bring the flag...
...from the checkpoint delta.
- Didn't you hear me?
- Yes, sir...
Come on.
What happened, Bilal?
Nothing.
Just a small cut.
Apply mud on it.
It will get healed.
- Bilal, you okay?
- I'm fine.
Is everything okay, Shikha?
[Siren]
Sir.
The results are here.
We have divided the probies
into two squads for the next task.
Capt. Rohan will lead Squad Alpha.
And Capt. Tank
will lead Squad Bravo.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Kripal.
- Sir.
No matter how well
one performs individually...
...in group or in the buddy
exercises...
...the biggest skill
for a commando...
...is leadership.
- You know what I mean.
- Sir.
[Moving car]
[Siren]
- Are you having fun?
- Yes, sir...
You'll enjoy it more now.
You are being divided
into two squads...
...for the second and the most
dangerous part of Dozakh.
Rohan, Manit, Bilal, Sharma,
Vishnu, Tej Bahadur.
You all are Squad Alpha.
Rest everyone is Squad Bravo.
Squad Bravo.
Your leader will be Capt. Tank.
And the one to lead
Squad Alpha is...
I'm sure it's Rathore.
Capt. Sharma.
Capt. Shikha Sharma.
You are not even able
to stand straight.
How are you going
to lead the squad?
I'll do it, sir.
Are you ready for the most
difficult challenge of Dozakh?
Yes, sir.
I can't hear you, Capt. Sharma.
Yes, sir!
Good.
Keep this in mind.
Tell her that she
is leaving against our will.
The doors of this house
are forever shut for her.
We loved her so much.
Where did we lack?
We got her educated.
And she isn't even
ready to listen to us.
I lost my son because of
this obsession with the army.
And now she is...
Don't feel bad
for what your dad said.
He is angry right now.
He'll be fine after a while.
You can go.
You must go.
I know one thing about you, Shikha.
You can achieve whatever you want.
And if someone stops you
from doing something...
...you will definitely do it.
[Mother] 'Just be careful.'
Actually, girls are changing
but not guys.
Guys don't like girls
who leave them behind.
Always keep this in mind.
March.
Come on... Fall in!
Hurry up.
Captains.
Till now, Mr. Naved and I...
...were here to hold your hand
just like a shadow.
Consider this a real mission...
...and not a task.
In these exercises,
live ammunition will be used.
Remember...
...ignorance can lead to disaster.
In the first stage,
you have to reach here.
Enemy's territory.
Point A for Squad Alpha.
Point X for Squad Bravo.
After reaching there,
if you succeed...
...you might find ration
to survive in the mission.
We'll be following you anyway.
You have only 10 minutes
to study the map.
Quick.
Okay, Vishnu. You and I will
be in charge of navigation.
Manit, you will be my 2IC.
Bilal, medical.
Tej, communication.
Capt. Rohan, weapons.
Any doubt, Capt. Rohan?
No, sir.
Did you all study the map?
- Yes, sir...
- Good.
Then give it back.
If you can’t do without a map..
...you are not worthy
to be in the special forces.
Yes, sir...
All the best, buddy. You have
to do the back seat driving.
You know how good women
are with directions, right?
Capt. Sharma.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Which way, Vishnu?
Left or right?
Let's go right.
You are wrong, Shikha.
We just crossed that hillock.
This is the right way.
Try to recall the map.
That hillock was in the north.
We need to go that way
and not this way.
I know what I am doing.
And I heard both of you talking.
Just because I'm a girl,
my navigation is wrong.
- When did I say that?
- You didn't but you thought so.
- Seriously, Shiks.
- Capt. Soren. It's Capt. Sharma.
Really?
So the authority card, huh?
Okay.
Cool.
Roger, ma'am.
We are going this way
and that's final.
Sir.
I marked this tree an hour ago.
We have come back
to the same point.
Great.
You know what?
Surje would've been really happy
if he were in our team.
We are prancing around a tree
like in a Hindi movie's song.
S**t!
Which way, Capt. Sharma?
I'm really sorry.
Let's go back to that hillock.
- We'll start navigating again...
- Negative.
Neither do we have time
nor do we need to go back.
Time and effort,
both will go waste.
Anyway, it's going to be dawn soon.
It'll be easier to navigate.
We should wait.
Makes sense.
I still think we should go back.
Okay, fine.
Halt till daybreak.
Capt. Rohan, weapons check.
- Vishnu.
- All in.
- Capt. Sharma.
- Bilal.
- All in.
Sir.
One of my magazines is missing.
Manit.
- Manit.
- All in.
Tej.
All in, sir.
All in.
You can't make
everything official, Tej.
- It was there till we crossed
the last point, right? - Yes.
So, it has gone missing
somewhere in-between.
We are taking a halt.
Just go and search for it.
[Footsteps]
Vishnu and Manit, head west.
Rohan and Tej.
You will approach
the house from the east.
- Bilal will give cover. Copy?
- Copy.
Go.
[Footsteps]
[Whistle]
Alpha2 to Alpha1.
In position.
Twenty yards away.
The wall is broken.
Roof is missing.
There is complete silence.
No sign of activity. Over.
Alpha3, over.
Alpha3 in position.
There is a wall in front of me.
I can't see the house. Over.
Copy Alpha3, hold position.
Bilal, hold position.
Alpha2, you will go ahead.
We'll give you cover. Over.
Okay.
Moving in 3, 2, 1. Out.
[Footsteps]
Alpha1, all clear.
Over.
Copy. Squad Alpha.
Moving inside. Over.
Where is the food?
I swear, Vishnu.
Today I don't mind having bland,
boiled chicken served in the mess.
Yes, dude.
It's been 34 hours
since we had food.
Where is the food?
There it is.
Oh, s**t!
Don't move. It'll blast.
Take cover.
[Beeping sound]
Careful.
What the f**k!
[Beeping sound]
Alpha1, there is a bomb
here, not food.
It got activated as soon
as Vishnu stepped on it.
It's an IED.
I repeat, it's an IED.
It's a 155 mm shell.
It contains 6 kgs TNT...
...with blasting power
of 300 pounds.
[Vishnu] 'If I move even slightly,
everything around me...'
...in a 100 metre radius will
be destroyed.
Good to know because we are
just 30 metres away from you.
Manit, is there a timer?
I just said, it's a f*****g IED.
We just have 2 minutes 45 seconds.
Please order.
- Capt. Vishnu, hold position.
- Copy.
Capt. Manit, you have worked
with IED explosives before.
[Shikha] 'Correct?
Can you work this?'
I can do it.
But...
I would have to check
the blasting cap.
I'll get to know
once I find the source.
- Spring or pressure mechanism?
- Spring. But lots of wires.
Bhatti's favourite brand must
be United Colors of Benetton.
[Manit] 'B******d,
it's a rainbow of wires.'
Manit, hurry up.
F**k.
I am doing it, dude.
It's too hot. Can't f**k
around with it too much.
Manit, eliminate the
wires one by one...
...based on what they
are connected to.
This is not the video in, video
out lead of TV, Capt. Sharma.
You know you take stating
the obvious to another level.
Manit, please focus on your job.
Okay, it's not the green wire.
Black is out too.
75 seconds more, Manit.
I can see the damn numbers, dude!
Okay.
There are two wires.
Red and blue.
One of them is connected
to the blasting cap.
- If I cut the wrong one,
it'll blast. - F**k.
Okay, Manit.
Look carefully.
Where are the wires connected from?
Both are going into
the same box, dude.
- F**k.
- What?
- We are f****d.
- What...
Both wires have been stripped down.
Both have been tied...
...and connected
to an electric device...
...which is connected to the timer.
I think it's the red wire.
I'm going with the red.
- Wait.
- What, dude? We are losing time.
It's a trap.
Go with the blue.
Are you f*****g kidding me?
Bomb is in front of me.
The device is in my hand.
I feel I should cut the red wire.
I'm going with the red.
Manit, I have an instinct.
It's reverse psychology.
Go with the blue.
Instinct?
What about logic?
We lost many hours because
of your instinct, Capt. Sharma.
It's not the time for guess work.
I'm going with the red.
- Manit, blue. - Red.
- Blue.
- Red.
- Blue. It's an order.
- Manit, go with the red.
- Rohan, you stay out of this.
- Blue...
- Red...
Red!
[Beeping sound]
It stopped.
Vishnu, it stopped.
Vishnu, we are safe.
Hurray!
[Cheers]
[Manit] 'Die another day, b*tch!'
Well done, bro.
Close one.
- Seriously. Logic.
- Not instinct, but logic.
Well done, Manit.
But what you did
amounts to breach of orders.
Are you being serious?
Yeah. Manit didn't follow
the orders of his team leader.
Thank God he didn't
follow your orders.
Look what happened when
Vishnu followed your orders.
There is a reason there is a chain
of command in the army, okay?
And you out of all people
should know that.
Excuse me.
You need to be alive in order to
follow the orders, Capt. Sharma.
Are you upset with Manit
or with yourself...
...for two terrible judgements
in a row now?
- Stop getting personal, Bilal.
- I'm not getting personal.
Bilal, Shikha.
Time out, guys.
Shikha, come on.
We are a team.
We maybe a team.
But the last I checked
the army was not a democracy.
Unbelievable.
Just because you were
made the leader of this task
do you think you are God?
The entire jungle would
have burned to ashes...
...due to the amount of TNT
present in that bomb.
Okay. Guys, obviously
I'm glad, we are alive.
No, it's not that obvious.
Rules are rules.
That's the first thing
we are taught...
- ...when we come into the academy.
- What the f**k, dude!
S***a, I saved everyone's life.
This is the thanks I am getting.
Lower your voice!
I'm still your team leader.
Yeah. But maybe not on merit.
Excuse me.
I guess we all agree that our team
leader is wrong and we are right.
- And we know to set things right.
- Oh, really?
How, Capt. Rathore?
Do you really want
to know, Capt. Sharma?
[Moving car]
[Door close]
- Jai Hind, sir...
- Jai Hind.
At ease.
Any problem, Capt. Sharma?
- No, sir. - Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
In that case,
well done, Squad Alpha.
You defused the bomb successfully.
Had it got detonated,
you wouldn't have lost your life
but could have been badly injured.
Anyway, Squad Bravo
completed the task an hour ago.
Let's move ahead.
The last and the most
dangerous task.
Ten kms ahead,
in the enemy's village...
...point B.
You'll have to retrieve a very
important packet from there.
And because you didn't
get anything to eat...
...you can eat these pills.
It will re-energise you.
Chew it.
These are not vitamin pills.
These are sleeping pills.
These pills will prepare
you for the day...
...when you would complete
your operation without sleeping...
...not for hours but for days.
Despite being deprived of sleep...
...you'll have to be alert
and take the right decision.
The one who sleeps today...
...might go to sleep forever,
during a real operation.
[Birds chirping]
[Shikha] 'If he can do it, so can I.'
[Shikha] 'If they could do it,
even we'll be able to.'
[Shikha] 'If he can do it, so can I.'
[Shikha] 'If they could..'
I can't do this anymore.
We can do it.
She is so stubborn.
I say, stop this game, dude.
We can do it.
I can do it.
[Gun shots]
Everybody, take cover.
Retaliate.
It's an ambush!
Everybody, take cover!
Tej, Vishnu.
Right side.
- Manit, Rohan. Left side.
- Copied.
- Bilal, with me.
- F**k!
Give me cover, Vishnu.
Vishnu, what the f**k, man!
Give cover!
Tej. Vishnu.
Manit, this way.
Capt. Vishnu...
Capt. Vishnu, are you all right?
Capt. Vishnu!
Tiger calling for Alpha..
Tiger calling for Alpha
Alpha1 come in.
- You're okay?
- There are moving targets.
Take the defensive position.
Tiger calling for Alpha...
[Beep]
S**t...
[Gun shots]
There is some problem.
There is no communication
since 15 minutes.
I'm not able to understand.
[Screams]
What happened, dude?
Where are they?
Stop it!
[Gasping]
Pascal, come in for tiger.
[Screams]
First aid party!
Hurry up.
[Aparna] Come on, guys.
Hurry...
[Aparna] Bilal, stretcher one.
Shikha, stretcher two.
[Aparna] Easy...
Watch her neck.
[Aparna] That's it...
Easy.
[Aparna] Lift Bilal's stretcher properly.
[Aparna] Be careful.
Hold her head.
Come on... Pick it up...
Let's go... Move.
[Heartbeat]
Breath.
Capt. Bilal got injured
and Capt. Shikha fell unconscious.
That's why I had
to take over the command.
Is it?
But what happened
as such over there
that Capt. Sharma
ended up in this state?
How did all this happen?
Bil, I'm so sorry, man.
No, dude.
Don't apologise to me.
There is someone else
whom we should apologise to.
If you say, shall I talk to dad
about your posting in Lucknow?
- Your family is there.
- No.
I'm fine.
I'll be just fine.
Any idea how is Shikha doing?
She'll be fine.
Even you'll be fine.
Everything will be all right, sir.
Everything appears to be fine, Tej.
But a few wounds never heal.
There are scars that stay
with us for our whole lives.
Anyway, all of us have to
write the debriefing reports.
I've written mine.
Take a look.
[Crunching leaves]
Shikha!
Here.
Drink some water.
Drink this water, Shikha.
Shikha, you need some water.
Drink it.
Come on.
Your injuries don't seem like
the normal combat injuries.
These nightmares, the anxiety,
high blood pressure...
...not talking to anyone,
increased heartbeat...
Medically this is borderline PTSD.
Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder.
[Phone vibrating]
Shivalik is calling
again and again.
Won't you talk to him?
Look, Shikha.
As the RMO, I have to submit
my report to Colonel Sathe.
And after reading my reports...
...Col. Sathe might initiate
a court of enquiry.
I am asking you once again.
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
What happened over there?
[Bhatti] 'During Dozakh...'
...because of your good
or bad performance...
...your ranking on the
leader board might change.
You all must be aware...
...that Capt. Bilal won't
move ahead in this course.
For now, I want you...
...to write everything
in detail, in your debriefs.
Especially, Squad Alpha.
After all what happened
over there as such...
...that Capt. Siddiqui and
Capt. Shikha Sharma got injured?
Sir.
But our two buddies
are in the hospital.
Capt. Bilal has been informed.
He will submit the
report before leaving.
Capt. Shikha will submit
her report once she recovers.
Anything else?
So, come on.
Write down.
Sir, I wrote what I could recall.
Capt. Siddiqui,
I hope you recover soon...
...and go back to your unit.
And volunteer again
for the SFTC next year.
Mr. Naved will help
you fill your exit form.
Do inform me,
if you need something.
[Phone ringing]
Capt. Rao.
Yes, sir.
I have read the debriefs.
I'll be submitting my reports
in the next couple of days.
Yes, sir.
Right.
[Footsteps]
Medical and debriefing reports
are submitted together.
There is nothing written
in the debriefs...
...which can justify your injuries.
Do you know that
Capt. Bilal Siddiqui...
...had to leave the course
because of his injuries?
Before leaving, not once
did he come and look you up.
- Bilal is your friend, right?
- There are no friends.
Everyone is a competition.
And, only winning and losing
matter in a competition, Aparna...
...not friendship.
[Typing]
I refuse to believe this.
Sexual assault on a
fellow officer in SFTC.
It is not possible.
In fact, till date
no such incident has taken place
in any of our training academies.
Till date, men and women officers
were never trained together...
...at the same place, Bedi.
What if it's a hoax?
The IP address of this mail
has been traced to Kolipad.
- I've got it checked.
- So what?
If we don't handle this...
...the army will get
defamed for sure.
For now, only we have
received this mail.
What if it is sent
to a news channel?
Someday there is going to be
a witch-hunt at prime time.
Heads will roll.
[Phone ringing]
Damn it.
I said no phone calls.
Okay.
Put him on.
Yes, Mr. Mathur.
She is doing fine.
It's in three weeks.
All right.
It shall be arranged.
The defence minister
herself wants to attend
the passing out parade of the SFTC.
POP is in three weeks’ time.
Bloody hell.
Looks like, we are sitting
on a ticking time bomb.
- Good morning, sir.
- Relax.
How are you feeling now?
Very well, sir. Thank you.
Thank you for asking, sir.
I still didn't receive
the RMO's report.
But looking at you...
...it seems you will
take time to recover.
Capt. Sharma, you know...
...that Capt. Siddiqui had
to leave after Dozakh.
You also know
Capt. Surje's condition.
I am trying to say that so
far you've done everything...
...with passion, preparation
and commitment.
But after recovering...
...it won't be easy to
catch up with everyone.
Actually, it will
be really difficult.
And I don't want the future
of a good officer to be damaged.
If you want to leave now...
...I will not consider
you as a failure.
I mean it.
In fact, if you would like
to volunteer next year...
...I myself will recommend you.
But...
...the final decision
is going to be yours.
[Bedi] 'Has any official
complaint been lodged yet?'
Not yet.
But maybe the complaint
has been suppressed.
Stop spinning
conspiracy theories, Raman.
Sathe can't do that.
Bedi.
Sathe's port from
colonel to brigadier...
...is due this year.
One such incident
can finish his career.
[Phone ringing]
Good morning, sir.
Sathe, I called about Dozakh.
How did it go?
The usual, sir.
A few injuries...
[Sathe] '...a few unexpected
incidents.'
And Shikha?
Well, the Dozakh
reports are confidential.
But if you are asking me
officially then probably I can...
No...
It's all right.
Sathe, you know
the stakes are really high.
So, just keep me updated.
Yes, sir.
Either Sathe is
concealing the truth...
...or he genuinely
doesn't know anything.
We don't have time
to do guesswork...
...sitting in Delhi.
You mean another official enquiry.
Exactly.
But we have only 3 weeks.
We need someone
who can go there...
...and check all the facts in
an unbiased and objective way.
Someone whom we can trust.
Since you have already
given all this a thought...
...tell me, who is going
to lead this investigation?
Well, someone whom
I implicitly trust.
There is only one officer
in my mind.
Someone who can call
a spade, a spade.
- Imtiyaz Hussain.
- Literally?
Your poker champ?
In such a short time,
no one else can do this work.
I agree that his
ways are different.
But you know what?
Nine times out of ten, they work.
Okay. Let's hope
for all our sake...
...that this isn't that
proverbial tenth time.
You blink, you lose.
I know that.
[Ticking sound]
Yes!
Dear, always remember.
In life as well as in poker...
...if you want to win, focus
is always on their eyes.
Dad, you win against everyone...
then how do you lose
against me and mom?
Dear, you are a champ.
And your mom is a
bigger champ than you.
No one could defeat
your mom till date.
-[Mallika] Immi.
- Yeah. Coming.
You know I always win
and dad always loses.
Taste this and tell me...
How is it?
Mutton is not cooked properly.
Come on, Immi.
Even the Hyderabadi Nawabs'
don't throw such tantrums.
Come on.
I belong to their family.
Really?
Shut up, liar.
- I crossed check
with your aunt also. - Is it?
She told me that you are not even
remotely connected to the Nawabs.
- Okay. I'll get a proof.
- Okay.
- Eid Mubarak.
- Dad!
- Grandpa!
- Oh...
- Eid Mubarak!
- Eid Mubarak, dear!
Dad, you are so late.
I had some work at the office.
What do you mean by late?
Biryani is being
cooked since 4 to 5 hours.
Sir, you have come
just at the right time. Please.
Okay, Mallika. I need to borrow
your ex-husband for a little while.
- May I?
- Sure.
"Sexual assault on
Capt. Shikha Sharma!"
The First Test Case!
You can't be serious, sir.
I genuinely hope
that this isn't true.
If it is then we need to
bring the culprit to book.
He should be punished
so severely...
...that no one should even think
of doing something like this.
Language is quite clinical.
He has written adm for
administration and not admin.
cdr for commander
and coa for company.
Army abbreviations.
And look at this, sir.
Time stamp.
Only soldiers use
such kind of time stamp.
It means that certainly
this mail has been sent...
...by someone from the SFTC.
Anything else?
I read Capt. Shikha's file...
...when she was chosen
for the Test Case.
She is a shooting champion
but quite emotional as well.
And being emotional
in the special forces...
...is like inviting danger.
You have three weeks.
You need to resolve this case...
...before the course ends.
Roger, sir.
Wilco.
Will comply.
And you.
Got my poker face on, sir.
Will you finish the packing
today itself, Mom?
My train is scheduled
to leave tomorrow evening
You are going to join
the special forces.
Everything should be perfect.
You seem to know the
special forces very well.
Why?
Didn't I spend so many
years with your dad?
Even the toughest
people give up there.
It's a very difficult course, dear.
I see.
It seems as if Sakshi Malik
is going for a wrestling match.
You're more excited than me to
see me in the SF's uniform. Right?
The uniform and the status
are two different things.
You got the uniform.
Now, you need to earn the status.
Keep one thing in mind, dear.
This is an opportunity...
...which your grandma
and your mom didn't get.
Only you got it.
No matter what...
...never give up, dear.
You are the most special girl...
...that is why you are going
to join the special force.
So cute, my Mom.
What do you keep blabbering
all day long in English?
I don't understand a single word.
Listen to me carefully, Mom.
Neither I nor you
or grandma will lose.
Do you know why?
Because my mom
didn't teach me to lose.
If you ever lose...
...I'll break your legs.
Sure.
Ma'am.
Shikha.
Shikha, what are you doing?
Shikha, you need some more time.
I don't have the time.
I need to complete the course.
And what about your injuries?
What'd you do when Colonel Sathe
will read your reports?
The injuries are mine
so the story will also be mine.
Everyone will have
to believe what I say.
- Are you sure about this?
- Affirmative.
Anyway the entire Squad Alpha
said that nothing happened.
So, nothing happened.
"I shall help you soar high."
"I shall fight this battle.
Just resolve to win."
"Just resolve to win."
[Surje] 'Who is this hero?'
He came into the picture...
...like Sunny Deol in Damini.
[Rohan] 'Colonel Imtiyaz Hussain.'
General Raman's son-in-law.
Sorry. Ex-son-in-law.
Few people are very evolved.
Husband and wife are good
friends even after divorce.
They celebrate all
the festivals together.
Then they go back
to their respective homes.
I wish every marriage
was like this.
Wives would've visited on festivals
and then gone back to their houses.
The point is, B*******d...
...which festival has he
come to celebrate here?
A few festivals are celebrated
while a few are observed, Surje.
[Avinash] 'I think he fits
into the second category.'
- Maybe he is our new instructor.
- I don't think so.
[Shikha] 'Good morning, gentlemen.'
What did I miss?
[Surje] 'You here!'
Aren't you happy to see me here?
What are you saying, ma'am?
We are obviously happy to see you.
Good to see you
back on your feet.
Thanks, Surje. I missed
your jokes, dude, actually.
What will we do during the war
if we get scared in Dozakh?
[Surje] You are right.
- Good to see you, Capt. Sharma.
- Tank.
I am sorry that Bilal had to leave.
Even I regret that I couldn't
meet him before he left.
Good morning, officers.
Lieutenant Colonel Imtiyaz Hussain.
Good morning, sir...
Let's cut to the chase.
I'm not your new instructor.
In fact I'm here
for a special purpose.
Squad Bravo, you may leave.
In poker they say...
...if you can't read
your opponent's cards...
...you better play
only with a good hand.
What happened in Camp
Dozakh, Squad Alpha...
...that Capt. Siddiqui
had to go home...
...and Capt. Sharma,
to the hospital?
Somebody?
[Imtiyaz] 'Anybody?'
Nobody.
I've read your debrief reports.
And according to
all your reports...
...nothing happened over there.
But we got an anonymous mail.
According to which...
...not something but many
things happened there.
So, whom do we believe?
An anonymous mail...
...or the officers
of the Indian army?
I think officers
of the Indian army.
So, I want to give you all
one more chance...
...to recount what
exactly happened.
This happens many times...
...a few details becomes
sketchy during actions.
So this time, write after recalling
the things properly. Please.
Last time you couldn't write
your debrief report, Capt. Sharma.
Looking forward to
reading your report. - Sir.
[Surje] 'What have you
guys done as such...'
...that he had to come
here to solve the issue?
Surje, you can't joke always.
Bravo's number might be next.
Do you know the SF has
become very strict nowadays?
For every failure, a new
committee initiates an enquiry.
Everything is monitored
very closely, Surje.
A committee will be set up
if there is a failure.
Check the leader board. For now,
all the Bravos are in the top.
S**t.
What, Surje?
Again?
These are combat injuries.
They'll heal.
Sorry, Capt. Sharma.
Please take care of yourself.
Thank you for all
the support, guys.
"Thanks for the support."
Was she thanking one of us
for sending that e-mail?
But why would any one
of us send that mail?
Yes. But when we have written
everything in the debrief...
...what was in that e-mail?
We know what we wrote
in the debriefing.
We don't know what she has written.
But why would she send a mail if
she was writing it in the report?
I think someone else did this.
- Like who?
A friend or a well-wisher.
Well, Bilal was her
good friend amongst us.
No, sir. Capt. Bilal can't do this.
He wrote what he was told.
Nobody told him.
He wrote what happened.
I hope... I hope we all
wrote what happened.
B******t, Imtiyaz!
I think you didn't read
the debriefs properly.
I read all the reports, sir.
And they are all worded
exactly the same.
Not a single word changed.
It means what Shikha has written...
...is what the entire Squad Alpha
wrote. Am I right?
Right, sir.
- They are the SFTC commandos.
They are trained to remember
things even while asleep.
If everyone has written the
same thing then this is the truth.
Even if I agree that everyone is
lying then what about Shikha?
Why is she lying?
- We need to find out that, sir.
Maybe she is being
pressurised to say this.
Or maybe it's all a cover-up.
Lt. Colonel Hussain,
are you pointing a finger at me?
No, sir. All I'm saying is that
everyone is a suspect for me...
...and every reason is valid,
until the truth comes out.
This...
This is the truth, Imtiyaz.
If something like this
had happened...
...then I would have been
the first person to find it out.
Sir, with all due respect...
...either you co-operate
with me now...
...or wait for an official
investigation.
I see.
Lt. Colonel Hussain.
You and me, us...
...sitting in my office
and talking about this...
...means me
co-operating with you.
Do you think it'll be easy
to find out the truth?
They are the SFTC commandos.
If they have decided
to conceal the truth...
...then they'll take it
to their graves.
Cardinal rule of poker, sir.
If all the players are bluffing...
...we should raise the stakes.
So that the weakest player
folds first.
[Locker opening]
[Locker closing]
"So, Bilal had multiple
fractures in the leg."
"Injury in his head
and concussion."
"Rohan had bruises
from falling on the rocks."
"And Vishnu's right side
was completely stiff."
And Shikha?
Which side of Shikha's head
had wounds?
- Sir. It's all in the report, sir.
- Oh.
Yeah.
On the right.
- What is for lunch?
- What?
Smells like paratha.
Aloo paratha.
Sir, will you have it?
Now that you are insisting,
I'll have it. Fine.
Thank you. Clarified butter.
Are the doctors allowed to
have clarified butter? It's good.
What do you think after looking
at Capt. Shikha's injuries?
Are these regular combat injuries?
Yes, sir. According to the patient
these are combat injuries.
It could be sexual assault as well.
Well... I just told you, sir...
...that according to the patient,
they are combat injuries.
Are you a lawyer or a doctor?
Capt. Aparna, you very well know
how to catch someone lying.
The heart beats faster.
Are you sure that Capt. Shikha
didn't fall unconscious...
...because of some other reason?
- Like what, sir?
- It could be anything.
She could be pregnant.
Sorry, sir. But why
would she be pregnant?
There are lots of
good looking men around.
They all stay in the same dorm.
Surely she is not a virgin.
Sir, I can't believe you
just asked me this question.
Relax.
These are just routine questions.
Sir, would you ask these routine
questions if she were a man?
Would you have been able
to answer this question...
...if she were a man?
Anyway, thank you.
Shikha's best quality
is that she is loyal.
She is loyal to her country.
She is loyal to her team.
And she is loyal to her boyfriend.
Loyalty is a strange quality,
Capt. Aparna.
You know, sometimes when
you are loyal to a person...
...you end up being disloyal
to the institution.
You understand what I am saying?
Yes, sir.
- Sir, I have patients waiting.
- Last question.
There were no nail marks on any
other member of Squad Alpha...
...other than Capt. Shikha.
Am I right?
Yes, sir.
Check your pulse rate,
Capt. Aparna. It's quite fast.
Capt. Shikha Sharma has a
boyfriend. Study boyfriend.
And RMO Capt. Aparna is trying
to hide something for sure.
Listen. Show me the register.
- Yes.
- Who are you, sir?
- Police Special Branch.
What happened, sir?
4th July,
Saturday night at 10:01...
...this mail was sent
from this IP address.
But there is no entry
for that time in this register.
It's a crime to use cyber cafe
without an ID. You know it, right?
Sir, it's the closing time.
- Sometimes it happens.
- "Sometimes."
I am sure, that time must
have been chosen on purpose.
Try to recall.
It happened last week.
It's a small town. I'm sure
many people don't come here.
Try to recollect who it was.
A tall guy, fair, muscular.
With the crutches...
I mean, he must have been
using crutches to walk.
Yes, sir.
A tall man had come here.
- Tall?
- Yes, sir. Tall.
He was wearing a jacket.
There was a muffler
around his neck.
- Just...
- Muffler?
Yes, sir. It was of this colour.
Red colour.
This...
Sir, it's not working
since two months.
Here is what you can do.
- Close this cyber cafe as well.
- What, sir?
[Car moving]
[Imtiyaz] 'It is said
that in war as in poker...'
[Imtiyaz] '...if you
want to win...'
...you should know the strengths
and weaknesses of each other.
And you all have...
...overcome Dozakh together.
But do you really know each
other? So, your task today is...
...to write down the strengths and
weaknesses of your course mates...
...in these forms. Through this,
we will collate the data...
...and make your
psychological profiles.
And don't worry.
Your views will be confidential.
So please, be brutal.
[Imtiyaz] 'Red ones for strength.
Blue for weaknesses.'
And your time starts now.
[Surje] 'B*******d.'
This is betrayal, boss.
That s***a said that the reports
would be confidential.
And he leaked it so easily.
What is this, Vishnu?
You think I am horny.
Just because I crack jokes,
you wrote this in my report!
Joking around is fine
among ourselves, Vishnu.
You know this will f**k my ACR.
Surje, sorry.
I thought it's confidential...
Whatever I'm, I'm upfront.
I am not like you guys.
God knows what you guys did...
...that the James Bond had to
come for the combing operation.
You think I don't
deserve to be here.
I am taking advantage
of my dad being a general!
I've cleared every obstacle
of the special forces...
...and that too with
flying colours, Tank.
Not my dad.
You get it?
F*****g lunatic.
- Sir, what does this mean?
- Lack of initiative.
Sir, why? Because I am a
soldier and not an officer...
...you think I can't
take good decision.
This is not true, Tej.
And before saying anything
to me look at your report.
What is this?
"Capt. Manit is not a team player!"
- Really, Tej?
- Yes, sir.
You do what you think is right.
You don't listen to anyone.
I'm not the only one who says this.
Everyone says this.
Actually, you are right.
I shouldn't have written
lack of initiative.
I should have written careless.
As far as I remember you lost
your magazine during Dozakh.
But sir, you told me to hide
this from Capt. Shikha.
- F*****g idiot.
- Boys...
Relax. This is the Indian army.
We have a decorum here.
Colonel Sathe is testing us.
[Tank] 'So that we react this way.'
Please don't fall for it.
Not Colonel Sathe. Lt. Colonel
Imtiyaz Hussain. He has done it.
And this is not the last time.
I have a feeling, he will
try to trick us like this again.
Unbelievable, Imtiyaz. You leaked
the psychological profile reports!
I just gave you the permission
to conduct a class.
- And I took them to task.
- Imtiyaz.
This is completely unacceptable.
This could create
a rift amongst them.
We are trying to unite them
and not separate.
Sir, the team
which breaks so easily...
...is not worthy to be
in the special forces.
What do you mean?
Only Squad Alpha knows
what happened in Dozakh.
And sir, my gut feeling says...
...that even RMO, Aparna does
not have the entire picture.
Imtiyaz.
You have my full support
for the investigation.
But there is a code
of honour in the army.
Which is sacrosanct...
...and which is above anything.
I agree with you, sir.
But with all due respect...
...is this code of honour more
important than a lady's honour?
Sir, something has happened.
And either the one who sent
the e-mail can tell me this...
...or Capt. Shikha herself.
And right now, both...
Both are lying, sir.
Reports look good.
Your progress is also good.
I am from Haryana.
It is in my blood.
Thank you for everything, Aparna.
Shikha, Colonel Imtiyaz
came here to meet me.
What did he say?
He didn't say anything.
But he had some very
disturbing questions.
Like.
-[Shikha] 'May I come in, sir?'
- Yes.
[Door opening]
- Sir.
- At ease.
You are asking questions
about me from everyone, sir.
So, I thought I myself
should come here, sir.
I don't play poker, sir.
I used to play with
catapult when I was a kid...
...and I am now, a shooter.
I prefer talking to the point, sir.
Point taken, Capt. Sharma.
So, why don't you tell me
the truth point-blank?
The truth is, sir
that I am a Belieber.
"What do you mean"
is my favourite song.
Pink has always been
my favourite colour.
I'm not a virgin.
I'm sexually active.
I have a steady boyfriend
but I'm not promiscuous.
And I never got pregnant
till date, sir.
Well, I am not asking
about all this.
But okay. Now that we are talking,
why don't you tell me?
You seem to be very
emotional about...
What's his name? Shivalik.
But you didn't even call him
after Dozakh.
You didn't even tell him
what happened with you.
I really appreciate the fact
that you worked really hard...
...to get the records
of my messages and calls.
But if you think that owing to such
tactics I'll become emotional...
...and I'll crack,
it's not going to happen, sir.
Till date I never met a lady
who is not emotional.
Women are emotional, sir
but they are also smart.
Like your ex-wife, sir.
Pardon me, sir. But...
Maybe that is why she left you.
Military Intelligence, sir.
Handpicked after
rigorous deep selection.
What happened, sir? Aren't you
used to intelligent women?
To be intelligent and to
think others as stupid...
...are two different things.
You think I don't know who
leaked the strategy class reports?
I know you have friends in MI.
Capt. Sharma, I know that
something has happened with you.
And you are taking revenge
by leaking the reports.
But if you tell me, I can help you.
- I can help you.
- I don't want anyone's help, sir.
You can carry on
with your investigation.
The one who sent the e-mail
might tell you something.
Maybe you sent that e-mail.
You may leave, Capt. Sharma.
One thing that I like the
most about Colonel Sathe.
He loves reverse psychology.
Red form and blue form
in the psychological tests...
Blue wire and red wire
in the bomb test...
Blue means enemies,
red means friends.
Blue wire was supposed
to be cut, Capt. Sharma.
But as per everyone's debriefs,
the red wire was cut.
[Imtiyaz] 'Why?'
Manit, I have an instinct.
It's reverse psychology.
Go with the blue.
- What about logic?
- Manit, blue.
- Red.
- Blue. - Red!
[All] 'Raju...'
Raju, here...
Back...
Tank, back.
Manit, back.
Capt. Shikha.
Come, let's play a game.
I don't play games, dude.
I am a sportsman.
Well, I must appreciate your
sportsman spirit, Capt. Manit.
What do you mean?
Which wire did you cut
during bomb defusal?
Red or blue?
Capt. Manit, red or blue?
Blue.
You told us that
you cut the red wire.
Why did you lie to everyone?
Is this your team spirit?
You didn't want to give up
in front of a girl.
Your male ego couldn't handle this.
Sir, you said that
you cut the red wire.
[Tank] Red wire?
Even in our task, blue
was the right wire.
As my 2IC...
...you must have a very good
reason to tell a lie like this.
Please enlighten us.
We are all waiting.
- I lied for the team.
- Sorry?
- For the team?
- With all due respect.
You took a wrong decision first.
Because of which
we lost a lot of time.
And we didn't even
get our supplies.
So, after a point I felt...
...Rohan should be our
team leader instead of you.
He was the best amongst us,
Capt. Shikha.
Are you the commandant here?
Will you decide who should
be the leader of which team?
I was not the only one.
We all thought so.
Even Bilal.
Anyway, what difference
does it make...
...if I cut the red wire or blue?
The fact is we were all safe.
Isn't that what matters?
What say, guys?
Hey. Good that you
were not in our team.
She is asking you nicely.
Whereas the Squad Bravo
would've done your kambal parade.
You are safe.
If you want, you can
complain to Colonel Sathe.
Vishnu, even you
were with him, right?
B*******d, even you
didn't tell the truth.
Shikha.
Shikha, stop please.
Shikha, listen to me.
Shikha.
Shame on you, man.
Why did you do this to me?
I was wrong during
the navigation exercise.
You were right.
But seriously.
This!
How do you look at yourself
in the mirror?
- I'm really sorry, Shikha.
- It's too late.
Such a big lie!
Why?
Shikha, I'm sorry.
And believe me, it's not about you.
There is one more lie,
bigger than that...
...which I am hiding.
Shikha, my whole
f*****g life is a lie.
I am gay.
- Red. Red!
- Blue.
-[Manit] 'We are safe!'
- Hurray!
Die another day, b****h!
- You said...
- Hush.
Everyone has their own
secrets, Capt. Vishnu.
Someone lies to save his life...
...whereas others,
to save their jobs.
Remember the bartender?
- So, where are you from?
- From Bangalore.
What is the matter, bro?
Time for some cocktail?
[Vishnu] 'Manit knew my secret.'
[Vishnu] 'And if anyone in
the army comes to know...'
[Vishnu] '...it was the end
of my career, Shikha.'
[Vishnu] 'While growing up...'
[Vishnu] '...I thought it's
just a passing phase.'
And I tried.
I tried a lot...
...to fit in, to be macho,
to be a man.
I even joined the army.
But I guess, I am what I am.
And every passing day...
...it's being difficult for me
to hide this truth, Shikha.
Please try to understand.
I'm...
I'm really sorry for this.
Capt. Vishnu Soren.
You were attached with
Bihar Regiment for three years.
- What is their motto?
- Work is worship.
Work is worship.
I was faced with the same
dilemma after Dozakh.
Should I sign the exit form
or continue my job?
You are a decorated officer.
You were selected
for the special forces.
There must be
something special in you.
Vishnu, our deeds defines us.
Not your sexuality
and not my gender.
You were right, sir.
Capt. Sharma is a tough cookie.
I'm hardly left with
more cards to play.
It means you
finally met your match.
I am really intrigued, sir...
...as to why she
is hiding all this.
What could be the reason?
Imtiyaz.
Defence minister is coming
for the POP.
In fact she wants to induct
an all women battalion...
...in the army.
Shikha's case is very important
for the future of the Indian army.
Sir, I tried stealth and surprise.
But Shikha didn't fall for it.
I think I should try
some guerrilla tactics.
Something to grab her by the balls.
You have a really complicated
relationship with women.
[Raman] 'Don't you?'
Not really, sir.
It's quiet straightforward.
Anyway, Imtiyaz, keep me updated.
Sure, sir.
Hi, Vikram.
I need a favour, dude.
Yeah.
The number is 9814...
I told you that I was very
busy the last few days.
So, I couldn't call you.
Yes...
You tell me.
That's it.
Yes. Fine.
Dad.
He must have gone out.
Okay, fine.
I need to go, Mom.
Yes. You take care.
I am fit.
You don't need to worry at all.
Okay?
Fine.
Bye, Mom.
Bye...
After going to the academy...
...it's the first time Shikha
messaged me and called me, friend.
This has to be perfect.
[Man1] Lucky night, bro.
Dude, Shikha is not
like other girls.
One second.
This has to be perfect.
Candles, check.
Music volume, perfect.
It's looking good.
Dude, which oil did you send?
Eucalyptus?
It was told in the school...
...that its bark is
used to make paper.
[Man1] Not paper, bro.
Mood.
[Man1] 100 percent successful.
Okay. I hope so.
[Door bell ringing]
One second.
Listen.
I think she is here.
I'm going to call you back.
Okay?
Bye...
[Door opening]
[Door closing]
Boo!
[Screams]
- Got you.
- What the f**k?
- Hi! - What kind of childish
behaviour is this?
What's wrong with you?
Sorry, dude.
Look at the decoration.
Look... Why did you
switch on the light?
Sorry.
I had told you
that I was very busy.
What happened?
- You told me that...
- What?
- You said...
Are you all right?
This is a very bad idea, Shivalik.
I'm going back.
Hey, Shikha.
Listen...
I have been really
worried about you.
It's okay, dude.
- How are you?
- Very good.
- What happened here?
- It's nothing.
I missed you so much.
- So...
- Stop it, Shivalik.
Don't you understand?
We are meeting
after so many days.
So what?
Is this the first thing
you think about?
Shikha, why are you
reacting like this?
I thought you are stressed so...
Just wanted you to relax.
That's it.
Is this the only way to relax?
- Shikha, enough.
- Enough of what?
We can meet outside, right?
For coffee or dinner?
Why do we always meet
in the hotel rooms?
What are you trying to say?
That your candles, this music,
your massage oils...
...is all f*****g b******t.
It is just a means to an end.
Only one thing is
important for you.
That you get what you want.
Whether I want it or not,
how do I feel about it...
All that doesn't matter.
You will never understand,
Shivalik...
...what I actually go through.
You have a comfortable 9 to 5 job.
You sleep till 12 o'clock
on the weekends.
And you think everyone's life
is the same.
What the f**k is wrong with you?
Will you say whatever you want to?
You got no business to judge
me like this by the way.
I stood by you throughout
everything in your life.
Even today I left everything
and came here...
...as you sent me a text.
I thought it will bring
a smile to your face.
I thought you need me.
But no, I was wrong.
Because you are selfish.
You are downright selfish.
That's right.
This relationship is about you.
What do you want?
What are your needs?
Did you ever think about me?
"Shivalik, how are you?"
"How is your work?"
"Are you all right?
Are you happy?"
You know what?
You keep this attitude of yours.
Because I am leaving.
Yeah, get lost.
- You know. See you...
- I don't need you anyway.
I don't need anybody, Shivalik.
F**k!
[Car speeding]
Well played, sir.
Well played.
You can hack our phones
and message us, sir.
But you can never
hack into my brain.
Never say never, Capt. Sharma.
Well, if you just tell me
what happened that day...
...I won't need to do all this.
My answer will
remain the same, sir.
Nothing happened that day.
Most of the domestic abuse
victims say the same thing.
"I slipped from the stairs and
got hurt. Nothing else happened."
My injuries are regular
combat injuries, sir.
And, the injuries and wounds
about which you aren't talking.
The wounds on your soul.
What about that?
Who assaulted you, Capt. Sharma?
Who made you feel
less than an officer?
Tell me.
Answer me.
I saw how you handled
Capt. Manit's lie.
And now, you are lying.
Why such double standards?
I never thought you will
turn out to be that type.
The type that choses
ambition over self-respect.
"Boss touched my thigh.
So what?"
"Next promotion is mine."
"Superior at work place
wants to sleep with me."
"It's okay."
"At least the
corner office is mine."
You became the poster girl
of a politician.
You became the champion of
the feminists in this country.
But you are perfectly fine with
sexual assault at work place.
Frankly, Capt. Sharma.
Your feminism is really convenient.
In fact I would say you are
more of an opportunist...
...and not a feminist.
You're absolutely right, sir.
I am that type of girl.
I can do anything for
the corner office, sir.
What is sexual assault
in front of ambition?
I am here to make history, sir.
And to achieve something, we need
to make some sacrifices, sir.
This is what you wanted to hear,
right?
Now, may I leave.
Please understand.
I want to help you.
No, sir.
You want to save me, sir.
You want to be my hero.
But this is my story, sir.
And there is only
one hero in my story.
Myself.
Thirty six hours
had already passed.
No water, no food, no sleep.
The target was 500 metres
away from us.
And then suddenly
machine guns started firing.
We were taken by surprise.
[Gun shots]
Tej, Vishnu.
Right side.
Manit, Rohan.
Left side.
Bilal, with me.
Bilal.
Are you okay, Bilal?
Capt. Vishnu.
Bilal.
You okay?
Rohan, come in.
Manit, come in.
Manit.
Bilal, are you okay?
Bilal.
I fell unconscious. And I
couldn't see anything after that.
Let's talk about the
things which happened...
...when you were in your senses.
You were Shikha's buddy.
How would you say were
your relations with Shikha?
Good, sir.
Very good.
Friendly.
No one was ready to befriend her
when she joined the course...
...except for me.
As the stress increased
during Dozakh
...it must have had an impact
on your friendship as well.
Sir, you know that disagreements
are common during such situations.
Be specific, Bilal. What was
the reason of the disagreement?
Shikha's navigation
led us the wrong way and...
That's why.
Tell me, Capt. Siddiqui.
Shikha was made the
team leader of Squad Alpha.
Were you completely
okay with that?
Yeah, initially I was.
Then when the mishap
of navigation happened...
...I felt Rohan is better
suited for the job.
It means, though
you were friends...
...you were not happy that Shikha
was made the team leader.
Why?
- Sir, I just said...
- Is it because she is a woman?
No.
No, sir.
Not at all.
I genuinely felt that Rohan
is better suited for the job.
It means that Shikha
is not a good leader.
Sir, I didn't say that.
Shikha is really good.
But there are a few people in
Squad Alpha who are more deserving.
Like who?
Like...
Like Manit.
Rohan or perhaps me.
It means everyone except Shikha.
Sir, I didn't say that.
Shikha is good.
In fact very good.
Very good for a woman.
This is what you mean to say,
right?
- No, sir.
- You know, Capt. Bilal...
Shikha was your friend.
First lady commando.
Exemplary in all
her courses so far...
...yet you couldn't
trust her 100 percent.
When Manit cut the blue wire
instead of red and lied...
...you supported him.
All of you supported him.
Just because you couldn't accept
a lady officer as a team leader.
- This is not true.
- Then you fell unconscious...
...but you and every member
of Squad Alpha...
...wrote exactly the same debriefs.
Word by word.
What is all this?
Some kind of a bro code
in your boys club.
Except that because of
this Capt. Sharma...
...whom you call your friend...
...got into trouble.
What type of friendship
is this, Capt. Bilal...
...that you didn't even have
the balls to look her in the eye...
...and say goodbye
to her as you left?
Fine.
You all are saying
that nothing happened.
So, I'll also write in my report
Shikha is nothing
but a manipulative liar.
And she shouldn't pass this course.
Sir, no matter how Shikha is...
...she is not manipulative.
You are trying to save your friend.
I wish I could protect her, sir.
I wish.
But trust me, sir.
Shikha is a strong girl.
She can protect herself.
I am not protecting her now.
Whom are you protecting then?
[Shikha] 'Bilal, are you okay?
Bilal.'
[Screams]
[Man2] 'Alpha1, come in.'
So, you won't tell me anything.
Fine.
Capt. Sharma, I don't
want to hurt you.
Let's keep it civil.
But I don't wish to do so.
What happened?
Being a Rajput, why
have you suddenly lost your valour?
Stealth and surprise.
First lesson of the special forces.
[Pained scream]
Come on, Rohan.
One more.
You know I can take it.
Stop!
Very good, Capt. Sharma.
Are you okay?
Are you fine, Capt. Rohan?
I know what the truth is.
And I also know
that you know the truth.
Sir, it's not what you think.
It's exactly what I think.
- No, sir.. It's...
- It is exactly what I think.
I just met your dearest
friend, Capt. Bilal.
- Sir, he is an overemotional...
- Relax, Capt. Rathore.
Capt. Bilal didn't say anything.
What are you doing here
if Capt. Bilal didn't say anything?
You invited me here.
And now you are asking me
what I am doing here!
I know that you had sent that
anonymous mail, Capt. Rathore.
Right cyber cafe, right time,
right mail, right recipient...
But you made one mistake.
He was wearing a muffler.
- Just...
- Muffler?
Yes, sir. It was this colour.
Red colour.
Your daughter must have gifted
this bright pink muffler to you.
Am I right?
Frankly, Capt. Rathore...
...till 2 hours ago, you were
accused number 1 for me.
But your Krav Maga
exercise saved you.
[Imtiyaz] 'Shikha's injuries
are on the left side.'
[Imtiyaz] 'But you are a leftie.'
A right-handed person
has assaulted Shikha.
I think it's time now,
Capt. Rathore...
...that you tell me
what happened that day.
36 hours.
Keep walking.
[Siren.]
[Rohan] 'Without food or sleep.'
- Red.
- Blue. - Red.
[Rohan] 'Moreover,
we were given sleeping pills.'
[Rohan] 'Some people were
having hallucinations and...'
[Rohan] 'Some just
couldn't take it.'
[Gunshots]
[Pained scream]
- Alpha 1, come in.
- Rohan.
Rohan, where are the targets
coming from?
They are moving targets.
I guess, we've been surrounded.
Bilal, are you okay?
Bilal.
Bro, shall we move ahead?
We are losing precious time, man.
Bilal...
Capt. Sharma.
Bilal is a tough cookie.
He will survive this.
But if we stay here, we'll
never reach the end point.
Capt. Rohan, take the
defensive position.
We can't leave Bilal behind.
Would you say the same
if this was a real war?
You can win the war
with logic, Capt. Sharma...
...and not with emotions.
Capt. Manit, would you
have said the same thing...
...if you were in Bilal's place?
Rohan, do as I say?
Take the defensive position.
[Gunshots]
[Screams]
Bilal...
Bilal, you okay?
Bilal, are you hit?
Bilal.
Tej Bahadur, is Vishnu all right?
No, sir.
Tej, is there firing in the
direction that we just came in?
No, sir.
This way is clear.
Tej, you'll move back
along with Vishnu.
- We will give you cover. Copy?
- Yes, sir.
[Gunshots]
Vishnu.
Come on.
Capt. Sharma, are you
suggesting us to retreat?
If you and Rohan give me cover...
...Tej and I will go in the middle
and establish the perimeter.
We need these points, Capt. Sharma.
We have to finish
this exercise, damn it.
I will not risk the
lives of my men...
...to complete this exercise,
Manit.
[Gunshots]
You are a f*****g coward.
S***a, you are putting up
a drama saying...
..."I'll not risk
the lives of my men"...
in order to hide your cowardice.
Rats are the ones
who hide, Capt. Sharma.
Men don't hide.
Men fight in war and
that too, only to win.
Hey, Amitabh Bachchan.
We will win the war
only if we stay alive.
This is not a simulation exercise.
These bullets are real.
We just have one way
and that is to move back.
We have to retreat.
What do we do? Do you
want us to behave like girls?
How dare you, Manit!
Do you have any doubt about
who is in command here?
- Are you?
- Yes, I am.
1950 Army Act, Section 46.
Misconduct, desertion,
disobedience, use of force.
You can get
court-martialled for this.
I won't put my squad at risk...
...because of your machismo
and ego trip, Manit.
And if I'll have to shoot you
in order to save my squad...
...I will fire.
We have to retreat.
And that is final.
Did you understand?
[Screams]
What the f**k are you doing,
Manit?
[Screams]
Sir, that was the moment
which I'll regret my entire life.
Because I was the only one
who could have intervened.
But I didn't.
I chose the wrong side.
But believe me, sir.
I had no idea what
would happen next.
[Screams]
You f*****g b***h!
Are you done now, s***i?
Now you see, I'll put
you back in your place.
Manit, what are you doing?
Manit!
[Cough and gasping]
[Unbuckle belt]
[Manit]
Stop it.
Manit!
- Manit!
- Shut up!
[Cries]
[Pained scream]
Manit.
B*******d.
You f*****g b*****d.
Shikha.
Capt. Sharma.
Capt. Sharma, are you okay?
[Gunshots]
Sharma.
Capt. Sharma.
F*****g a*****e.
What were you doing?
Shikha, everything is fine.
Shikha, you are fine.
Shikha, look at me.
Rohan...
[Buttstroke]
Manit, s***e.
B*******d.
What the hell are you doing?
Rohan.
Rohan, try to understand.
If she were conscious...
...we both would have been
charged with disobedience.
And we would've never become SFs.
[Coughs]
Now, it will be her
words against ours.
And no witness.
[Coughs]
We have given our blood and
sweat to reach this place.
We cannot let this go.
[Coughs]
After that the firing stopped
but we had lost radio contact.
Maybe even Mr. Bhatti had found
out that there is something wrong.
She slipped.
She hit her head.
Capt. Rathore, I'm not
able to understand...
...why you didn't lodge an official
complaint with Colonel Sathe.
Because it wasn't so simple, sir.
Bilal saw me with Shikha
and not Manit.
Manit would have blamed me and...
It would have been just
his word against mine.
And I thought Shikha would come...
...and complain against
Manit to Colonel Sathe.
But she didn't say anything, sir.
When did you think about
writing this anonymous mail?
You are not troubling mom, right?
-[Arshi] No.
-[Rohan] 'I spoke to my daughter'
[Rohan] 'in the evening.'
Good girl.
'Dad, I want to wear
the army uniform just like you.'
Then I went to the military
hospital to meet Shikha.
I couldn't see
the state she was in.
I couldn't hold it, sir.
I had to do something.
I couldn't see injustice
being done to Shikha, sir.
Sir, she is also a fellow officer.
She is also my course mate.
Bilal was Shikha's
as well as my friend.
Yet he chose me.
He remain quiet.
[Footsteps]
So, officers.
It's time for the two last
exercises of the course.
Which means the last opportunity...
...to increase your rankings
on the leadership board.
So far the rankings are...
...Capt. Surjewala at number 5.
Capt. Tank at number 4.
Capt. Rohan, number 3.
Capt. Shikha at number 2.
And Capt. Manit is at number 1.
10 shots in 90 seconds.
Five shots from assault rifle
and five shots from pistol.
The target will be moving
in the last shot.
Two fans will be placed
on both the sides.
The speed of air will
be 10 miles per hour.
- Capt. Surjewala, will you start?
- Sure, sir.
[Beep sound]
[Whistle]
[Gunshots]
[Beep sound]
Sir, can I go at the end
if you permit?
Why, Capt. Sharma?
Is it a new technique
to be number one?
Permission.
[Gunshots]
[Fan sound]
[Whistle]
[Gunshots]
[Gunshot]
Hello, Capt. Shikha.
Your wrist must be hurting
after Krav Maga bout.
That's why you
missed the shot as well.
It's okay.
Happens.
Actually, Manit, you are
a cross country runner.
You think one step at a time.
I think about future.
It's too deep.
You won't understand.
[Manit] 'Yes, sir.'
Yes, sir.
I know, sir.
Thank you very much, sir.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
What happened, dude?
You seem really happy.
Do you remember about my brawl
I had during my YO's course?
Yes, you told me. It's was
your ex-girlfriend's issue.
That got solved.
How?
- It was a false complaint.
- You're tactical, s**le.
That is why I'm at number one
on the leader board.
Number one.
Good.
[Gunshots]
[Imtiyaz] 'Close shot
there, Capt. Sharma.'
What do you mean, sir?
I mean to say, you were right.
About what, sir?
That you don't need me.
You are the hero of your story.
I know you missed
the last shot deliberately.
During the final exercise...
...rank one and rank three
will be paired. You knew it.
That's why you went to
number three from number two.
Why would I do that, sir?
In order to end
what Manit had started.
I know the truth.
Sir, my truth is that...
...I am in the special forces...
...because I deserve
to be in the special forces, sir.
Not because of my gender
or in spite of being a girl.
I am a soldier's daughter, sir.
I am an athlete.
A shooting champion.
Since childhood,
I always had one dream...
...that I would wear this uniform
after I grow up.
And no feudal...
...misogynistic...
...criminal, unofficer like man...
...can neither snatch away
this dream of mine, sir...
...nor my sense of justice.
Let's get the past done.
Sir, I had already told you...
...I am enough for myself.
Shikha.
Think about others
and not just yourself.
Other lady officers
will come after you.
We must set an example for them.
- And defence minister...
- Defence minister...
...whose poster girl I am, sir.
I maybe her poster girl...
...but I am not her or any
politician's puppet, sir.
As for all the lady officers...
...then I am trying to set
an example for them, sir.
Till now...
...why weren't girls inducted
into the Indian Special Forces?
The authorities have their
reasons and they are valid.
This is my only opportunity
to prove them wrong.
I deserve to die
for this country...
...as much as any man.
The lady officers will
come here in future...
...because we will earn
our right to be here.
If I fail in this test now, sir...
...the door of active
combat will be closed...
...for thousands of girls.
And you won't let that happen.
I'm happy that you are looking
at the larger picture.
In fact, I respect you for that.
But still we must name and
shame the b*****d, Shikha.
I...
Not we, sir.
In my 26 years of career...
...I turned out to be
wrong for the first time.
Imtiyaz, give me
that officer's name.
He does not deserve
the maroon beret.
Sometimes to figure out
the opponent's game...
...we have to call all
the bets on the table.
But these are rankings
for tomorrow's exercise.
Yes.
Shikha has come to number
three from number two.
Which means her buddy has
been changed in the final exercise.
God d**m it.
Capt. Manit!
I'm going to roger that fellow.
But not now, sir.
What do you mean?
It's my honour, my self-respect.
In order to protect this...
...I don't need
the help of any man.
- But, Shikha...
- I won't complain, sir.
He will confess.
But, Shikha, still...
Please give me 24 hours.
Just 24 hours.
Please.
[Sathe] 'This is absurd, Imtiyaz.'
Manit needs to be
thrown out right away.
But sir, you won't be able to
do this without my report.
Don't teach me what
I can and can't do.
Just 24 hours, sir.
Shikha has asked me and I
am asking you. Please, sir.
You'll get Manit's confession
in these 24 hours.
Lieutenant colonel
Imtiyaz Hussain...
...if Manit commits another act
of injustice in these 24 hours...
...will you take the
responsibility for it?
I'm turning the situation
on its head.
What will we do if Shikha
takes a severe step?
Sir, Shikha came so far
just because of her ability.
You had no hopes
from her on day one.
But today...
Just give her one chance
on this last day.
Then you will get both the
complaint and the confession.
And that's my promise to you, sir.
Now, she isn't the test case, sir.
In fact, she is the best case.
Don't think as a commandant.
Think like a soldier, sir.
And Shikha is a soldier
who deserves her justice.
[Phone ringing]
- Yes, Mom.
- It's the last chance
and you have to come first.
- Or else...
- You'll break my legs, right?
[Shikha] 'I know that, Mom.'
I don't know about coming first.
But I will finish what I started.
[Shikha] 'Dad must
have gone somewhere.'
Yes, dear.
- Forget it.
- Dear, we all are with you.
Just wait and watch...
...you will be the number one.
I'll call you after the exercise,
Mom. Okay?
Take care of yourself.
Bye, Mom.
[Door knocking]
[Gunshot]
Going beyond enemy lines...
...is a part and parcel of every
special officer's life.
But...
...our work is not just to cross
the border and kill our enemies.
Many times, we need
to rescue the hostages.
Be it civilians,
political prisoners...
...or our own soldiers.
Your last exercise is
hostage rescue operation.
Lieutenant Colonel Imtiyaz.
Officers, you will perform
this task in pairs of two.
You need to cross the border
and enter the enemy area.
And without using any ammunition,
you have to rescue the hostages.
And in the heat of the moment...
...if you use ammunition...
...you will be disqualified.
Dummy hostage...
...can be anywhere among
these five locations.
And if the enemy traces you in
the process or if you get caught...
...you will be out
of this exercise.
And if you are able to cross
the border...
...you will regroup at Point Alpha.
In order to complete this task...
...very buddy pair
will have just two hours' time.
Remember one thing.
Your real weapon...
...is your sharp mind and body.
So, get ready.
Just don't slow me down,
Capt. Sharma.
Want to finish with the flourish.
Don't worry, Capt. Manit.
You will finish...
...with a flourish.
[Bhatti] 'Attention.'
Are you people ready?
Yes, sir...
- [Whistle]
[Boots thumping]
[Wire cutting]
[Battle-gear noise]
[Door opening]
[Footsteps]
[Gun cocking]
- [Gun cocking]
[Man falling]
[Man kicking]
[Pliers snipping]
[Gun cocking]
[Kicking]
[Footsteps]
[Huffing]
I specifically told you not
to slow me down, Capt. Sharma.
Slow you down!
You are here because of me.
Who saved your life a while ago?
S***a coward.
You no more address me
with respect.
Really?
Will you declare to the whole world
that you saved my life?
And you didn't save my life.
I was handling myself.
I was not asking for help,
like you girls.
Girls will only ask for help
when guys like you are with them.
What the f**k!
Unfortunately, this is army
and not a kitty party.
There are no points
for bitching here.
You know, this...
This is exactly why girls
shouldn't be inducted into SF.
It's fine to be doctors and nurses.
But active combat
is not your cup of tea.
You come here professing
your love for the country.
When you go through hell here...
...you people want cushy postings.
What else?
Marriage in four years
and then pregnancy.
Then a same-station posting
with your husband.
You take care of kids.
While we will handle the guns.
Seriously.
You are a girl. So, be like one.
Don't try to be a man.
Just do what you are best at.
Which is what?
To turn guys like you into men?
What do you mean by that?
You are a guy but not a man.
Did you forget my manliness?
What is the use of
you being an officer?
You are neither smart...
...nor are you deserving.
You act like an animal.
Where do you get
this arrogance from?
Tell me.
Just because
you were born with a d**k.
Isn't that why you didn't complain?
Why didn't you complain?
Were you scared or ashamed...
...that everyone will get to know?
What will people say?
What about your career?
Test case will be a fail.
Wasn't this the reason,
Capt. Shikha Sharma?
Or is the matter something else?
Maybe you enjoyed having me
on top of you.
I felt it.
That's why you stopped here
as soon as you got the chance.
Listen.
There is still time left
for the task to complete.
You want me to finish
what we started?
I know you like it rough.
You f*****g bastard.
I knew you would again do
something like this.
I am scared...
This is a simulation exercise,
Capt. Shikha.
The bullets are fake.
Drop the gun.
[Gun cocking]
These are real bullets.
Shikha... Come on.
Drop the gun.
Tell me. What were you saying?
- Shikha, what are you doing?
It might fire. - Tell me.
- What?
- F**k, dude.
What does this mean, Shikha?
This means you are f*****g dead,
you a*****e.
And you know what.
I will finish what you started.
- Shikha, listen to me.
I made a mistake by not
shooting you the last time.
This time I won't repeat
the mistake, Manit.
Shikha, listen. Easy. Look.
It's not just your dream.
It's also your mom's dream.
- Easy...
- Shut up.
Your brother committed
suicide, Shikha...
...when he couldn't fulfil
this dream. You've got a chance.
The Ministry of Defence chose you
among so many girls, Shikha.
You can't do this.
- Move back.
Shikha, I...
I am not doing anything.
My hands are back.
I'm not doing anything.
Just listen to me.
Look at me.
If you pull the trigger, Shikha...
...you'll end up in jail.
- Everything will be over, Shikha.
- Shut up.
- How can you shoot me, Shikha?
I... - Shut up.
Stupid emotional woman.
S***a, you can't handle a gun
and you will shoot me! B*******d.
You'll shoot me?
- I'll show you what you deserve.
Don't move. - F**k you.
What happened? Nothing happened.
Aren't they real bullets?
Did you think I'll ruin
my entire life...
...for a c******a like you?
What are you looking at,
B*******d?
I am from Haryana..
Even I know to swear.
C*****a.
Look what is in your hand.
Look.
Look!
My gun and your fingerprints on it.
Now, look at this.
Here is the camera.
You have confessed your crime...
...and you shot
your fellow officer.
Do you understand the implication
of this?
Or shall I explain you
the sections?
You are out of the army,
let alone special forces.
You'll f*****g rot in jail
and I'll make sure of that, Manit.
C*****a.
B*****d.
F*****g a*****e.
- [Punch]
[Shout]
[Cries]
[Huffing]
[Choking]
Stop, Surje.
- Hey...
- She can handle this.
Bloody b***h.
Did you forget Dozakh?
F*****g b*****d.
[Shout]
- Stop her...
- Stop, Surje.
That a*****e deserves it.
I didn't forget Dozakh, Manit.
I was waiting for this day badly.
I purposely got
my ranking to three...
...so that you be with me.
And I'll take revenge
for all that you did.
I am from the intelligence, C****a.
I have your entire biodata.
You used to hit your girlfriend,
right?
Do you know why I was quiet
till now, H*******e?
Because I was waiting
for the moment...
...to deal with you alone.
So that I teach you a lesson...
...that would prevent you or any
other man from daring to do...
...such a thing
or even thinking about it.
[Boots thumping]
How dare you, Manit?
How dare you?
- You were trying to be a man!
- Shikha.
- Capt. Shikha.
- You'll show me my place?
Shikha!
[Crying]
Sorry, sir.
[Huffing]
[Dummy dropped]
[Sathe] 'The army's job
is to protect...'
[Sathe] '...the country,
the country's values, freedoms...'
[Sathe] '...and its citizens.'
[Sathe] 'The army's job
is to protect both.'
[Sathe] 'Its men and its women.'
[Sathe] 'A lewd man
like Capt. Manit...'
[Sathe] '...is a disgrace
to the uniform.'
[Sathe] 'And there is no place
for such people here.'
[Sathe] 'Whenever someone breaks
the code of honour of the army...'
[Sathe] '...the army teaches him
such a lesson that no one...'
[Sathe] '...will ever think
of doing something like this.'
[Sathe] 'But there always will be
a bad apple amongst the good ones.'
'But there always will be
a new beginning as well.'
Capt. Shikha Sharma,
you were right.
Work is worship.
I need to go.
There is no place for me here.
The world is changing, Vishnu.
Look I am in SF today.
They will have to open
the doors for you too.
Till then I will be honest
to myself.
Rest is up to them to decide.
I salute you, Capt. Soren.
[Flag fluttering]
- One.
- Commando...
- Two.
- Three.
- Commando...
- Four.
- Five.
- Commando...
- Six.
- Seven.
- Commando...
- Eight.
- Nine.
- Commando...
- Ten.
Do you think that you
deserve the maroon beret?
Yes, sir...
Even I think so.
You are the elite of the elites.
And I'm so proud to pronounce
this honour upon you.
Dozakh, netherworld, hell...
...is over from today.
But from today...
...your answerability
towards your country...
...will start afresh.
[Boots thumping]
In sea, on earth, in air...
...there won't be anyone...
...above you or ahead of you.
- I'm very proud of her.
- You should be.
[Boots thumping]
[Trumpets blaring]
[Shraddha] 'We've always heard
that women...'
[Shraddha] '...are not
ready for the Special Forces.'
[Shraddha] 'It's wrong.'
[Shraddha] 'Women were always
ready for the Special Forces.'
[Shraddha] 'Now, the Special Forces
are ready for women.'
And today Capt. Shikha Sharma
has proved it.
She has topped her course.
And this is just the beginning.
Like I always say...
...that patriotism
doesn't have a gender.
Now, I would like to request
Colonel Sathe...
...to award the prestigious
Commando Dagger of the SFTC...
...to Capt. Sharma.
"Winning is my habit.
That spells doom for my enemies."
"The love for India
runs in my veins."
"The motive of my life
is to protect this country."
"The love for India
runs in my veins."
"I am not weak.
I am no less than anyone."
"I don't mind dying."
"I take pride in saying
that the tricolour is my life."
"The love for India
runs in my veins."
Didn't I tell you
that she is strong?
[Trumpets blaring]
[People clapping]
"The love for India
runs in my veins."
"I will turn the tables around
by flying high."
"I'll win the fight.
Just resolve to win."
"Just resolve to win."
"The love for India
runs in my veins."