Where is the gold?
Gold?
We would like to welcome everyone onboard.
Hello, I am Vijay Walia.
Chairman, Kohinoor Airlines.
When are we getting our salaries?
Next week with the Diwali bonus we'll
get all our pending dues.
We won't even get a box of sweets on Diwali,
and you're dreaming of a bonus.
Jasmine. You haven't
paid the rent for six months.
We slogged like maids for 20 years.
We let them deduct pay for taxes.
Then for provident fund.
And we let them screw us over.
Is our company bankrupt?
Madam, what are you saying?
Swear on Mother Goddess, Mr. Bindra.
We're bankrupt.
Swear on God we're bankrupt.
Rajvanshi sir.
Show some humanity, Jasmine.
A poor guy is...
Scoundrel.
Shall we keep it?
Are you out of your mind?
If we get caught,
they will ban us from the airport,
let alone an airplane.
You turned out to be such a sly guy,
Mr. Mittal.
We don't have money to buy biscuits,
and you guys are rolling in gold.
Help us too, sir.
Will you be able to do it?
We're going to live
it up today like the rich.
Where are you going?
To do an exotic dance?
Want to see.
Comedy?
There is someone knows about us.
-What are you doing here?
-Customs.
Customs?
What's in the bag?
Shit.
If you are going,
make sure he gets a good view.
Sethi ma'am.
Money can turn anyone into a gangster.
How can he just get away?
Because he's rich, baby.
Oh, shit.
Look at Titanic.
The rich escaped in boats.
Who had to drown?
The department has
received some sort of tip.
You are going nowhere, madam.
I am scared.
Then sing.
Which one?
"Gold. So much Gold."
Seriously?
Geetu.
You're a capable pilot,
you're good at everything.
But I can't do it.
Fly the plane.
Papa!
Is the tip confirmed?
Solid.
Does the jail have internet?
Sir, please be seated.
They were saying they
were preparing for some arrest.
Arrest?
You. Sit, moron.