- This is a $1 billion super yacht,
and it's big enough to hold
an entire city on the water.
How do humans build this stuff?
And I'm gonna show you the
difference between this
and a $300 million mega yacht,
a $50 million giga yacht,
all the way down to this $1 yacht.
Why did you sell me
this boat for a dollar?
- The storage just kept racking up.
- Yeah.
- $18,000.
- It's cost you 18 grand
a year to store this?
- Correct.
- Interesting.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
And after stepping on board
it was pretty clear why
this yacht only cost $1.
Okay, now that we're on the water
what are we working with in here?
- I don't think the floor's
supposed to do that.
I don't know if this
is even worth a dollar.
- Oh, we're actually sinking. Oh.
The boat literally started sinking
right when we put it in the water.
- Oh, my God. Let's go.
- We gotta go up. We're sinking.
Jump, Chandler.
My baby!
I paid a dollar for that.
That was the $1 yacht.
Later in this video, we
have a $50 million yacht
a $300 million yacht, and
the $1 billion super yacht.
But before all that,
here's the $1 million yacht
which is a little smaller
than I thought it would be.
Hop on, boys.
All right.
- Let's see the inside.
- On the $1 million yacht,
you get a surprisingly big living room,
a lower deck with a master bedroom,
another bedroom that I can't stand up in,
and then you got some
double beds for the kids.
- Wait, you have kids?
- Chris, Chandler, Karl, Nolan.
- Don't worry, boys. I got this.
Coming on the break to break.
- Please stop. Someone's
gonna send a rescue boat.
- We need the coast guard.
- I wonder if I turn this, if he'll fall.
Stop.
- This is fun.
Oh.
- For a million dollar
boat, I'm not gonna lie,
it's a little smaller than I thought.
Let's see if these guys watch our videos.
- Oh, my God, it's Mr. Beast.
- Hey, he has seen our channel.
That's pretty funny.
So, now we're going to
the $10 million one.
- 10 million?
- See ya.
- It's gonna be great.
- Bye.
Oh, my God. He's fast.
- And now we are on the $10 million yacht.
Let's check this out.
- Holy crap, the front of the boat's huge.
It's just way bigger than the last one.
Look at the view.
- I'm getting some good sun here.
I'm really pale.
- Oh, my gosh. Yes,
this is a nice bedroom.
For $9 million more I
can actually stand up.
And right down these stairs
are four more massive bedrooms.
Why are there two toilets side by side?
- Oh, that's a bidet, Jim.
- For your butt?
- You poop in here
and then you wash your butt in here.
- Why don't you just use toilet paper?
- You're so American.
- And upstairs is another seating area.
Oh, my gosh.
The seats on the $1 million
yacht were leather and hot.
These are actually soft.
- Soft and practical.
- This boat is the nicest
boat I've been on so far.
- Well, just wait until
you see the next one.
It's massive.
And because it's so massive,
I invited all my friends.
Go have fun.
- Go, go, go.
- This boat is meant to hold 150 people.
They're gonna have a lot of fun.
- Whoa.
- Oh, my God.
- This is wild.
What is the difference
between this and a mansion?
- This is a mansion.
When does it stop?
Jimmy, I'm still going.
- This is definitely the nicest
bedroom we've seen so far.
And it's nice because my
head doesn't hit the ceiling.
I can barely touch it now.
This yacht has a living room, an office,
a massage parlor, two dining
rooms, and seven bedrooms.
- This is the best yacht
I've been on so far.
I'm driving the boat.
- Chocolate.
It's not Feastables.
- It's not Feastables.
Thank you for saving
my life.
- You're welcome.
No way.
♪ You gotta ♪
- No.
- Hey buddy, are you relaxed?
- Yeah, I was.
- Are you done with your massage yet?
Here you go, take a bite.
- That's some good chocolate.
- So, we got all of the
goon squads in here.
This is a $25 million boat with 30 rooms.
Why are you guys in here?
- This bed is so comfortable.
- Even though this yacht
comes with a world class chef
the boys still wanted pizza.
So, I planned a little surprise.
Do you know what we're standing on boys?
- A boat.
- A hospital.
- An H.
- A boat.
- A helipad.
And Uber conveniently does
helicopter deliveries.
That can't be real.
- Oh, it's real.
- Is that a helicopter?
- Pizza.
- I can't believe it's actually works.
- Pizza!
- Pizza, pizza, pizza.
- All this for some pizza.
- Woohoo.
- Pizza, pizza, pizza.
- I am terrified of parallel parking.
He just landed a helicopter
on a moving boat.
Who wants some pizza?
I know you're not supposed to swim
after you eat a bunch of pizza,
but you're on
- Jump.
a $25 million yacht.
Which thankfully when you pay 25 million,
you can get some jet skis.
- Oh.
- Tariq flipped the jet ski.
Yo, Mac. Catch this pizza.
Oh.
- Oh.
- Oh. Oh.
- $25 million yacht and I'm
the only one enjoying it.
- If you thought this yacht was crazy,
look at this video of
the $50 million yacht.
You know what?
Honestly, let's just go to it right now.
Zoom in.
And now, we are on the $50 million yacht.
This yacht is over 200 feet
long, four stories high,
can hold over 200 people, and
comes with a 20 person crew
with this homeless person I found.
Sup guys?
- When you pay $50 million,
you're given this remote
that can call the crew
at any time you call me.
- Sir, did you call me?
- No, I just wanted to
show how this works.
But that's not the only
thing the remote does.
They said this TV goes up and down.
- That's cool.
That is slow, dude.
Maybe it's like...
I'm gonna go downstairs,
you guys go upstairs.
Tell me if you find anything cool.
- Okay.
- Bro, it is massive.
- It's like a whole nother boat up here.
- Jimmy, there's nothing
cool up here. Don't worry.
- This is crazy.
- Whoa.
The interesting thing is
I've just been walking
and I don't know if I'm
at the halfway point,
the end of the boat, or if I just started.
This thing's huge.
- Meanwhile, Nolan overslept.
So, he was still trying to find us.
Have you seen Mr. Beast?
- Yeah.
- Are you lying to me?
- Apparently Pete Davidson is there.
If I don't see Pete Davidson,
I'm gonna sink the $50 million yacht.
- Meanwhile, we noticed
another boat was approaching us
and then the owner did this.
I was waving at him and
he showed me his butt.
- That's gonna be someone's
dad one day, dude.
- All right, catch.
Oh.
- Where are they going?
- Gimme that, gimme that.
- Are they backing away from us
or are we just that much better?
Oh.
- Get 'em.
- This is the best.
- Oh.
Oh.
The guy that's bigger and
stronger than all of us did it.
Wow, Chucky.
- I wonder what kind of
food they got on this yacht.
- I heard they have lamb.
- They do not have lamb.
- Mm-hmm.
- No.
- Cut to the dinner.
- Oh, man.
- Whole lamb.
Thank you so much.
- It's really good.
What projects
do you have coming up?
- Uh. Ooh, I'm very excited.
I have a show called Bupkis
coming out on Peacock on May 4th.
- Three days before my birthday.
And while Nolan was
still trying to find us.
- Which direction did Mr. Beast go?
- We noticed a lot of boats
surrounding our floating billboards.
I didn't even know you could
put billboards in the ocean.
And we thought they might
want some chocolate.
- I'm delivering chocolate.
Yo, you guys want chocolate?
- Let's do this.
Oh, my gosh.
- Best chocolate I've ever had.
- Let's go.
- It's so good.
- Yeah.
- Let know if this is
the best chocolate bar ever.
- Oh, my God. Out of 10, it's an 11.
Hershey's don't know nothing.
- Hershey's doesn't know nothing.
Everyone agrees it's
better than Hershey's.
You need to try it.
Tell me what you think.
- Honestly, way better than Reese's.
- That's what I like to hear.
What do you give it?
Aye.
- A 10.
- I'm flying Feastable bars
to people.
Aye, Feastables incoming.
- Oh, no.
- Let go of the string.
One Feastable bar delivered.
Hey Karl,
they're trying your gummies.
- If you wanna try the best
chocolate bars, cookies,
and gummies on the planet?
Go to Walmart, 7-Eleven, or
any Albertsons stores right now
or go to feastables.com right
now if you wanna order online.
Hey, what do you think?
- This is amazing.
This is better than every other chocolate
so why wouldn't you get Deez Nutz?
- I agree. Put our nuts in your mouth.
- Oh. Alright.
- At the end of the day,
Nolan finally found us.
- Jimmy.
- Nolan.
We had another five star dinner.
And the next morning we boarded
one of the world's largest yachts.
This is the $300 million yacht
and it has over 50 crew members
waiting on your every request.
Tons of luxurious rooms
and nine master bedrooms.
Oh, my gosh. Great.
- Welcome aboard.
- I literally can't see the
top of the boat from here.
We are the 69th
largest yacht in the world.
- Is that a factual statement?
- Yes, it is.
- That is crazy.
There are six floors, a massive pool,
and a hot tub with a view.
This is nice.
- It's ridiculous.
- It's my favorite boat so far.
- The $300 million yacht comes
with a state-of-the-art gym
that overlooks the ocean.
- Oh, what?
- Dude, if my boat had
a gym, I'm working out.
- A movie theater with
windows that auto darkened
whenever you watch something.
And even the table is worth $3 million
and the piano plays itself.
I want one of these in my house.
All the boys disappeared in the spa.
Come with me.
Oh, you're getting a haircut?
Yeah. Karl was in the sauna.
Are you alive?
- Barely.
- That does not look comfortable.
And I don't even know where Nolan is.
- Oh, it's so hot.
- Man, really got in a hot tub
with a sunburn.
- It's too hot.
- Dude, there's more downstairs?
- Whoa.
- Oh, my gosh.
- You think they have enough jet skis?
- What's behind this door?
- Oh, I'm doing this.
- One of us is getting thrown
off the side of the boat.
- Huh?
- He was last.
- Bye.
- Hey, always, always
be ready for nose goes.
- Jimmy, can we eat some food?
- Yeah, when you get back.
Boys, we must act like rich billionaires.
Clink.
Would you rather have 300 $1 million ships
or one $300 million ship?
- You could almost have one
for every different day of the year.
- I'm not gonna take care of 300 boats.
- Which would you rather have?
300 boats or one big boat?
- You want the big boat?
- Gentlemen, did any of you
notice a boat pulling up?
- No.
- On that boat might be Tom Brady.
By might, I mean it is.
And we should probably go say hi to him.
- Let's go.
- Hey, Tom.
- What's up, guys?
- And if you don't know who Tom Brady is,
he is the number one
quarterback in NFL history.
So, this is where you get
your haircut on the boat.
So, it turns into a dentistry.
- Where you wash.
- Clean your teeth too.
Is this the nicest boat
you've been on?
- My God, are you kidding me?
- Yeah.
- It's crazy
if you eat too many Deez
Nutz bars before breakfast.
I literally had to hide them in my house
because I knew these two would sneak
to right where they're at.
- Yeah.
- I did. This place is so fun.
It's really an endless maze.
I think it's a nicest boat in the world.
That's what we do.
- It's so beautiful.
- It's crazy.
- We still have more floors
to go on.
- Tariq's, the master
of the camera.
Thank you, thank you.
- This is a way nicer helicopter pad.
- When I think of a
helicopter pad on a yacht
this is what I think of.
Not what we had before.
And with Tom Brady here, of course,
we had to play some football.
This is the most fun version of catch
'cause you just do this and
he just throws it there.
- Nope.
- I just suck.
- That's what I got paid
for, Jimmy. Come on.
- I wanna see if you could
hit my drone out of the sky
- Oh, no.
- with a football.
- All right, if I hit the
drone on the first try,
maybe I should come out of retirement.
- I like that.
- Dad, you're gonna like miss.
- I probably will miss.
- First try.
- Go, go, go.
- Oh.
He got it.
- Nolan, put your sunscreen on.
Karl's probably the worst
wide receiver you've ever thrown to.
Unless you dome him in the head,
he's probably not gonna catch it.
All right, Karl, don't screw this up.
Just throw it as far as you can.
You hit him in the chest.
You gotta hit him in the head.
- It's a bad placing.
After chilling with Tom Brady,
we hung out in the movie room
for the rest of the night.
Would you say this is
the best boat so far?
- 100%.
- But keep in mind,
there's still a billion
dollar boat after this.
- How big can that get?
- It is four times bigger than this boat.
- These things get bigger?
- This ship is bigger than
three statues of liberty.
- Holy crap.
- You cannot fathom how
massive this ship is.
It is literally a floating city
that is 1200 feet wide
and 17 stories high,
and it fits almost 10,000 people.
In all the other ships
we had our own rooms
but this ship has over 2000 rooms.
This boat has water
slides, an indoor mall,
a basketball court,
and tons of other stuff
I can't even name.
- I ran out of fingers.
- All of which we have to ourselves.
Have fun boys.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Brother, it's that way.
- Oh, okay.
- Let's see what happens.
- Whoa, there's a water slide.
- There's a whole entire
waterpark up here.
I'm breaking the rules.
- We're running, we're running.
- Sorry, lifeguard.
They literally have live
music in the waterpark.
What the heck?
- There's even an entire
sports floor that has
everything you can imagine.
- Mini golf.
- Let's go.
- We're literally playing
mini golf on a ship right now.
Interference.
- And I wasn't exaggerating,
when I said this ship is a city.
There's literally seven
neighborhoods on this ship.
This is insane.
We're still on a ship.
And just for reference, this is what one
of those neighborhoods look like.
- So, I went down to the slide
and now I'm teleported into
like a different world.
And you have a carousel?
- They have shops, restaurants,
arcades, even a Starbucks.
Hey, Chandler.
- Hey.
- A hundred million people
are watching.
Let's see if you make the shot.
- This is crazy.
Like how can I use all these seats?
I'm only one person.
- And apparently there's an entire floor
for indoor shows and events.
- What is this, bro?
We got the whole ship to ourselves,
selves, selves, selves,
selves, selves, selves.
- Obviously, I don't need
this giant ship all to myself,
so I wanted to share this
experience with you guys,
my subscribers.
- I love Mr. Beast.
- Subscribe to Mr. Beast.
- Holy cow, this boat.
- It's actually pretty nice.
- Let's go, boys. Let's get it.
- We're gonna go ride the carousel.
- Carousel, carousel,
carousel.
- Where'd Chandler go?
Oh.
- And just when we had thought
we had seen everything here.
What is this?
How do humans build this stuff?
Also in this giant mall,
inside of this giant ship
there's a bar that comes
down from the ceiling.
Wait, what are those robotic arms?
- That's our bionic bar.
- Oh, it's all right, buddy.
- Oh.
- Whoo. Woohoo.
This is sick.
- From the kids menu.
- Oh, my God.
- See how much you guys, my subscribers,
we're enjoying this ship.
- Never let go.
- And I had one last
surprise for my subscribers
on the cruise ship.
So, I had Nolan gathered
them all together.
I have a big announcement
for all of you.
To all the subscribers
we brought here today.
We're giving you a
three night free cruise.
- And if you wanna be in
a video in the future,
subscribe so you can join us next time.
We filmed a secret Mr. Beast
video that will never
be uploaded to YouTube.
The only way you can watch this video
is by buying a Feastables
product within the next 30 days
and scanning the QR
code on the back of it.
There's literally never been a
better time to buy Feastables
from Walmart, Albertsons,
7-Eleven, or feastables.com.
I spent over a million
dollars on this secret video.
You wanna buy Feastables,
so you can watch.