Welcome back to the vlog.
First of all we will have
tea and enjoy the view.
The lady is going down to the falls,
we will also go down
and have tea first.
So let's do one thing, let's go to the
falls, there are two ways to go the fall,
One goes down from here
and the other one goes ahead.
I have heard that the one
ahead is better, so let's go down.
Bro, I swear I didn't know
that Chhattisgarh is so beautiful.
I don't have words for
the winds and valleys here.
Oh, so we have to park
the car here and go down.
This is the nature's trail, there
is a way to go down from here.
They said that the water is too
much, so the way to go down is closed.
But let's try.
It seems to be a valuable thing from here.
Barricading has been done here
so that anyone does not go ahead.
Is it your duty here?
A few days ago, someone went inside here.
Does he comes from the village behind?
Yes, I saw it on TV.
He jumped from here,
Jumped from the front?
This girl jumped, but she survived.
The boat saved her.
She knows how to swim.
If she knows how to swim,
maybe she wasn't save,
God saved her.
Have you come here
before, or this is the first time?
- First time..
I really wanted to go boating,
Because I saw on the internet
that boating is done here.
They take to near that.
It is said that the fun of seeing is in the monsoon.
- Yes
And it changes color also.
Now there is a little muddy
water, it turns white in winter.
It brings a lot of soil on the way.
But it is said that
this soil is very fertile.
These kids gave me a challenge.
Bro, do one thing, hold the
drone in your hand and show me.
I said
Challenge accepted.
So now let's go down.
The sad thing is that I saw on YouTube
that they take you right next to the falls.
It is not possible in the monsoon.
You have to come back in winters.
This is the way to go down.
Let's go.
Look at that, people have reached below.
It is very beautiful.
This gate comes from our resort.
And this is where we came from.
This is a little small, where we came from.
This is a long route?
- Yes
Jai Bholenath.
Let's visit, Bholenath.
It was Monday yesterday.
I couldn't go to the temple.
They are saying that the
water level is low here.
It will fall more in August.
The water level comes up to here.
- Yes
You are leaving today, right?
Yes in evening.
Okay, brother.
Take care.
I have come wrong way. there is no
way to go ahead. I have to go back.
It seems that the water has
come up to here from the soil.
It is the soil of the river.
We have read in our childhood
which is the alluvial soil.
It is very fertile.
Which is that soil? I forgot.
Where is the way to go?
How have people reached?
If I reach from here,
it seems i will reach.
It looks fine.
I found the way.
He has gone from here.
When you come here,
you will see light rain.
When the rain falls, it is
the water of the waterfall.
It stays like this in the whole atmosphere.
Now we have reached to our water.
Look at the view of
the waterfall from here.
Nice.
Ohh, I have to go.
Leave it.
I will go from ahead.
Bro, My curiosity is
forcing me to go ahead.
Those people have left in front of me.
It seems that people are
having a lot of fun laughing there.
We should also have fun.
Found it.
I have reached, here it is that people.
They are doing camping.
Nice.
Here it is.
This black-black hut.
This is our hut.
We went from
there in the morning.
This
This People met us.
Look at this.
People are still standing.
This is the picture point.
We came from there.
And then we came down here.
I think it's done.
That's all there was
to see in the waterfall.
It's 9 o'clock now.
Checkout is at 11 o'clock.
What am I doing tomorrow after this?
I have no idea.
I had just planned this.
But I know that I have to
spend another day around it.
So let's see what it is.
Then we will go.
There are stairs.
But I always feel that
before climbing the stairs,
I should see it for the last time.
But as soon as I see it,
I feel that thousands and millions of tons
of water fall from this fall every second.
Man can't even think of making
something like this man-made.
Only he can do it.
The ultimate creator.
After leaving the hustle
and bustle of the city.
And coming here in the arms of nature.
I don't feel like going
back to the city at all.
If you listen carefully,
nature says a lot to you.
It's such a beautiful waterfall
you should definitely come here.
But one thing makes me sad to see here.
Everything is good it is.
It is called India's best waterfall.
It is called India's Niagara Falls.
But look at the people.
There are only a few people.
And as far as I talked,
everyone here is local.
If you go to the airport, there
is so much tourism promoted.
There are so many big hoardings.
It is also at Delhi Airport.
It is also at Raipur Airport.
But when you come on location,
The facilities are less
according to the number of ads.
If you look at Niagara Falls.
The entire economy of Niagara
City goes from where to where.
They have made so much there.
Hotel, restaurant, casino.
Just people will come to see the waterfall.
If people have come here.
If now I have to drink tea and coffee here.
I will drink tea and coffee
here and spend 300-400 rupees.
It will take in the economy here.
But there is nothing.
So if you want to promote tourism,
you have to do development here.
How old is this temple? 100 years old.
- 100 years
100 years old.
The stone and statue look very old.
The building of the temple is not that old.
And this stone looks very old.
Can I sit here for a while?
I felt such a new energy inside the temple.
I decided to sit with Lord
Shiva for half an hour.
Although I was getting late.
But Lord Shiva made me sit there.
Look at our Nandi Maharaj
looking at his Lord Shiva.
But there is something in this.
As soon as I took off my
shoes at the temple and
put my bare feet on the marble.
I felt a strange feeling.
I felt very good.
My check-out is at 11 o'clock.
It is 10.30 am already here.
There is no smell.
Can you smell it?
No.
There is no smell.
I don't know what kind of incense it is.
I don't feel like saying bye to it.
But a final bye.
The work is going on.
If they are making it,
they should  make it good.
But look here.
There is a tea shop for tourists.
This one.
This is the market to eat and drink.
What a good opportunity.
If we invest here and we will make good.
How big a tourist this place can be.
And how much revenue
can be generated from here.
I feel like thinking.
We don't have that thinking.
We don't have that thought.
How to make it big.
In foreign countries they
don't have tourist places.
They construct it first.
They will construct it and develop it.
Then tourism in it.
It takes so much time for
them to make a break-even.
Nature has given us tourist places.
We have to build infrastructure around it.
We are behind in that too.
Bro, I am Super late.
And now I am moving ahead.
206 was supposed to come, got it wrong.
That one.
there are so much ants here.
Finally.
No matter how late it is.
We have to transfer a cup of tea and data.
Because I don't have space.
I have to charge the battery.
I was about to check out from the room.
That's when I got a very bad news.
Is the water full there?
Yes, water is full.
Hello.
Bro, I am in trouble.
What happened?
You told me to go to the falls.
Chitrakote Falls.
Yes.
Then you told me to go to the cave.
The cave is closed in monsoon.
Oh.
I didn't know about the rain.
It is closed in monsoon.
So there is nothing else to do here.
There is nothing left.
There are temples there.
Can you go there?
What is the name of the temple?
Danteshwari.
Danteshwari Temple.
Let's say goodbye to the falls.
One last time.
Bye.
It's a very beautiful place.
But there is one thing.
If you come in the
monsoon, it is very beautiful.
It will be fun to watch.
But you won't be able to go boating.
But if you come in the winter.
November, December, January.
Then you can go boating.
And I saw it on YouTube.
Where the water is falling.
You go near it.
And people are like this.
How far is it?
I wanted that experience,
I couldn't get it Next time.
We are checking out from here.
But I have some trouble here.
Yesterday I was in
trouble and today too.
And that's just because of one person.
He is following me.
I don't have anything
to eat and give him.
I don't have anything.
So the thing is that there is nothing to do here.
Caves are closed.
So I am thinking.
To leave from here.
I will have to stop in Raipur.
So, I will stop somewhere.
Or I will see the night at flight.
I will shoot there.
Let's go.
Amcho Deva Homestay.
But let's see, how are homestays is.
Let's ask here, I can't see anyone where.
Sister.
Is this the homestay board outside?
Is it the one in front?
Okay.
It's this one.
Brother, look at the door.
Empty.
I have Checked out the room.
It was nothing special.
It was a simple room.
I thought, these houses,
like people live in this
house if i got a room to live with them ,
Then you will definitely
get to know their life.
I like the food that is prepared in the kitchen
of the local people, the kind of food they eat.
They sleep the same way,
how they fill water in the morning.
To see such a life, but
this was a normal room.
Come on, let's go back to Raipur.
This is the rental car, they gave me fuel just like one stick,
Now there are two sticks.
So I have to fill so much
petrol that when I reach Raipur,
I have to return it in one stick,
otherwise I will suffer a loss.
They are making money with this
engineering, we can study how it works.
I stopped here to get a bottle of water.
This is the way to Raipur and this is the straight way to Chitrakoot.
So thank you Chitrakoot,
I liked it very much.
It was a very beautiful waterfall.
For Caves I have to visit again
because it is the largest cave in Asia.
And it is said that the sunlight
does not even go down.
There are such fish in the water that
they have not even seen the sunlight.
So I feel like going down there.
There is so much treasure in Chhattisgarh.
If we promote tourism here,
then a lot of tourists will come here.
Thank you so much for watching this vlog.
Take care of yourself, we
will meet you in the next vlog,
Bye.
I have a tease of Vlogging.
We complete these 6-6 hours in 8-8.9 hours.
And all our places, yesterday we
missed the waterfall cause of this.
Today I didn't even miss the
flight of Raipur.
Have to go to Raipur.
Subtitles by Mohit