It's a good thing to have a towel after a bath, otherwise
everything dries up.
So this is in the shape of an L.
Like this, like this, and like this.
We got it dug here.
We'll mix it with manure and leave it like this for a day.
We'll get a lot of broccoli and tomatoes here.
Comment below if you want this too. 20% discount.
Have fun.
Mom scolded you?
Why did mom scold you? Mom scolded me.
Let's ask mom.
Mom, why did you scold me? What did you do?
Aww, Pihu.
You beat mom up?
No, no bad.
Two October posts, Sam.
Did you come to meet me at your house?
Not Anji, Swami Chinmayal Anji's satsang.
Today is 22nd September, iPhone 15 has been launched.
We have to go get it.
We had booked it.
I was busy in the morning, I said let's go.
She said we'll go in a little while.
Then I got ready, then she got some work.
Now how will we go, bro?
How will we go, bro?
Think, son, think.
This is what you have to think about.
The World Cup is coming up on 5th October.
I can't miss my cricket practice.
It's very important.
We have reached Rashi.
We'll pick Rashi up from school.
This is how you come on the way.
Come fast, come fast.
We're going round and round.
What? We're going round and round.
We used to live in this area.
It's been so many years since we've been here.
It feels good.
We've come to Pacific Mall to get our phone.
And we'll give it to the car in the valet.
It's okay in the valet, it saves a lot of time.
I'll tell you, isn't that the old Eterno?
I mean, he didn't go in the valet.
All the Audi's were standing there.
Eterno? Eterno was there.
They must have said,
Eterno for 100 rupees, they're giving it for 100 rupees.
Sir, should I keep my helmet too?
Yes, sir, you can keep it.
Look, outside the Apple Store.
It's like getting a free iPhone for 1.5 lakhs.
Oh, man.
Look at this.
Apple First Day.
Look at the crowd, man.
All these people have come to buy a new phone today.
We have to wait here.
There's a lot of noise outside.
It's a mess.
Sir, I mean, I can't believe that people are so crazy.
To pick up a phone for the first day.
Should we do it like this first?
Let's wear the helmet first.
Sir is going to lose his life.
Do you want to switch it off?
Sir is saying, he won't be able to pick it up from you
tomorrow.
Thank you, sir. Thank you so much.
Wear the helmet first.
Here, drink it.
My 1.5 lakh phone fell.
I was just kidding.
Sir, if someone opens a new phone, and puts it here, will
Apple clear it?
Oh, I got it.
Put it on the table.
It's like a carpet.
This is the new cable.
Both are type C cables.
Apple people change it every time.
There's no on-off button in this one.
This is Rashid's and this is mine.
Okay?
It's light.
Zoom goes up to 25x, right?
No, optical zoom.
This has 3x.
This has 5x.
It's more than that.
It's digital.
Yes, it's digital.
I thought it has 25x, but sir is saying it's Pro Max.
I only took Pro.
Pro has 9x and 15x.
Sir, it's possible that if I go out of here,
and accidentally drop the phone,
Apple Crypto is here,
and they upgrade it to Pro Max.
No.
If someone, for hypothetical purposes, goes to buy Pro Max,
and gives this as a replacement,
Pro Max will be 20-30% reduction.
Did you see the result of your negligence?
So, he bought the wrong phone.
512GB.
We didn't even want 512GB.
I'm seriously thinking that
where does he keep his mind?
He said it was some tank influencer.
It doesn't even have 25x zoom.
And I came to buy it because
I need more zoom for the video.
Because every time I go,
I change my phone, and it doesn't come from DCI.
Basically, he gave it to me.
Gaurav.
Look at this.
You should have tried it once.
And see, it goes up to 25x.
Dad and mom will also watch the video,
and add more.
No, no, no.
Why didn't it cut?
Look, the video is up to 15x.
It's only in the photo, Ritu.
It's in the photo.
Thank you, Apple.
You saved my money.
Dad and mom, don't get angry.
It's the same.
I'm committed towards my fitness goals now.
I'm happy to buy a new phone, but I'm also a little sad
that I bought the big one.
In the big one, there is zoom in the photo, but not in the
video.
But I didn't have to buy the big one because in the big
one, there was only 13 Pro Max, which was sold out.
Now it's difficult to keep the big one.
The small one is fine in the pocket.
Apple takes so much money from you.
Bro, put a good camera in every phone.
The problem is that even if I look outside the store, but
there was so much crowd in the store,
the manager of the store said, he is a helpful person,
so he said, sir, don't go out.
Because I said, sir, once I go to buy a phone,
Whatever you want, we will bring it inside and give it to
you.
You sit in the back room comfortably.
He is sitting in the back, because of which he was left
behind in life. Anyway, now I'm leaving for cricket
coaching.
It's time for me.
My sir is waiting for me there.
I took out my new gloves.
Look at the condition of my old gloves.
The gloves are torn by playing.
When you have someone with you who is torn by playing,
then it is very happy that you have used it.
Bye-bye.
Bye. Love you, sir.
Even the shocker doesn't move in this car, so we move.
By the way,
I have reached my home.
I got a little late today.
I parked the car and ran here.
When we were in school, when we came late,
instead of two rounds, three rounds were punished.
Now Gaurav's one more session is about to start.
Let's see how it goes.
In the next episode
A special guest arrives!
We play cricket so well.
Mom, I will also play well.
If you practice,
it's not like that in the air.
What happened to you?
It happened like this, then you are doing it with your
hands.
Sir, how are they learning?
A little about them.
We got to know that we have been sending them here for two
hours and some outcoming classes
What are you saying?
Where will he learn cricket at night? We don't understand
such plans of his.
This is his coach.
You are sweating so much.
How is the practice going on?
It's going well.
It was a good session before you came.
Hit it Piyu, hit it.
It's such a heavy bat ball.
It's falling down.
Very good Piyu, very good.
Piyu, hit the ball.
Very good.
Piyu, hit the ball straight.
Mom, the ball fell down.