This is incredible!
- What's happening in our village?
At this rate, nobody in our
village will be safe anymore
A daylight robbery! Something
needs to be done about it!
He's the victim today. Tomorrow,
it could be anyone
Right! Something needs to be done.
- Where are you guys going?
You come along, too. Or she'll
carry you away too!
Will he help? - He's the only
one in the village...
who can solve the problem. We'll
have to fall at his feet!
Right! You're right!
What happened?
- Are your ears blocked?
No.
- So come on
What's happening? Is it
something scandalous?
Nobody knows. Narayan Dada's son
was carried away by a witch
Look at them! The bloody
herd of sheep!
They're here to chew on our
brains, early in the day!
Say we're closed for a fortnight.
- What for?
The DCP's mother's getting
married again
Where are they going?
- They just walked by!
Entry to women is forbidden...
Am I going to walk there to help?
Come here and talk to me
Why are you guys wailing?
What's wrong?
You are our Lord and Master!
Our saviour in trouble!
Why? Where are your other saviours?
- But you are the most powerful!
My son has been carried
away by Kartaniya's men!
Kartaniya? Who's this lizard?
That woman from the cattle market!
- She has abducted his son!
Is she going to pickle him?
Are the cops around only to have
photos taken of their shining medals?
Go and tell them that
I've sent you. Dismiss!
We went to the police, sir.
We even mentioned your name
But the witch still wouldn't
spare his son!
So you're at my feet because you're
disillusioned with the police?
I don't poke my nose in
other people's affairs
I fight only my own battles.
Go on now, get going
That witch gets all her help from
the lady in Anpara village, sir
Laxmi's goons are standing in
attendance, to defend them
Lawyer...
- Sir?
Use the phone. Summon
my kids immediately
No, sir. We ought not to
interfere in this matter
Why not?
- It has to do with womenfolk
You never know what twist
the tale might take
Don't you guys knows? Seth
Angarchand's men...
never get involved with women!
And you still come here?
Go away now! Mind your own
business! - Listen...
Yes, sir.
As far as I can see, this is
no ordinary case of women
The lady at Anpara and her children
are involved in this scandal
She's a very stubborn woman.
If anyone asks me for help against her,
I'm surely
going to help him!
Sir, call for you
Balli, come home immediately.
- Right, Daddy
lmmediately.
- Right away. Immediately
Hail Lord Hanuman,
Lord of Celibacy...
Phone for you, sir
Shakti, see which fool it is
Who the hell is it?
Your mother was nurturing a spirit
wasn't she? I'm the same ghost!
Brother! It's Daddy.
- Daddy who?
Daddy!
Daddy, talk to brother...
- No. Come here immediately
Right, Daddy. We'll
start immediately
Hold this for a moment
Well? You couldn't recognise
my father's voice?
I don't tell my father's
voice either
I'll play your father's
voice for you right now!
Is this the law college
boys' hostel? - Yes
I wish to talk to Jaichand.
- I'll call him
Who is it? Go on?
Didn't you go to college today?
Daddy?
I went, came back. And
went again and...
Is that a carrom-board you've
been bouncing off?
I'm going back in the
afternoon, daddy
No, no need to go there.
Come home immediately
No, I'm really going in
the afternoon, daddy
Must you keep raving,
you idiot? Listen to me
We got some important business to
finish. Come here immediately
Wow! All the wealthy men together!
At the poor man's door?
So you're the poor man who abducted
a poor farmer's son?
And you now want to swallow
his piece of land in ransom?
Bring that boy here immediately.
- So you've come to take the boy?
He's not coming out, sir.
- He can't? Never mind
We can walk. We'll carry him
No, none of you guys can
take him away from here
We are taking him away
We don't use our expensive footwear
to walk to such places
Sir, this is a cattle-market. I
clean scatter with these hands...
I use this hand to wash my backside
A punch with this one
will stink even more
I'm not standing in the
hot sun for too long
Finish it all up quickly. Let's go
Which sonofagun dares take
away the boy from here!
Dammit! Silly bachelors!
How would you know what
heat a woman possesses?
Is there a real man among you
who can sate a woman's thirst?
If there is, step forth, you curs!
I'll show you what it means
to flee with a turned tail!
Get out of the way.
Let go of that child.
These are the people responsible
for all this bloodshed and violence
And the father and the sons ought
to be punished for their crimes
That's all, your honor.
Dear students, today happens to be
Anjali's last day at the college
But it saddens me to say that
an intelligent girl like her...
is abandoning her studies
to settle down in matrimony
However, it is a matter of pride
that Anjali is getting married...
to the Home Minister of our State,
the young Mr Govindrao Pachpute
I therefore extend our heartiest
congratulations to her
We hope there will be fame
and honor in her life
Let us therefore give
her a happy farewell
Anjali, listen...
- What?
Will you please help me?
What happened?
- This
What is this?
- My transfer order
You can have a word with the
Minister and have it stalled
Me?
- Yes, you
Now don't say you can't do it.
- I'll do what I can
Bye. - Bye, take care.
Give it to him on your nuptial
night. Don't forget!
Come. - Bye.
Spray the rose-water,
elephant! Spray it!
Spray the rose-water, elephant!
What sort of a mahout are you?
You can't make the elephant
spray the rose-water?
Give me the cane. I'll show you
Sprinkle the rose-water,
elephant! Go on!
There, Mother! The rose-water
and also the oblations!
What are you guys watching?
Clean the mess!
Sprinkle the rose-water, elephant!
Sprinkle it! - Sprinkle. - Keep going.
Who're you giving those dirty looks?
Who asked you to bring
the elephant here?
I did.
- What are you doing, Ma?
There's work held up in the fields
because the elephant's not around...
and you're holding a farce here?
A circus on display?
Circus? My grand-daughter's
getting married...
if the elephant sprinkles
rose-water, does it become a farce?
Have you forgotten the pride
of the high-caste families?
You call a sacred ritual a circus!
In that case, why don't you get the
elephant to serve the guests...
who arrive at the wedding? The
village will witness the honour!
An elephant serving food!
- Viru! Don't try to play my father!
What the elephant will sprinkle
on the people of Anpara...
I will decide, not any servant
But mother...
- Enough! Go inside
Brother Pratap, what's going
on with you around?
There'll be 10,OOO guests! And the
elephant's going to be around!
So you want me to sprinkle
rose-water on the guests?
Oh no, go ahead and build muscles!
I wonder what burden you're
going to carry!
Now look, Vir, if you're irked,
go and tell brother Surajbhan
There's no need to eye my
muscles! Is that clear?
There you go again!
Can't the two of you digest
anything unless you argue?
Vir, you don't want the elephant to
be there at the wedding, right?
Yes, brother
I've stuffed a kilo of cotton
in the elephant's ears!
That's when I brought it here!
Even if a bomb explodes...
the elephant won't hear a thing!
- That's very nice... well done!
Why don't you stuff some cotton
in your mother's ears too?
Remember one thing. It's the
marriage of a motherless child
There'll be not just elephants...
...there will be fireworks
at her wedding too!
We will invite only those people who
will bless her with all their heart
Do you understand that?
My foot you will!
Grandma...
- My princess has arrived!
My darling daughter has arrived!
Come, dear...
I hear the Home Minister's fiancee
had a grand send-off at the college?
Don't poke fun at her! It's
commonplace in colleges nowadays
Studies take a back-seat. Fun
and frolic take centrestage!
Why not? My friends came to see me
all decked up at my wedding too
Anjali... how are you?
Oh sure! You married this mountain,
and were laden with gold, isn't it?
Enough. - Where's daddy? - He has
gone to meet the Home Minister
He mustn't have been around, so he
must've stood around like a guard?
The Minister hasn't disappeared!
Get lost! He'll come back
Lord...
Where the hell are they?
- What's up, lawyer?
Send half a dozen men, please.
I can't carry this burden on my own
Really? Listen... lend
the lawyer a hand
Looks like the Home Minister has
sent a lot of gifts... hurry up!
Hurry up and get him out
What happened, brother-in-law?
What happened to him? - Let him get
some fresh air... Get some water!
But how did this happen to him?
- Daddy? What happened?
The cat got your tongue? Won't
you tell us what happened?
All I can say is that this
wedding is not taking place
The Home Minister claims that this
alliance is posing problems for him
And I say he's being instigated...
...so that our daughter's
wedding is stalled
Stall my grand-daughter's wedding?
Who dares? Tell me!
It's no good wringing my neck!
Rather you strangle Angarchand's neck!
He's the one who has had
this wedding called off
He has lured ten legislators
to his fold.
He has threatened the
Home Minister...
to call off the wedding, else he'll
be toppled off his position
And that is why he has refused
to go ahead with the wedding
And you know! Death, mosquitoes and
politicians are not to be trusted!
That's it! Bravo! Slam him to
the ground! - Flattened him.
Eat all you want to, let there
be no room in your tummy
There's no feast at Anpara anymore.
- There'll only be a mourning there
They were forging an alliance...
...with the Home Minister
to belittle Angarchand!
And now her own grand-daughter
sits humiliated at home!
I spat because the people of Anpara
have gone down on their knees...
...before me
Why did you have to spit?
One single spit was enough
I spat because you spat
on my face, sir
But you sat before me with
your mouth wide open!
Where else could I spit?
Go and sit elsewhere!
But this is surely not enough.
The story doesn't end here
She'll have to go through
a lot more misery
The mother and her children will
go through a lot more of hell!
Shakti. - Yes. - Are the fireworks
ready? - Yes, daddy
So what are you waiting
for? Burst them
What are you doing, Ma?
Are we all dead?
If you are true men, take
this gun and go there
Bring his dead body to me!
Lady! What madness is this?
Yes! The Ladyship of
Anpara has gone mad!
She has killed Angarchand!
Say that in the court!
Don't just watch! Stop her!
- Ma... stop there!
Watch out! If anyone tries
to stop me, I'll kill him!
Wastrels! Don't get
anywhere close to me!
Stop it, Ma... - Give me the gun. -
Listen to me... Ma.
Get the car out.
- What are you doing Ma? Wait...
have you gone mad?
Calm down! Ma...
Let me go! Leave me alone!
- Calm down, Ma...
have you gone mad? Quiet! Quiet!
Ma... Get some water quickly!
Great! What bigger blow could we
have dealt to them than this one?
Thanks to this, the children of
this place can now live in peace
The children of this
family are already living in peace.
You doubt that?
What sort of a life is this, sir?
Getting violent to help others...
resorting to bloodshed to humiliate
the family in Anpara...
what sort of a life is this?
What I'm getting at is...
they too now need to lead a
decent life too, isn't it?
No!
- I see!
So you're still against
the family in Anpara?
You must end this feud of 20 years...
...and put an end all the
bloodshed and violence
For how long will you keep
the fires of hatred alive?
The fires will live, lawyer! Do
you expect me to forget it all?
Even though the fires are dead,
the embers are still alive
Must I really forget it all? And
how many things must I forget?
Tell me... tell me!
My Parvati... the goddess
of my family
Before my very eyes, she was here
at the altar in this courtyard
And she finally breathed
her last in my arms
Must I forget that? I spent
14 years in prison
I endured the hardships of prison
life mentally and physically
Must I forget it all?
You just said that my children
need to lead a peaceful life
But why isn't that the case? Why
hasn't Balram got married?
Why haven't Kishan and
Shakti got married yet?
After Jai, no child was
born in this family
I always yearned to see a cheerful
baby. Why? Tell me
Angarchand can never forget
all these things. Never
It isn't an iniury on my body.
It's a wound on my heart
My fires will be sated only when
that woman and her children are dead
If pain could be expressed, every
wound of mine would speak volumes
Shut up! First think of putting out
the fires that rage in my heart!
Only a widow knows the anguish
of losing her husband!
You lost your father, but I did
not concede defeat to Angara!
But today I realize that Angara's
sons are true men. And my sons...
are iackals that hide behind
their wives aprons! Jackals!
Yes, keep saying that
to them, lawyer
Where are you going, Roopa?
Wow! The birds and the bees!
That's the beauty of a woman!
You see how they got drawn away?
Get this clearly! Only a woman can
create a rift in that family!
That there is no woman in their
lives happens to be their strength!
If there were a woman
in Angara's family...
it would difficult
for them to handle.
All four would take
different paths...
and thus, they would be weakened.
You don't get it?
We need a girl to destroy the
discipline of that family!
You will then see...
- Shut up!
Cut the crap! You've
been barking away!
My daughter's weeping because her
marriage has been called off
And this man is thinking about
getting those princes married!
Are you going to kill the girl because
her marriage has been called off?
She says she's not going to study.
- That's what she'll obviously say
But if she remains here, she'll
be even more miserable
So I suggest you ask her to
resume her studies again
The latest! Sensational
news! All for free!
Take it for free.
- How's it going? - Great guns!
Where's the rest of the money?
- What money?
This is not done! You never return
the balance to me ever!
Did I ever ask for
the balance from you?
When did you give me
any money at all?
Don't screw up my mood.
I've got work to do
Sensational news! For free!
Mind-blowing news! Take it.
The village belle returns...
she could not unite
with her beloved
He did not bring the bridal
fineries for her...
so who is she going to find now?
Look at this babe!
Just ask, why's
she so worked up?
Just look, what a babe!
Just ask, why's
she so worked up?
Just look, what a babe!
Why's she so arrogant? Why does
she fight with everyone?
She seems to be a spirit!
Her charm is a killer
Her eyes ooze oomph
Lightning strikes my heart
when she sways in her gait
She makes everyone
at college pine...
she won't let anyone get
their hands on her
She's a volcano waiting to erupt
Fair-skinned, beautiful...
she's sure a nymph
A blossoming beauty, she's
proud of her looks
Tell her, friends...
not to flaunt her airs
Let's give her happy memories
Let's find a prince for her
The poor girl's grieving...
let's make her a bride
Why's she always on her own?
She's such an enigma
Nobody knows what ails her
Someone reason with her,
she's all pumped up
At this rate, she won't
find anyone...
she ought to get back to her senses
The poor girl might end
up remaining a spinster
I told you folks that I'm not
going back to that college!
But you still thrust
me into that hell!
He humiliated me in front
of the whole college
I've lost all the
respect and honour!
Are you happy now?
- Who humiliated you?
Your Uncle has asked you a
question. Haven't you heard him?
Who else could it be? It was
Angarchand's son, Jai!
He had it published in a newspaper...
...and distributed it
in the whole college
Do you know what filthy things
they wrote about me?
That scoundrel dares?! Brother,
Vir... let's go!
Hari Singh, Deva... get your swords!
Get a dozen more men! After
we're through with him...
he'll never do a thing like this
ever again in his lifetime!
Where do you think you're going?
And what do you imagine?
He'll be waiting for you...
to welcome you?
Remember, you took a battalion last
time to fight over water rights
And what happened? Four
of your men got killed...
Seven were crippled,
four lost an eye...
and five were permanently blinded!
We're still paying for
their livelihood!
Bloody lawyer! You live off us and
lavish praise on that family?
We fought then for someone
else's water rights
But it now has to do with
the honour of our family!
He'll have to pay for toying with
the honour of a girl from our family!
This is too much, Ma. We're now
going to return after beheading them!
Let's go, brother.
- Wait
I don't want you to do anything
Can't you hear me? Go inside!
There's no need to pamper me!
Grandma, I went to college because
I cared for your feelings
But when it came to my honour,
nobody here is bothered about it
All the love just evaporated!
- Who said it evaporated?
Now is when the love
will flow, my dear
Maybe I'm getting old, but I
haven't lost the spirit yet
Then why did you stop my
father and my uncles?
Why didn't you let them
battle it out? But no!
Your sons must come to no harm,
even if I'm burnt in the process!
What do I mean to you anyway?
Why must you bother?
Have you gone mad?
Is that all you have got to know
of your grandma in so many years?
The best attack is the one
that makes the least noise
Listen, did he humiliate me or
your father or your uncles? No
He humiliated you. So you will
plot the course of your revenge
You will fight for honour. How's
he to look at? Handsome?
Who?
- Angara's son?
I don't know, I didn't
look carefully
Then you must now take a good look
You will have to give him
a sense of belonging...
and make him eat out of your
hands. Make him a pet
You mean, I must fall
in love with him?
Love? If you fall in love,
you're the first one I'll cremate!
There's a difference in what you
weigh and what you buy.
You have to just weigh.
You got to lay the trap
of everlasting love
Bring him to a position
where he licks your heels
When he's madly in love with you...
...and revolts against
Angara and his family.
And if you will say,
he'll even present...
...Angara's head to you on a platter
And what love and what alliance?
It'll be the end of the story
He'll bang his head on
the walls all his life
Our revenge will be complete.
Then, I'll have my peace!
You get that, little girl?
Listen, where's Jai's room?
Upstairs. Room number 6.
Want me to call him?
No thanks. I'll find him on my own
Hey, move.
Jai!
Jai! Wake up!
- Let me sleep!
That girl's coming here.
- Which girl?
Anjali.
- Don't tell me!
Yes!
- How did she get here?
How would I know? She is here.
Give me my pyiama!
Where the heck is it?
I'm not your wife! - Give me
my pyjama! - Here, take this.
You're on the bed, and your
pyjama's are on the floor!
The girl! Keep her out!
- Hurry up and wear it!
I want to talk to Jai.
- How come?
Jai... I need to talk in privacy
No way! Say what you have
to in his presence!
This is between you and me.
Rather we talk in privacy
Lucky!
Can I come in and talk? - Not
necessary. Speak from where you are
But I'm not comfortable here.
- What're you doing, girl... watch it!
This place is only for men; so come
out and say whatever it is!
I haven't come to stay anyway. But
I will say what I have come to say
What harm have I done to you, that
you're treating me like this?
There is an enemity between
our families...
but must you seek revenge from me?
My marriage was annulled
because of your father
But don't ruin my
studies now. Please
I request you... stop bothering me
Even if we're enemies...
...when a girl cries before
you and asks for your help.
And if you still bother her, it's
terribly shameful for a man
And I really believe that you're
the only man in your family...
who will not disappoint me
Go on... go inside
She shouldn't have said that...
how could she say such a thing?
What?
- She means you're the only man...
in your family, and the rest of
them are impotent, faggots...
so they didn't get married!
- When did she say that?
She said it to your face!
- And I didn't utter a word?
No!
- Did she say that?
Did she really? - Yes...
she did. - I'll show her!
Hey girl... what did you say to me?
That I'm the only real
man in the family, eh?
Was I wrong? Aren't you a man?
No!...I mean, I am!
Are the rest of my brothers impotent?
- Really? I just got to know
Is that how things are?
Poor brothers!
- Look, don't act too smart!
Don't mess with Angarchand's
sons, okay?
You'll land in deep trouble!
They're lions... jackals, actually!
One second, one second...
what names are you calling
your brothers, Jai?
You call them lions, iackals...
is it a family or a zoo?
Am I here in the nude? Get lost!
Who do you think you are?
The princess of Anpara?
You're actually a
contagious disease!
This son of Angarchand alone
is enough to deal with you!
I'll give you such a tough time,
I'm going to bother you so much...
I'll do all I can! I
hate you! I hate you!
Have you said what you had to say?
- No! I...
Okay, I have... so?
- Very simple
I'll love you just as
much as you hate me
Keep hissing like a cobra, and
I'll still try to charm you!
Yes, I love Jai. With all my heart
To hell with your heart! I'm not
going to let that happen! Never!
Did you seek my permission
before starting to hate me?
So what's the problem with
my love? It's my choice
Keep your love to yourself
and... just get lost!
That's exactly what I'm doing.
I didn't ask you to love me in return
Say it, then you'll know.
- I don't need to
I love Jai! I love him, I love him!
A hundred per cent! And nobody
has a copyright to love
Was it your father who
gave birth to love?
I love you.
What's going on here? Is this a
boxing ring for the two of you...
to settle family scores? If you
want to continue studying here...
you must behave yourself. Else,
get out of this college
I've told you, Madam.
It's not Jai's mistake
It's my fault. - There's no
need to say anything more
I've let you off on several
occasions without any punishment
And this was your last chance, but
you're saved because of this girl
You will leave now.
We could hear the commotion!
Who faced the music?
What have you done, Anjali?
This was your chance to have
him thrown out of the college
Not yet. Let him stay for a while.
- What are you saying?
What's the point in
plucking a raw fruit?
Just see what Anjali does
Rahul...
What the hell are you doing?
Return my clothes to me!
What's love doing to me?
Give my clothes!
I'm losing my sleep, my
peace and my senses
Give my clothes, I say!
Don't go away from me...
come closer...
what's love doing to me?
I'm losing my sleep, my
peace and my senses
The earth reioices...
the skies celebrate
What place is this?
Where have we landed?
The earth reioices...
the skies celebrate
What place is this?
Where have we landed?
It's the season of youth,
you and I are together...
there's mischief in the air
Ours is such a lovely meeting...
come into my arms
A yearning, a daze...
this is a huge kick
What's love doing to me?
I'm losing my sleep, my peace,
my sense of time
Tis such a splendid moment,
a cool breeze blows
Our hearts are skipping
a beat, there's an aching
Tis such a splendid moment,
a cool breeze blows
Our hearts are skipping
a beat, there's an aching
You are the one I desire, you
are the one I think of...
even if you don't realise it
How will I tell you
about my state...
you may never believe me
I yearn, you're blissfully
ignorant...
I'm loving every moment of this
What's love doing to me?
I'm losing my sleep, my peace,
my sense of time
I will be dead. She has started
to walk in my dreams even.
What are you doing?
- I'm quitting college
I can't stay here anymore.
That girl's gone crazy!
You have no idea what she
has been doing to me!
If my folks get to know,
they're going to kill me!
You don't iump out of bed for
fear of the bedbug, do you?
If you're a real man, have the
girl thrown out of the college
But she's been following me around!
I love you... she says!
What can I do about a girl like
her? - Say I love you to her
What? Me? I could
sock your face for that!
Let alone fall in love,
Angarchand's sons don't...
...even look at girls!
Remember this.
To fall in love...
...Angarchand's sons need to be
born in another man's family
Yes, that'll take a
hell of a lot of time
How could you say I must love her?
- When did I say you must love her?
Don't! Don't ever!
- Then?
Pretense! A drama of love!
- What?
Don't you want those in Anpara to
go down on their knees to you?
What?
- It's the girl who approached you!
How can you let such a great
opportunity slip out of your hands?
I'd advise you to trap her in a
web of love to such an extent...
that there's no way out for her!
After that, all of them will plead
and beg at your father's feet!
Save our daughter's honour!
Please save her honour!
Lmagine! The nemound respect
you'll command in your family!
Think! Imagine!
Stop thinking! This
is time for action!
Lmagine! You and your father
will have your revenge!
Two birds with one stone! I
can feel the goose-pimples!
I hope that will not
create any trouble.
Never mind, it'll get okay...
- Not this
All this could create an uproar!
- But there ought to be an uproar!
There'll be fun only if
there is an uproar!
Now go and tell her what I told
you. - But what have I to say?
I'll bring a flower every
day to your hostel gate?
No, not flower! Make
that a rose! Simple!
It's not simple! You go
and say that to her
Angarchand's not my father! You
want the revenge, don't you?
Go and say it to her! Hurry up!
Excuse me, Anjali.
Could you come here
for a minute, please?
Just a minute.
What is it?
I couldn't sleep all day.
- All day?
No, I mean, all night. Sorry.
- I couldn't sleep all night either
Really? Was it because of me?
No, I couldn't get sleep. There
were a lot of mosquitoes in my room
It's your guts and sense of
humour that I really admire!
My rose.
Nothing.
Whether you believe me or not, I'm
telling you the truth today, Anjali
No girl as beautiful as you has ever
told me that she's in love with me
It's the first time such a thing
has happened to me. And it has...
You hear drums?
- Yes, drums in my heart!
And I thought, I ought to
share my feelings too
Anjali, I really like
you a lot. I love you
It's the beginning of our romance.
- Listen...
you can't say that and
get away so easily
I need to be convinced that you
are the speaking the truth
I need to make sure about
your feelings - Ok.
Swear it on your mother that
whenever I call you...
you will leave your
family and come to me
There's no hurry. Think twice. You
can let me know later, okay?
May I go now?
Take flower.
Let's go! She's bloody dangerous!
- But what happened?
She pushed me against the wall.
- But what did she have to say?
Say? She actually stung me!
Whenever I call you, you must leave
your family and come over to me!
I got to swear it on my
late mother! Am I crazy?
That's even better! Fantastic!
What's the problem with that?
Your mother's dead, isn't she?
She's not going to die again
She's not watching what you're
doing. Take it from me, it's a ploy!
Be one-up on her! Use a ploy on her!
Ask her to swear on her late mother!
What are mothers for anyway?
You swear on them when
they're dead, really!
What if she takes an oath?
- Okay, you take the oath too
No way, I'm Angarchand's son.
I never go back on my word
A mere word! It's not the
Supreme Court's verdict!
Call her before she calls you over!
When she leaves her
family and comes.
Her entire family will bow
to you! What do you say?
You're right.
- I knew it. Go on
Excuse me Anjali, one second, please
Have you made up your mind already?
You can take your own time
No, I've thought about it
and even made up my mind
You will also have to give me your
word. Swear it on your family
What's the big deal? I swear
it on my family...
whenever you call me, I'll leave
all of them and come over to you
Now you make the promise.
Give me your hand. Go on
Slowly but surely, you're
the one who stole my heart
And I didn't even get to know
Quietly, secretly,
you cast a spell...
and I didn't even get to know
We kept consenting
and disapproving...
secretly, we pined...
and the things it all led to
Slowly but surely, you're
the one who stole my heart
And I didn't even get to know
You are the one I dream
of every night
It makes me sigh wistfully,
it leaves me restless
I'm crazy about you...
I wish I were the glass
you held to your lips...
you know not
Slowly but surely, you're
the one who stole my heart
And I didn't even get to know
At your side, in your arms...
I always wish to be
Pangs of separation I do not want
to suffer, even for a moment
You are the one who possesses
my memories, my love
Yours is the scent that
lingers on my breath
You mean the life to me
Uncle... there's nothing between us
You're making a mistake. Come
on in, I'll explain...
Go and keep this inside first.
We'll talk later
Actually...
- I told you to keep it inside
We'll talk later. Get going!
What's on your mind?
I don't tell beggars
what's on my mind
Listen... if you mean well,
I will stand by you
I'll cut off the hands of those
who try to stand in your way
But if you are trying to
settle family scores...
I'll be the first one to pump
a bullet into your chest
That's what I'm out to do. Hit
me, if you have the courage
Damn you!
Let go.
What are you guys looking
at? Thrash him!
No one interferes!
This is between Angarchand
and the Anpara family!
Just pick up the corpse
when one of us dies
Anjali! Anjali!
What is it?
Your Uncle and Jai are fighting
it out like mad dogs!
Hurry up and come down. Else,
one of them's going to die!
Jai. - Don't dare look at her
or I will kill you.
Let go.
My foot, you will kill me! Bring
your dead father back to kill me!
I'm going to kill you!
- Calm down, Uncle...
You'll go home in pieces! Angarchand
will see the consequences!
I swear, take him away if you don't
want him to see dead at my hands!
Leave me alone!
His folks will be happy
to see him alive!
Let me go, Anjali! - I told you
there's nothing between us!
So why did you get into the fight?
- What was it that I saw?
I'm not blind!
What was all that?
Speak! What was it?
At grandma's behest, I...
- What?
It was meant to create a rift
between Angara's sons
I was just a puppet, Uncle. It's
grandma who holds the string
God Almighty!
That old woman's out of her mind!
And you listen to her?
What do you think Angara's sons are?
If they get the slightest of doubt,
they'll kill the two of you!
They'll bury you alive! The old
woman knows how powerful they are!
Do you want to know the truth? With
a little change in your destiny...
you'd have been born in
Angara's family, not ours
Your mother was in love with
Angarchand's eldest son, Balram
She even left her family
to marry him...
but your grandma wouldn't
let it happen
She had your mother forcibly
abducted from the wedding altar...
and got her married to your
father.
In the melee... your grandfather shot at Balram
But the bullet struck Balram's
mother. Angarchand's wife
She died. In retribution, he hacked
our father in broad daylight
And all this happened only...
...because of the stubbornness
of your grandmother!
You now want the same kind of
bloodshed for yourself all over again?
I'm on neither side now
But please don't tell everyone at
home about this and create a fuss
What'll happen if I tell them?
They'll either give you a thrashing...
or stop you from studying further.
But guess what will happen... when his folks get to know?
There will be bloodshed
lt'll all be over. Just
think about that
Who was it that dared raise
his hand at our brother?
Who dared to hit our brother Jai?
That brawl you got into! Your
brothers got to know!
They're out there, barking away!
- So now?
So indeed! You want to become
the hero of Anpara...
and your brothers, the villains!
They'll bury you in this very bed!
I saw the daggers in their hands!
They've come prepared for the kill!
What are you talking? Have you told
them that I'm here?
Am I crazy to say that?
Go out there and tell
them that I'm not here!
Are you mad? They'll clobber
me if I go down there!
Your mad brothers bash up anyone
they can get their hands on!
I'm running away now! That's it!
Run... for your lives! You too get lost.
There are madmen out there!
Save your lives! Run!
Who hit our brother?
Who was it? Where's he hiding?
Speak up, who hit my brother?
Speak up, or we'll carve you out!
Get him! He's running away!
Must be there, that wretch.
Stop. - Stop... where
are you running to?
Who has kept the door open?
Stop there!
Where the hell is he?
These college boys are difficult
to catch nowadays
Help!
Get him!
Why did you hit my brother? Speak up.
I did not. - Strong man, eh?
You hit my brother?
- You dare hit my brother?
Not me...
- Not you? So who was it?
Brother! He hasn't done anything!
Leave him alone!
Who hit you? Who?
- Speak up, who hit him?
I hit the man, he didn't hit me!
- Tell us his name!
If I tell you, you'll go there
and raise a bloody storm
Just give us the name
The name!
Veeru.
Brothers, listen to me. Don't
go there... please!
Find him, he must
be around somewhere
All right, go ahead! But kill
me before you kill him!
What will people say if
you even touch Viru?
That the elder brothers
had to rush...
...to avenge their kid
brother's beating?
I won't have any respect left!
Rather you kill me right now!
All right, if something of the sort
happens again, just hack him
And feed him to the vultures so
that everybody gets to know...
we're not cowardly men
Go to iail for that if you have
to. Only real men go to jail
But you mustn't spare him
Is there something
you wanted to say?
And without the boatman,
my heart trembles.
You didn't want to ask why I got
into a fight with your uncle, did you?
It wasn't my mistake. He said I
shouldn't meet you, not love you...
who the hell is he
to say that to me?
Even if the Gods order me...
I'm not deserting my love
Jai. There was nothing of the
sort you imagined there was
I'm not in love with you.
Whatever I said or did...
was all a falsehood
My love and my sweet words were
meant to be a big deceit
It was a game I started at the
behest of my grandmother...
but I got to know that she was doing
it only to settle family scores
I realised then, how disastrous
the consequences could be
So I have decided to put
an end to this pretense
Please, Jai... forgive me.
And also forget me
Hey, stop there...
you're through with your story?
Now listen to my epic!
Like hell you will lie to me! I was
the one who was deceiving you!
At my friend Lucky's behest.
To settle old scores and
so on and so forth!
And what did you think? That
I've fallen in love with you?
Are you crazy? Look at your face!
It's like a melon on a papaya tree!
And listen... what else did you
say? That I must forget you?
I need to think of
you to forget you!
Now get this into your
skull! I hate you!
I hate you a thousand times more
than you can ever imagine!
A thousand times more! Good bye!
The oar paddles across the waves...
Without the boatman...
...it causes an upheaval in my heart
Wake up!
I've done nothing...
what are you doing?
My sleep is ruined and
you're snoring away!
I haven't driven your sleep away.
I'm not a girl. But constipation.
Let me sleep in peace.
- It was your bloody idea!
I was happily doing my own thing...
and you stoked the fires
of love in my heart
Now when the smoke is rising,
how can you keep snoring?
But you told her that you're not in
love with her. End of the chapter!
Shove the book under your
pillow and go to sleep!
You want me to sing a lullaby
for you? In my guttural voice?
Love isn't about throwing
a tenant out of your heart!
Something's amiss?
- I can't get sleep
One minute, one minute...
you mean, when you shut your
eyes, you see that girl!
And when you open your eyes,
she disappears!
Right?
- Yes!
I know this disease very well.
It's a very dangerous ailment!
You're a hopeless case. You're...
What the hell are you doing?
- But why're you screaming?
I screamed because you screamed.
And why did you scream? I was scared!
I was wondering what would happen
when my brothers got to know...
that I've fallen in love.
And you landed here just then!
You're in love, why're you scared?
Raise the banner of revolt!
Go and marry the girl, I say!
Take her away to Dubai... - Shut up!
You talk any rubbish! One
can't decide these things in a hurry
I'll have to think about
so many things
So stand here and think about things.
I'll lie in bed... and think!
Tally ho!
Make sure you don't wake
me up when I'm thinking!
You? At this hour? How did
you get into the hostel?
I did my best... to hate
you. I really did
But... I couldn't, I don't know why
Did you also try?
- What?
To hate me?
I know, you tried.
And you also failed
I don't think we can
ever hate each other
So why don't we accept the truth?
I know you're in love with me.
But I want to hear you say it
It doesn't have to
be here and now...
I'll come tomorrow
Slowly but surely, you're
the one who stole my heart
And I didn't even get to know
What happened of her class?
I wanted to know about the same.
But couldn't get any clue.
Madam, can I meet Anjali Kashinath?
But she has left
- Where to?
Her folks came this morning.
They took her away
Listen...
Anjali has gone away deliberately
so that you don't meet her again
She asked her folks to take
her away and just left
She said that you mustn't
try to meet her ever again
She could've said that to my face.
I wouldn't have swallowed her
I'm going to meet
her now at any cost
Even if I have to go to Anpara.
- Anpara?
Yes, Anpara
You're right. You must go
and fight for your love
You're going with me.
- You've gone mad!
No way! You're going to set
a stack of hay on fire!
Just come with me!
That girl in red... The one there.
With long tresses.
What's this?
Adhesive.
- So much?
Must be for some painting
job. Why bother?
What has adhesive to do
with a painting job?
One more question and I'll
seal your lips with it!
Letter, ma'am
Looks like they're all upstairs.
Get me a ladder
Come soon, just see what is written.
Listen. If there's a
problem, just whistle!
You know how to whistle?
Shut up!
- I can inform your folks then!
They're the ones who'll perform
your last rites, isn't it? Go on!
Hold the ladder.
- Hurry up!
Shut up, will you?
- What are you standing on?
The ladder!
- Not the ladder. It's my hand!
I can't bear to see someone getting
beaten up... You better go.
Hmm. - What hmm. - I will die.
What will I say, where I was.
Before you only...
What happened?
- What happened?
The scene... it scared me
But it's a comic situation.
Why must you be so scared?
Well, it was a comic scene...
but I bit into my finger
instead of the wafer
Carnivorous girl... she
bites into fingers!
You... get the hell out of here! Go!
Give me some wafers first.
- Here you are. Go!
Now say that you love me.
- Shut up!
All hell will break loose if
someone sees you! Go away!
I'm not leaving! First
say that you love me
No, I don't!
- Lies, lies!
In that case, you'd have
told me yesterday!
You thought of professing
your love in the morning...
...and then chickened out
Look, I've taken the risk of
getting all the way here to see you
Unless you tell me that you
love me, I'm not leaving!
Someone is here. I had
seen it with my own eyes.
What are you saying? Won't we come
to know of someone arriving?
We are the watchmen here.
Don't trouble us.
I'll wait in the storeroom.
Unless you come and say I
love you, I'm not going!
Whatever happens! Okay?
It takes a good 3 hours
to go to the market...
...to buy the goods and come back.
I'm going to the storeroom!
- Have you gone mad?
Both of us will get killed!
- No, no! I got to go!
And... how am I going to kill time?
- Hide somewhere!
If you're bored, catch the
movie playing up there!
Please do not trouble.
How will we get out?
Has Raia arrived?
I wanted to ask this
only. Is there any news?
He told me that he would be here.
What happened?
It's nothing...
- Something wrong?
No, there's nothing.
- I'll take a look
No, where are you at fault?
You remain busy in parties
and with your friends.
Who left that storeroom open?
Is someone there?
- Yes, lady?
Lock that door. And
set the dogs loose
So that no one can either enter...
...or go out of here.
Imagine what would happen then
Both of us...
What happened?
- I don't know... nothing
Something wrong?
Why's that dog barking so much?
Look if there's a jackal in there!
Take a look!
A family of dogs!
Listen... there seems to be
someone behind those leaves
Ghost!
- Get lost, soon.
Over there! Get him!
Freeze! Or I'll make
a sieve out of you!
Scoundrel! Thief! You came to steal?
Is this your father's house?
You came to steal the utensils?
I wasn't here to steal, I swear!
My name is Lucky...
I had come to take the
notebook in Anjali's class.
Notebook? You iump a wall for that?
I didn't want to disturb you!
So I jumped over the wall!
Shut up! He's a real thief!
His eyes are like a frog's!
That's how they've always been! The
whole family has eyes like mine!
Don't let him go. Hand
him over to the police
Call Anjali here. Then hand me
over to the police, the navy...
Shut up... Anjali!
I'll be back
What happened, daddy?
- Do you know this boy?
Lucky... roll number 32
Yes, Lucky. My class-fellow.
- See? You believe me now?
They were handing me over
to the cops! - What for?
How would I know!
- What for, daddy? Why?
It's nothing. Go to bed!
May I go, Lucky?
- Sure, go on. Thank you
I'd have been turned into an
adhesive! - Shut up and get going...
or else you will be crushed.
Come out, I am saying that.
Stop. - Don't hit.
- Where are you going?
Whom were you looking for?
- No one...
I was only taking a leak.
- Right!
I'll make you leak from everywhere!
- No!
Anjali, I'm not leaving
unless you say it to me
Listen to me, please!
- Don't you want me to go away?
Please go away before
someone lands here!
Who did you come here with?
- No one, I swear
Where's your buddy?
Are you saying it or not?
- Jai, please!
All right, I'm staying put then
It's okay, it's all right...
- Very well, I'll say it!
I have no friend at all!
- Where's that rascal Jai?
I don't know any Jai!
- Watch out, frog!
One punch, and you'll stick to
the wall like a lizard!
I don't just love you, Jai...
you mean the life to me!
You're my father's son-in-law and
my grandma's grandson-in-law. Okay?
Is that enough?
What are you doing here?
- Nothing
So go on inside... hurry
You guys can fall in love, get
married, or even go to hell!
But why must I keep getting beaten
up for you all the time?
Who asked you to iump off that tree?
I didn't! The branch gave
way and I fell down!
Lucky for you, I fell down.
Or you'd have been caught...
and they'd have given you such a
thrashing, you'd be thorn to shreds!
You ought to be grateful
to me. Ungrateful man!
Well, well! Have you ever
acknowledged my favours?
What favours?
- You asked me to fall in love...
and I did, didn't I?
- So?
So what? When I took the risk of
falling in love at your behest...
it's your responsibility to protect
our love. Remember that
Which law says that? Take
a look at your father!
Every female is allowed inside,
including bitches, asses and mares...
but not womenfolk! Look in the
whole of India with a lamp...
but you won't find a grumpy
old man like your father!
And look at my father! He happily
died, three days after I was born
And look at your old man!
He's sworn to life!
He won't die and won't let die!
And he swears
you to something crazy everyday!
If you really want to marry that
girl, there's only one way out
Reform your brothers. Make
them cozy up to women
If even one of them gets romantic
and gangs up with us...
our iob will be done!
Marriage for me? At this age?
Have you guys gone crazy?
You're not as old as you think.
- Guys older than you get married
Really?
- That's not what he means...
Whatever my age, I can't get
married in this lifetime
I once set out as a groom to get
married, but it didn't happen
And I have no regrets. Nor do I
think I have taken a wrong step
But guess what I see whenever
I hear of a marriage?
My mother's body,
wrapped in a shroud
And our father, shackled and
being held by the police
Do you want me to forget all
that and still get married?
Sorry, brother. I didn't come
here to hurt your feelings
Neither does he plan on
getting married, right?
I spoke because I didn't want our
family to go without an heir.
Without an heir? As if we're
the last of the dinosaurs...
we face extinction and the world
won't get to see dinosaurs again!
Go on... get the hell out of here!
How dare you ask me to get married?
I'm a sworn celibate!
I recite the Hanuman Chalisa
everyday. Forty times!
I visit the shrine at Bairangpur
every month to pray...
that the destruction called woman
does not ever come to possess...
...my heart and soul!
And you want me to pray
for saris and blouses?
What will the Lord say? That
I've let Him down?
I'm going to kill you!
What are you doing?
- I'm wringing his neck!
Leave him alone, please! - Who the
hell are you to stop me? Who?
I'm his close friend!
- Close friend? You beggar!
Before I end his story, get the
hell out of here! Out you go!
Hail Bairangbali! The
Lord of Celibacy!
That's the wrestler.
Don't stand around to talk to him
If he asks, say we're here for
Lord Hanuman's oblations
Don't look at him...
- Hey... come here
You insist that we guys
ought to marry, isn't it?
Six years ago, this is exactly what
I was pestering my brothers with
For how long would they get off
both the sides of the bed?
And remember what dad said then?
Your brothers have decided... they are not getting married.
So why do you want to get married?
That's it. I decided
to do my own laundry.
But I'd never get married
And nor will I let anyone
in this family get married
Which means none of them
is going to lay an egg
What?
- I was talking about poultry...
Come in... you come here!
Look Murky...
- Lucky
Whoever you are, it's your company
that has done this to my brother
Look at me! If I see you with
my brother ever again...
I'm going to wreck your knee-caps
C'mon... come here!
Get some rat-poison and
feed it to these guys!
Kill the silly asses!
So long as your brothers live,
you can never get married!
Not you alone, they won't
even let me get married!
This is the end of your friendship.
We go our ways
Hey Lucky...
- Forget it
Where are you going?
Listen to me!
I know our union could bring
about an earthquake
But I'm not afraid. To be honest,
I just don't care
You have no idea how my
father brought me up
I was only five when my mother died
But my father and my brothers never
let me feel the lack of a mother
And yet, I'm willing to leave
all of them for your sake
Should I call you, will
you come to me?
Try me out
You will never leave me, will you?
What?
Come here
Don't be scared. I'm with you
Don't yell! I'm coming
I asked you to come here
You've turned out
to be a smart girl!
So the fish has taken the bait!
You are now truly grandma's girl!
He will behead Angarchand if
you ask him to... won't he?
He will, won't he? He's
crazy about you, right?
Yes...
- Yes!
I'll tell you what step you
must now take. Come with me
Jai! You have it made! Your
wedding band's on its way!
Jai, you have it made!
You can love anyone you want
to, and even get married!
Your rotten father and brothers
can't do a thing to you!
Who was it who got most worked up
when we suggested marriage to them?
Your brother Kishan! He can't open
his mouth before us anymore!
The so-called celibate!
- What's all this about?
Where does this brother of yours go
every Saturday and Sunday?
Bairangpur. Lord Hanuman's temple.
- No!
He goes not to Lord
Hanuman's temple!
He goes to Gangapur to meet someone!
Who?
- His wife!
He's been married for seven years
and even has two children!
He has kept them in hiding
You're talking about my
brother Kishan, right?
And he's no celibate, he's
the playFul Lord Krishna!
He goes not to the Lord's
temple at Bajrangpur
He goes to meet his wife. Gopi.
Who happens to be a
teacher in Gangapur
Lucky, if you're spinning a yarn,
you're really unlucky, I warn you!
I knew you wouldn't believe me!
I knew it... I have solid proof!
Look at this!
This is your brother Kishan. And
he's definitely not a celibate!
Moron!
This is the first sensible thing
you've done in your lifetime!
Wow! Brother Kishan!
What a smart game!
Here, Gangapur has arrived.
Let's ask there.
Does a school teacher
called Gopi live here?
School teacher?
- Yes
No. There is a lady called
Gopi who lives nearby
But she's not a school teacher.
- Is her husband's name Kishan?
No. Her husband's name is Murari.
- Murari? It's someone else
You always listen to some
drivel and drive me berserk
Let's go now...
- Hang on... one moment
Is this Murari?
Right. This is Murari indeed
And his wife's name is Gopi?
- Yes
But she's not a school teacher.
She trains children in dancing
One, two...
One, two, three, four...
One, two... One two, three, four...
Who is it?
- Before brother can arrive...
we'll produce her before father.
- Right!
Who is it?
Who?
- Sister-in-law!
Get up! Who are you?
This is your brother-in-law! Jai!
- Jai who?
Me... Hail sister-in-law!
- Sister-in-law? Who?
Aren't you brother Kishan's wife?
- Kishan?
No, I'm not Kishan's wife.
I'm Murari's wife
It's one and the same thing!
I'm sorry, your husband's name
is not Murari, it's Kishan
And I'm his younger brother Jai.
Where are the children?
I haven't seen them, but
they must be very cute!
Listen... where are you going?
- Children! I'm your Uncle!
Call me Uncle, please.
- Uncle!
Quiet! They're not my children.
They're here to learn dance
Set that child down... go on!
And get going... get out!
What are you doing, sis-in-law?
- I'm not your sister-in-law!
It's no good, sis-in-law.
The cat is out of the bag!
Kishan has told Angarchand the
truth!
I don't know any Angar...
nor am I any Kishan's wife.
Get going... get lost!
Sister-in-law!
Let me tell her the truth!
- All hell will break loose, Jai!
Lt'll be worse if I don't tell her
My poor brother won't get to see
his wife and children before dying
Speak softly... she might listen!
What are you doing?
What's the matter?
- Nothing, let's go
Something surely is...
- Nothing...
What were you saying? Tell me!
- Go on. Tell her
Sister-in-law, I'm sorry, I don't
have the permission to tell you
But there's no other way now
My brother has met with an
accident! - What happened to him?
He broke a bone in his tummy
- There are no bones in the tummy!
I mean, his legs are broken.
And he badly wants to see
his wife and children
I'll be back in a moment.
Don't go away!
Ok, bye.
Sir...
- Yes?
Is your name Kishan?
- Yes... who told you?
Where did you meet Kishan? Not
Kishan! My name is Murari!
You know my name, don't
you? Murari... okay?
I told them, but they
wouldn't believe me
Who wouldn't believe you?
- Brother
Whose brother?
- Your brother
My brother? - There was also
a toad of a guy with him
A toad of a guy... did
he wear this ear-ring?
Yes.
- Damn it!
Where did they go? - I showed
them the way to your house
What? My house?
- Yes. A right, left... and straight
My house... what harm
had I done to you?
I'll pull your guts out!
Why're you angry with me?
- Angry?
Did I ever tease your sister? Did
I misbehave with your mother?
Rotten scoundrel! Damn you!
Hurry up children...
Thank God you're all right
And they said you had
met with an accident
That you had broken limbs!
- What can be worse than this?
You've fallen in the hands
of these wastrels!
You boys ought to be ashamed! He's
right here, hale and hearty...
...and you said he had
had an accident!
May the worms get your tongue!
Dogs! Are you going to be happy
after ruining my family?
Fantastic! You're married
and having all the fun
And how about us? Have you
ever given a thought to us?
Let's go, Lucky. Let's
bring dad here!
And then we will see whether
this marriage happens or not.
Stop him, Gopi... stop him!
Brother-in-law, please stop...
- Don't stop me, sister-in-law
We're not staying here,
no matter what happens
Brother, say whatever you have
to only to father, okay?
You're my father's last mistake!
Have mercy on me... please!
You want to get married, don't you?
I'll get you married, okay?
Gopi... - A sister-in-law is
like a mother. How could you?
Dumbo! Not her!
I'll get you married to anyone
else you want, okay?
Not I but he wants to get married.
Whoever you say, blind
or crippled...
I'll get you married to
her, okay? I swear!
Really?
- Of course
You won't back out, will you?
- You don't trust my word?
One moment...
I swear it on my children.
I'll get you married to
the girl of your choice
Why're you hollering away? It's
enough that your father's crying!
Okay?
In that case... there's this
girl I'm in love with
What girl? I'd get you married
even to a tigress!
Who is she?
- She's very much there but...
Go on.
- She's from Anpara village
Grand-daughter of Laxmi Devi. Anjali
You promised me! You gave
me your word, brother!
No promise! It's all over!
And what are you watching?
Take the kids inside!
Laxmi Devi's family, eh? You're
playing games with me?
Find another girl! This marriage
is not taking place!
You want me to get you married, so
my kids will find another father?
Get lost!
- I must bring daddy here!
Listen... why do you keep dragging
dad into this mess?
Can't you let me breathe easily?
Couldn't you find another girl,
except this female ghost?
Are you or are you not
standing with me?
I'm not lying down now, am I?
But let me tell you...
if anyone except you, I and this
rat gets to know about this...
...marriage, I'll.
Will it cause trouble?
- Trouble?
I'll bust your eyeballs!
- Don't tell me!
We're headed for trouble.
- What happened?
Step aside... come
How was I to know that the two of
you would reach a compromise?
I told Shakti that Kishan
is already married
What? You told Shakti?
Moron! By now Dad must
have got to know!
Brother? - His eyes are open.
He could be alive.
Sister-in-law! Fetch some water!
Is it true?
From what I gather
You've tossed a live fish on
the burning sands, Shakti
If there is even an iota of
truth in what you say...
only three sons of Angarchand
will remain alive
I'll hack Kishan to pieces and
feed him to the vultures
And if what you say proves
to be untrue...
Angarchand will still have
only three sons alive
I'll give you the same treatment
I'm worse off than a badly who has
a scorpion crawling on his head!
Gopi, stuff the kids
in a bag. Let's go!
Shakti could get here with dad
and elder brother any moment
And when's that ass arriving
with the taxi?
If the taxi doesn't arrive
on time, we'll all be sunk!
Don't worry, brother. Everything
will be all right
Shut up!
I'm sitting on a frying pan and
you ask me not to squirm...?
Hurry up!
All this has happened
because of you!
Let me just get into another house,
then I'll turn on the music for you!
You're doing nothing to help!
Stop shouting now!
Hurry up, else we're all
going to be cremated!
The cab has arrived!
Hurry up! O God!
What's that in your hand?
- I made some sweetmeat
Sweetmeat? You mother...
- What are you saying?
I'm being stripped and you're
making sweets! Dump it!
Will you distribute sweets
at a time like this?
Why've you left all this here?
Gopi...
Gopi! Go on inside! Go!
Father?
Back... we're going back! Hurry!
God! Gopi...
Who are you?
I was going out to do something
important and...
I'm a strong believer
in auspicious timing.
I'm in a bit of a hurry
Have we met before? Who
is this elderly gentleman?
So you want me to tell you his name?
I only asked his name... why're
you gritting your teeth?
Is it a difficult name?
So you've forgotten
father and brother?
I see! So he's your father and
you're his son! Very nice!
But why're you creating
a fuss out here?
Worthless chap! Do you remember
now or do you want another slap?
One more slap may remind
you that you are Kishan!
I'm not Kishan.
- Are you not Kishan?
- I'm not, I'm not, I'm not!
You are slapping me
for refusing to say that I am not!?
If you are not Kishan,
land a slap on my cheek
Go ahead. If you are not Kishan,
give me a slap on my cheek!
Hit me!
Hit him... hit!
Take him and get the
hell out of here!
I'm sparing him because he happens
to be of my father's age!
Go away! Else, I won't
spare him either!
Go away... God! I'm running
out of patience!
Go away!
Balram! Jai!
Yes, father? Yes?
You idiots have been blind!
You never asked Kishan where
he went and whom he met!
I ought to have had the
whole information!
He's not setting foot in
this house ever again!
Very well, father
Even if he comes, he's not getting
in without meeting me
Even if it happens to be
in the dead of the night!
Very well, father
Hail Lord Bairangbali!
Lord of Celibacy...
To Thee I offer my obeisance's,
O Devotee of Lord Rama...
O Almighty Lord...
Why have you called all
of us here, father?
You boys are now perhaps beginning
to think that...
I'm ruining your lives
By not getting you married, I'm
sowing thorns in your lives
Is that true?
Father, why are you
saying such things?
Answer my question. Do you
really think like that?
No, not at all
I don't think like
that either, father
And what do you think?
No, father. The two of us
don't like that either
Talk only for yourself. He'll
speak for what he thinks
I haven't thought like
that so far, father
Which means you might start
thinking like that in the future?
No
In that case, I've begun to think
that I've made a very grave mistake.
...by not getting my sons married
When there was a proposal for
Shakti long ago, I had laid down...
...a condition
That Balram would get married
first and only then...
anyway, I withdraw
that condition now
Let him not get married,
if he doesn't want to
But the rest of you must get
married. You must, mustn't you?
And thus I have decided, that
Kishan will get married first
Why? What happened?
You will put the wedding necklace
around the girl of my choice...
...on an auspicious day
He's getting married?
Putting the wedding necklace
on another woman?
Let me see how he gets married
He's not doing it out of his own
will. He's being forced into it
His father has locked him up
and he's getting him married.
I swear to that!
And he's getting married too?
- Yes
Before he does that, he'll have
to see me and my children dead!
What are you doing? Listen!
This is getting worse!
Sister-in-law...
Listen to me, sis-in-law...
Sister-in-law... - Come on.
What will I listen to now? Who
do I have in the world anyway?
I'm here for you.
- Shut up!
Look at your face! Toad!
- Toad?
Sister-in-law... - My children
and I are doing to die!
Sister-in-law... what are you doing?
Please don't do something
rash! Sister-in-law!
I have to answer all the questions!
Please, sister-in-law...
I'll break open the door! I'm
telling you, I'll break it!
Here I come!
Won't you even let me change?
You're wrecked the utensils,
cursed chap! Damn you!
Balram...
we're going out for a while.
- Come on, dear...
The way he broke the pitcher!
Fantastic!
Brother, Gopi...
- Yes, she's going to whack Krishna!
Brother! Sister-in-law Gopi!
Hey girl... what do you think
you're walking into?
Stay out! Haven't you read
the signboard? Get out!
I'm not staying out! I'm
related to this family!
These children are part
of this family!
The sons in this family
are not even married!
So where did the kids come from?
She has gone mad!
No, I'm not mad. I'm your
son Kishan's wife, Gopi!
My brother's a respectable man!
If you utter a word against him.
We'll throw you out!
- Get lost!
Send my husband out first.
- Aren't you going away from here?
Kishan!
- Say I'm not in!
What will I say, where you've gone?
- Say I'm dead! Go on!
Coming, father!
Brother! It won't help
if you get scared!
Look at me... I'm
with you! Be brave!
There's no need to be scared!
Just do as I told you to!
Okay? Go on.
- No... you come with me... come!
What is the matter, father?
Are you not feeling well, son?
- I'm all right
Come here!
Is this your husband?
- Yes!
Look there. - Tell them!
That I'm your wife!
That you don't want to get
married a second time!
That these kids here are our own
children! Tell them, please!
What rubbish is she talking,
dad? Who is this woman?
That's exactly what I'm
asking. Who is she?
You don't know... no?
- No
You don't know? No?
Cheat! You don't know me? Don't
you know these children?
When you got to know you're getting
a new wife, you forgot all...
...about us!
Answer me... speak up!
Do you have any proof. A ring,
perhaps? Or a locket?
Yes, I do!
- What?
The wedding necklace. The
vermilion on my forehead!
And these two children!
Swear it on their heads that
they are not your children!
That I'm not your wife! If
even that's not enough...
where's your brother
Jai? Where is he?
There he is... hiding there!
Call him out and ask him;
he knows the whole truth
Jai! Come on out!
Yes, father?
- Come here
Do you know this woman?
- Brother-in-law...
at least you must admit
that you know me!
That I'm your sister-in-law,
that these are our children!
Tell them!
I've asked you a question,
Jai! Do you know her?
Yes, I know her
It's an old habit of hers to take
her children into families to...
...extract money
My God! - It's true.
I've seen her many times!
For him this sinful earning
seems to be everything.
Women like her must
go to the police!
Brother... why drag
the police into this?
What a shame! This wretched woman...
Brother! It'll be even more
shameful if the police arrive here
Why?
- Well, maybe they will suspect us
I'll see her off.
- I'm not going away!
Sinners! I'm not going anywhere!
Silence! Who knows whose bundles
of sin they are...
who knows what you're trying
to palm off to us!
Throw them in a well or the rivers!
Oh yes, that is what I will
do! To save my husband...
I'll strangle my motherly
instincts! Just you watch...
I'll dump them in the well of your
very own house. C'mon, come...
Come on...
Gopi, listen to me! Don't do it...
Give the child to me, Gopi.
You are my wife...
and these are our children!
I played this drama only
to save your lives
But I'm not scared
of anyone anymore.
Let them discover what they want to
Father... forgive me
I've been deceiving you
Please forgive me. Please pardon me
Filthy scoundrel! You want
me to forgive you? You cur!
Get up! Up, I say!
What did you think? I pretended
to get you married...
only to make you speak the truth!
Scoundrel!
You are his elder brother!
Stop your father... please!
Rascal... Out of my way, girl!
Please let him go!
- Lay off! Stay away!
Shakti, drag her away! You
dare deceive your father!
I'm going to kill you! And
you want me to pardon you?
When the handle of a sword snaps,
it's your own hand that is injured!
You dirty scoundrel! Get up...
I'm not going to spare you!
Insolent! How dare you
hold father's hand?
No one has dared hold
his hand, or stop him
Go and ask for his forgiveness.
Fall at his feet and apologise!
I've made no mistake for which I
must seek forgiveness from father!
What sin has brother
Kishan committed...
...to get beaten up so mercilessly?
He got married, he has two innocent
little children...
is that the reason?
If you still think I've
done wrong, kill me...
but I cannot stand by father
in this injustice!
What do you need us for, father?
Why're you taking care of us?
To get beaten up by you?
Or get into brawls with
people for your sake?
You don't need sons, what
you need are thugs!
You need not your flesh and
blood, you need monsters!
What are you watching, wastrels?
Throw the two of them
out of the house!
I don't want sons who are
not loyal to their father!
They no longer exist for me!
Ask two people to lend a shoulder
to carry my bier...
but don't ever ask them
to touch my body!
Get the hell out of here!
Go away, you scoundrels!
Henceforth, Angarchand shall
have only two sons
After my death, don't even let
them get a glimpse of my body!
Broken! Angarchand's arrogance
is shattered!
Ruin what is left of Angarchand!
Finish him!
Finish that wretch off, too.
Angarchand's sons are
enough to finish him
Let the fireworks continue.
Let there be a celebration!
How did you get here?
- I walked in through the door
You talk too much, don't you?
What have you come here for?
I have come to meet Anjali.
What have you to do
with my daughter?
That's something I'll tell only
her. Please call her here
Anjali, as I promised, I've left
everything and come to you
My family and home... everything.
You must fulfill your promise now
Hey! What rubbish are you talking?
You walk into our house
and play with our honour?
You keep out of this.
Let me talk to him
My child, tell him, that you
are not in love with him...
that the love was only a pretence!
Also tell him that even if his
father comes at begs at our doorstep.
...you will still not
change your decision!
What did you think? That my
child would go away with you?
She was only taking revenge
from you! - That's a lie!
Anjali, tell them that
this is not the truth!
Why are you quiet? Tell them that
we're in love with each other!
Tell them what we have decided!
Now get the hell out of here! Or
you'll be crippled... get out!
You don't need to be afraid
of anyone. I'm with you
Separate them...
- Let her go!
Get inside. I'm going to kill you!
I'm going to kill you!
Don't dare touch!
Your father's going to carry
your corpse away from here!
What are you doing?
- Go away!
Or I'll take you apart
with my bare hands!
Oh get lost!
I only came to see whether
my love would stand by me
After what happened, I can see
from your face that
I needn't say anything!
I will come and take her away.
Do what you can to prevent me!
Will you go to meet him?
Will you? Speak up!
Yes, I will go! A thousand times!
I'll go to him every
time he calls me!
You will go to meet him?
- Wait, let me deal with her
Ma, stop it!
- Let me go...
Anjali, you go inside.
What do you want to do? Kill her?
I told you not to interfere!
- You don't interfere!
Stay away!
Use your common sense!
This is all Ma's doing!
She's the one who instigated
Anjali. She's the one to blame!
Blame her... ask her!
What happened now? What?
Anjali, you come inside
Don't cry
Viru did right by stopping you!
What good will it do by
beating up the girl?
What had to happen has happened.
Now get the girl married
at the earliest
Make her see reason and bring
her back to the right path
Keep your advise to yourself!
It's because of your advise
that we have to see this day!
Why? All I said is that we ought
to plant a girl in that family
When did I say that we must send
the girl from your own family?
Enough, let's forget about this
and think of the future
At the earliest possible,
find a suitor for Anjali
She must be given away in marriage
in not more than a fortnight
In a fortnight? Am I going to
pluck the suitor from a tree?
Pluck him from wherever you have to!
It's just that he ought to be...
of an equal status and
command equal respect!
You're speaking as if I carry
such guys under my arms
As if I need to flap my
arms and they'd pop out!
Well? What have I done?
In that case, let's get the suitor
from your flapping arms
Dr Sattu... Satyendra. Your son.
What's wrong with him?
Yes, what's the problem with that?
- No, there is no problem...
We have no problems either.
Let's just go ahead
Actually, Jai has issued a threat
that
he'll do whatever he wants to
I hope he doesn't bump
off me and my son
No, he won't do anything
Don't ask me, my love, what
state my passions are in...
Robbed... plundered...
is my precious modesty
Why ever did I...
set out for the marketplace?
I met this faithless youth...
who asked me for my heart
He took me for a naive belle and
started forcing himself on me
How I fought back...
it was an eye-opener
I wonder why the treacherous
knave picked on me
Robbed... plundered...
is my precious modesty
Why ever did I...
go anywhere near his lair
He held my arm and said,
come closer, darling
I felt shy to begin with,
and then I was scared
When he reached for my finger,
I freed my wrist
That was the first night, I
couldn't realise what he was upto
Plundered, robbed...
You've been thrashed and thrown
out of the house, isn't it?
But you needn't worry. I'm with you
If there's anything you want,
just let me know
Give the gentlemen two cups
of tea! In my account
If we need anything from your
account, we'll let you know
That'll be too late. We have
an old score to settle
So let's settle it now.
- That's what I'm here for
Some thugs are beating up your
brothers in the cattle market!
Hurry up! Else, they'll get killed
Who sent you here?
- Laxmi Devi
Come on out, you rats!
You guys are holed up here
after sending hired goons?
Come on out!
Hey old hag... you think you're
going to make us brothers fight?
Remember, even if we brothers
have a thousand differences...
if someone casts a stone at us,
your sons won't have heads on their shoulders!
And we won't hire thugs. We'll
come here on our own...
and settle the issue! I'm telling
you that. You get it, old hag?
Go away, you dog...
Wait!
You are a loudmouth indeed!
What did you say?
If someone casts a stone at you,
my sons will be beheaded?
In that case, I'll have your
brother garlanded instead!
Do you know why your brother
spat in your father's face...
and walked out of the house?
To marry my grand-daughter!
I'll make sure...
that your brother puts the
bridal necklace around my...
...grand-daughter's neck!
And that necklace is going to
strangle your father to death!
Go and tell your father,
the burnt out ember...
to stop it, if he can!
Mother, what nonsense
are you talking.
Whom did you ask
before saying that?
My daughter and that
beggar? Never!
If you're going to decide
everything on your own...
why are we here with you?
You morons will always
get things wrong
Will I let the marriage happen
just because I've said so?
She'll marry the suitor
you choose for her
In that case, why did
you tell lies to them?
I did.
If I didn't, all our efforts till
now would have gone down the drain
Now watch their story
coming to an end!
Command me, father
Do I bring him alive or dead?
Stop there!
Whose permission did you take
to set foot on this land?
We are not here to fight.
Have you brought a match then?
Get going.
- We always heard that Angarchand...
never turned away anyone who
came asking for his help
Damn you guys... get
the hell out of here!
Hold it, Shakti... Let them come
My respects
Please forgive us, Angarchand
Please don't harbour any will
for the mistakes we have made
Please forget everything
- Damn it!
Your son had come to our mother,
asking for help to marry my daughter
And mother only wants to
defeat you. All the time
So she reiected the match
we had decided for the girl
My mother is now insisting...
that she will have my daughter
married to your son at any cost
However, we want her to marry the
one we have fixed her wedding with
If our mother or your son still
try to disrupt this wedding...
we'll have to do something about it
You decide now...
- You will have to do nothing
I'll be the one who will
do what needs to be done
You want this marriage to
take place, isn't it?
I'll make sure she marries the
suitor you have chosen for her
Father...
- Shakti!
When someone's lying on the floor,
you have to bow to pick him up
I'd take defeat from anyone! But
if I'm defeated by my own son...
I'll be ashamed of myself!
Where's your father's
respect and honour?
He was so proud of himself!
But only to defeat his son, he will
go and guard someone else's wedding!
Is he a landlord or a watchman?
- That's enough...
Brother, you had to
loose your head now only?
Could you suggest a better time?
I could wrap your legs
around your neck!
I'm already in trouble and...
here she comes!
But what he want?
And have Anpara's daughter
married? Tell me!
Madam Gopi, your yelling is
getting to be too much!
Jai, if you're going to sit
here and listen to him...
you might as well do
it all your life!
We must go there and
stop the wedding!
Whether we have to take on
a demon or your father!
You tell me, you want
to marry that girl or not?
Who's this so late in the night?
My sons and your father
have got together
But nothing means more to
me than Anjali's happiness
And thus I, an elderly woman,
appeal to you...
you must surely come there
and tie the wedding necklace around her neck
It is in this hope that I will
dress my little girl as a bride...
and send her to the wedding altar
Please preserve my honour
I know what my mother
must've said to you
And what do you think?
Is she really going to
get you married to her?
She only wants you and your father
to fight between yourselves
And that is why she came
here at this late hour
It wasn't to get you married to her
Maybe you don't know...
...but my mother is very much
a part of the conspiracy
Just as she came to you to ask you
to tie the wedding necklace...
my brothers went to your father,
to seek his help...
at my mother's behest.
- This is a new ploy!
When they saw that you're going
to get married to her...
they're using new tactics!
- We know how to get the wedding done get going!
- Get lost!
Bloody toad! One punch and
you'll be flattened out!
What are you doing? Get out!
- Listen to me...
Hear me out, Jai!
- Get out!
I haven't revealed all this to you
because I'm worried about you
It's the girl I'm worried about.
The one who's part of my family
She asked me to warn you...
so that you wouldn't fight your
father and cause each other's death!
Else, she's not going to live
You want to die?
Get out of the way!
Run me over! So you can all win!
Whom are you out to defeat, father?
You're going to guard their
wedding, so you can defeat me?
Which son has ever won glory
by humiliating his father?
Won't you get out of the way?
- I won't!
You will have to hear me out!
They're plotting to
deceive you, father!
Don't give them any help...
- Balram!
Rather than talk to him, run
him over with the car.
Let's get going!
But hear me out at least!
I'm telling you that I'm not
going there, father. I'm not!
You mustn't go there either You
mean the world to me, father!
I let you go once,
because I loved you
But don't put me to anymore tests.
Father means the world to us also
Which is why we will go there and
make sure the wedding takes place
If you get there and try
to disrupt the wedding...
I can even take your life to
make father keep his promise
This is Angarchand's son Balram
speaking to you...
is that understood?
I'm the same father's son!
But if this is the case...
I'll prevent the marriage
from taking place!
Greetings. - Who is that?
My sister-in-law and
my brother-in-law
Welcome...
Who are they?
The chief from the neighbouring
village. With his wife
Welcome
Stand right here! And don't budge,
unless I ask you to!
Don't waste time. Get
those vessels out!
Hey... wait there
Balram, check out who they are
I'll take a look, don't bother.
That's how they are...
latecomers!
I'll take care of them.
- Hurry up
Who is it? Gangatai?
Go on... Quick!
Why're you so late?
- I couldn't find huge vessels
All right... Babubhai... go ahead
Hurry up.
So you're here, too?
Let the marriage take place.
You'll see then...
Come.
I'm glad we covered our faces.
Else, we'd have been beaten up
Always cover your face, you
rascal... - Quiet, brother!
Stand up! Why're you sitting?
- Who asked you to sit?
Sit quietly, pal.
They're not serving a feast here,
bro! Get to your feet!
What are you doing?
Where to? Come on, quick!
And don't make a noise!
Damn this loincloth!
Go and stand by the toilet.
I've drawn up a plan
Just stand by me. Okay?
Go on! Hurry!
What are you doing, Uncle?
- Standing by you
Remain standing. I'm leaving!
Stay here, no one must
get in from here, okay?
They're all very tense.
Anything could happen
I don't think he would take
the risk of coming here
Angarchand's keeping a strict vigil
If Jai lands here, Angarchand's
going to slit his neck!
You're out of your mind? You're
guarding a closed door!
Come here!
Guard this place... no
one must get through!
Sister-in-law, I hope there
won't be any trouble?
There will surely be trouble!
Jai's a very dangerous boy
Come here... quick!
- What? Is there trouble?
No, not yet. But who
knows about tomorrow?
Really?
- Come here, come
Don't be afraid, I'm with you.
Wet your throat, if you wish to
With what?
- Rum, whiskey... we have it all
We're all drunk.
- What if somebody finds out?
Nobody will get to know.
I'll send my brother-in-law,
he'll handle it
No, I don't want to...
- Yes, say that to him...
he'll force you and you
can gulp down a drink
I'll send him over... have patience
Brother-in-law! Come here!
There's a problem...
- What is it?
Nothing... you needn't yell
It's not so serious.
- So what is it?
The groom's getting the blues.
Because of the marriage
In his tummy.
- What's in his tummy?
What can be there?
He wants to go to the loo.
Is this the time for such things?
Can't he control it?
- How can he?
What if he wets his pants?
He's feeling shy... come and help, please
Why don't you take him to the loo?
- How can I?
There are women there.
An elderly man like you
can make them see reason
He's going to refuse, but you must
insist that he goes to the toilet
lmagine how nasty it'll look...
...if it happens in the
middle of the ceremony!
Nasty, right? So go on!
Come on.
- I don't want to do it
Do it right now... the pressure
will increase later
Nobody will get to know. Hurry up!
- But I don't want to...
Come with me, come...
Over there.
- But I don't want to do it
So what's wrong? Everybody does it!
Everybody does it?
- Yes, we do it early in the day
Ask the women to move there for
5 minutes... it's an emergency
Please come...
- Quick!
Hurry... there's water in there.
Get it over with quickly,
I'll stand right here
Won't you come in with me?
- Why must I?
To keep me company.
- No way! Go on inside!
Company!
Bad tummy, I see
Oh, you are here.
Where's the groom?
He's in the loo and
you're keeping guard?
The auspicious hour is passing
by, they're waiting for you
Have patience, the boy has a bad
tummy. Let him feel relieved
There'll be a flood at the altar!
- I'll handle the flood
Go outside, my wife's waiting
for you at the dining-hall
Right ahead, the room there?
- With your hands down... go
Why are you pushing?
Son.
Papa...
- My son... where are you?
Have you finished yet?
Sit down, dear
You chant some real good
mantras and really well at that.
Come, son.
Where's the groom's father?
Take his blessings
Look... it's Jai!
Put down that wedding necklace!
Put it down!
Set it down...
- Hold it. We're not stopping him
Let Angara stop him.
We mustn't interfere
Your son is here...
to put the wedding necklace around my grand-daughter's neck!
What sort of a man are you?
The whole world believes...
that Anpara never goes
back on a promise
If that is really true, you
must slit your son's throat!
Shakti, Balram... what
are you waiting for?
Can't you still see what's on
this woman's mind, father?
She didn't enact this drama
to have us married
She wanted us father and sons
to fight and kill each other...
that's the only thing she wanted!
I came here only to make
you realise the truth!
I have no intentions of defeating
you and marrying her
Forgive me
My father had once had
your wedding stalled
And it's my turn today
I can't give death to my father
to grant you a new life
Without my father's blessings and
approval, we cannot live together
Wait!
Put the wedding necklace
around her neck
Put it around her neck, I say
Only if father says
I know how father feels.
Do it without any fear
If you're really Angarchand's son,
put the necklace around her neck!
Snatch that necklace from him!
- Give it to me...
I have the necklace!
- Don't let anyone get you!
Here it is... on this woman!
- This is mine!
Get out!
- Gotcha!
Here you are... run
away with it! Run!
Jai!
You're old enough to be my father
and you're angling for me, rascal!
Shameless man!
Give that wedding necklace
to me! Give it!
What are you waiting for,
morons? Pick it up!
Jai! Come here!
Up there!
None of them must get
anywhere close to it
Without the wedding necklace,
the marriage cannot take place!
Get him! Catch him! After him!
Don't let him escape!
This has to do with the
honour of my family
If you wish to get to
my grand-daughter...
you'll have to finish all of us
No.
How much more of enmity, grandma?
Please forget everything
and accept our wedding
If you can't give us your blessings,
at least forgive us, father
We'll make a world of our
own someplace far away
No, you're not going anywhere.
Come here...
touch father's feet and
take his blessings
Gopi, here's our chance.
Let's touch father's feet
and take his blessings!
Come to me, my children.