- Hey, what's up?
MKBHD here on SuperSaf TV.
- What's up guys?
This is Jerry Rig on SuperSaf TV.
This is Gaurav, a.k.a.
Technical Guruji on SuperSaf TV.
- Hey, it's iJustine here on SuperSaf TV.
- What's up guys?
This is Austin Evans on SuperSaf TV.
- Super, SuperSafilicious.
- What's up guys?
It's Jaime Rivera from
Pocketnow here on SuperSaf TV.
- Hey there guys, it's
Mr. Q from Raqami TV here
on SuperSaf TV.
- What's up guys?
This is Michael Fisher on SuperSaf TV.
- Hey guys, Jenna Ezarik
here on SuperSaf TV.
- What's up guys?
I'm Tom, The Tech Chap on SuperSaf TV.
- Hi, I'm Michael Josh,
your gadget matchmaker
on SuperSaf TV.
- What's up guys?
This is David on SuperSaf TV.
This is Jon Rettinger back on SuperSaf TV.
- Hey guys, this is Colonel
Singala here for SuperSaf TV.
- What's up guys?
Saf here on SuperSaf TV.
And it's the one you've
all been waiting for,
the end-of-year
SuperSaf-Style collaboration
where we find out which 2023 smartphones,
some of your favorite
YouTubers choose to use
and are taking with them to 2024.
Now as always, there will
be two parts to this video.
In this video, we will be
looking at just smartphones.
But in the next video,
we'll have a bit of a rewind
and look at the best tech of 2023,
not including smartphones.
If you want to be one of
the first to see that,
then be sure to subscribe
and hit that bell icon,
so you don't miss it.
Right, to kick things off,
which smartphone do I choose to use?
Well, I have two sim cards,
one in an iPhone and
one in an Android phone.
The iPhone, it's very, very simple.
It's the big one, it's
the iPhone 15 Pro Max.
For me,
this still has the best and
most consistent camera package
for photos and videos.
Performance has been
great with the A17 Pro.
Excellent battery life
and finally, finally USB type C,
so I don't have to carry
around multiple cables,
especially with my Android smartphones.
And now my Android smartphone does change
throughout the year,
depending on what I'm reviewing.
But the device that my sim
card keeps going back into,
was actually one that
released early in the year
and that is of course the
Samsung Galaxy S23 Ultra.
Now, yes, it looks just
like the S22 Ultra.
But the fact that it still
holds up almost a year on,
is a testament to how good it is.
It's a great all-rounder
with excellent cameras.
The best extended zoom on any smartphone.
And this year, we had the
8 Gen 2 across the board,
no split between Qualcomm and Exynos.
That's me, let's see what
the others have chosen.
- What's up guys?
This is Austin Evans on SuperSaf TV.
My favorite smartphone of this year,
is a really clear and obvious choice.
You saw it a mile away.
It's the iPhone 15 Pro.
Honestly, this phone is incredibly solid
in every possible way.
I mean that.
Not only is the build quality terrific,
we finally got USB-C.
And for me, I spend a
lot of time using this
as my main shooter,
not only for photos but also for video.
And the fact that I
can walk into an event,
or pretty much anywhere I'm
going with just this phone
and capture all the content I
need, is such a game changer.
The iPhone have always
been good for video,
but the screen, the performance,
like there's basically nothing
I can really complain about
with this
and that is an incredibly
impressive thing.
So I love the Z Flip,
but honestly, the iPhone's beginning
to become my main gadget
like period, right now.
- What's up guys?
This is Michael Fisher on SuperSaf TV.
Saf, you ever think of doing
this round-up at a time of year
when I'm not utterly fried
and completely insane
with exhaustion?
No?
Fine.
What smartphone do I use?
All of them.
But hinges are preferred
and in that category,
the OnePlus Open is the one I would choose
if you made me pick just one
in the large-format category.
And in the flip-phone-clamshell category,
the Motorola Razr Plus,
or on your side of the ocean,
the Razr 40 Ultra, I think.
That's what the thing is,
the nicer one, the red one,
the leather one.
And I carry them together,
because I'm just that perverted.
And I don't have either
one with me right now,
because I'm using other
phones I would rather not use,
so I can do my job.
Thanks for the shade by the way.
- What's up guys?
This is Gaurav, a.k.a.
Technical Guruji on SuperSaf TV.
And my pick for this
year's smartphone is this,
the all new Samsung Galaxy Z Flip5,
especially in this new
bespoke yellow color option.
Now this phone is quite an
improvement from the last year's,
because now what we have
is a full immersive screen
on the outside,
capable of running almost
any app that you want.
The phone feels fresh.
Now with the zero-gap hinge,
I mean the form factor is quite improved.
And considering it's a small, tiny phone,
good for all the fun,
good for all the eyeballs.
And I mean this is my pick for this year,
the all new Samsung Galaxy Z Flip5.
- What's up guys?
It's Jaime Rivera from
Pocketnow here on SuperSaf TV.
It has been a great year for phones,
but if I had to pick only one,
it would be the iPhone 15 Pro Max.
Sure, it's got the looks,
new materials and more powerful telephoto,
but what I've liked most is performance.
I've used iPhones for years as a B-camera,
but LOG video combined with
that Blackmagic Camera app,
has made me a believer in a
phone becoming my A-camera
at some point.
Same thing with gaming
where the words console quality,
have been tossed around
a lot with smartphones.
But this is the first phone
to actually pull it off.
I think the word Pro fits
the name now more than ever.
Saf, again, thank you
so much for having me.
- Super, SuperSafilicious.
Hey!
Hey guys, this is Colonel
Singala here for SuperSaf TV
and welcome to my favorite
smartphone of 2024.
It's the OnePlus Open and close.
Open and close is back.
Yes, the OnePlus Open,
this is the most freshest phone ever.
Because you know what?
I can open and close,
plus we have that very sexy camera bump
and this very nice display of
faux leather made from petrol.
I love petrol.
Anyway, this phone is
smooth, it's vibrant,
big screen, great camera,
great for multitasking,
so I can (indistinct) and enjoy myself.
So Colonel Singala signing out,
open and close.
(Colonel Singala laughs)
Take it!
- Hi, I'm Michael Josh,
your gadget matchmaker
on SuperSaf TV.
You know, I love my iPhone.
And for most of this year,
I've been rocking the iPhone 14 Pro Max.
Of course, last September,
after the iPhone event,
I switched to the 15 Pro
Max in natural titanium.
The cameras on this phone are excellent,
but I especially love this
brushed titanium finish.
It's lightweight and
even matches my Oura Ring
and Apple Watch Ultra 2 with
my titanium strap from Nomad.
- Hey there guys, it's
Mr. Q from Raqami tv here
on SuperSaf TV.
Another year, another wrinkle.
You see, I'm a big fan
of the Samsung Fold5.
However this has taken over.
(taps)
This is the OPPO Find N3.
You see, I love how slim this is.
I love the sharp edges,
just the flat surface is really awesome.
It's got a really lovely screen as well.
Plus of course, open it up
and then you can see
that splash in your face.
Guys, the software on
this is pretty awesome
when it comes to multitasking.
I can go ahead and just open
up loads of different apps
at the same time
and see them basically full screen.
And it's cheaper than the Fold5.
Now, when it comes to an iOS device,
obviously, we're going
to have to choose this,
the iPhone 15 Pro.
Not the Pro Max,
because I'm actually Team Mini.
This is a pretty nice phone.
Why?
First of all, the titanium
little rounded edges,
just feel really nice to hold in the hand.
It definitely feels lighter as well.
Also, don't forget that we've got USB-C,
which means that finally
we can use one cable
to rule them all.
Guys, those are my two devices.
Boom and boom!
All right?
Take care.
(air whooshing)
- And just as I was editing this video,
we have hit 2 million subscribers.
Thank you to everybody for subscribing.
If you haven't already, do
consider joining the 2 million.
Let's get back to the video.
- Hey, it's Justine here on SuperSaf TV.
So the phone that I
have been using in 2023,
other than my iPhone 15 Pro Max,
yeah, I know,
I mean it's still a surprise like, "Hi,"
I have an I in front of my name,
I am who I am, just let me be,
the Pixel 8 Pro.
I have been loving this phone so much.
My sister and I actually did
a really fun livestream review
with Google this year.
So that was a lot of fun to do.
But I've really been loving the phone.
Not only do I just love the color,
but just this design,
it just feels different, it feels unique.
And I've always been a huge fan
of the way that the Pixels look.
And of course, it's deep
integration with Google
and all of the things that they're doing
with their AI initiative,
I am so here for it.
- Hey guys, Ashwin from
C4ETech on SuperSaf TV
and my favorite phone this year
has got to be the Nubia Z50.
Well, technically, it did
launch five days before 2023,
but I got it this year
and it's the one that
surprised me the most.
An 8 Gen 2 for 300-something
dollars, right around launch.
I went in with very tempered expectations,
but what I ended up getting,
was a solid phone I enjoyed using.
It even had a unique 35
millimeter equivalent lens,
paired with a solid sensor
with good software, a very
ergonomic form factor,
a faux leather back
that let you actually use the phone naked.
I mean this phone, the Nubia Z50,
I feel it's the perfect example
of a product punching way
over its weight class.
- What's up guys?
This is Jon Rettinger back on SuperSaf TV.
Another year has gone by
and I'm here to tell you
what my favorite smartphone
that I used all year is
and it's two phones.
On one hand, it is the iPhone 15 Pro Max,
'cause it's the iPhone,
the sort of the best of everything.
But the other phone
that's been in my pocket
since it came out
that I think is going to
be my phone well into 2024,
my sweet foldy boy, the OnePlus Open.
I love the aspect ratio,
I love the screen, love the technology.
It's not perfect,
but it's really close
when it comes to the world of foldables.
- What's up guys?
This is Jerry Rig on SuperSaf TV.
And for the past 13 years,
I've been an Android user.
But I decided to give iPhone a chance
and I have been doing so
for the past three months.
However, I'm switching back to Android.
Very long story short,
I can get more done on
Android with less taps
and I can schedule text
messages on Android,
which is important to me and
not a feature the iPhone has.
- What's up guys?
This is David on SuperSaf TV.
And I don't really have
a daily phone that I use.
I try to switch into whatever phone
that I'm doing a video on next.
But I will say that one phone
that I keep thinking about wanting to use,
is the Google Pixel Fold.
Its shape just kind of reminds me
of a Moleskine notebook in the best way.
And it's just so nice
to have Pixel cameras
and all that entails on a folding phone.
It's something I feel like we
all just have always wanted
if only the battery life
didn't suck as much as it did.
Maybe they'll do better with the next one.
- Hey guys, Jenna Ezarik
here on SuperSaf TV.
And for my 2023 smartphones,
I've been rocking the iPhone
15 Pro Max in natural titanium,
as well as the Google Pixel 8 Pro.
I love having the five-time telephoto.
I love all of the AI features
and best take on the Google.
And I'm always rocking an iPhone.
So there you have it.
That's what I've been rocking
as my main devices in 2023.
- What's up guys?
I'm Tom, The Tech Chap on SuperSaf TV.
Now obviously, there's been a
ton of great phones this year.
But for me, what I've been
carrying in my pockets,
well, there's two.
This guy, this is the OnePlus Open,
which I reckon is the best foldable phone,
you can buy right now.
I absolutely love this thing.
And also the iPhone 15 Pro Max,
which I'm recording this
on in 4K cinematic mode.
I just wish there was a 4K 60 mode,
so I can then slow it down afterwards
to get those nice slow-mo shots.
But yeah, mostly for video
and also the ecosystem,
the iPhone's been my main phone this year.
- Hey, what's up?
MKBHD here on SuperSaf TV.
So we're talking smartphones.
Favorite phone of the year for me,
there's a lot to pick from.
I think we've seen all of
them come out by this point.
And I think my favorite one is the one
that I'm going back to daily driving
after testing all the other phones,
which right now for me is the Pixel 8 Pro.
Lot of software features on this one.
(Marques giggles)
It's not really about the hardware,
it's got nice hardware too.
But it's so much software
to the point where if you live in a region
where not all of the software
features are enabled,
it's a notably worse phone.
But I live in a region
where I do have all the software
features and they're great.
So I like this phone a lot.
- So there we have it,
the smartphones
that some of your favorite
YouTubers choose to use,
2023-24 edition.
What are your favorite
smartphones of 2023,
the ones you choose to use?
Drop them in the comments below.
Remember, part two of this video,
the best tech of 2023
will be coming very soon.
If you want to see that first,
then do subscribe if you haven't already.
As always, a huge thanks
to all of my friends
for taking part in this video.
Yet again,
this is the ninth year running
that we've had this series.
And God willing, insha'Allah,
we will have the big 10th-year
anniversary next year.
So stay tuned for that.
If you want to see my top five
favorite smartphones of 2023,
that video will be linked here,
as well as a previous
collaboration linked here.
Thanks for watching.
This is Saf on SuperSaf TV
and I'll see you next time.