it's not like you know here's the word
here's the meaning what
[Music]
how many is visual on Tulsa we know that
we got our English from the British
people but we Indians are very smart so
we made a few changes in the language so
that we could call it our own so today
we are getting our friends from BuzzFeed
UK to guess some of the Indian slang
what do you know about Indian slang do
you know anything at all I don't know
any Indians like Indian origin but I
would say I don't think I know much
about slang yeah I don't really know
anything about Indian style
so this should be interesting so let's
start here is the first leg cheater [ __ ]
she took home cheater cheater [ __ ] it
sounds dirty like a guy that's a cheetah
cuz you're a dick like you know Sochi
event and maybe it's like a really
intense game of badminton a [ __ ] is a
chicken I don't know bad chicken a
naughty chicken a cheater co-op just
means somebody who who cheats so let's
see you guys are playing a board game
and then somebody cheats
Oh shady okay I would just pull that
person Jamie why is it got the word [ __ ]
at the end no idea it's a slang I mean
it gives a lot of emphasis it makes it
very very very interesting words next
chumming that's cute
chumming CHUM's are your friends come in
like you're vibing with the friends
you're hanging out with your friend
you're sitting down on the couch yeah
you're watching an episode of your
favorite TV show and you just you know
you come in no oh my god the way you're
laughing makes me think it definitely
isn't that how embarrassing it sounds so
sexual but I'm gonna say it's the act of
making friends I feel like this is like
when someone is sick and they like
vomiting and your chumming everywhere
the answer is when somebody is
menstruating oh why is münster
in such a weird way to say that
oh I'm just chilling today if somebody's
chumming you also say oh she's got the
channel yeah like that yes lovely lovely
next lange is non veg joke it's a dirty
joke I just think it's always like sex
what was wrong
to me a joke that has absolutely nothing
to do with a carrot like a joke that's
not PC maybe it is a joke about
someone's genitals and non of a joke is
basically a sexual joke yes ah
everything to do with the caring no so
what's the non-veg it involves all sorts
of meats so it's called a non-veg - oh I
love that next flag is funda is it like
when you have a policy in like a
rainstorm gonna dance out in the rain or
in the monsoon in your life let's have a
fun I would like to have that word to
come the meaning of this it sounds like
a thing you would cool someone like
you're a [ __ ] yeah
is it like a poop
it's a fun day out funny damn ok the
meaning of Fonda is fundamentals or
basics how would you use it dissenters
the funda of making a great omelet is
finding the right pan next mocking mug
someone it's like when you like steal
something from them all your mugging me
off is like you're taking me for dinner
something to do with tea like a mug of
tea
are you sure bugging is stealing I don't
know maybe you liked it you're dipping
something in a cup of tea and you're
like mocking it because we both love tea
in the UK and India mugging means to
memorize for a test
Wow Wow sort of like mug get in you
drink the knowledge in without really
processing it that's how I got through
school by mugging I didn't understand
anything
I just remembered it somehow oh yeah
that's what I did all the time like you
just like memorize the phrase and you're
like I've got this but I have no idea
what it means the next leg is bunking so
we have it to in in the UK I wonder if
it's the same in India probably not
maybe maybe not
bunking off like missing something
listening to music in your car
late night that's such a random guess
but if it's right then
hey wow look at me bunking is when you
skip like a day of school or a day well
actually you are right to skip class or
to skip work ah I see ok I thought that
was an old thing they like are you
bunking off like yeah I'm bunking up as
well next Lang is parcel it to be done
with it I'm done parcel it imagine
someone is being really really emotional
like they're crying loads that they're
just being a lot put that sort away send
it away parcel it the meaning of parcel
it is to order a takeaway so if you're a
restaurant would you say all can you
parcel it parcel this for me yes and
then they just pack the food for you
yeah maybe I'll try it and yeah and
they'll be like wow you say you're
really hot on your Indian slang okay
next head back those things that
Americans call swirlies where when
you're in school and someone flushes you
down the toilet all right like I wash my
hair
they can't be out watching my hair you
know what it's not I'm gonna treat
myself I'm gonna give myself a head bath
I think it's a cleanse
head back there's like the baptism it
cleanses your sins away so I think it's
a clam is it just like slang for getting
a like a head massage like it's so
relaxing that it's like beating your
head the meaning of head butt is washing
hair oh well that's what I said but I
thought it was too simple taking things
literally is probably the way to go so
all my invisible assistants here have
calculated the scores and we have a
winner and the winner of this challenge
is me all of you guys did really badly
I'm sorry I'm gonna take the award by
myself but did I lose them
because I think I changed things around
so you can never really lose if you're
an innovator I did not do well a bit
guttered I lost but you know what I
learnt a lot and I will be using these
next time owners Indian most Indian
slang seems to kind of make sense like
it's not like you know here's the word
here's the meaning well hey thank you so
so so much for watching this video if
you liked it please give it a thumbs up
and tell us in the conversation down
below what are some other slang terms
that we could make people guess okay and
yeah subscribe to BuzzFeed India for
more videos
you