bonjour mes amis
comment allez- vous?
so my friends , today we will learn
nous sommes which means
we are
let's practice some sentences with nous sommes
Are you ready?
I know that
you also like to roam around like me
sometimes we go to cafe with our friends
sometimes at restaurant
sometimes we watch movies in cinemas
with our girlfriends and boyfriends
all of a sudden we get a call from home
maybe your dad or mom called you
and you say " we are at coffee shop"
or you say" we are at the movies"
how will we say such nsentences in french?
thats what we will learn today
before learning the answer
we should know how to ask the questions
i.e the french for " where are you?"
how can we do it in french?
yes here it is
now its time that you are planning to watch my video
and i call and ask you " where are you?"
you are so clever
actually you are eating pizza or pasta in a restaurant
i asked you "ok guys where are you?"
u replied " we are at the restaurant"
how can we say it in french?
now suppose your mom is free from cooking food
you are sitting in the room with your brother
you mom asked you" where are you"
you said " we are in the room"
how can we say it in french
now suppose you got married
and i want to invite you to a dinner
when i asked you whether you will come or not
you replied that " we are on vacation"
we are in paris
how can we say it in french?
now i came to know that you are in paris
now you asked me" where are you?"
i replied " i am with my shooting team"
shooting in india
i said " we are in india|"
how can we say it in french?
ok, let's practice some more sentences
let's start
so in today's video, we learned that
how to use place names with nous sommes
and we practiced a lot of sentences too
I've given a lot of sentences in the description box for your practice.
And finally,
Don't forget to like, comment, share & subscribe to my channel
And do visit www.novafrenchcampus.com