Mary!
Mangu, don't. Leave me.
You mean, Don't leave me?
I'll never leave you. Come on.
Mangu, don't. Go away!
No way.
This is not the time to go,
but come closer.
Please give me a kiss.
Come on, Maggi. Come on.
Somebody will see us.
No one has seen us
for the past one year.
How would anyone see us now?
Please come on.
- No, Mangu.
Mangu!
- Who's it?
Maggi, how can you..
No, sir. Mangu touches me.
He harasses me all the time.
No, sir. Whatever she said
in English is all wrong.
Sir, if I have done something wrong,
then so has she.
We both are in this together.
Together?
Sir!
- Let her go!
Let her go!
Get out of here.
Having fun, alone!
I lost my job
because of this mere thing.
Don't worry. You carry on, please.