[guitar music]
- Welcome
to Sidemen vs. Mr. Beast.
[contestants clapping and cheering]
- Woo! Yes!
- Team Mr. Beast is going first.
Who is going to do the challenge?
- I'll do it. I don't know.
[contestants clapping and cheering]
- The first round is
called Honeycomb Maze.
- You must find the exit to the maze
without getting stopped by the bees.
- And the team with the fastest total time
wins.
Once you walk in, I'm
gonna start the timer.
- Oh, God.
- Are you ready?
- Goofy Goobers, you good?
- We're ready.
- Yeah!
[contestant laughing]
- Look at this bee.
- 3. 2. 1.
Let's go!
[horn blowing]
- Good luck, Jimmy.
- Go! He's going! Go!
Go right, go right! Keep going!
- Why's the bee not moving?
- Go right!
- He's actually elite.
[indistinct]
This man is moving quick.
- What are the bees doing?
- Boom!
[indistinct yelling]
[contestants clapping and cheering]
- You know what? This is too easy.
[confetti popping]
Let's go.
- 8.5 seconds.
- Yes!
- I mean, he's done it.
He's done it. He's done it.
We've got an eight minute
Sidemen Sunday boys.
- Oh, you silly, silly boys.
You thought you could get rid of me?
Well, guess what? Never!
It's Ethan, and I'm here to tell you
to hit that subscribe button.
We are not at 17 million subscribers yet.
What are you doing?
Click the red button!
[fire exploding]
- So is Sidemen team going now?
- Yeah.
- All right. Who's going?
[indistinct chattering]
- Yeah, I'll go. I'll go.
- You gotta beat that. 8 seconds.
- Oh my gosh.
- How am I even gonna beat that?
- Were there even bees in there?
- Bro, yes and you just
dodged all of them.
[Jimmy laughing]
- If JJ finishes it, he'll be lucky.
- I think JJ's best option is just brute.
- He's going to fight a bee.
- Just literally just run.
- JJ, are you ready?
- Yeah.
- You've got a very tough time to beat.
3, 2, 1, go.
[horn blowing]
- Go on, JJ!
- He's off. He's off. He's off.
- He already ran into one.
- Oh.
[contestants laughing and cheering]
- [Simon Run, JJ, run!
- Sounds like he's
smashing every damn door.
[contestants laughing]
- Bro, the door sound effect.
[contestants screaming and laughing]
- He just pushed the bee.
- He just shoved the bee.
- f*ckin-
Fam!
- Someone tell him the
bee's not Logan Paul.
- It seems like he's hit every door
but the right one.
- Get off me!
No. Ah! Get off me!
- He may actually die in this maze.
Is there food and water in
there? Because he might run out.
- Oh my God.
[bee buzzing]
- It's right there. It's right there.
- Oh God! No!
- No it wasn't.
Bro.
[indistinct]
- He's tried every door at this point.
- We're coming up on the clock.
- He thinks he's tried every door.
- Oh my God.
- Wait, wait, wait, he
just kicked the door open.
- That wasn't the right door,
but I still stopped the timer.
- Go back in!
- That's not the exit.
- Go back in.
- I mean, I technically stopped the timer.
They don't have to know that.
And, okay.
He's broken another door.
- No!
- No, go through that one. It's this one.
- Stop breaking the doors!
- Now he knows where it is.
- You're almost there.
You've almost got it.
There we go.
[contestants clapping]
- Nice.
- We'll give him a participation trophy.
- A minute sixteen.
- Oh wow. Okay.
- No confetti for you. I'm sorry.
- Oh...
- We should subtract 10 seconds
for kicking down a door.
That was funny.
- Yeah, that's alright.
Let's give him 56 seconds.
- Ah, nice.
[contestants clapping]
- Team Sidemen,
Who do you want to compete next?
- We need someone smart.
- We need our equivalent.
Nimble.
- Oh, Nimble. Nimble.
- Yeah, Vik.
- All right, let's go.
- Go on, Vik.
[clapping]
- Go on, Vik!
- I'm gonna go sneaky, stealth mode.
- Um, I wouldn't, I would go very fast.
3, 2, 1.
Go in.
[horn blowing]
- Here we go, go on!
Go on, Vik.
You're going the wrong way.
- Okay. How's Vikkstar doing?
He's the smartest of the Sidemen.
I'm worried for him.
He's already passed Jimmy's time.
Pressure is gonna be mounting.
It's not looking good for the Sidemen.
- Maybe this is smart.
- Where's the finish line?
- No, the bees don't know where he is.
- There's a bee there. On the right!
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no
that bee has seen him.
[door hitting wall]
[Vik screaming]
[contestants yelling]
- Run Vik.
- Get off me.
- He might be starting to panic.
[Josh chuckling]
- Get off me!
- He might be getting claustrophobic.
Go back in-
[Vik yelling]
[laughing] He came out the entrance.
- Well that bee is on him.
- He's moving so fast though.
- He's getting gang banged by two bees.
[Vik yelling]
- Yes!
[contestants cheering]
- So Vik, so come on here.
- Well done, Vik.
- It wasn't awful. It wasn't awful.
- It just wasn't great.
- It wasn't awful.
- Vikkstar did it in exactly one minute.
[contestants slightly clapping]
- One minute forty-eight
seconds versus eight seconds.
Chris, you can't possibly screw this up.
- Don't say that.
- Literally, even if
you tried, you couldn't.
- I believe in you. Come
on, look at the ground.
- Now that I've seen other people do it,
how did it take you eight seconds?
- All right, Chris, are you ready?
- I'm ready, Freddy.
- You've only got to beat one
minute forty eight seconds.
- I think I can do it maybe.
- 3, 2, 1.
Go in.
[horn blowing]
[clapping]
- Here we go.
- Faster!
- Oh, there he is. I
think he's in the middle.
[Chris laughing]
- Oh, he's being raped.
[Chris screaming]
- Oh he's so big.
Oh the bees are double teaming him.
- Get outta there.
- Where do I go? [laughing]
Buzz off!
- Oh my god, he's getting
close. He's getting close.
- Keep going, Chris, keep going.
- He's gonna find it.
- Oh ho ho, no.
- Yes, yes!
[contestants laughing]
- Hold him.
[struggled grunting]
Hold him!
- Kick the bee!
- The bee is making this really hard.
[contestants cheering]
[Chris yelling]
I'm getting bee made.
Where do I go?
- Here we go!
- All right-
[contestants clapping]
he made it.
- Dude, they were like grabbing me.
- I can reveal the winner.
What do you think happened?
It's team Mr. Beast.
- Let's go!
[contestants cheering]
- USA!
[confetti popping]
[contestants cheering]
- The next round is called DoorDash.
- Two members of each team
must race through a series of doors.
- To progress,
avoid the three solid wooden doors
by finding the fake door.
- 3, 2, 1. Go.
[horn blowing]
[contestants clapping]
- Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[contestants screaming]
- Yes, Vik!
Go Vik!
- Go Vik!
- Aah!
No!
- Yes Vik! [clapping]
- Go, go, go!
- Follow Vik. What are you doing?
[contestants screaming]
- No!
- Oh my God.
- Josh! Throw yourself, Josh.
- Come on, Chris.
[contestants screaming]
- Yes!
- Go, Jimmy. What are you doing?
[contestants yelling]
- Go, go, go, go, go.
Win this. Win this.
This is it. This is it.
- No!
- That's a foul.
- He won.
- Chris just won.
- He pushed him through to beat him.
[contestants laughing]
- It was you, me, me, you.
- He pushed him through, but he won.
[contestant laughing]
- Is Chris alright?
[contestants laughing and clapping]
- I was just in war.
- I put my arm through a wall.
- I just pushed you through that one.
- I know it's fine.
As I dove through, I hit my knee
and I was just like, I'm still
winning it doesn't matter.
[contestants laughing]
- You guys are trying
to lose at this point.
[contestants laughing]
- Like, what the hell?
- Nolan, don't mess up or
you're off the channel.
- 3.
- Hold them back.
- 2, 1, go.
[horn blowing]
- Go [indistinct]!
[contestants screaming]
- Nolan's a genius.
- Over here!
[indistinct yelling]
- Tareq almost flipped through it.
Yes!
- Right here, Tareq!
Push them out of the way.
- No!
[indistinct yelling]
- Hold him down.
Hold him.
[contestants yelling]
- Bro.
- Three in a row.
[contestants laughing and yelling]
- What the f*ck.
- Ooooooh.
[contestants laughing]
- Nolan got three in a row.
- He's a beast!
- Come here Nolan.
- You can't beat me.
I'm a Fall Guys champion!
- Well, the Sidemen f*ckin' suck.
- Bro, he just went
through every right door.
- Bro, he got four doors in a row.
I didn't even get to a door
before he got through it.
- You are being embarrassed
on your own channel.
- Our strategy was, I was
like, yo, you spearhead,
I'll just let you know
if you messed up or not.
- I didn't mess up though.
- He didn't mess up.
He didn't mess up.
- How?!
- You just gonna leave me hanging.
- Oh, that was embarrassing.
- Hey, buddy.
[contestant laughing]
- They spent half a million
dollars on this video
just for us to come in here and [laughs].
- Sweep the floor.
- Like how did you, when you
looked at this, for example?
- To me it just looks slightly different.
- Wait, so Nolan came in first?
- Yes.
- Who came in second?
- That's what I was asking.
I was so focused on Nolan.
- I'm gonna say it.
Not even a competition.
- Come on.
- I knew it was coming.
[contestants clapping]
- Come on.
- There's nothing we can
do there. There's nothing.
- Surprise, surprise.
The winner of that round: Team Beast.
There you go.
- Let's go.
[contestants clapping]
- That was a microphone
that I was fist bumping.
- We win!
- Yeah!
- I see it, I hit it, you know?
- We win those.
- I'm actually embarrassed.
- Yeah, I'm ashamed.
- It's all right. It's
all right. We go again.
- The next round is called On Your Bike.
- Two members from each team
must race through the
course on mini trikes
and take on the obstacle.
- And the first team to
complete a whole lap,
wins.
[timer counting down]
- Yo, here we go. Here we go.
- Oh, sh*t.
- Oh, go!
[contestants cheering]
- Go!
- Chandler carried those
bananas all day for that joke.
[contestants laughing]
- They caught it.
- It worked.
[contestants yelling]
- Chandler, go!
- Oh, he's been caught.
[laughing]
- Dude, he got caught by the banana!
- Look. It slowed him down for one second.
[contestant yelling]
- Go, Chandler.
- Oh wait, the ramp.
- Wait. Oh man.
- There's no way Nolan's getting up that-
- Nolan, block him-
- I can't get up the hill!
[Josh laughing]
- Just walk up it!
- Can we go push them?
- No.
- Oh God.
[contestants laughing]
- Ow!
- Oh, the Chandler banana again.
- I've broken my bike.
- Chandler's gonna have time to catch up
by the time they go over the ramp, bro.
[contestants laughing]
- What did you do over there, bro?
- He's not touching
his feet to the ground.
- I'll go, I'll help.
- How do we get up?
- Wait.
- Josh is coming.
- Should we go help?
- One person go.
- I'll go.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- Go, Jimmy, go.
[contestants laughing]
- I've got nothin'. I can't go, I can't-
- The bike broke.
[contestants yelling]
- No, I was so close!
- Dude, this is like a fight right now.
- Come here, Josh.
- Oh my God.
Just chaos.
- We put together an expensive
set for this to happen.
[contestant giggling]
- Literally for them to get
stuck in the first third.
- Oh no.
- Yes!
[contestant laughing]
- Go!
- Josh!
- Oh, Nolan's gonna fall off the bridge.
- Wait, the bridge is smoking!
- I can't do anything and I've
got no handle bars anymore.
- Wait, why is it literally
about to catch fire?
- Josh help.
Josh!
[Nolan screaming]
- Go Nolan, go!
- Simon, you need to ride it out.
Catch up!
- Nolan, you're way ahead. Keep going.
[indistinct yelling]
- Boys!
[contestants laughing]
[Simon screaming]
- This is much harder than it looks.
- Oh, what? Who's falling off and-
- Nolan's actually doing the best.
How is this possible?
- Simon go.
[contestant laughing and panting]
- What just got thrown?
- Nolan, keep going.
- I'm so tired.
- You're the only one
still doing anything.
- Push me up. My middle name is speed.
Ah, my balls.
[contestants laughing]
- Go Simon. Go! It's your Chance.
- Go Simon.
Simon, go.
- Oh, no.
[indistinct chattering]
- There you go. Yes!
- Let's go!
[clapping and cheering]
- Yes! Whoo!
Cross the finish line.
- We are the best.
- Push me!
- Cross the finish line.
- We are the best.
- What is this?
[contestant grunting]
- No, he made it. He made it.
- Oh, he fell across the finish line.
- Yeah! [laughing]
- Harry!
- Harry, what the f*ck?
- What happened to your bike?
- Harry, take this.
- There's just one left.
- Take my bike.
- To where?
- To go back through.
- I hope it's one lap.
- Wait, is Chandler gonna make it?
- I'll push you up.
- You got this Chandler.
- Chandler, keep pushing.
- Fight, Harry, fight!
- No, push me. Push me.
- If you finish we'll get
more points. Just finish.
- Help me.
- Just make sure you
lean back a little bit.
- Chandler, you got it.
[contestant laughing]
- You've got to lean back a little bit.
- Keep going!
- Go to the ramp, Chandler!
- Go go go! Push, push, push.
- f*cking hell, he's heavy.
- Push.
- Yes.
- Just pedal.
- Nolan, help him!
- Pedal!
- Chandler, he's on you.
[contestants laughing]
- Come on, Harry.
- sh*t.
- No Nolan, Nolan don't...
- Let him do it.
- Come on.
- Hey, no one helping.
- What the-
- Go. Go. Go.
- I'm trying.
- Pedal!
- I cant!
- What are you doing?
- You're out of bounds
- Harry, come on!
- Chandler, go!
[indistinct yelling]
The Banana!
- Harry, come on.
- That wasn't even trying to-
- Quick, quick, quick.
[fire exploding]
- Guys.
- Harry, we need this.
- Come on. Go, go, go, go, go.
- Push him up. Push him up.
- Come on, Harry, go.
Who's gonna win?
[contestants yelling]
[board banging]
- Oh my-
- Oh it's a photo finish!
- We won. I think we won.
- Oh my gosh.
[contestants laughing]
- That's the line bro.
- We won.
- That was a photo finish, [indistinct].
- We won!
- We have to take it back to the tape.
[board banging and contestants laughing]
- Oh, we won. I think we won.
- Oh my gosh!
[contestants clapping and laughing]
That was the slowest photo
finish I've seen in my life.
[contestants laughing]
- I say we chalk that up as a tie,
and do one more round.
- All the way.
- Yeah, do we have more bikes?
- This is cooked.
[contestants laughing]
- We need someone,
we need someone lightweight
on the next one.
- The people that assembled
this forgot the screws.
All right, it's only been two seconds
since the last race.
Switched to bigger cars, cause
the other ones fell apart.
- They're bikes.
- Harry, just kept hitting it.
[timer going off]
- Go!
- Karl's in the lead.
Oh my god!
- Tareq, don't bottle it
- Is that Karl?
Wait, he went off the track.
- Tareq's killing it.
[indistinct chattering]
[grunting and yelling]
- Okay.
[contestants clapping]
- He's flying.
- This is already the easiest job.
- Go on, Josh.
Go! We practised this.
- Drift it.
No, Josh. Come on.
- He's not helping him get up.
- Oh no!
- They're coming all the way around.
- Karl, cock block him.
[contestants laughing]
- Go that up- [indistinct]
- Go Josh, Josh go.
[indistinct yelling]
[contestants clapping and cheering]
- He just rammed him off the track.
- Go, Karl!
[contestants laughing]
- Hey, you can't do that.
[contestant grunting]
- Yeah, go Tareq.
- Now it's Tareq's turn.
[yelling]
[indistinct chattering]
- Oh no.
[yelling]
- Tareq, go!
- I'm gonna fall.
[contestants yelling]
- Tareq, go!
- Oh my god.
- That's fine [indistinct]
- Ai yai yai!
No!
[bike slamming]
- Catch, catch, catch-
- You better not blow this for us, Tareq.
[laughing]
- He took his bike.
- No!
- What is he doing?
What is he doing?
- That's gotta be illegal.
That's gotta be illegal.
- Look at my bike, bro.
- Get on, Tobi!
[contestants yelling]
- No, no, no, no!
- Oooh!
- Tareq, I can't help you!
- Pedal!
- Don't check if he's okay, keep going.
- Oh no!
- Look at my bike!
[contestant chuckling]
- Karl, go! I'm r-
Karl, go-
- Okay, I'm coming-
- Go!
- Tareq, push him.
[contestant grunting and laughing]
- We got it. We got it. We got it.
- Look at Tobi's bike.
Look at the handle.
- See we're used to this.
We do this every day man.
- Oh, sorry.
- What is going on?
- They're fighting.
- Where do I go?
[contestants laughing]
- Is that allowed?
- Punch 'em. Punch 'em.
- Oh Karl is [indistinct]
- Karl, get on the bike.
- Oh my god, if Karl fumbles it.
- Karl, go.
[indistinct chattering]
Karl-
- Go Josh.
- Go Josh!
- Maybe Karl didn't ruin Mr. Beast.
- Go Josh, go Josh,
there's still time.
- Let's go.
- Stay in the back. Stay in the back.
Stay in the back-
- No!
- Oh no!
[indistinct yelling]
[all cheering]
- No!
- He turned his wheel.
- Go go go!
- That was genius.
- Whoa, this is bad.
- My wheel's sideways.
- Pull him back. Pull
him back. Pull him back.
- He's blocking the bridge.
- Wait he's still going,
I thought it was done.
[contestant screaming]
- Lord Jesus, please.
- Ah! The wheel.
- Jesus, take the wheel.
- The wheel's sideways.
- Jesus, take the wheel!
- So Josh's finished.
- Josh has done two laps.
- Josh is finished.
- Yeah, Josh and Karl are done.
- Oh, okay.
- Wait, so wait. How are we ahead?
- No, you're not. Tobi
hasn't finished one.
- He's cuttin' corners.
- No.
- So Tobi's done two, he fell off.
- We're ahead.
- Oh he did?
- We're ahead!
- Wait, they're ahead?
- Go, go, go, go, go.
[indistinct yelling]
- Go.
- Push.
- Pedal!
[indistinct yelling]
- Somebody help me.
- Use him!
- Just help me!
- Pedal forward.
[contestants yelling]
- Pedal! Karl.
- Oh, man we lost.
- Hey, Cheat! Cheat!
[contestant screaming]
- Throw your own teammate off, yes.
Yeah sabotage your own teammate.
- Oh my god.
[all exclaiming]
- Ooh!
- Wait.
- Wait. I dunno who to give that to.
- We have, we have to run that back.
[camera clicking]
[contestants screaming and laughing]
- Whoa!
- And the winner of that
round: team Mr. Beast.
- Let's go!
- That's us.
[contestants clapping]
- That's embarrassing...
- I did it for my Squad.
- Bald eagle soaring.
- I'm the squad.
- Yeah.
- Maybe America is better.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Oh no...
- Prove it wrong. Prove it wrong, alright?
I'm cheering for you,
hey. What're you doing?
- Hey, you'll get us in
the World Cup, that's fine.
- This fourth round is called Grid Iron.
- You have to catch the ball
and score a touchdown
[men cheering in background]
in the fastest time possible
without getting caught by the other team.
- The team with the
fastest total time wins.
- Y'all, y'all, y'all ready for this?
- Karl, do it for America.
- Hey, when you hit a
touchdown, hit that griddy.
- I would pay to see Karl hit the griddy.
- We're going no hands.
We're going no hands.
- Going no hands. [laughing]
- Oh no, that's embarrassing.
- Is that disrespect?
- We've got no arms. That's
how confident we are.
- If Karl loses-
- Karl!
then that's it I will disown him-
[horn blows]
- Don't drop it.
- Go!
- Go, Karl!
[contestant grunting]
- Oh! The speed!
[indistinct yelling]
- Oh!
[clapping and yelling]
- America!
[contestants clapping]
- I think he was out of bounds.
He was out of bounds.
- No shot. No shot.
- It's a touchdown.
[contestants cheering]
- Oh, let's go.
- Lazerbeam is an idiot
'cause he definitely
stepped out like four times.
- Yo, that turtle's stuck.
Everybody make fun of that turtle.
[JJ grunting]
- Hey, pile on.
- Do you wanna say goodbye to it?
- Piss off.
[contestants laughing]
- What is this?
- Whatever that is.
- What is that?
- I don't know what that
is, but I'm not there.
[contestants chanting]
- If they can get JJ
in the middle of that.
- Yeah [laughing]
- He's done for.
- I think he's just
gonna breeze through 'em.
They ain't gonna stop him realistically.
- How long do you guys think
it's gonna take KSI to do this?
I think maybe five seconds.
- JJ remember you can't,
we actually have to win this one, man.
- Guys, can you start from the 20?
- Hey, they want us to
start from the 20 yard line.
- Hey, how 'bout you suck my nut sack?
- Come on, JJ.
- Let's go, JJ.
[horn blowing]
- Oh, god.
- He's off.
- Oh.
Oooh!
- He's overdoing it. He's overdoing it.
He's overdoing it.
- Get him!
- He's overdoing it!
- No!
[contestants laughing]
[contestants cheering]
- Yes!
What!
[grunting and yelling]
[contestants laughing]
[grunting]
- Alright.
- What do I do?
- Don't f*cking lose.
[contestants laughing]
- Okay guys, do me a favour.
Crunch this mutha f*cka.
- Dude, Nolan's gonna get destroyed.
- Look at him. He just looks terrified.
- Josh is really strategizing, by the way.
- Well, they got a formation.
- We have a very obvious weak side.
I'm just saying
when you have Josh, JJ, and
Harry in a line like that,
and then you have Tobi, Vik,
and you can just run at them.
- What's wrong with Tobi and Vik?
- They're just very petite.
- What do you mean by that?
- Small, pequeno.
- Hey, what's wrong with petite?
- Yeah!
- Don't let him through, boys.
Do not let him through.
[contestant yelling]
- Come on, lads!
[chanting]
Come on, lads!
- Do this buddy. [clapping]
- Wow, they're intimidating.
[horn blowing]
- All right.
[indistinct yelling]
- What is that run? Oh, no.
- Hold him back-
- Oh!
- Hold him, hold him.
[clapping and yelling]
[indistinct yelling]
- Oh, the Josh.
- Josh has got him.
[contestants laughing]
- You're not done. Get back in there, son.
- He's not done.
- He's still going.
- Keep going.
- Go Josh.
- Go!
[contestants laughing]
- Josh really tried.
- Nolan just got man handled.
- I don't think I got 10 feet.
[contestants laughing]
- Two.
- Got a win.
- I want Harry to get one on his ass.
Like I want him to push someone over.
- He doesn't even have pads on.
- Harry, are you ready?
- Come on, Beast.
- Come on, Harry.
- Let's go, Harry.
- Let's go, Harry, let's go.
[horn blowing]
- Go on now!
- Oh no.
- He's fumbled.
- Go, go, go.
- Oh no he's down.
- Oh no.
- Coach.
- Thanks for giving me the opportunity.
- Hey, I want to tell
you, boy, you can do it.
You're gonna go all the way to state.
- I ain't gonna say
much, but I am gonna say,
you either run or you're dead.
[Tobi yelling]
[horn blowing]
- Here we go, lads.
- Oh no.
- Nice. Nice.
- Oh.
- Well, in the flip flop-
- You just gotta hold it.
You just gotta hold it-
- He's wearing flip flops.
[contestants laughing]
- Keep him there, man.
- They got speed, bro.
- Nice.
- Oh.
- Oh. Take him down boys.
[indistinct yelling]
- You either run or you're dead.
- Run, Chan, run.
[contestants cheering]
- Get back up, get back up.
- Oh, he's wearing flip flops.
Why don't we take that into consideration?
- Let's go, boys.
[contestants cheering and laughing]
- Yeah!
- Hey, he was in flip flops.
In hindsight, not the best strategy.
- Come on, Tobi.
- Let's go, Tobi.
- Let's go.
- Tobi!
[contestants clapping and cheering]
- His movement.
Watch.
- His movement's crazy.
- Yo, he's about to be here
without even realising it-
- He's gonna slide cancel.
- How many seconds you give him?
- I think he might do it in
like six seconds, you know.
- Really?
- Come on, Tobi.
- Come on, Jizzle.
- Let's go!
[clapping]
- Tobi.
- Give 'em the jizz.
- Tobi. Tobi. Tobi-
[horn blowing]
Tobi. Tobi. Tobi.
[yelling]
- Come on, Beast.
- Oh, there's a gap here.
- Oh!
- Watch out for the wall.
- Tobi!
[contestants clapping and yelling]
- Yeah!
What, what!
[contestants grunting]
- And the winner of that challenge,
finally on the scoreboard...
- Yes.
- Yes!
- After so many challenges.
[contestants laughing]
- We felt, we felt bad.
- Yeah.
- Team Sidemen.
- Yeah!
- We had to give 'em one.
- Woo!
- I'm keeping the jersey.
- Hey. Football is their thing.
If we beat them it
would've been embarrassing.
- I was gonna say,
the American sport is when
you finally showed up.
[contestants laughing]
What are you doing?
- Let's do baseball or basketball.
- Oh no, no, no.
- Please no. Please no.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- With the score already being 3-1
to Mr. Beast's team, we
have to raise the stakes.
For this last round, whichever team wins,
wins the whole video.
- The first person to
stop in the right place,
exactly above the arrow,
wins for their team.
- If you don't go far enough,
or you go too far,
you get dunked in the pool.
[upbeat music]
- I'm gonna show you boys
how this challenge is done.
- Go on, son.
- He's got the surfer in him.
- Oh, whoa.
- Oh no.
[contestants yelling]
- Oh!
- No!
[contestants laughing and clapping]
- Oh, you almost did it though.
- That was actually really close.
- That was really close...
- That was-
- I'd recommend going slower.
- On a scale of 1 to 10,
how freezing are you?
- Oh, my f*ckin' balls are in my body.
[contestants laughing]
- You're...
- Hug me, Jimmy.
[contestants laughing]
- So this is what happens if you fail.
- Gotcha.
Who, which team goes first?
- Team Sidemen.
- I agree.
[laughing and clapping]
I agree.
- For God's sake, man.
- Hey, son!
- Come on JJ.
- Come on.
- We believe in you.
- I'm scared.
- It's not that bad, buddy.
[contestants chanting]
- Don't celebrate first.
- Ooooooh...
- Oh, that's way too much gas-
Oh!
- Wait.
- Ah...sh*t.
[contestants indistinctly cheering]
[contestant screaming]
[contestants laughing and clapping]
- Yo, he decked the GoPro.
[JJ shrieking]
- f*ck me, that's cold, brother.
- Hey, I'm good.
- I don't wanna do it.
[contestant clapping]
- I flew all the way from
America to here just for this.
- Jimmy, how many centimetres
in between the start and the end?
- Bro, what the f*ck's a centimetre?
- How many, how, feet?
- Inches.
- Bro, speak English.
[contestant laughing]
- See how I still have my shoes on?
- Yeah-
- That's how confident I am-
- Yeah! [cheering]
- that I'm about to crush this.
[contestants cheering]
- Okay.
- We'll see, mate.
- I rate 'em, you know.
If I had that many subs,
there's no way I'd do this.
[contestants laughing]
- 3.
- 2. 1. Go!
[board sliding]
- Wait.
[contestants cheering]
- All right, whoa.
[indistinct yelling]
- La la la la. La la la la.
Hey hey hey.
Goodbye.
[contestants laughing]
[buzzer sounding]
- It's so cold.
- [indistinct]...you did that.
- The wet shoes.
- My balls. It's so freezing.
- Come on, Harry.
- If there's one man that
can save the Sidemen.
[contestants yelling]
[board sliding]
- For f*ck's sake.
[contestants laughing]
[buzzer sounding]
- That moment of realisation.
[contestants clapping]
- I said pull it back a little bit.
- You told me sprint full-
- Yeah, but I told you
pull it back at the end a little.
- If you get it, we win.
[contestants booing]
- Oh, no.
- No way, bro.
- No way, no way.
- Bro, why don't we
[indistinct] this sh*t?
[contestants laughing]
- All right, stop it. You
gotta take it. Take it.
[contestants laughing]
- Jesus Christ.
- Good boy.
[contestants laughing and clapping]
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
[contestants laughing]
- Man saw Jesus.
- Buddy.
Hey take, here have my towel.
Have my towel.
Did you give up on life for a second?
- What happened?
- You just, you went like this
and instead of coming
up, you just went down.
- It was so cold, I think my
brain turned off for a second.
- Oh, Vik, I beg you, just do it.
- Vik, just do it, please.
- I beg Vik does it.
- He's gone toilet to lighten his weight.
- We ready?
- Go Vik!
[indistinct yelling]
- Go Vik.
- Let me get a tall glass of Vik.
[board sliding]
- What. What. What?
[indistinct cheering]
- Vik! Vik!
- Ooooh!
- Yes.
- I want you to know, Vik,
I'm not gonna enjoy this.
- Oh wow. The tape is
here. He did not make it.
He was about a solid foot away.
- Jimmy, do you wanna help me?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Wait, here, let me do the honours.
- Why make it painful?
No!
Why?
- Huh?
- Oh no!
[contestants groaning]
- Hey, tease him.
- Ooooh!
- Alright, this time for real.
- Naughty, naughty.
- Whoa...whoa!
[contestants cheering and clapping]
- Ahh!
- Oh man.
[Vik grunting]
- For the love of God. Someone do it.
- Nolan you got this.
- You got this.
- You good?
- Come on, buddy.
[contestants booing]
- No chance-
- That's a determined-
[board sliding]
- Oh.
- Hey! No, no, no.
[indistinct groaning]
- Nah, nah, nah-
Come on, buddy.
- I'll let you put yourself in. Go on.
Now you put yourself in, Nolan.
- Bye!
[Nolan groaning]
[contestants laughing]
- Oh, sh*t.
- Oh, that is freezing.
[contestants laughing]
- That innocent "bye".
- I regret this, so much.
- Just stand up here, look
down the barrel of the gun.
[contestant laughing]
There's nothing bad about it, man.
- All right, let's see it.
- Simon, save us again.
- Minter them. Go on.
- Hate is my big biggest
motivation, pussy.
- Oooh...
[clapping and chanting]
[chanting speeds up]
- Yeah, I like it.
- He's done it.
- He's short. He's short.
I'm gonna go push him in.
- f*ck, Simon.
[groaning and booing]
- I'm sorry!
- Holy sh*t, why are you so much harder
to push than Vik?
- I hate the Sidemen.
I hate all of you.
- I don't wanna be pushed
in by the other team.
- I just like torturing the boys.
- This is horrible.
- Here, help me push him over.
[contestant screaming]
- This is why it's my job, Jimmy.
[buzzer sounding]
[Simon groaning]
[contestants clapping]
- I don't wanna do this.
- I give that a 10.
- Someone's gotta do this, man.
- Alright, let's do this.
- All right, Tareq. Let's see it.
[board sliding]
- He's off.
[indistinct chattering]
- I think he's done it.
- I think he did!
[contestants screaming and clapping]
- Let's freaking go!
- Did we do it?
- I love you!
- Even though we won,
I think we should still push Tareq in.
Come on, come one, come on.
[contestants laughing]
- Thumbnail this.
- All right.
- Wait, wait, don't hold this.
That your sh*t thumbnail.
[water splashing]
[contestants laughing]