Friends, when you imagine the Middle East,
you probably think of deserts.
But Oman is quite special.
It has date palm forests
and tall mountains.
Here, you can swim with turtles,
and, in Oman, you can also see
one of the most dangerous forts in the world.
A fort that could never be breached by an enemy.
Because its defence system was so immaculate
that you'll be shocked to see it.
The security system of this fort
was truly amazing back then.
If you tried to enter the fort from this gate,
the soldiers could throw rocks from above to k!ll you.
So even before you enter,
you can see the first post,
from where they would throw rocks on you.
If you escape this,
you will reach the Pitfall 1,
where they would throw hot oil or date syrup on you.
The date syrup.
That's where the hot oil would be poured on you.
So you better be quick to escape it.
Now, they've covered this with glass,
or else, you could have fallen into the pit.
When you would run from the hot oil,
you would fall into this pit.
And if you escaped it too,
you would reach the Pitfall 2.
They could drop something from here,
the M*rder Hole 2 is right above it.
You could fall into this pit and perish.
Catch enemies off guard,
in the dark passageway.
It was dark,
there were no lamps like here.
Yeah.
So some of the stairs had wooden planks
that could be removed to expose
deep, gaping pits.
And then you would be at the third pitfall.
And the fourth after that.
And the fifth.
So, not just once but
you would have to escape five times,
if you want to breach this fort.
We've safely escaped 2 pitfalls,
Let's move on to the third pitfall.
Oh! This is the third pitfall.
As soon as you open this door,
you have this door here,
as soon as you step through it,
you'll fall into the pitfall.
There's a door before every pitfall.
These people were so clever,
the doors would be closed,
and when you try to open the doors,
they will pour oil on you,
and if you manage to open it,
you will fall into the pit.
And after passing through all these stages,
I don't know if there has
been a single intruder in history,
who reached the top.
If he did,
this is the view he would have seen.
These are the places
from where you would pour the hot oil.
It can really go deep inside.
300 years ago,
Nizwa was the capital of Oman.
That's why today,
Nizwa is an important tourist attraction.
The city of Nizwa.
And this fort,
back then, the Sultan of Oman,
lived here and ruled over Oman.
The best thing about Oman
in comparison to the other Middle Eastern countries,
is that this is a sparsely populated country.
Wherever you go, there won't be a crowd.
You'll see very few people.
So you can take your time to explore everything.
Like, you can see the fort,
this is a major tourist attraction,
but you can hardly see anyone else here.
I'm the guy who has been assigned
the duty of throwing the stones today.
Oh, you're throwing the stones today?
On the intruders.
Okay, I'll be the one who pours the oil then.
I'll be over here, okay?
Yeah!
The wood on the door,
this is the same wood from those days.
This is walnut wood.
Even in their shooting style,
they had some nice designs.
Like, if someone was close to the fort,
and they had to shoot him,
this is the slit they'd use,
so that they could shoot downwards.
But if the target was far,
this is the hole for that,
they could shoot from here.
And there's another angle here.
So they could shoot in three different angles.
These 3 angles were all around 360° of the fort.
So you can imagine the
level of protection of this fort.
There's a well in this castle fort.
Look at how deep it goes.
You can see my reflection at the bottom.
-Oh, my God.
-Zoom in.
This is a big area,
that includes the Nizwa Souq, Nizwa Fort,
a historical wall,
that was used to protect the fort from enemies.
We're walking on this wall now.
You can see some old buildings here,
some parts are being renovated,
some have been renovated already.
But look at how extraordinary it looks.
It feels like you have time-travelled
to 2,000 years into the past.
Don't be distracted by my cap,
there's 'Australia' written on it,
I wore this because I didn't have any other caps.
And it's too sunny here.
And if you remember the Australia vlogs,
I got this cap for free in Australia,
so I'm wearing this cap.
After this, we went to the Nizwa Souq.
The old city market,
that looks like a historical place.
Omani dates.
Look at the varieties here.
Less sweets ones, okay.
There are dates everywhere.
You will know the difference
between this one and that.
-This one's good, right?
-I like this.
I think this is the fourth variety I've tried.
At home, mostly we have the Medjool ones.
There are more than 200 varieties of dates in Oman.
They have so many types of dates in this shop.
You'll be exhausted by the time you've tried them all.
They have seedless dates,
date honey,
and the tahini sauce to dip the dates.
This machine is making sesame sauce.
The sesame seeds are put into it.
And this machine is grinding the seeds
to make the sauce.
You can see it here.
And the sauce then drips into this pot
where it is collected.
Oh, wow, there's so much sauce.
You can smell it also.
They have given us this sample to try.
Pure tahini sauce.
It is warm!
The contrast between
this sauce and the dates
tastes quite good,
because it tastes a bit sour,
and the dates are sweet.
So when the tastes mix,
it makes a good snack.
So we decided to buy 1 packet of dates.
But they actually gifted it to us.
They would not accept any payment.
Very, very sweet.
Though it was pretty affordable, to be honest.
0.800 Rial.
[$2.08 or ₹172.35]
800 Baiza.
A Rial is divided into 1,000 Baiza.
This dagger that you see here,
this is the logo of Oman.
Even on Oman's flag,
there's a dagger in a corner.
In ceremonies and special occasions,
people carry such daggers.
If you are interested in visiting Oman,
you can try Gainwell Travel,
they offer customised travel itineraries and packages,
of many places, including Oman.
The link to their website is in the description.
You can check it out.
So this is a banana
and a palm tree plantation.
You can see we're walking on the irrigation system,
so we don't wanna step on anything.
There are no dates on any of these trees,
but when they are, they look like this.
They grow in bunches.
There can be more than a thousand dates in a bunch.
Oman's population is less than 5 million.
But there are more than 7 million date palm trees.
Can you imagine that
there are more date trees
than people in this country?
There was a small hill here.
The view from here is simply amazing.
You can see the date palm tree
plantation spread over this area.
And behind it, you can see
some interesting, historical civilisations.
We finished checking into the second hotel now,
and as soon as we entered the room,
look at what we found.
A huge YouTube cake.
Welcome to Al Bustan Palace.
That's the name of this hotel.
And they have my latest photo on
top of this YouTube cake.
Probably edible.
And the Play Button, Subscribe,
wait a second, Dislike?
No, no, no, let's remove the Dislike,
-Dislike also?
-We don't need it here.
These cakes look really interesting.
They look really good.
But unfortunately, it's not
possible to eat so much sugar,
it's just too much.
If you take an hour-long speedboat ride from Muscat,
you will reach Al Daymaniyat Island.
It is a protected nature reserve
and a wonderful site for eco-tourism.
So we're on the beautiful island now.
We're the only ones on this island.
-The only ones?
-Look, there's no one else around here.
-We're about to go snorkelling.
-Yeah.
There's a small problem.
Someone, one of us, I won't say who
forgot their swimming pants.
So they have to go in undie.
Underwater, you'll find more than
100 species of corals,
more than 280 species of fish,
but if the thing this place is most famous for,
are the turtles.
The endangered species of green turtles,
often come here to nest,
and while snorkelling,
these turtles can get very close to you.
In this video, you can see
that they aren't scared of humans.
Now, we're at a special museum in Oman.
The building is so unique that
I'm in a science-fiction movie.
Not in 2024, but in 2124.
It looks so crazy.
Look behind you.
This building feels like it's AI-generated.
It's so perfect.
Everything looks so proper
you won't even find a single
dust particle on this floor.
This is the biggest museum in Oman.
Oman Across the Ages.
The museum building is so huge that
there is more than 900,000 m² of exhibition space here.
And in some galleries, the ceiling is so high,
some are more than 20m high.
The hunter-gatherers who lived in Oman 6,000 years ago,
lived in such huts.
These are some historical
Omani sea routes over here.
Look at this, the screen is so big,
but there are gaps between the screen.
To go further into the museum,
you can pass through the gaps in the screen.
This museum has been designed very creatively.
There's another screen on the other side.
Friends, here you can clearly see,
the Omani national emblem.
That has two swords and a dagger.
This is the passport of Oman's previous Sultan.
You can see it.
Along with his Driver's License and ID Card.
You can see the number on the ID Card,
00000001.
Most of the things that you saw in this vlog,
were from around Muscat.
But apart from this, in Oman, you can see deserts,
the highest mountain in the Gulf,
as well as the Gulf's Grand Canyon.
We showed the Grand Canyon in the previous vlog,
you can click here to watch it too.