Hi Guys, Whats up? Thanks a lot for watching Booxoul...
Today, we are going to talk about...
Teri Bhais ki pooch (Your Buffalo's tail)
Ant sant mat Bol (Don't talk Rubbish)
types of words...
In English, we call these informal phrases, 'SLANGS'
In our country, that's India...
almost everyone wants to speak English as fluent as they can...
but what happens is...
while speaking we run out words!
I can't increase your vocabulary in this short video
even if it was a bit lengthier I couldn't, because ...
umm... my vocabulary sucks!
So, like 'Teri Bhaiss ki pooch' doesn't mean 'Buffalo's tail' in English
Similarly, there are some words, some slangs
which means a bit different than what they seem
So, let's see them!!!
The first slang is 'SICK'
We all know, what SICK means in general
when someone is ill or something like that...
but in English as a Slang, it means a bit different
In English, as a slang it means that something is very amazing or excellent
for example...
She looks sick in that Dress.
and I overacted
We just went to Nikhil's Party last night. I mean it was SICK! I wanna go back again.
and I overacted again!!!
The 2nd slang is 'binge-watch'
Don't we all sometimes watch the whole season at once?
Watching one episode after other and again and again...
That is what known as 'binge-watch'
For example...
I just binge-watched 13 reasons why and I love that show now!
The 3rd slang is Butt-Dial
Sometimes #accidentally we call someone on our phone while it's inside our pocket or while sitting
So, that call that's an accident is known as butt-dial.
For example...
Hey, I think you butt-dialed me yesterday.
You called me and then it was just noise.
The 4th slang is 'BAIL'
We all have heard of this word 'BAIL', at least in Bollywood movies
Someone's inside jail? Let's bail him out...
But in English, it's a bit different
In English, it means 'Leaving suddenly/Abrubtly'
Suppose, you go with your friends to watch cinema and then you realized
Oh F**K! I forget to do the homework!!!
So, you'll say
Hey guys, I'm sorry. I'm gonna bail!
The 5th slang is Feeling Blue
It simply means 'to feel sad'
If I'm saying that I'm feeling blue that means I'm feeling sad
The 6th slang is 'by the skin of my teeth'
In Hindi, we can phrase it as 'Baal Baal Bache'
For example...
I managed to pass my exam by the skin of my teeth.
The 7th slang is couch-potato
Couch-potato is a person who sits on the sofa all day and does nothing!
Like a friend of mine...
So, that's all guys!!!
If you like this video, then please like and subscribe
And if you ever feel like sharing it, then don't hesitate Brother and...
Brother