Friends, this is the
First Class in Emirates.
Friends, our tickets have been
upgraded to the First Class.
The lounges are up ahead,
and there's even a gym here.
A gym in the airport!
This one?
I thought it was that one.
Fast Lane.
Is this your fast lane pass?
Fast Lane pass ready!
Our gate is at C
they told us it'd take half an hour
to reach there by walking.
This airport is so huge that
you can walk for half an hour in it
all within the same building.
This is the poster of Spirit of Dubai.
But this woman in the painting
seems to be carrying the Indian flag.
Quite an international painting.
People of all kinds.
And even some Mongolian army.
And we're at their First Class Lounge.
And the Business Class Lounge
is on the other side.
So actually, we were rejected from
the First Class Lounge,
because they said that the upgrades,
do not include access to the Lounge.
Even though our seats got upgraded,
the upgrade doesn't allow us to go to the Lounge.
So we're not fully in First Class.
We're actually half a class.
*Such an insult.*
There's a golden palm tree at the airport.
Look at those gold bars.
No, you're doing it to the Business Class,
you need to do it to the...
This is a Boeing 777 plane,
Airbus A380 is better than this.
Because that has 2 floors.
This is the same.
I'd say that this is the second best.
What's our seat?
Wow, there's so much space!
I don't see any place to
store the bags above us.
Wow.
They've even provided us slippers.
It literally feels like a room, you know?
Like you booked a hotel room or something.
They've kept flowers there.
Oh, yeah?
Once you close this, and that one,
we'll kind of have our own little cave.
There are so many mirrors here.
The one that you can see here,
is the TV.
The real mirror is here,
in case you need to put on make-up.
There's a mirror at the side,
behind the lamp.
There's a mirror at the bar,
so that you can check out the drinks stored here.
There's a mirror at the back too.
The seat is less of a seat
and more of a mirror maze.
And we've taken off.
Most of the seats in the
First Class are empty.
If I zoom in a lot,
I can see the Burj Khalifa.
See, there it is.
Let me reduce the brightness a bit.
They have an accurate map here.
Look at how fast the plane is flying.
The seat belt sign has been turned off,
let me take out the tripod
so that I can show you everything properly.
By pushing this button,
this door closes.
Now that the doors have closed,
this has turned into a room of sorts.
No one can peek in from the outside,
because the doors are quite tall.
And there's a barrier between me and Juli as well.
This one.
By raising this one,
this will become a proper room.
See you.
Do you see how high these are?
From both sides.
The only thing missing is a roof on top.
But there's no roof,
It's just empty space above us.
Above this height,
and above this height here.
So if I stand up,
I can easily peek in.
Even so, as I told you,
there's a lot of privacy.
Let me open this one,
Because there's some nice light here.
Pull Here To Open.
Since this isn't allowing me to pull,
we'll have to push the button.
And now let's take a look at the menu.
The menu here is so good.
There're so many dishes for you.
And such posh dishes.
Like, see this one.
Honey Roasted Pumpkin with Thyme.
Pan Fried King Oyster Mushroom.
I will order this dish.
And don't be misled with the word 'Oyster',
this is a vegan dish.
Oyster Mushroom is a type of mushroom.
Not oyster.
Award-winning triple cream blue cheese from Germany.
Well, that is fancy.
Premium aged Dutch gouda.
Handmade red...
How do you pronounce that?
Juli has already made her bed here.
Actually, they've even provided mattresses here.
So you can take out the mattress,
before you lie down,
and there are pillows obviously.
And a blanket as well.
You can see how spacious this is
when you look from above.
Look how much space I have to spread out.
My feet are still not reaching the end.
There's so much extra space in here.
So do you wanna work on something?
Or write down any ideas?
Just press that thing there.
What thing?
This board.
-This?
-Yeah.
-This one?
Oh.
Wow.
They gave you a whole notebook.
With an Emirates plane.
-I'm gonna work.
-Work on the next video ideas?
We've closed both doors here.
Juli is going to sleep,
and no one will come to disturb us,
so I think this is the best time
do the most exciting thing.
What's the most exciting thing?
The various buttons that we have here,
and the different secret compartments,
let's explore those.
First of all, here.
This opens and closes the door.
With this, the table tray comes out,
And this makes the bed.
So let's turn this seat into a bed.
Wow!
Look at the width of this bed.
I have big hands,
I span 15 cm approximately,
so I think the bed is 45cm-50cm wide.
The blanket is here,
there's the mattress,
Juli has already laid down her mattress.
Apart from this, there's a small iPad here,
this controls the TV screen.
And there's a compartment here.
You can store your phone here.
Right above it, are these buttons,
that moves this barrier.
What is this thing?
This looks like a fan of sorts.
I don't know which button turns this on.
And with the buttons here,
these lights can be turned on and off.
This button controls the brightness of the lights.
You can control the brightness as well.
There are so many settings here.
Press.
What happened?
What did this open?
Oh, I got it, this basically
is pressed to bring out this iPad,
and this button locks it.
There are two more buttons.
Let's press them and see what happens.
Oh wow, it's ascending in style.
This drinks area moves up a bit by pressing this.
And pressing it again, send it back.
Oh.
What's this thing?
Wow.
So big.
This is so huge.
That was some quality sleep here.
Since this bed is so spacious,
Sleeping normally, on your back,
though it is possible in business class,
but you can't move from one side to the other.
You have to sleep straight on your back.
But there's so much space here,
you can sleep on your sides,
and even fold your legs and sleep.
You can do it all.
It is so spacious.
And the mattress that they've provided,
this is so comfortable.
Food's about to come.
Let's see how the food will be.
I'm watching the movie
Bunty and Babli 2.
I haven't watched it before.
Even the screen's so big.
This is their Mango Avacado Salad.
And this is the first course.
Friends, the main course has arrived.
This main dish looks like a meat dish,
but these are oyster mushrooms.
A seasonal salad with it,
and the pumpkin side dish.
And a delicious feast is ready here.
Friends, can you see this?
This is unbelievably good.
After experiencing luxury at this level,
the only point of concern is that
whenever we travel next,
how will any experience match up to this?
We'll be disappointed.
So after I made the video on cold drinks,
you might wonder what I drink
since I don't drink cold drinks,
other than drinking water.
I've ordered a virgin mojito here.
A virgin mojito contains water and lime juice,
and sugar.
If you reduce the amount of sugar in it,
to relatively, there's nothing harmful in it.
Like this one has little to no sugar.
Very little sugar.
If you want to drink this,
keep in mind that normally,
virgin mojito contains a lot of sugar,
but if you drink it with only a little sugar,
Normally they make it with soft drink.
Pour some soft drink,
then lime juice, and mint.
This one hardly has any, if any,
sugar or soft drink,
so it's more like sparkling water,
with lime juice and mint.
And it's extremely refreshing.
Even the bread basket was special here.
When I took out a bread from here,
it turned out to be garlic bread.
See the garlic stuffing in it.
Another big difference,
are the headphones you get.
Look at these, they look so high quality.
And everyone gets a snack basket.
And it has everything.
It has some nuts, some trail mix,
gummy bears.
Chocolate, of which I already ate a piece.
And some vegetable chips.
Let's see what's going on here.
Oh, they booked the VIP package.
What is that?
Let's stick to work.
There's a hilarious scene in the movie.
When the Bunty-Babli song plays.
So they say Masha'Allah in the song,
and the subtitles write it as Hallelujah.
Wait, you'll see now.
It's interesting to read the subtitles.
To see how things have been translated,
sometimes the translations are really weird.
There are some things that I've still not understood,
What are they actually?
There are always some undecipherable things.
Like this one over here.
It seems like a speaker.
But what's the purpose of having a speaker?
For announcements?
Yeah.
If you look at the quality of the things
in comparison to the normal seats
or business class seats,
they're of high quality.
They're a fabric layer here,
this isn't just plastic.
It's real gold.
This is real gold?
I don't think so.
That would be too much.
Another interesting thing here,
this is a light,
that's normal,
But this is the AC vent.
I've finally figured out how to turn it on.
It turns on like this,
and blows so much air,
you can literally dry your hair.
If you look at the bottom here,
there's a charger here,
you can close this.
Another USB charger here.
And a belt that you can pull out.
I think the purpose of this belt is different.
Because there's another belt lower than the first.
And I think both belts can be attached there,
and keep the bags secure.
in case the bags are moving about.
Talking about the corner spaces,
there's a corner space here,
what have they put there?
This is a small compartment.
I might just be an empty space.
And the magazines and headphones were placed here.
These two doors,
that's actually one door,
the blinds point down.
We can look down from the inside,
but someone outside at eye level,
won't be able to look inside.
This is the first seat where you can
fold your legs and sit.
Whenever I watch a film,
I regret it because
On this flight of 5-6 hours,
I feel like watching a movie here is a waste of time.
That I'm missing out on a chance to enjoy.
Each minute spent on this seat,
should be fully enjoyed,
not wasted by watching a movie.
That's what I'm feeling repeatedly.
This is another unique angle here.
I'm showing you the seat from all angles
so that you get the best idea.