"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"One, two, three!
And one, two, three!"
"Listen from the above
to one, two, three!"
"Yeah!"
"One, two three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"One, two, three!
And One, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
"Tolerating
thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
"Darling, don't leave me!"
"Don't break my heart!"
"You are under the oath of my oath."
"Say you want to know."
"I am beat and here we go."
"Mamma, you like move."
"Move, come on."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Free! Free!"
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
"Absolutely!"
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
"Tolerating thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
"Darling, don't leave me!"
"Don't break my heart!"
"Darling, don't leave me.."
"Don't break my heart.."
"You are under the oath of my oath."
"Your youth is the most
talked about everywhere."
"My heart has been waiting for you."
"You are under the oath of my oath."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!" "Free!
"Going from the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
"Free."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"One, two, three! And one, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
"Tolerating thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
"Let's take out the one, two, and three."
'This country! Our country!
The rising country!'
'The leader of our rising country!'
'This is a business man.'
'And this is the business of a man.'
'And this is the rising don!
Laxminarayan! No. 1!'
Who is Mumbai's king?
'I mean, he is a brother son!'
Brother son, what's that, brother!
Just like there is star son!
Just like that, there is Brother son.
Sunny Deol, Bobby Deol, Hrithik Roshan..
..Sanjay Dutt, Abhishek Bachchan.
You are the
Abhishek Bachchan of hooliganism.
Your father, Pappu MMS.
Was the Amitabh Bachchan of hooliganism!
'And today his refugee is being released.'
'That means his first murder, killing.'
I have to kill you.
What have I done?
You dare seize brother Batlya's land.
Why you..
- No! No!
Kill him, brother.
Kill him Laxmi!
- Kill him, brother.
'But will his first
killing be hit or a flop.'
Who are you?
Aslam Phoda! Chikne! Tell her.
Who is Mumbai's king?
Who is it? - Brother, right now
she seems to be king and King Kong.
Hit them.
'Poor Laxminarayan.'
'Brother Batlya tried to
explain Laxminarayan's mother a lot.'
What did he explain?
'Laxmi's mother!
Bullet fired from the gun..
..and the child that's
once born cannot go back.'
'But only a mother knows her pain.'
I thought you will commit 2-4 murders.
'Settle down in life.'
I will get you married to
Chhota Khujli's daughter..
..Meena Khujli, but you
turned out to be useless.
Slowly mother!
Laxmi's mother!
Laxmi's mother! Laxmi..
Kanta!
Go and do all this at your home.
Brother! Brother,
give me another chance.
Dear..
..you never get to hit two
fours on the same ball..
..and you never get a second
chance in the same lifetime.
Laxminarayan, there can't
be another foot like you..
..in the entire world.
"I am helpless and useless."
Wow!
"Helpless.."
'It means hopeless.'
This..
Biting! Biting!
- What?
The shoe is biting me.
- Then you bite the shoe.
Hey! Hey! Hey listen, thief!
'This is Laxminarayan No.2!
MBA from Jharkhand university.'
'He has only two rules in his life.'
'Rule no. 1, the boss is always right.'
'Rule no. 2, if the boss is wrong..
..then follow rule number 1.'
Mr. Laxminarayan!
- Yes sir.
I think we need to have a little talk.
- Yes sir. - Sit.
On the sofa or the chair, sir?
Chair!
- Left or right sir? - Left!
Your left or my left, sir?
My left!
This left or the extreme left sir?
Get out of this door!
Now just leave, you idiot! Idiot!
Sir, I came in through that door.
There are two doors! Shall
I go from here or there?
Just get out! Get out, you idiot!
Get out of my office now! - Okay.
"It's a secret matter."
"May we be together!"
"Wear my inner wears,
whether it is day or night."
Come, come.
Take it, sister, take whatever you want.
Take a look.
God knows where they
come from to sell underwear.
Brother, buy an underwear.
- I don't want it.
They are very nice underwear, buy it.
I don't want it.
Buy it! If you wear it yourself,
you will turn into Superman.
It won't tear if you fly wearing it.
If you fight with someone
wearing it, it won't tear.
If you climb the Qutub Minar
If you jump from the Qutub
Minar wearing it, it won't tear.
Everything you wear will tear,
but not the underwear.
That's Laxminarayan's guarantee.
My head will surely explode
because of your blabbering.
Shall I give it to you in writing?
I told you, I have underwear.
If you do, then why don't you wear it?
How do you know I
haven't worn underwear?
You know my nature.
'And this is Laxminarayan No. 3!
And he says.'
I can tell you what's written in
the letter seeing the envelope.
I can tell the son's
size by looking at the papa.
How nice.
'He has been selling underwear and vests..
..since he didn't even wear underwear.'
'By selling underwear and vests..
..he has started a garment factory.'
'Bulbul Lingerie's.'
This is the first and..
Ballu, what's going on?
- Dad. Who are they?
Dad, they are our brand's models.
And right now, we are
having a photo session.
Are they models, or just cluster of bones?
It seems as if they have
fallen ill wearing our lingerie!
Then who will buy our product?
We will have to wear all of them.
And the underwear is okay,
you and I can wear it.
Who will wear that? Your father?
Dad, please don't say underwear,
Say lingerie for God sake.
- Keep quiet.
You fool.
What's all this going on?
'Uncle Shakespeare had said,
what's in the name.'
'But uncle forgot, what if
when three names are similar?'
'Laxminarayan 1!'
Laxminarayan 2!
Laxminarayan 3!
"One, two, three!"
Hiralal!
- Yes.
The diamond is worth 20 crores..
..and the entire journey is by road.
- Yes.
Go comfortably, and
bring the diamond. - Yes.
Take this 2 rupee note.
Son. You will get that
diamond worth 20 crores..
..only when you will give him
this half torn 2 rupee note.
I swear what an idea.
Really nice!
Brother, don't be tensed.
I am there.
Now I will bring that
diamond from that Pondi!
Challenge.
"Don't ever stop!"
"You got to rock."
"Since I saw you, I was amazed."
"Your eyes wounded me."
"Your intoxication immersed in my veins."
"Your beauty mesmerised me."
"You got to rock, darling."
"Don't ever stop, darling."
"My beloved."
"My heart fell for you
that's not a mistake."
"Stay in my arm that's my only desire."
"I said to the Lord, my darling."
"I thank you."
"My heart is in pain."
"Now you decide my fate."
"You got to rock, darling."
"Don't ever stop, darling."
"My beloved."
"All I ever talk about is you."
"Your fragrance lights up my world."
"My life belongs only to you."
"Only your image is immersed in my eyes."
"Whichever path now you will walk on."
"My destination lies there."
"Come my darling,
my craziness is telling me."
"I am now your lover."
"Darling! My heart says!"
"Come and listen to the saga of my heart."
"Darling, you are my companion!"
"Your intoxication is growing."
"Don't make me restless anymore.
No! No! No!"
"Your gait is the best."
"Do me a favour, accept me."
"You got to rock, darling."
"Don't ever stop, darling."
"My beloved."
"You got to rock, darling."
"Don't ever stop, darling."
"My beloved."
"You got to rock, darling."
"Don't ever stop, darling."
"My beloved."
"You got to rock, darling."
"Don't ever stop, darling."
"My beloved."
Hira stop!
Stop Hira! I know you have the diamond.
We are very dangerous people.
He isn't listening to us.
He is still running, idiot.
Kill him.
Don't touch me!
You don't love me anymore, isn't it?
I love you my bubblaboo!
How romantic.
Say, Chandu loves Chandni.
Chandu loves Chandni.
It sounds so nice.
Keep saying it.
Are you mad?
I mean, let me show it too sweet heart.
Let me show it too.
I didn't do anything.
Chandu, there is someone.. at the window.
There is no one. Come baby, come.
What happened?
See! Really! Chandu, there
really is someone there.
There is nobody there.
- There is someone.
What is it?
Why are you peeking in the
car and scaring my girlfriend?
Brother, I am not scaring her?
Take a look at my back?
Why should I look at your back? Get lost.
Brother, for Gods sake,
take a look at my back.
I am not like that.
- I am not like that too.
Brother. Please, take a look at my back.
Help me! I have been shot in the back!
Take a look at my back!
Oh yes!
O my God, come on.
Run! Run!
- Come on, quickly.
Start it!
- Come on, run quickly.
Brother please this bottle..
- This bottle.
Batlya!
- Chandu!
9820.. 123.
- Leave me!
Albert, they are running away.
Albert, you deal with him.
I will stop the car.
Girl and boy, stop the car.
- Chandu.
I will count till three.
1..
- Faster.
2.. stop, 3!
You cannot die!
Shall I shoot you?
The boy and girl ran away, sad travelling.
Pinto, this Hira is dead.
And that diamond.
Fake diamond.
Take it out.
I hate tooth aches.
Tooth.. one!
- And people, two.
Papa will be happily shocked to see it.
Yes!
This is the 20 crore diamond.
"Everybody say dance."
Do you know why I call myself papa?
Why papa?
Because D'mello's Yadav,
only knows how to get.
Pa.. pa!
Papa!
"You idiots."
And you left the 20 crore worth diamond,
right there.
"You idiots."
No papa, no. Not the current, papa.
"Everybody say dance."
Pinto.
- Yes papa.
You know, we get electricity
only for 2 hours in the entire day.
Shortage, papa, shortage.
And that too, you make me waste.
Yes papa.
Tell me, where is the diamond.
No!
- Tell me.
Gods!
Like every time, there is a
power failure this time too, papa.
Now, it will return only tomorrow, papa.
Shabbo!
- Papa!
When there is a power failure,
where does it go?
In the invertors, papa.
Then switch on the invertors.
- Okay, papa.
"You idiots."
Is this a joke?
We are somebody's children too.
We forget things too, papa.
You have invented these bombs, isn't it?
Yes papa, I have made it.
I have a crash course diploma papa,
in making bombs.
Now this bomb will kill you both.
Papa, may you never have a power failure!
One's..
- No Papa!
Two's!
- No Pinto!
Tell me where is the diamond?
But I don't know anything, Papa!
"You idiots."
"You came to search me."
- And three!
No.
Papa, it didn't explode.
Why doesn't it explode?
Papa, you have planted the bomb here..
..and operating the remote from there.
How can it explode?
Come in the range.
Should I sit on the
bomb and press the button?
What kind of a bomb have you made?
Why doesn't it explode?
Papa, don't hit me.
Don't doubt the inventor.
I can't make a mistake in making the bomb.
I have done a crash course diploma.
Show me the remote.
Here.
See this. - Papa, you have
placed the battery wrongly.
Oh!
- Now you say oh! Interchange it.
And now see how it explodes.
See.
That's all.
It was simple, isn't it papa?
At least now tell me where is the diamond.
Chandni, look at this diamond.
Our fate will shine like this too.
Now I won't have to do this sales job.
We won't have to live in
this car showroom's washroom.
We won't have to listen to Laila madam.
Let's run away.
You idiot, they must be looking for us.
The situation will calm down,
then we will..
Till then, we will have to
keep this diamond in a place..
..where no one can see it.
I have an idea.
What?
Why did you put it in the petrol tank?
Look, no one will be able to see it here!
Even I can't see it.
- This car is for sale.
What if someone comes to buy it?
No one has come to buy
it for the last 7 months..
..why will anyone come now?
The death of a man, and
the mistress of a woman..
..you can never save
yourself from them.
And Yadav's death has been decided.
Kill him!
Whom should we send, brother?
After Hira's murder, the police
has become very alert in Pondi.
Brother! Brother! Brother! Brother!
Greetings, brother!
Greet him!
- Greetings.
I have heard, there is a
shooter's post vacant with you.
Give my son one
chance to commit a murder.
As long as I am alive,
he makes his career.
Gets settled.
Give my Laxmi this contract.
Give him please.
Yes brother, I will put in all my
effort for committing this murder.
There is no chance that I will fail.
And if he fails this time,
then he is a big fool. I tell you.
A bloomed rose and a stomach upset..
..doesn't stay forever!
- Yes brother.
This time I am completely sure..
..that Laxminarayan will
surely commit this murder.
Thank you, brother.
Brother, I will always be
indebted to you. - That's enough.
Keep this. It is imported.
It will fire so stealthily..
..even you won't know that
the bullet has been fired.
But brother, whom do I have to kill?
Poets have fans, and walls have ears.
Go to Pondi!
Your room will be booked
in hotel Blue Diamond.
You will find an envelope in the room.
The person whose photo
will be in the envelope..
..you will have to kill him.
Brother.. brother..
- Just a minute.
First you will have to
take my diamond back from him.
I want that diamond back at any cost.
Don't worry, brother.
Take some marijuana and go to sleep.
- Very good.
Now I will directly hit the target.
Laxminarayan! This is the
first time I have heard this name.
Papa, this is a very inauspicious time.
Let us flee to the village.
We are in the village.
Papa. Let us go in the city,
the car is ready. - Idiots.
I will give him a torturous death.
Pinto.
- Papa!
Make such a bomb that will explode.
Laxminarayan will come,
but he won't go back alive.
Hello sir! Morning sir!
Laxmi, you idiot, you stupid, you fool!
Listen to me carefully!
- Yes.
I have seen an old car on the net.
Car, wow sir! How is it sir?
I want to buy this car!
Go to Pondi right now.
Check the car and give
them 1 lakh rupees advance.
Alright, you understood that?
- Right, sir.
I will mail you the other details.
Please check your e-mail.
Which mail sir, g-mail,
yahoo mail, hotmail, rediff mail.
Or the new mail these days sir, zapak mail.
It delivers quickly, sir.
Idiot.
I will fax you through the computer..
..switch on the fax machine.
- Yes sir.
Sir, there are two fax machines.
Which one should I switch on?
The left or the right.
Left one!
- Your left or mine.
My left!
- Which position are you in sir?
I cannot see it on the phone.
Because if you are sitting in front of me..
..then your left is my right.
And my right will be your left, sir.
And if you are sitting besides me..
..then your left is my left
and your right is my right.
Laxmi!
- Because sir..
This is the last chance for you.
If you don't do this right,
then I will fire you!
Understood!
I understood, sir.
Go to Pondi right now.
And stay in hotel Blue Diamond.
Blue Diamond! The room will be booked.
Okay I will send all the details there.
Understood?
Okay sir.
Remember, I want this car at any cost.
I want to gift it to my wife.
Which wife, sir?
The one in Worli or the one in Bandra?
You idiot! I will.. in you!
You fool..
Yes sir.
Why is the boss always so angry?
What are you doing madam?
When Laila buys a car to sell,
she checks it properly!
Madam, my car.
I cannot sell your car.
Not just you, no one
can sell my car now.
You are Laila!
- Yes.
You see, we are from ICUC bank.
You had taken a loan of
25 lakh from our bank?
Yes!
And you haven't paid a single installment..
..for the past 10 months.
Actually I..
- No problem, ma'am.
We are always at your disposal,
at your service.
Actually, we had come
to give you a notice.
What notice?
If you don't deposit all your
installments within 5 days..
..then we will seize all of your cars.
What? You cannot do that.
We can do that madam, because..
..we are idiots and fools.
I will call the police.
We are the police.
We work part time with
the bank for recovery.
Okay madam, have a good day.
If you are satisfied with
our services tell others..
..if not, tell us. Take care. Come on.
Yes sister, what do you want?
Give me a size 40 bra in this material.
40! Fine. My dear beloved..
This one looks good too, isn't it?
- Yes, I like it.
Yes!
- Hey dad, what's up?
What are you doing?
I am taking sister's bra out.
Don't say bra, panty and all, please.
Shut up, you fool.
What else will I call it as? A pajama?
I have been selling it since
you didn't even start wearing it.
Here sister, 42, it will be a perfect fit.
Listen to me..
- Brother, not 42, give me 40.
42 will be a perfect fit.
I told you I don't
want 42, give me 40.
What are you talking? How do you know?
Surprising! It is my size,
who else will know about it?
Seeing the blouse I can
tell the size of the bra..
..and seeing the pant..
..I can tell you the size
of the underwear. - Oh God.
You know my nature.
- Yes.
Yes, absolutely right.
Her husband asks me about her size.
Fine brother.
Come on, that will be 150.
- Here.
Yes, tell me.
At least give me a bag, brother.
What will you do with a bag..
..you have to go home and wear it..
Fine brother, fine. Tell me.
You have to leave everything,
and urgently go to Pondi.
You have to meet the designer..
..who has created our
new valentine collection.
Actually, I have seen the
designs on the net. Yes.
You just have to go and make
an agreement with the girl.
I will go to Pondi, you don't worry.
You relax in Singapore, fine.
If you like the designs,
then give her 1 lakh rupees.
She will need it.
- Okay.
What is her name?
Billu Batra!
- Not yours.
Leave that bra! Leave that bra!
Get lost!
Yes, tell me.
Please pen some things down.
This pen doesn't even work.
Let it be dad. Just reach Pondi
and go to hotel Blue Diamond..
..I will courier you the
pictures and all the details. Ok.
Please papa. Please don't
say bra and panty there.
Keep quiet, you fool.
Let me take a look at her design.
I am a designer.
And my brand Pure
Diamonds will be famous soon.
The entire world will
wear my undergarments!
Wow!
Neither less nor more! Bubblegum!
Oh God, this man eats my
brains and gives me a headache.
He doesn't have brains at all.
I don't understand what should I do now?
Please leave from here.
It's simple Ms. Jia.
Either you leave or throw me out.
Actually, your first
papa and my second papa..
..were partners in this restaurant.
So either you buy this restaurant from us..
..or sell it to us.
You know I don't have
the money to buy it.
Why don't you take half?
Happiness, sorrows and bubblegum!
These are the things
M.M. Munde never takes in half.
The entire world knows that.
I will pay your money gradually.
How gradually, Ms. Jia.
Tomorrow my client is coming to meet me.
They will surely like my designs.
And then Jia's doors of
destiny will finally open.
Come at 12 o'clock and take your money.
Okay! Okay Ms. Jai!
Tomorrow whether you lose or I will.
For now, I am, leaving.
"I cannot live without you."
O God, Jia is not a fraud!
Laxminarayan should like my designs.
Laxmi!
- Mother.
Here is your ticket.
And listen son,
commit the murder nicely.
Now, you leave mother.
And remember, don't eat
anything anyone gives you.
These criminals mix some
intoxication in the food..
..and give you to eat.
- Really.
And then they steal your luggage.
- Yes mother.
Remember, don't tell
your name to anyone.
And yes.
- This is 25,000!
It will be useful to you in a foreign land.
Mother, that's enough. Don't cry!
Have you taken the gun?
- Yes mother.
Have you loaded the bullets?
Yes mother.
- Take care of yourself.
My son is going to commit a
murder for the first time.
Mother, you don't worry.
Please stop crying.
Nothing is better than a gun, and
don't regret if you lose it. Toys.
Sorry! I am buying it for the child.
I don't have 1 lakh rupees in my bag.
Oh! Wife children..
- Excuse me, sir.
Which bus goes to Pondi?
The one behind you! Wife children..
- Excuse me, sir.
The left one or the right one sir?
The one that just left, that one.
- Oh, God.
Stop! Hello! Hello
Hello!!
No one is listening. Hello!
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
Brother, what are you looking at?
This is Pahadganj's good.
- What?
This is Karolbaug's piece.
This can't be Karolbaug's piece.
This is Pahadganj's piece,
this is Khurana's goods!
She doesn't belong to Khurana,
she is my wife.
I am not talking about your wife..
..I am talking about your
wife's bra, this is Khurana's goods.
Khurana sells such goods.
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
Absolutely.
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"One, two, three!
And One, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
Have we reached?
Why is there police up ahead?
My name is Mayawati Chowtala!
Come on, all of you open your luggage.
Come on, all of you.
Uncle. Open your bag.
Take a look! There isn't anything wrong!
And you know my nature.
Why? Are you my husband?
Your nature depends on my future.
This.. what is this?
- There is this one too.
What is all this?
- All of this belongs to me.
Do you wear all this?
No, I sell it.
I had come here for
business so I brought is along.
I thought if I sell some pieces..
..then it would be enough
for my bus fare too. Okay.
Get out of here!
- Fine, I will set it up there..
Come. "Wear my inner wears,
whether it is day or night."
He has set up a shop.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Come. Madam, it's a wonderful piece.
It will fit perfectly.
Yes, you come, Mr. Chavanprash.
No ma'am, you have got it wrong.
I am not Mr. Chavanprash.
I am Mr. Laxminarayan, ma'am.
Come on, open your bag.
Which one ma'am,
the left one or the right one?
The left one, come on.
Ma'am, your left or mine.
Were you born in a military family..
..that you are doing left right?
Come on, show me that one.
Open the zip.
Ma'am, there are two zips.
Should I open the one in the
front or the one in the back?
Tek Chand.
- Yes madam.
Take him away.
Open all his zips and search him.
And where you don't find a zip,
tear it, put a zip there..
..then open it and search it!
Madam, you are getting me wrong ma'am.
Listen to me ma'am.
- Take him away. - Come to the side.
Sir which side, this side or that side?
Come straight with me.
- Okay.
Come.
All the goods are sold, this
is the last one remaining.
For you.
Where is Ganda Nala?
Why uncle, do you want to clean it?
No. There is the hotel
Blue Diamond besides it.
I have to go there.
Can you see that buffalo, straight.
- Yes.
Follow him.
He bathes everyday in Ganda Nala.
Go.
- Fine. Hey stop..
See. If you can see, left
is left and right is right.
Then what happens basically..
..is that, left for you is right for me..
..and left for you is not..
- Forgive me, Lord.
Madam, you are
unnecessarily wasting my time.
There is nothing in my bag.
That I can see that you are a
sensation without the weapon.
Still show me the bag.
Fine. Take a look what's in it?
Look, there is a pant.
What is this, comb!
This is fried snack, mother had given it.
And this is my.. gun.
Where did this come from?
No, no excuse me, that gun..
Lay down your weapon and surrender.
I will do that, but first let
me think where did it come from?
Lay it down or else..
I will thrash you black and blue.
No madam, please don't
come forward, please.
Please!
- A fool like you will shoot me.
I will shoot you in the mouth and
it will come out though the ear.
Why you..
You killed a 'Jaatni'.
He shot the madam, the
station has become a widower.
Madam, are you fine?
- Move back.
Ma'am! Ma'am! Ma'am! Please Ma'am!
You dare scare a
Jaatni with a water gun!
If I don't teach you a lesson,
my name isn't Mayawati Chowtala.
Ma'am, sorry ma'am!
Honestly speaking this gun belongs to me.
I bought it because holi is approaching.
But I was scared seeing you physique..
..and I put the gun in his bag.
He is an honest boy,
ma'am, please leave him.
Please ma'am.
Spare him.
- Yes ma'am.
Tek Chand.
Gentleman is asking to spare him.
Let him go.
- Thank you madam. Go!
Thank you, ma'am. I am highly obliged!
I think I should take
your leave now. Thank you!
You will have to give
an application for that.
I didn't understand that.
I obliged you..
..won't you oblige me?
You are too much into
left right isn't it?
Ma'am, please ma'am.
- Come on.
It is not about the
question of obligation ma'am!
After a long time I have
caught a sweet man like you.
I won't let you go without a kiss.
Ma'am, please.
- Come on. Ma'am, please.
Where are you going?
- There.
Where?
- In the left.
Your left or mine.
Madam. Madam, senior sir has called.
He would want me to
massage his wife again.
Ma'am, please let me go, please.
Today I am on duty.
Otherwise a beauty like you has
never escaped me. - Thank you, ma'am.
Tek Chand.
- Yes ma'am.
Take down his name and address
and let him go. - Fine madam.
Come on, lets go.
- Yes sir.
I know you must want
me to massage madam.
Yes. - I am very sorry.
You are very smart..
..you don't seem from
the face but you are.
But how did you slip the gun
in my bag, I am surprised.
You were standing in front of me..
..and I was behind you.
What do you mean, show it to me?
Of course.
You were standing in front of me..
..and I was behind you.
You were looking on the left.
Your left! Complete left.
I came slyly..
- But your other bag was on the left.
Remembered.
- Oh yes.
You were standing in front
of me and I was behind you.
You were looking on the left.
I came slyly opened you zip
and slipped the gun in your bag.
Did you know?
- No.
But did you know?
- What do you mean?
Here is your gun.
You met me here, don't meet me there.
Understood.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
How can I help you sir?
I don't even take my
father's help, you know my nature.
No sir, I don't know sir.
But I know your nature.
Your size is 52, but you wear size 48.
48? How do you know, sir?
If it would have been 52, then
you wouldn't be adjusting it!
Tell me, which room
is booked in my name?
Your name?
- Laxminarayan!
Laxminarayan!
Room 504, sir.
- 504, fine.
Listen.
- Yes sir.
There should have been
a letter in my name.
Just a minute sir, I will check it.
Here sir.
Fine! Come sir I will show you the room.
- Come.
Excuse me.
- Yes sir.
In which room is Laxminalayan!
Laxminalayan or Laxminarayan?
Laxminalayan! Not Nalayan, Nalayan.
Give me a moment, I will just check.
Excuse me sir, there is no
one here by the name of..
..Mr. Laxminalayan!
- He is not.
Wait for a wait!
He will come! He will come!
Welcome sir!
- Hey typing!
There will be a booking in my name.
Your name, sir.
Think, Laxminarayan,
or what will the people think?
What is he..
Hello.
No sir!
I am not like that, sir.
You are getting me wrong,
sir. I am not like that, sir.
I am from a good family, sir.
Sir, my name, sir..
See my card, sir, I am Laxminarayan sir.
Move aside.
- What? Laxminarayan!
No sir, Laxminarayan!
I was searching for you.
- Why sir?
Come in the corner.
- No sir.
I don't use oil or cream, sir.
Come in the corner..
- I am not like that sir.
I will never do it again sir.
I beg of you sir.
- Come in!
I am a gentleman, sir.
- Go inside.
What are you doing, sir?
I am not feeling like it, sir?
You can force me.
What are you doing, sir?
Sir, I am not like that, sir..
Someone has given you wrong information.
My pant was drenched
that's why I was doing that.
Sir, please sir.
Here, catch.
- No, I won't.
The boss has given it. Here.
The boss had said.
It has the complete information,
isn't it?
The job should be taken care of.
It will be done.
Otherwise your career.
- No career, sir.
I beg of you, sir. The job will be
taken care of. - Okay, take care.
The job will be taken care of.
You are..
Your keys, Mr. Laxminarayan!
No, don't take my name.
Laxminarayan! Don't take the name.
I am not talking to you, there is
a courier for Laxminarayan. Yes.
It's for me. You are Laxminarayan?
- Yes.
Is he Laxminarayan?
Yes, he is Mr. Laxminarayan!
Oh, so you are Laxminarayan!
Sorry, I didn't know you are Laxminarayan!
But now it's confirmed
that you are Laxminarayan!
Take this and sign here Laxminarayan..
..where it is written Laxminarayan.
Thank you Mr. Laxminarayan!
Yes Laxminarayan!
"Enlightened men have said."
"Everyone feels young at heart."
"When it is our turn."
"The expiry date always turns old."
Is she showing the lingerie
design or design of the car!
"The entire world was empty."
"There wasn't anyone crazy in love."
"Or any uselessness."
Do I have to kill her? But why?
"There wasn't anyone crazy in love."
"Yes, sir"
"Spiderman. Spiderman."
Mr. Pipite wants to buy this car.
- "Spiderman."
"Spiderman." - Its better if
he buys a cycle for his wife.
"Spiderman."
Laila!
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Tolerating
thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
Have you seen this newspaper?
It's written, diamonds
worth 20 crore leads to murder.
20 crore worth diamond..
This diamond is worth 20 crore.
O my God Chandu, then
we should take it out.
Hey! Have my fear my dear.
Tonight we will open the tank
and take the diamond out. - Really?
Yes. - We'll have a great fun.
How much money will we..
10 lakh.
This car has been sold in 10 lakh.
What? This car!
It's sold. How is that possible?
That's what I am thinking.
The car which no one even came
to take a look at for 7 months.
Someone is coming to buy it.
Who is coming? Laxminarayan.
Today this car won't go anywhere..
..because today at 11
o'clock Mr. Laxminarayan..
..is coming to take a look at the car.
So both of you make this car shine..
..so that he is dazzled by
the car's shine. - Okay.
Hello. Come and take
your advance at 2 o'clock.
Mr. Laxminarayan is
coming at 11 o'clock!
Chandni! Chandni! What are you doing?
What will we do now Chandu?
We will lose the
diamond along with the car.
Idea, we won't let
Laxminarayan reach here.
We will kidnap him on the way. Really!
I have to close this deal today.
I have to impress
everyone with my charm.
You have to do it, you have no option.
Ok? Let's go.
Morning sir!
Laxminarayan, nice meeting you sir.
No good! No good! No good!
Hi, Laxminarayan.
How do you know the name?
Sir I know it since my childhood.
Who told you?
Of course sir, my papa.
And who told your papa?
Naturally sir, he will know it.
He buys underwear and
vests from my shop..
..then he will surely know my name.
Laxminarayan,
underwear and vest seller.
My name is Laxminarayan.
You..
- Yes, and you know my nature.
There is a lot of confusion sir.
Sir, my name is Laxminarayan
and I don't know your nature.
And I don't want to know it.
Okay sir. - Listen. Hey!
What a strange man.
He knows my name but not my nature.
Excuse me madam.
In which room is Laxminarayan?
There is Laxminarayan
"I am waiting, I am waiting for you."
"I am living a
lonely and restless life."
"Taking you in my arms,
will give me life again."
"My beloved, should be crazy."
"I want a guy that's in my heart."
"I want a guy that
immerses in my heart."
immerses in my eyes."
"I want a guy that
immerses in my heart."
immerses in my eyes."
"I want a guy that makes me restless."
"I want a guy that
belongs only to me."
"I want a guy that immerses in
my heart. Immerses in my heart."
"I want a guy that belongs
only to me. Belongs to me."
"Immerses in my heart."
"His name is on my lips."
"His image is in my dreams."
"Everyone says he is so dashing."
"I search everywhere for him."
"When will I find him?"
"Guy! Guy! Guy!"
"I am waiting, I am waiting for you."
"I am living a
lonely and restless life."
"I want a guy that
will take me to Paris!"
"I want a guy that will
take me around in a Merc."
"I want a guy that
will take me to Paris!"
"I want a guy that will
take me around in a Merc."
"A lover that will
shower everything on me."
"Adorns me with the
moon and the stars."
"I want a guy that immerses in
my heart. Immerses in my heart."
"Immerses in my heart."
"Belongs to me."
"Everyone is crazy about me."
"Everyone loves me."
"The one that will stay in my heart."
"He doesn't look at me."
"I am spread my
intoxication every moment."
"He might get intoxicated sometime."
"I want a guy!"
"I want a guy that
immerses in my heart."
immerses in my eyes."
"I want a guy that makes me restless."
"I want a guy that
belongs only to me."
immerses in my heart."
"Immerses in my heart."
Why do people run away when
I take Mr. D'mello's name?
I don't understand.
Mr. D'mello.
Excuse me.
Excuse.. excuse me. Anybody home?
Hello!
Hello! Mr. D'mello!
Papa, he looks like Laxminarayan!
Wearing a tie he has come to
kill you in your own house.
He thinks you are a dog, papa.
Shall I kill him right now, papa?
No.
Let me first find out,
who is this daring man.
Who has sent him?
The car is right here, but I
don't know where they are.
Seems like they are not at home.
Oh Hello sir! Nice
meeting you finally.
My name is Laxminarayan! Hands up!
Sir, you are mistaken!
Misunderstanding sir.
Sir, I am Laxminarayan! Ok.
Put your hands up!
Which one sir? Left or right? Sir.
- Both.
Sir.
- "You idiots."
Walk quietly!
- Where, sir?
Left.. or right, sir?
Left. Sir, your left or my left sir.
"You idiots."
- Papa!
Does she design bra, panty or cars?
Laxminarayan, she does her
business in cars just like you.
Nisha, mail this to Mr. Kumar,
and tell him that I will come..
Excuse me, madam.
Yes.
Madam, you are the one
in the photo isn't it?
Yes. Who are you?
Oh I am Laxminarayan.
And you?
Hi, I am Laila. I was waiting for you.
So you do business in car too.
- Yeah!
Yes, I deal in cars.
I have a car business.
And you know my nature!
Even I deal in car.
Where do you keep the goods?
Goods!
Goods! This one.
Seems like you are getting restless.
Hey since I have seen the photo..
..I can't take my eyes of it.
It is such a nice design, wow.
You will never find
something like this anywhere.
Thank you. If Khurana
sees it, he will be jealous.
Then, are we ready to make the deal.
Of course. Show me the goods.
You know my nature..
..I don't make the deal
without seeing the goods. No
Fair enough. Come, I will show it.
Come.
See this gun.
Seems like it is English make.
It's Chinese, but
looks absolutely English!
Papa, don't talk to him much.
He asks a lot of question Papa.
"You idiots."
Sit.
Where should I sit sir?
On the sofa or the chair?
On the chair?
- Sorry, sir.
There are so many chairs.
Which chair? Left
one or the right one.
Left one.
Sir, your left or my left sir.
"You idiot."
- Question paper, come here.
On this chair.
Dirty.
You really are very daring.
- Thank you, sir.
You came here directly.
You couldn't have come, sir,
if I had called you.
You stay so busy,
that's why I came myself.
Anyway sir, shall we finish the job.
Sorry sir, I am in a hurry.
I have to take care of another job.
- What?
What do you mean?
After taking care of me, you
will take care of another job.
Sir, sometimes I have to
take care of 5-4 jobs.
I stay busy all day sir.
Marvelous.
- Thank you. - Marvelous.
Learn from him! Learn
from him! Learn from him!
Excuse me, sir. - Learn from him!
Excuse me sir. - Learn from him
You always hit me in
front of everyone.
Sorry.
Sir, can we finish it off now?
Shall we do it here
in front of everyone..
..or somewhere alone?
Papa, he is asking for your choice.
Would you like to die here,
or.. inside? In private.
"You fool!"
"You have come to kill me!"
"Are you mad to take a
contract in my name!"
"You fool!"
Whom do you work for?
Sir.. Virus auto, sir,
I had given you my car.
Virus auto!
Seems like an international gang, Papa!
What's the name of your boss?
Mr. D.M Pipat, sir. Mr. D.M Pipat, sir.
Why does Pipat want to kill me?
Sir, actually he.. kill you!
Kill you! Why would
he want to kill you, sir?
Then why have you come to kill me?
Sir I kills.. no sir, K I L L, kill.
You put an s after every word,
that's not right sir.
That's Papa's s, he will
use it wherever he wants.
"You fools." Why do
you want to kill me?
Why will I kill you sir?
You are joking, right sir.
You are joking. - Hey.
Papa, don't talk to him kill him..
..or else he will kill
us with his questions.
You think my death this is a joke.
Sir, sir, sir, sir,
sir, sir, sir this gun.
Shoot the idiot!
- "You fool, you came to kill me?"
"Are you mad to take a
contract in my name!"
He is dead. Marvelous shooting.
- Yes.
Marvelous shooting.
- Thanks. Long distance.
Congratulations.
- Albert, papa learnt how to shoot.
Thanks my children. Excuse me.
Oh God.
- Mr. D'mello, this is not fair.
Sir, you know I have
to go for another job.
Still you ruined my face.
Where is the bathroom?
Bathroom.
- Left.
Your left or mine.
"You fool."
Headache has come here again.
- Your Tamil will kill me Ms. Jia.
And yes, M.M. Munde!
Murli Manohar Munde!
Neither less nor more. Bubblegum!
You asked me to come at 12
o'clock and take the money so..
Whose? Ms. Jia, please.
I am in a very serious
mood today so no jokes.
Bubblegum! Please. Please.
Look, Mr.
Laxminarayan hasn't arrived..
..so you will have to wait
for a while. No Ms. Jia..
..now no more waiting, please.
Actually, I am not feeling
well and I am a bit hot tempered.
Then cool it, and have coconut water.
Not coconut Ms. Jia!
No coconut, please.
I don't like coconut. You
please give me the money.
Then sit comfortably
below that coconut tree.
No coconut! Ms. Jia, why are
you saying coconut all the time?
Either you give the money,
or I will take it.
Sorry. Simple.
Sir.
- Yes! - Cold drink or tea?
Can I have some water?
Ms. Jia, someone fired a bullet..
Is it that you have called
goons to kill this Munde.
Mr. Munde, there are no goons here.
Munde! Mr. Murli Manohar Munde.
Neither less nor more.
- Your bubblegum. - Thank you..
..very much. But Munde
won't be scared of any goon.
Remember that. Wait here,
I will just come.
Listen, wait here, why
are you coming after me?
What the hell. Where
is that Laxminarayan?
Jia, could it be that
he is somewhere around..
..but he can't recognise you.
Yes, it is possible.
Eat something.
Excuse me, I need to
announce one name.
Laxminarayan!
Sir, I didn't come to kill you!
I didn't come to kill you!
Sir, trust me sir, I
didn't come to kill you!
Then, who have you come to kill?
I haven't come here to kill anyone.
Mr. Pipat, my boss. He
asked me to meet you.
You can ask Mr. Pipat!
Give me his number.
Fax number or phone number sir.
Phones. Landline or
mobile number, sir?
Mobile. India or Singapore, sir?
Where is your boss?
Sir, he is in London?
Then why did you say Singapore?
Sir, I was scared.
Please leave me. Please.
I will give you the number.
00447866789!
Very small. Here.
It will ring! It is ringing!
He will pick it up.
Sir, my boss is a very educated man.
Oxford University, I
am his special man.
He will pick it up! Actually sir,
time difference in the morning..
Hello. - Hello, hello, hello sir.
Laxminarayan here, sir, from Pondi.
Who Laxmi? - Your Laxminarayan,
sir, from Pondi sir.
You fool, did you get the job done?
Sir, there is a small problem.
That's why I called you.
Laxminarayan you idiot, I don't
want any excuses. I want results.
You fool, you lousy fool,
stupid, idiot.
Call me when the job
is taken care off..
Abusing in Hindi from London.
- Sir.
Or else I will shoot you.
- I know you love me sir.
Lousy idiot!
- Sir.
I think he hanged down the phone.
Internet call sometimes.
Papa, I had told you earlier.
Kill him.
What?
- "You fool." - Thank you papa. Sir!
Why did you do like this sir? This?
You ordered him to kill me, isn't it sir?
You cannot do this sir. Try and under..
Sir, what is this sir?
Even papa doesn't know.
- Danger?
Look sir, it is so comfortable.
To sit, to lie down.
You don't even have to adjust it.
Absolutely, it should be comfortable..
..while getting up and sitting down.
Yes.
- Otherwise people complain.
They have to adjust every time.
You are right.
- Gents can do it.
Yes.
But ladies face more problems!
- Yes.
Show me.
I showed it.
You showed me the
effect and side effect.
Show me the goods.
What more do you want to see?
This.
I have been showing
you this since then.
Madam, what you have been
showing since then is nice..
..but I am a
complete business man. Yes.
Until I don't see the real thing,
I don't take the delivery.
Show me the real good. This one.
Show me the red colour
underwear and vest. Full piece.
What?
These are your boss's goods.
'O God, boss's diamonds.'
- I am sorry.
I delayed a bit, your
boss must be angry with me?
He is very angry with you.
Please tell him sorry on my behalf.
I will always be indebted to you.
Please. I am very tense.
I am.. sorry.
Please, just try and understand.
Excuse me.
I will just come.
"I am helpless, hopeless and useless."
I cannot kill him.
Now that she has
returned brother's diamonds..
..then why should I kill him?
Seems like there is a
power failure, papa!
Now it will only
return tomorrow, papa.
Excuse me. Don't you have inverters?
- What?
Don't you have inverters?
Why you..
- Papa, he is challenging you.
I will bring the inverter.
- Wait.
Papa, forget about the electricity..
..kill him with the bomb.
Excuse me sir, I am
not that Laxminarayan.
It must be some other Laxminarayan.
I am not him..
Has he gone mad?
Sir, he is Laxminarayan!
He is Laxminarayan!
He stays in my hotel.
I have seen him, sir.
Please release me, sir.
It is the question of my job.
He is putting up a charade, papa.
There is another Laxminarayan, sir.
He is staying in
room number 500.. 504.
I am not that Laxminarayan, sir.
He is that Laxminarayan,
who has come to kill you..
..the underwear and vest one.
"You fool."
If what you say turns
out to be false, then..
Sir, you are talking as if you
will do whatever I will tell you.
Do whatever you wish too!
Marvelous idea.
Come on, show me.
Who is that other Laxminarayan?
Come on.
Papa, you took the tie..
..who will bring the
person wearing the tie along?
Don't worry.
If you want the money, then
you will have to show the goods.
That's how it is?
Seems like you don't
know business. Bye.
I have been selling underwear
and vests for the past 40 years.
Stop! You..
I will stop if you show me the goods.
Otherwise, I won't.
'What are you thinking Laila?'
'If this deal is not finalised..
..then you won't be able to
pay the bank installment.'
'And if you don't pay
the bank installment..
..then you will lose everything.'
But you will look at
it from a distance.
And you won't tell anyone about it.
Fine!
Show it.
But, not here.
Then where?
In your hotel.
Fine. Come, then.
Tell me, who fired the bullet?
The bullet was fired from
that direction, we were here.
Why you.. Gatotkutch!
- Yes, madam.
Isn't he that boy without the gun?
I, too, think so, madam.
Come on.
- Yes, madam.
So sensational! What are you doing?
Did you fire at this Munde?
Tek Chand.
- Yes, madam.
Search this boy.
Yes.
- If you don't mind, sir.
Why do you always search people?
Don't you know?
Police never leave the chance
of taking anything. Understand.
Come with us to the 'Thane'.
(Police station).
Why Thane, I live in Ghatkopar?
If you act too smart, I will kill you.
Then you will cry all your life.
Madam, your button is open.
Oh! Catch him.
Madam.
- Not me, him! You idiot!
- Mr. Laxminarayan, my money!
Hey, where did you go?
Ms. Jia, where are you
running to, speaking in Tamil?
Laxminarayan! Laxminarayan!
"One two, three.."
Catch him! Catch him!
"Coming in the world is free."
- Tek Chand, run.
"Going from the world is
free." - Catch him. Stop!
"See the drama of the world"
- Stop!
"Absolutely free."
- Ms. Jia, stop.
Catch him! Catch his legs.
I caught it, madam.
Not mine, his.
- Let go! Catch him, not me.
I won't spare you. Let me go.
Tek Chand, come on.
Laxminarayan!
- Ms. Jia!
"Everybody say, you fools."
Follow me.
"How dare you"
"you want to get me killed?"
I will get down first.
I will help papa cross. Me..
- Me.
I will help Papa cross.
Excuse me, can I help you across?
- Okay.
By going there?
Okay. First you help
me across. Carefully.
Give me your hand.
Which hand sir, left or right?
- 'One, two, three.'
Give me any hand, or else
I won't be able to cross.
Oh!
Very good.
Catch him. Don't run.
Papa, don't worry, we are with you.
"He has come out of the frying pan!"
"He has landed into the fire."
"He doesn't accept his crimes."
"He has been forced too."
"Meera danced tying the anklet."
"You dance without the anklet."
"Sway and dance."
"If you fall, then take my advice."
"Only after lots of effort,
does a plant turn into a tree."
You go to the right.
You go to the left and look for him.
- Okay.
And me.
"My dear, careful! Girl, look out."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
Sir, sorry, sir.
You will murder me!
Sir, that Laxminarayan is someone else.
I will kill you.
Why will you kill me?
- You are after me?
Sir, I am not after me.
- You dare take my contract.
Sir, I didn't take any contract..
Can't you watch where you are going?
Yes, I can't watch
where I am going so?
You hit me!
- Yes, I hit you, so?
If he wouldn't have
been along with me..
..then I would have killed you.
Who wouldn't have been with you?
- Him!
Where did he go?
Help! Help!
Pinto.
"Run, Run! Sprint, sprint!"
"Don't sleep, wake up."
"There is trouble behind you."
"Pick up your pace and run."
Hold, there is a
police woman in the front.
"Lose your pride,
lose your arrogance."
Laxminarayan, I will not spare you.
- "Everything is distorted."
"Since I have been
kicked in the back."
Hey, what are you doing?
Come on, move.
Yes, madam.
"There are desires in the heart."
"Your mind says that."
"Only when you sweat it out,
can you buy an A/C!"
"One, two three! And One, two three!"
"One, two three!"
"Tolerating thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
Chandu, where is that Laxminarayan?
This way! No, no this way,
come on, quickly!
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
- There he is, catch him.
"Absolutely free! Absolutely
free!" My money. - Ms. Jia, stop.
Laxmi.
- Come on.
O God! Where did he go?
Laxminarayan, stop!
Look, don't follow me.
Look, your boss must have told you..
..to give something
more in exchange of this.
Then give that, and go.
No! But how can I give you that?
You are so young.
What does it have to do with age?
You know, younger people than me..
..have progressed more than me.
But I cannot do the same with you.
I am sorry.
Laxmi, you were my last hope.
And if you betray me,
then what will happen to me?
Kill me! Kill me!
Kill me! I want to rise up!
Kill me! Kill me Laxmi! Kill me!
Kill me! Please. Let me go!
Kill me Laxmi!
- Let me go!
Let me go!
Please Laxmi.
What did you do?
I stopped him from going.
Come on, pick him up.
Don't touch him, he
is my Laxminarayan.
No, he is our Laxminarayan.
He is mine!
- He is our piece.
Do you think he is a piece?
He is Laxminarayan.
He is mine.
- No, he is ours.
- No, he is ours. - Just a minute.
Yes, madam.
- Chandu, where are you?
You know, Mr.
Laxminarayan was supposed to come..
..here at 11 o'clock.
Madam. - Yes madam, but
your Laxminarayan is here.
He is standing here with me.
Come here quickly, I have to leave.
Yes, come fast okay.
Okay.
- Thank you.
Two minutes more sir, please.
He is not our Laxminarayan!
I told you he is my Laxminarayan!
- Yes.
This is yours too, come on run.
- Get lost.
Laxmi!
"Everywhere you get, one on one free."
"The one who knows how to read,
it is beneficial for him."
Excuse me! Sorry!
Life is precious. To
hell with the show.
My check out time, sir!
Good morning, sir!
Looking very fresh today, sir!
Me? Thank you, sir!
Sir, I want to checkout!
Please make my bill!
Why, sir? You were
supposed to leave tomorrow.
Yes, but I want to leave now.
Sir, please make my bill. Sir, please.
Any problem, sir?
No problem, sir. Make my bill.
I want to checkout.
Room not comfortable, sir?
No! Very comfortable! Sir,
please hurry up! Sir, please.
Food not good, sir?
- My luck is not good!
Will you change it?
What kind of a man are you?
You are going on asking questions!
Please! I want to checkout! Please!
Life is very precious.
To hell with the..
"You fools."
Come!
- Yes!
Why are you laughing, fool?
Catch everybody!
Check what the matter is!
Yes, ma'am!
Mrs. Sinha! Come on!
Ma'am! Inspector ma'am!
Did you recognise me?
You are Mayawati Chowtala's man!
How can I forget you?
What has happened to you?
What happened?
Did you collide with a truck?
Something like that!
Please ma'am, take me with you!
My dear! You are irresistible!
But what to do? I am on duty.
I can't do much.
Ma'am!
- Found him?
Ma'am, didn't find Laxminarayan!
What? Ma'am, I am Laxminarayan!
Quiet! Let's search there.
- Okay, ma'am!
Bye! See you again!
Ma'am, please! Take me,
ma'am! Take me!
Take me? Did you take Viagra?
That you can't
control yourself? Come on!
Ma'am! Ma'am, take me with you, ma'am!
Because those three people,
they are following me!
Move back! Don't
play with my feelings!
Otherwise I will kill you!
But why?
- Then you will regret!
Move back! Go!
- Ma'am!
Tek Chand!
- Ma'am! - Quiet! Move back! - Ma'am!
Ma'am! Ma'am! Ma'am! I
am the same Laxminarayan!
Ma'am! Ma'am! I am not Laxminarayan!
Ma'am! I was telling you
that I am not Laxminarayan!
Come!
Yes, sir!
- I want to check in, sir!
Are you sure, sir?
- Yes, sir!
Get in! Get in! Get in!
Sir! Sir, please!
Shut up! If you utter a
single word, I will shoot you!
No, sir!
- Laxmi!
No, sir! No, sir! No, sir!
Come
One minute! Stop him! Stop him!
Fool, I am pointing a gun at you!
Still you are flirting with a girl!
And you are making
me flirt with her too!
No, sir! Never, sir!
I was just telling you that
he is the same Laxminarayan..
..who had come to shoot you.
- What! - Yes!
Why didn't you say he is the one?
You only said to keep my mouth shut!
You! - I think he is a
cunning man! - No, sir!
He would have beaten you
with that girl's sandals!
Hey!
- Like that day!
Come on, ma'am! I have
freshened up! Now show!
I.. I never showed
it to somebody before.
What? You didn't show it?
How do you do your business?
Please don't call it business.
It sounds very cheap!
What cheap, ma'am!
In our business the customer doesn't..
..touch without seeing the goods.
And we too have to show it.
You too show it?
- Yes!
And you know my nature!
And ladies check everything!
Is it loose? Is the size proper?
We have to show everything.
I've been doing this
business for the past 40 years.
Show it.
Look!
- Yes!
Its only about seeing, right?
But who hit me?
I don't know! There were two of them!
They hit you with a stick and
they were going to take you.
Then I stopped them
and told them that..
..he is my Laxminarayan!
You said that?
- Yes!
Then they spoke on
the phone and ran away!
And then you brought me here!
How could I have left you there..
..in that state, Laxminarayan?
Has it stopped paining?
The pain has just started.
What are you doing?
Why are you removing your clothes?
If I won't remove it
then how will I show it?
I don't want it!
It's wrong! It's wrong!
I know your nature!
But you know my nature!
Laxmi! - I am not such a man!
- Laxmi! Laxmi! Laxmi!
You go!
- Laxmi! Relax!
These things happen in
this age! I know! Just relax!
"Secretly. Secretly."
"These talks and meetings are secret."
"Beloved, don't leave me."
"Don't go."
"The twilights are asleep.
My breaths are lost and awakened."
"Beloved, don't leave me."
"Don't go."
"You have just dwelled in my heart."
"You have just come in my dreams."
"You have just come in my arms."
"Don't go."
"These talks and meetings are secret."
"Beloved, don't leave me."
"Don't go."
"The twilights are asleep.
My breaths are lost and awakened."
"Beloved, don't leave me."
"Don't go."
"Everybody say. Fool!"
"Fool!"
"Fool, you have come to kill me."
"You are mad that you came here."
"Boss, he is loose like a kite."
"Sir, here there is
electricity 24 hours."
"Hey, fool!"
"Look at the man on the right."
"Sorry, sir. A slight confusion."
"Your right or my right?"
"Oh shut up! Shut up!"
- "He is angry."
"People on my left."
"Really, really angry.
- Really, really angry."
"I will kill you in one go."
"Go? You mean I can go? Thank you!"
"Somebody make him quiet."
"Secretly. Secretly."
"I want to sleep in your tresses."
"I want to lose myself
in you all the time."
"In my fervour I tell you."
"Don't go."
"These talks and meetings are secret."
"Beloved, don't leave me."
"Don't go."
"You have just dwelled in my heart."
"You have just come in my dreams."
"You have just come in my arms."
"Don't go."
I am.. I am sorry.
- Why?
I spoke to you rudely.
- When?
When I told you to shoot me.
What was your mistake?
Actually I am not like this.
If there hadn't been a problem,
I wouldn't have said it.
After papa's death,
I have become all alone.
And I will have to
vacate this house too.
Do you know? That goon says that
if I didn't pay him the money..
..then I will have to marry him!
I will not marry that crazy guy.
I will not marry him.
It will be better if I commit suicide.
I will kill you! If you
speak of committing suicide!
I am there! Here!
How much do you want?
I had brought 25,000 rupees!
Only 25,000 rupees!
Don't worry!
Take this chain!
It's worth 24,000 rupees!
That's it?
Meaning this is fake.
You can keep this ring.
It was for my namesake wife!
Namesake wife?
Yes! I have just called
Meena my wife! - Is that so?
It's worth 20,000 rupees!
I thought you will at
least give me a lakh. - What!
You knew that I will give you money?
- Yes.
O my God! Do I look like a fool?
- Fool?
Munna! Pappu! Take away everything!
TV! Fridge! Sofa!
- Mr. Munde!
Washing machine!
Take away everything!
- No, no, please!
That too!
Please, Mr. Munde!
- M.M. Munde! Murli Manohar Munde!
Neither less nor more! Bubblegum!
- No!
Take it! Please at
least take half of it!
Look at her drama! A
bundle of note in her hand!
Give it to me! Take
everything that this girl has!
Munde!
Come on! Leave the money!
And get lost!
You will scare me with him?
- Yes!
I won't let you stay here! You too!
Hang on, uncle!
You please put your
finger in your ears! - Why?
Do it! Do it!
- Why?
Sit!
Sit! Sit!
Now tell me!
From today this girl is
your sister. Got it, Munde?
M.M. Munde! Murli Manohar Munde!
Neither less nor more! Bubblegum!
Gun?
Give me the bubblegum.
- Take it.
Henceforth if you trouble her..
I won't spare you!
What are you saying?
Hey, listen! You foolish man!
Listen to the threat completely!
What? - Yes!
If you ask money from
her or if you harass her..
..then I swear I
will shoot from Mumbai..
..and it will hit your back.
And like a buffalo stuck
in 26th July 2005 flood..
..you will be lying upside down dead!
Got it?
No, brother! No!
Jia is like my child. She is my child!
Munna! Pappu! What are you doing?
You people come
whenever I call you! Leave!
Don't you have any work?
- Shut up! Done?
Come on! Touch her feet and leave!
Otherwise I will kill you!
Sister! I love you!
Like brother and sister!
You don't worry. Your
brother is with you.
And you didn't tell me that you
know such a big don in Mumbai.
No problem. If you
need anything, call me.
Money! Bubblegum! Please!
- Get lost!
Yes! Let's leave!
Wow! You played the role of
an underworld don so well!
Munde ran away in fright!
But from where did you get this gun?
I am underworld's don!
Really I am a don!
Are you really..
..a don?
Son! Son! Laxminarayan!
Laxminarayan is my father!
And I am his son! Okay!
Here there are father, son and uncle.
Three types of Laxminarayan!
Now which one do you want, sir?
Can you take me to his room, sir?
God knows that after
Sonu's mother's death..
..I suppressed all my emotions!
You again awakened it!
I call every woman my sister.
Seeing the blouse size,
I tell them the size of the bra.
But I never cast
lustful eyes on anybody.
No! No!
You have slandered me!
Who said to show this?
I sell underwear and vest.
What else will I see?
What! You said you deal in cars!
You deal in cars, right!
I do my business in car!
Is it wrong to sit in the car
and sell underwear and vest?
You said you will buy it
from me and sell it at 5%.
God! I was talking about the design..
..which you were
going to show me, ma'am!
Which design?
- This one!
This red design!
This is a photo of a car!
So why are you showing your
innerwear standing like this?
It means you are not
that Laxminarayan..
..who was going to buy the car?
No!
So you thought I was that person..
..and you did this with me!
What have you done!
If you are not that
Laxminarayan then where is he?
He must be somewhere! I am here!
- O God!
Good afternoon!
Hello, sir!
- Hello, sir.
Relaxing, sir?
- Yes, sir.
Sir, your son has come!
Sir, your father!
Hi, dad!
He is not my dad!
You tell him! Sir,
you are not his father!
When I am not married,
then how will I have a son?
And now I think I will never marry!
I understand, sir. Each person
has their own choice, sir!
Don't worry, sir.
We have another Laxminarayan!
I will show you that!
Don't leave!
- Good night, sir!
Good night! Good night!
- Sorry to disturb you, sir!
Not at all! Not at all! - Enjoy
yourself while you are here, sir!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Marvelous acting. Marvelous!
D'mello sir! D'mello sir! D'mello sir!
Sir, I told you that there is
another Laxminarayan in the hotel!
Now even the manager
said it! Will you let me go?
Shut up! My life is in danger!
And you want to leave!
Sir, please! Sir!
- Albert! Go! - Sir!
Ma'am, listen to me!
Now I touched you, it's over.
I mean whatever happened, it happened!
Listen to me!
- Don't touch me! You..
O no!
Now you will have to buy this car!
Its worth 10 lakhs!
You pay 9 lakhs! Okay!
9 lakhs! Ma'am, I look
like a fool! But I am not!
Shut up!
- Why should I buy the car?
If I didn't pay the bank
installments within 5 days..
..then they will seize my showroom..
Because of this I..
Otherwise I am not
such kind of a girl!
I too am not that kind of a man!
You think I am Khurana!
I too have a reputation!
You can ask anybody at Chandni Chowk!
Talking rubbish!
If my son came to know that in
a hotel room with a girl, I..
O God! O God! O God!
Ma'am, you hide in the bathroom.
- No!
Hide in the bathroom.
Somebody has come! - No!
Hide in the bathroom. Go there!
Just lock the door from inside!
- But..
Hello, sir! Are you Laxminarayan?
- Yes!
Are you Sonu's father?
Hi, dad! What's up?
You returned so soon!
You were in Singapore, weren't you?
Actually dad, my work got
over soon. So I thought..
You thought that papa
doesn't know anything..
..about bra, panties, design.
I will go and explain to him!
Dad, please! Please call it lingerie!
Shut up! You fool!
I have been selling
underwear since the time..
..you had not even
started wearing one!
And you will explain to me! Leave!
- Leave? Why?
Hang on!
- Where are you going?
Dad, bathroom!
- Why?
To use it!
- No!
Now I won't let you use it anymore!
You have already reduced so much!
Don't you eat?
Now I won't let you reduce! No!
Dad, please move!
Otherwise I will do it here!
If you went in then
I will be trouble, son.
Please, dad!
- No!
- I said no!
Please, dad!
- No! No! No!
Dad, what is she doing here?
Son, she is..
You know my nature!
Now I know, dad!
Sorry, son.
Come on, Laxminarayan!
Now what to hide from your son?
Your dad was finalising a
deal with me in this room.
What deal?
- Shall I tell him, Laxminarayan?
No, I will tell him.
- I will tell him.
He is my son.
We normally talk. You leave. Fine.
Come on, Laxmi. You won't
get such a chance again.
Your dad, in this room,
sitting on this bed..
..finalised the car deal with me, right?
Car deal? When?
- Yeah!
Just now on this bed we both..
Shall I tell, Sonu?
- Yes! No! Why?
Your dad wanted to hide it from you.
Actually he has bought a
vintage car to sell his goods.
For 10 lakhs.
10 lakhs! - Yes. - Daddy, what is this?
We have a car!
Cancel! Cancel this deal!
- The deal..
Laxmi, you said the deal is fixed.
The bed..
The deal is fixed!
- But, dad.
- And my advance of 1 lakh!
I.. I can't believe this!
I am sitting in front
of an underworld don.
Can I.. can I just please touch you?
Oh thank God.
Oh, you are just so real.
Do you know? Why I started
working in undergarments?
Because like underworld,
this too has 'under' in it.
Underworld.
Undergarments. We are so similar.
I have got 1 lakh.
- No, dad.
Laxminarayan, thank you!
The car is yours.
I will leave. I have to make the agreement.
You come at 4 o'clock.
And bring the remaining 9 lakhs.
Okay.
- Okay! Okay!
Laxmi.. thank you. You saved me.
You put me into trouble.
I always wanted to
marry an underworld don.
There is so much
excitement and thrill in their life.
Husband leaves in the morning.
And wife doesn't even know whether..
..her husband will come back or not.
When husband comes at
night and kisses her..
..it feels like the last kiss.
Because a bullet
might come from anywhere.
And the husband gets
killed in an encounter.
I just.. I just love this feeling.
I just love dons.
How many murders have you committed?
You really didn't know that I am a don?
How could I have known?
So why were you waiting
for me in the restaurant?
It's my restaurant.
I received the message
that you are coming there.
So I came there with my bag.
Oh! So brother called you there..
..and he sent me there to kill you!
Your boss is a brother?
- Yes.
Do you know? This was my first murder!
For this extortion
money mother had offered..
..so many arecas in the temple.
Every Tuesday she would go
walking to Siddhivinayak temple..
So that her son gets one
chance of committing a murder.
After worshipping so
many Lord Ganesha's..
..I got this chance!
I thought I will commit one
murder and settle down in life..
..then I will marry
Chhota Khujli's daughter..
..and make my future bright.
But.. everything
messed up because of me.
Kill me. Laxmi, kill me.
What are you saying?
You don't worry. I am there.
From today every bullet will
have to pass through me first..
..to reach to you.
What? - You will fight
with your boss for me?
Now I will show brother
what I can do! - But you..
I will leave now.
Laxmi!
Your namesake wife's ring.
Now is there any need for this?
I will return soon.
- I will wait for you!
Yes! My sweetie pie, Laxmi.
Brother Batlya! You and here!
Dug grave and hidden
news are easily seen!
Is the work done?
- You were right, brother.
Flowers and ailment
don't last for long.
I am fine now, brother.
Here are your goods. Your diamonds.
Diamonds! Diamonds!
Did you see? Did you see,
Chhota Khujli?
Didn't I say that Laxminarayan..
..will someday
fulfill his mother's dream?
I am proud of you!
How many bullets did you shoot?
- Not even one!
I see! I see! I see! You
must have chopped and killed!
You must have strangulated and killed!
Your thinking is so small, brother!
Like lizard's egg.
Laying down life is
greater than taking life!
Learn something!
I am not an ordinary brother like you!
To deal in diamonds
and for it kill somebody!
I thought you are a
level headed brother.
But now I found out that
your level is only one.
Did you kill the person?
No!
Because I want to be a godfather!
Godfather!
Even this Chhota
Khujli can be a father!
But you become God when
you lay down your life!
And today I saved her life.
Here are your diamonds.
From today our paths are different.
Because I won't work for a
stupid and foolish brother like you!
You slander
underworld's name for underwear.
Check your diamonds.
And Chhota Khujli, get your daughter..
..Meena married to some other goon!
I am not interested in her!
What is this?
- Diamond!
Is this diamond?-Yes!
Look! It's written here too!
Pure diamond! Look! Look!
Look!
Where will I wear this diamond?
It's your choice! Why do you ask me?
Check it properly!
Laxminarayan doesn't
leave a job incomplete. What?
"One, two, three."
What? What are you looking at?
Say thank you! And give the payment!
Tell me something.
Is there a nice corner in this hotel?
- Why?
"One, two, three."
- Your payment is quite big.
If I paid you here, people will stare.
Yes, there is one,
brother! There is a corner!
I will show it to you! Come! Come!
- Come!
Let's go, Chhota Khujli. Come.
Hit him! Hit him! -Brother!
Why are you beating me, brother?
Beat him! Hit him!
- Brother!
Fool! - If you don't want
to make any payment, fine!
But why are you beating me?
I am a fool! I am stupid!
And.. and I will wear this!
I will wear this! I will wear this!
Tell me where the diamond is!
Here is your diamond!
The diamond which was snatched..
..from me and I lost my honour.
You can snatch this and
disgrace a person too, brother.
Diamond! Diamond which shines!
Brother, see this! It's shinning!
Hey! The diamond which Yadav stole!
Now who is this Yadav, brother?
Yadav! He! He is Yadav!
Oh no, brother! I had come to kill her!
Who is she?
- She stole your diamond.
Yadav stole the diamond!
Then why did you send her photo?
I sent you his photo and not
her photo in the envelope!
Then why did I get her photo, brother?
You are lying!
- You are lying!
You sent this photo, brother.
And you also sent diamond's photo!
And you are beating me too!
King Kong.
Tell me! You didn't receive his photo?
No! Otherwise
I wouldn't have spared him.
I even thrashed him.
- When? Where?
He was running on the street!
- Now where is he?
Brother, I don't know.
But the person whom he was
following he is in this hotel.
Come. Come. Show me.
Brother, why are you wearing goggles?
- What if he recognises me?
Brother, you really have it.
- What?
Goggles.
Mr. Davar! Laxminarayan here!
I need 9 lakhs.
- Dad..
9 lakhs!
If there is a shortage of even a
penny, then the work won't be done.
Yes. And you know my nature. Got it?
I need 9 lakhs!
9 lakhs!
The price of killing papa
is 9 lakhs! Congratulations!
Isn't it too much, papa?
- Idiots!
Sir, now you are clear?
You have another Laxminarayan.
Now can I leave, sir?
- Not now!
Where will you go? The
climax is still left!
Okay, papa!
- Look brother! He is that Yadav!
Where is he going? Where is he going?
Come on! Let's check!
O God!
Never before have
I seen such daring shooters!
I will kill him in such a
way that even death will say..
..what a death!
Wow! Albert!
Papa!
- Pinto!
Before Laxminarayan kills me.. shoot him!
Come.
- You come!
How does..
How does he know that you want to kill him?
Brother, shall I kill him now?
- Hey!
You won't kill him.
Our paths are different.
Brother! Listen, brother!
Brother! Brother! - Leave!
I am a cheap brother! - No, brother!
No, no, no! My thinking is
small like lizard's egg.
No, brother! My thinking
is small like lizard's egg.
Not just that I am
myself lizard's egg, brother.
You are very kind!
Give me one more chance!
Feelings for that
girl made me emotional.
My heart melted, brother.
One chance. Just one chance!
Stand up!
And remember!
Beauty of youth and the urge
to urinate don't last for long!
Don't go after girls.
And concentrate on your career.
I give you another chance.
- Thank you, brother.
But remember!
- Thank you.
If your bullet misses him,
then my bullet will kiss you!
Don't worry, brother. This
time I will aim his head! - Move!
Pinto! Kill him!
No, sir! I beg of you,
sir! I beg of you!
I have still not got married.
A girl's family is
coming to see me next week.
Sir, please. Leave me!
-I will leave you!
I'll let go of you.
First leave me! Leave!
Sorry, sir! Sorry, sir!
- "You fool."
On one condition!
What? I accept all your conditions!
We won't kill him!
- Very good, sir! Good! Good!
You will kill him!
- Very good!
No, sir! No! Don't do this!
Sir, I have never even killed a fly!
How will I kill a man, sir?
Albert! Teach him how to kill a fly!
Papa!
Sir! Sir! Sir! You seem to
be an intelligent man, sir.
Genius, sir! You are so handsome, sir.
Leave me, sir. I hope you
understand my problem, sir.
Kill!
- What, sir?
A fly!
- Fly?
Lovingly. It's a female.
- Female.
It shouldn't hurt her.
Okay, sir!
The glass shouldn't break!
And I should kill the fly too!
How is that possible, sir!
You people have..
God is looking!
God will punish everybody!
Kill! Kill!
Kill! Otherwise I will beat you!
"Fools!"
Sir, she flew away! Sir!
- No! No!
Chandu! Do something!
Otherwise the
diamonds worth 20 crores..
..will go with the car!
Now only God will do something!
God! God! God!
God! God, do something!
Lord Ganesh! What are
You looking at? Say something!
Excuse me!
You?
- You?
You both and here!
You both should be ashamed!
You both hit that poor, innocent,
nave, simple..
..loving Laxminarayan and ran away.
We are paying the
price of that mistake!
Actually we thought he
is that Laxminarayan..
..who was going to
buy the car. -But ..
..he wasn't that Laxminarayan.
Which car?
There is a wrecked car, ma'am!
It didn't sell for 7 months.
It would have been so good if it
had not been sold for 2 days more!
Are you talking about 6121?
Yes!
- How do you know?
That wrecked, unlucky car is mine!
Please send your
bank executive tomorrow.
I will pay all the remaining EMIs.
20 crores!
Ma'am, even if you
give 75%, it will be fine.
Are you mad?
- 25%! Fine! Give 5%!
O no!
Oh! Hi, Jia!
- Hi, Laila!
No, no, no!
- Congrats!
Your car has been sold for 10 lakhs!
- Is that so?
The papers are ready!
And Laxminarayan will
come at 4 with the payment.
Here is 50% of the advance!
- No, no!
I don't need this now!
I have changed my mind!
I don't want to sell this car!
Are you joking? Here are
the car documents. Read it.
I don't want to sell this car!
Okay!
- Do I look like a fool to you?
No! But I am taking this car!
- Over my dead body!
This is my car!
- I made it a car! - Is that so?
I have spent money
on it! -What nonsense!
Look at this! I have
put up the headlights!
And this paint! I
got it painted! Got it?
And? And? And?
And what else? And! And!
Look at the tyres! So old!
I paid the money!
I got it changed! Look!
Open your eyes and see!
Hello!
Ma'am!
- Excuse me, ma'am.
With great toil you sold
this car. And she was refusing.
So Chandni made her unconscious.
Am I right, Chandni?
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Well done! Very good!
- Wow! Good work, Chandni!
If you were hitting her, then
why were you standing behind me?
Ma'am!
- Ma'am, please!
Dad, please! Think once more!
Even I am thinking
that we should leave soon.
We are getting late. Got it?
20 crores!
Bring water! Ma'am is fainting!
Let her faint! Bring the car
and let's run away! - Okay!
Hey! Hello! Hello! Hello!
It's my diamond! Because
the car is in my showroom!
Excuse me. Diamond is mine.
Because the car is mine.
But we found the diamond!
- So it's ours.
Yes!
- No, it is ours.
How can she..
Quiet!
The diamond belongs to
all four of us! Okay!
Okay!
- Okay!
But if Laxminarayan
came to buy the car then?
We will sell him the car!
- What! - What!
What!
- But we will remove..
..the diamonds before that!
You too! Dad, you never listen to me!
"The queen of my dreams,
when will you come?"
Hello.
- Hello, Laxminarayan!
Laila here!
- Yes!
Can you come after an hour!
After an hour!
Actually it will take some
more time to get the papers ready.
Fine. You know my nature.
I will come after an hour.
You are so sweet. Thank you so much.
Hurry up!
Here! You stopped me!
While going for an
auspicious deed, you shouldn't stop!
Fool!
- Okay! Okay!
Come on! Let's have coffee!
Coffee? This in the room..
Where will you roam with this?
Let's keep it in the locker.
Will it be safe in the locker?
- Of course! Come!
Come! Fine!
Hello, sir!
- Sir! Keep this bag safely!
I will return in an hour.
No problem, sir.
Laxminarayan! Room number!
- 504!
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
Right, sir?
- Yes! Carefully!
Plan has changed.
It means now I don't
have to shoot him, right?
Thank you, sir.
- What's the hurry?
You will have to kill him.
- Sir, why?
But using a bomb and not a gun.
Pinto, manufacture such
a bomb which explodes.
I am a diploma holder.
Am I right, papa?
Albert! Bring a bag similar to
the one he kept in the locker.
We will fill that bag with bomb.
Then.. we will exchange it.
We will have 9 lakhs.
And he will have bomb.
He will press the remote.
- Me?
How can do it?
- Shut up.
He hit me.
"One, two, three."
- He is a fool.
For that poor man's money,
he is killing him with a bomb.
Brother, he only took your goods.
Shall I kill him?
Wait! What are you doing?
We will kill him in his style!
Meaning with a bomb?
- Yes!
And now we don't have to worry about..
..finding a similar bag.
Really, brother. You have it.
What?
- Brother, bag!
See this.
The bomb can explode if you touch it.
What shall I do?
- Keep it in this! Hurry up!
Fine, papa!
Now let me go! Let me go, papa!
- Papa!
He is calling you papa like us, papa!
"You fools."
Welcome to the family!
- Thank you!
Can I leave now?
- Papa, a photo!
"Fool!"
Correct, sir?
- 505! Thank you..
What are you doing, sir?
It will explode!
What, sir?
- Sir, bag!
Oh! Bag!
- New bag, sir!
Okay, sir! All right, sir!
Okay, sir! Sir, thank you! Sir,
thank you, very much!
Marvellous acting!
Good morning, sir!
You too have to keep the
bag for safe depositing, sir?
How do you know?
- Albert! Pinto!
You both go and exchange the bags!
Papa, the entire hotel staff is here!
It's a serious work, Papa! You know.
Yes, so much tension.
Laxminarayan!
Flirt with the girl
standing behind me.
Who! Me?
You! Who else!
Misbehave with her!
She will scream! Help! Help!
I will come and beat you!
All the hotel staff will gather here!
They both will go
and exchange the bags!
Simple!
Sir! Sir! Sir, I beg of you!
Papa!
Papa, my father! DM!
District Magistrate!
My great-grandfather.
Chief Justice! Bhatinda!
Nobody in my family has
misbehaved with a girl.
You are telling me to do it?
I don't know how to
misbehave with a girl, papa.
What is there to do?
Go to her and say.. will you come.
She will get irritated.
Go! How will you say it?
Will you come.. ma'am?
Ma'am! Is she your sister?
- No! No! No!
Will you come?
- "Fools!"
- You!
No, no! Which one? Which one?
- The one who is standing behind me!
I really don't remember.
Sir, left or right?
- Left!
Sir, my left or your left?
Somebody make him quiet!
- Your left!
Sir! Sir! Sir, there
are two girls to my left!
"Fools!"
The one in pink dress.
"One, two, three." - Sir, there
are two girls wearing pink dress.
Light pink or dark pink?
Laxminarayan!
- No!
You do one thing!
- Yes, sir!
I will go and misbehave
with her! And you beat me!
My pleasure, sir! I mean..
I mean with my hand or leg, sir?
Leg!
- Left or right, sir?
You can beat me any way you want!
You beat me!
Otherwise I will kill you!
I.. I am going to misbehave with her.
Best of luck. Papa!
- From my side too..
Good luck! Best of luck!
"Everybody say!"
"Fool!" -You always ask..
..right or left!
- Sorry, sir!
Just enjoy life! Look!
"Fool!"
- Look how papa does it!
Will you come?
"One, two, three."
My room or your room?
What?
- Listen! Come!
Sorry! Sorry! Look, I am
not that kind of a man!
I am also not that kind of a woman.
Don't you have
father or brother at home?
Why are you acting smugly?
Look, it's off season!
I will give you a discount of 50%.
- Look, please!
A girl is flirting with papa!
Come! Come!
- Help!
Come!
I will do whatever you say!
- Don't touch me! Please!
Come! Please!
- Beat me! -Excuse me!
Excuse me, guys! Try and understand!
I will take whatever you give me!
Don't touch me!
Everybody is watching! - Come!
Excuse me!
- Beat me!
Aren't you ashamed to tease a
woman who is like your mother?
No, no! He is not
misbehaving with me! - Beat me!
Beat me! Hard!
What are you doing? He is
my customer! - Beat me hard!
Why don't you beat me?
- Leave!
Don't touch me! Please! Hey, beat me.
Leave!
Leave him! What are you doing?
He is my customer! Leave him!
Why are you beating him!
Leave him!
- Ladies and gentlemen!
Look at this!
- Hit him.
Come and see this!
He was teasing a woman!
- O my God!
Idiot!
I won't spare you!
You have harassed me!
Stupid man!
Why happened?
- Leave! Leave!
What are you doing? Leave!
What happened?
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
42!
Laxminarayan!
I think I am destined to kill him!
Stand straight! Stand straight
otherwise I will beat you more!
An unlucky man is being beaten!
- Amita, come!
Go and help!
- Go and see!
Go!
The door!
I have hit him! Now call
the police! Call the police!
Call the police.
No, no, no! Sir, please
don't do that! - Police!
Police!
- No police! Please, sir!
Sir, don't do that.
- Police! - My hotel is a very good..
"One, two, three."
Police! Call the police!
- No.
You are right. No need to call
the police. The work is over!
No police! No police!
- The work is over!
Mummy, papa won't do this again!
Papa, say sorry to mummy! Come on!
End the matter, sir.
Sorry!
You thrashed me badly!
He thrashed you so badly, papa.
Like a dog!
You said to beat papa!
- But not so badly!
Please, let me go! You guys
got what you wanted. Please!
Papa, he too thrashed you.
He thrashed papa black and blue!
He is a dangerous man.
He even knows the
size of your underwear.
Papa!
- Papa!
That Laxminarayan is
running away with the bag!
Here you are, sir! Right, sir!
Hey! Hey!
- Where are you going?
You too get your bag!
I will press the remote from here.
The bomb will explode.
Not from here. Take him.
Take him from here. - Fool!
Come!
- Come on!
Come on!
"One, two, three."
Come on, boss.
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
"Coming in this world is free."
"Leaving the world is free."
Shall I press the button?
- Press the button.
Not now! Not now!
- "One two, three. One two, three."
Come on! Sit in the car!
Papa.. - Come on! - Please
let me go! Get him in! Please
Press the button!
- Which one, papa?
The left one.
Now you can't even ask whose left.
Because left is the
same for all of us.
Aim at Yadav, Laxmi! And Khujli,
you aim at Laxmi!
Today, either he or he will die.
One! One.. two.. three.
One.. two.. three.
It didn't explode! It didn't explode!
Idiot! I think it's not in the range!
Albert! Take the car closer.
"It's like that. So heat it up!"
"It's like that. Yeah!"
Brother, I think they know
that we are following them!
They are increasing the speed!
I will speed up the car! You aim!
1, 2, 3.
"One two three." Drive faster!
We are getting late!
Don't you know my nature!
Papa, it didn't explode!
Why doesn't it explode?
Drive closer!
Brother! Brother, he is in
my range. Shall I shoot?
Hang on! First we have to find
out where is the diamond. - Yes!
I will speed up. One, two, three..
It didn't explode.
"It's like that. Yeah!"
"It's like that. So heat it up!"
Papa!
- Yes! "It's like that. Yeah!"
The car in the rear wants to
overtake. Shall I let him do it?
Papa tell him if he
let's him overtake..
..our car will be in the middle
and we won't be in the range! Mad..
I say crush him!
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
"You are coming into this world fee"
One, two, three.
Laxminarayan, it's
your first murder! Shoot!
"You are coming into this world fee"
One, two, three.
For the sake of your mother, shoot!
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
It exploded! It exploded!
Papa! What could I do..
- Hey!
Papa, he is running away! Catch him..
No, papa!
I was going to take your permission.
May I take your leave please? Please.
No! You can't leave until
he doesn't die! Follow him!
You miss still water
and dead grandma a lot.
Yes, brother! -Why are
you looking at my face?
We shouldn't spare Yadav! Come on!
- Where, brother?
Dad! Dad, listen! Listen!
Dad, she is fooling you!
Son, you too be fooled. Its great fun!
Laila!
Laxminarayan, you have come!
Come! Please come!
Please come!
- Here!
So nice to see you!
- Its 9 lakhs!
Here.
- Thank you! - And where is my car?
Polishing is going on!
You guys hurry up!
Laxminarayan has come!
And its cash. Count it. Fine?
Count it. - Okay.
Yes..
- Count it properly.
What is this?
- I got bundles of 10s. What to do?
Is this bundle of 10s?
This is panty!
She calls panty a bundle!
Panty! I had put the bundle in this!
- How did the panties come here?
These are my designs!
How did you get it?
Hi, Jia!
You! How dare you come in front of me!
You told Laxminarayan to
take my samples and to kill me!
Wait and watch. I'll kill you.
Dad, is this what you told her?
First tell me who is she?
Dad, she is Jia. You
had come for her designs.
I didn't even meet her. Greetings.
Greetings. Who is he?
I am Laxminarayan.
Underwear and vest seller.
So who was he?
Hang on! Hang on! Who was who?
- I..
Dad, what's the matter?
You didn't meet her?
You gave me this
photo in the envelope.
So how could I have met her?
- And this was..
..for the other Laxminarayan.
Who is this other Laxminarayan?
There! There is Laxminarayan!
What kind of project have I accepted!
You have made me a dog!
Press the button!
Hey!
What kind of bomb
have you manufactured!
It doesn't explode!
- Laxmi..
..I have a diploma.
From where did you get the diploma?
Papa, we will go in
front of him and press it!
Some things don't work from behind!
I had come to buy
panties and I got a car.
That Laxminarayan
had come to buy a car.
And he will get panties.
This is the same car
which I wanted to buy!
Right said, Mr. Laxminarayan
O my God!
- Not that Laxminarayan!
God knows where he will be!
Excuse me, ma'am! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Excuse me, ma'am!
Excuse me, ma'am! Excuse me, sir?
Can I come in? Can I come in?
Can I say something, ma'am?
- Sure.
Sir! Ma'am, I am the
other Laxminarayan! I..
Hey! He was in the room next to mine!
He was the one!
- Right, sir!
Ma'am, I had come to buy
the car for Mr. Pipat!
Oh yeah! Mr. Pipat had called me!
Right, man! I am his man!
- Oh!
Pipat's man!
- Right, sir!
Tell me something.
- Yes, sir!
Your Pipat..
- Yes, sir.
He doesn't have a wife?
- No, no, sir! He has two wives
Come on, dad!
- Two wives? - Right, sir!
And he has kept a man too!
What kind of man is he!
Let's go there! Come on!
Take this! Take your photo!
I got it by mistake. Keep it!
And yes, sir! Sir, your photo!
You had come to kill him, sir.
One, two..
Why doesn't it explode?
Sir, you are a sharp shooter.
Sharp shooter. - Sharp shooter?
- No. I sell underwear.
You didn't come to kill him?
Then who had come to kill him?
Third Laxminarayan! He came to me!
Brother, there!
There! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Pinto, press it!
No, no, no! Papa!
Please! Please!
Don't press the remote! Please!
Why?
He is your papa? Greetings!
No, no, no! He is not my papa!
Everybody calls him papa.
So I also call him papa.
- Everybody's papa!
D'mello Yadav! Gangster!
"Everybody say." "Fools."
Nobody move! -"Fools."
Otherwise I will shoot!
O my God!
Take whatever they have! Come on!
Laxminarayan!
You had come to kill me?
- O my God!
D'mello Yadav!
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
Ones..
- No, papa! No, papa!
Papa, don't press the remote.
It will explode, papa!
Please, papa!
- Hang on!
Please
- Where is the bomb?
Sir! Sir, in your bag!
One. Two. Three..
There is a bomb in my bag?
- Yes!
Is this a bomb?
This is the cover of the bomb.
Then where is the bomb?
The bomb is in your bag,
D'mello Yadav!
You? Who are you?
Laxminarayan!
- The third one!
Orange is never hard.
And Batlya's enemy
never has enough time.
Hey! Hey!
Your bomb will kill you.
Give the remote.
Papa, don't listen to him.
We had changed the tag of
the bag. Pinto, show it!
I had changed it!
Papa! Papa, I had myself
changed the tag of the left bag..
..with the right one.
And I had changed the tag of
the left bag with the right one.
I don't understand!
Can I say something? Can I..
Okay! Can I say something?
Please! Okay!
Please! Please! You guys
drop the guns! Please!
Thank you, guys. Now you
listen to me carefully. Okay!
Excuse me! Get me the table please!
The left one. Get me..
.. the right one. Thank you very much.
Now tell me who changed the tag first?
I did it! I did it!
- How did you change it? Show it.
I changed the tag of the
left bag with the right one!
I see! When you did it then the
left was your left or my left?
My, It was my left.
Then I shifted the
left one to the centre.
And I changed the right
one with the left one.
That's it. Simple. One, two, three.
BBC. Bomb. Bra. Cash.
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
Then one two was made two one.
Then again one two was made two one.
And one was exchanged with three.
One, two, three.
Absolutely clear and simple.
You guys get it?
No? You.. One.. two.. three.
No?
You understood?
No, no, no.. I say press the remote.
The one which will explode,
it has the bomb.
Sir, I think this is the best idea..
- Wonderful..
..considering that you
guys are.. -Papa press it.
One.. two.. three.
You are slandering me since morning.
Is there a bomb? Or he
is just pressing it.
No, sir. There is a bomb.
I myself saw it.
But it doesn't explode.
He has manufactured it.
Hold this. Show me the remote.
One.. two.. three.
The plus and minus
signs are interchanged.
How will it explode?
It should be the other way round?
Make minus as plus. And put
the cap. And say one, two, three.
It exploded, papa?
It didn't explode! It didn't explode!
It didn't explode!
Since morning you have
been humiliating me!
You humiliated me in the car!
You've humiliated me a lot.
You humiliated me in front
of these girls! I will..
Hey! Rangeela's Jackie Shroff! Quiet!
You are beating me
in front of everybody.
What can I do if the
battery is not functioning!
Right! Right! Isn't it
better to open the bag and check?
Right!
- No!
Now it's not about the bomb exploding!
It's about my honour!
Now until the bomb doesn't explode..
..give me the gun!
Hey!
- Give me the gun! Give me the gun!
Otherwise I will shoot!
Give me the gun! - Give the gun!
Otherwise he will shoot himself!
Please! Give the gun!
- Quiet!
You don't say anything!
I will explode you
before the bomb explodes!
Albert, come here!
- Fine..
I am normal with you!
Go and buy two
batteries from the shop. Go.
I don't have change.
- Change!
I will give you. But
bring it quickly. Go. Go.
Thanks.
Pinto! Pinto!
Why do you harp Pinto the whole day?
You pronounce it improperly!
He always add 'S'
after an English word.
He makes us say fathers.
People have one father in the world.
And we have 5.5 lakhs fathers.
- Right!
Papa, you shouldn't do that! -Yes!
Hey! I will thrash you!
Papa adds S. But why
are you interfering?
I will thrash you. He is a fool..
Pinto! I brought you from the street!
From the orphanage! I gave
him clothes! I gave it to him!
So did I give an application?
To adopt me?
Father dies in darkness
and the son in a powerhouse.
Here are your clothes. Dramatic man!
- Pinto!
You always beat me in
front of others. - Pinto!
What happened?
- Listen to me!
Yes!
- Listen!
Did you buy it from Pahadganj?
- Yes.
Its Khurana's goods.
- How did you know?
Only Khurana sells such cheap stuff.
Do you know?
Saying Calvin Klein,
he gives us Khurana's goods.
He is a miser!
Calvin Klein doesn't
make such underwear..
How could you say that? - You look good.
Ma'am, I am telling you.
Don't say it in public.
- This man!
Kills by giving electric shock.
During power cuts he
kills by using the generator.
You don't cry. Ask him.
Shall I tell him
what happened on Sunday?
This Sunday or previous Sunday?
Fool! You!
- Sorry!
Sorry! Say it clearly!
Pinto! Pinto! Don't get angry!
Don't get angry!
Batlya brother, you don't interfere.
Look, you are like my younger son.
Yes. That's why I am telling you.
Who killed your Hiralal? We did it.
Now where did
Hiralal hide the jewellery?
We don't know! Tell me!
You know something.
Memory has become weak!
Which diamond? What diamond? What car?
One, two, three.
- This was the one!
"One, two, three. One, two, three."
Papa, they both are the one!
Tell me! Where is the diamond?
I don't know!
Very good, Chandu! Don't tell him!
Even if you have to lay down
your life! Don't tell him!
Okay! Chandu! Where is the diamond?
Stop it! What are you doing?
Tell him that it's in the petrol tank!
Petrol tank!
It's my diamond!
- It's my diamond!
I have bought the car! Its mine!
I had come for the diamonds!
- it is mine. - It's mine!
I have the gun! So the
diamond is mine, papa!
But petrol tank is not opening.
How to get the diamond?
"One, two, three." Then..
Heave! Everybody heave!
What are you doing? - Vomiting!
- Vomiting! - Vomiting! - Vomiting!
I said to turn the car!
- Oh!
Which one? This one or that one?
His questions and answers!
What do want?
- Give me two batteries.
Which one? Big, medium, small?
- For remote!
Which remote? VCG, DVD or TV.
For the remote of a bomb.
Fatehchand.
- Yes, ma'am.
Did you hear what I heard?
- Ma'am!
Guys! Guys! Guys! Hold it up!
Hold it up! Hold it up!
Up! Up! Up!
Your right! Your right!
Not my right! Here! Here!
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Leaving the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free."
Good.
Hey! Hey!
- Diamond!
I saw it in the photo!
Today this diamond is mine, papa!
One, two, three.
My Pinto! Pinto!
Pinto! Somebody save him!
Diamond! Diamond!
- Hold this!
Yes!
- Doctor!
Hey! Hey!
This is my diamond!
As long as D'mello Yadav is there..
..this is not possible!
Give me this diamond, Batlya!
Doctor! Doctor! Will I get well?
Will I get well?
- Leave me, Pinto! Leave!
Give it to me, Yadav!
- Yes!
Give me the diamond otherwise..
Here.
Who is the king of Mumbai!
- Me!
Come on! Come!
You fraud! You look so nice!
Catch him!
- Stops!
Hey!
Dad, here!
Here!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Excuse me! Son, climb up!
Hang on! I will do it!
Excuse me!
My Pinto will die!
Don't make him stand on the car!
Brother D'mello, throw the stick!
Throw the stick! - Hang on!
The stick is of no use! Throw the bag!
If anybody moved I won't spare you!
I know everything!
There is a bomb here!
Bomb and here? Who told you?
Here there is no bomb.
- No.
There is no bomb!
- No! No! No! No!
Mayawati Chowtala's
information can never be wrong!
Tek Chand!
- Come on!
Tell me, Albert. Where is the bomb?
He is a child. What will he know?
- Get lost!
We don't even know who he is!
There is no bomb here! Who are you?
There is a bomb!
- Which bomb?
The one whose battery is this!
Which battery?
- For the remote!
Oh no!
This is not a bomb's remote!
- Then what remote is this?
This is a TV remote!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Where is the TV?
- There is no TV! - TV..
We have the remote. We have to
buy the TV. - We will buy it later.
So this not a bomb's remote?
- No! No!
The bomb won't
explode by pressing this?
No! No!
Then press it and check!
- Yes! No! No! No!
Why are you scared?
When there is no bomb, it
won't explode! - Correct!
And if it exploded then
you all will be in trouble.
So one..
No! No! No!
Two.. Where are you going?
Three!
There is no bomb here.
If there was a bomb,
it would have exploded.
And if there was an
explosion meaning there was a bomb!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Quiet! Silence! If anybody speaks..
Papa!
- Who spoke up? Speak louder!
Hail Goddess!
- Papa!
Say it again!
- Hail Goddess!
I am asking who is making this noise!
Papa!
Who is stuck down?
Papa, I forgot to say
that this is a time bomb.
What are you saying?
- What!
By mistake I got time bomb
instead of remote bomb, papa.
Then at what time will it explode?
Uncle, at 6 o'clock!
By the way papa, what's the time?
Hang on! Hang on! 3 seconds to 6!
It means one..
- Two..
Three.
Papa, did the bomb explode?
- One, two, three.
'Pinto's bomb blasted the diamond..
..and not the people into pieces.'
'Its said that nobody gets
anything before the right time..
..and more than what they deserve.'
'Everybody got their
share of diamond.'
'What Laxminarayan one and Jia got..
..with that they bought their
share of restaurant from Munde.'
'Today too Laxmi's mother
wants her son to be a shooter.'
'And she tells the
same thing to every goon.'
If this time he fails, he is not
his father's son. Let me tell you.
'Laxminarayan two bought
some shares of virus autos..
..with his share..
..and today he is the board
of director in that company.'
'And his boss Pipat..'
Pipat.
- Yes, sir!
I think we need to talk.
- Yes, sir.
Sit. - Sir, on the
chair or the sofa? - Chair.
Left or right?
- Left.
Your left or my left?
'Laxminarayan three sells underwear..
..and vest in a bus and not in a car.'
'And Laila is his brand ambassador.'
'Mayawati Chowtala gave
bribe with her share..
..and she has become a jailor.'
'And her prisoners are Albert,
Pinto, papa and Batlya.'
'Chandu and Chandni have
bought the showroom from Laila.'
'And it's heard that they
are going to marry soon.'
'But they are still
running in the race of life.'
'To be one, two and three.'
"Your youth."
"Listen to my song. One, two, three."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"One, two, three!
And one, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
"Tolerating
thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
"One, two, three."
"Darling, don't leave me!"
"Don't break my heart!"
"You are under the oath of my youth."
"Say you want to know."
"I am beat and here we go."
"Mamma, you like move."
"Move, come on."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Free! Free!"
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"One, two, three!
And one, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
"Tolerating
thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
"One, two, three."
"Darling, don't leave me!"
"Don't break my heart!"
"You are under the oath of my youth."
"Your youth.."
"Your youth is the most
talked about everywhere."
"My heart has been waiting for you."
"You are under the oath of my youth."
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Coming into the world is free!"
"Going from the world is free."
"Look at this charade of the world."
"Absolutely free! Absolutely free!"
"One, two, three! One, two, three!"
"Me and you! You and me!"
"The world's A B C D!"
"Tolerating
thousands of difficulties."
"To rise up from a plant to a tree."
"Let's take out the one,
two, and three."
"One, two, three. One, two, three."