How much can you make a business with Layers?
We can make millions
As a creator, there are many ways to earn money
We should know what we shouldn't do
I think that technology is coming
I don't want to tell you
Please cut this part
Am I fake?
Am I pretending?
Today we have a creator with us
Who you know for technology
But I think of him as a good businessman
Normally we hear that to make a business
We should have an idea
Then we make a business and do marketing
But he has reversed this wheel
First he created a distribution
Then he is making a business
And I think he is making a business in a very smart way
In some places, I am having a problem
I think I should ask questions
So we will ask questions
Let's know about him
Hello friends, I am Shlok Srivastav
We are making tech videos
We have been making videos for 10 years
And along with that
I have a passion
In every person
I also have a passion for design and aesthetics
I always wanted to make something
In which I can put my love
If it reaches the audience through physical products
It will be great
So we have built a clothing brand
And a mobile accessories brand
Apart from that
We have executed a lot of social media and marketing
projects
In the last 6-7 years
It has been an insightful and interesting journey
We have done a lot of big launches
The next few years are definitely going to be very strong
I don't know how to praise myself
You are doing very well
Tell me
When you started the YouTube channel
Did you decide to launch a product?
Or was it a journey as a creator?
While doing it
When you got the audience
Did you think of selling something?
As a creator
There are a lot of ways to earn money
Because you have a lot of things
You can do marketing for a company
Like there are so many companies
You can help them in marketing
We have also built applications
We have built different things
And I have noticed that
There is a different game everywhere
Making a product is a different game
Our main goal was to inspire
Because I saw a problem
In India
There is no shortage of resources
It's not like we make so much food
That we feed the whole population 3 times
So I faced a problem with the mindset
So my goal was
To make something different
Something strong
Something that creates a movement
And we tried that
With layers
That product was not successful before
And that product was not in the market
No one knew what skins were
There were few people who knew
But apart from that we created the market
So when that emotion
Gets attached to a project
I think it propels it
Same with clothes
I saw that all the clothes in India
Are being sold by international brands
And Indian brands are selling it cheap
Some are selling it for 200 rupees
Some are selling it for 500 rupees
We are cutting the price
No one is making such expensive clothes
So we tried to solve that problem
It took us a long time to solve that problem
It took us 3 years to make clothes
To make such clothes
That are dealing with international brands
It took us 3 years to make the same skins
To install the factory
To set up the manufacturing
To see the operations
The technologies that are used for that
I think
We have to make money
Business can run only with money
If there is no money
Then what is business
I don't believe in that
I think if we want to make something big
Internationally We need money
But the goal was to create a movement
I think we have done that
To some extent
But now the goal is
To take the Indian brand
To an international level
I have thought about it
If you count on your hands
Like we were asking you
There are so many brands that are selling Indian brands
We can't count on our fingers
We don't even know the brands that are selling outside India
And there are very few brands
So I think someone has to break the barrier
Someone has to make international business from India
So we
Go into that risky area
And do things
Now it's a stove
So one thing I wanted to ask
Which is honest
You have worked on your personal branding
Because I think
I have seen this constantly
I am from a marketing background
So I notice small things
What I noticed
When we talked
There was a fire in the message
Some of your keywords
Like we were talking normally
We were talking like this
And when we make videos
We talk like this
We will do this
Did this happen naturally
Or did it take time
Because if I watch old English videos
At that time
Body language
And as we are transitioning to recent
There is a difference in our body language
We have changed a lot to make a relation with our audience
This is honest
Yes 100%
Like a person
I have thought a lot about this
Am I pretending
And what happens is
I have seen myself
Like every person has a different style
When he is going to meet girls
He becomes sweet
When he is going to meet his brothers
He has a different vibe
Like this
Same person
If he is talking to kids
He becomes sweet
And if he is talking to his friends
He becomes sad
So I saw that
I used to try to talk sophisticated
Professionally In my college
Then I thought
My friends are coming
After that
I felt uncomfortable in English
Because our mindset is like this
When do we speak English
We have to speak formally
It becomes a habit
Hindi becomes a comfort
So I imagined
My friends are sitting behind
I am talking to them
Like when we were talking before
I was a business owner
To a business owner
But now I know
Many young entrepreneurs are watching this
So I want
They should also
Feel the same
That's why I change a little
So who is your audience
If you imagine
What is their age
Where do they live
Where are they studying
So I imagined my audience
When I started
I imagined my age
Because they are the same type
Who are doing everything
So I imagined
In the beginning
Guys who are interested in tech
Because usually 5% of the guys are interested in tech
This is the start of YouTube
Majorly 16 to 24 years old guys
Who are studying engineering
Those who are studying coding
Engineering That is my audience
Engineers are interested in technology
They attract them
If you see anything
They get attracted
So I took my audience
And I was not deciding
Now it is different
You will be able to notice
My way of speaking changes
The way of speaking changes
The way of showing things visually changes
On Instagram
There are a lot of girls on Instagram
There are a lot of people on Instagram
Who follow for fashion
There is a different vibe on Instagram
The audience is very different
People on YouTube know about tech
Let me give you an example
Recently I go out less
I went to the bank
I had to do KYC
I have to go there
I had to change my account
I saw a girl
She said hi
I watch your videos
Age Reversal
I uploaded this video 2 years ago
I was confused
She said
I asked where did you see
By chance we cut the clip
And uploaded it on Facebook
She did not know about our long form video
She did not know about tech
She knew that we upload short clips
She just saw our video on Facebook
You will not believe
In our audience
There are only a few Indian cities
There are cities of Bangladesh
There are a few cities outside India
There are a few cities of US
There are a few cities of Canada
I did not know
Every platform
There is a different audience
And now it has become so different
That everyone has to treat it differently
So there is a different type of content for everyone
Yes 100%
We are not able to optimize for everyone
I try to make content that
Can cater to everyone
Now what happened?
You grew your channel
It became a base
People were knowing
Your demographic was clear
A 16-24 year old kid
You made a product around his needs
The first product was Layers
I am also a Layers
Your audience
I will tell you
When I was doing engineering
I had a Micromax
A116 Micromax was not a good brand
I did not like Micromax
I used skin
Just to hide the Micromesh
At that time all the phones looked the same
The phones were sold on screen size
Today there is a lot of trend
At that time screen size was a big issue
It was a big phone
Micromesh canvas
If I had put a skin on the back, my Micromesh would have
been hidden
So my target
If I think why I used the skin
To hide the Micromesh
If we talk about today
The phones become prominent
So according to me most people
Don't use the skin
If I try to think demographically
Then you tell me
Because I want to know your point of view
I am trying to think
Who buys
One people
Who like to keep their phones naked
Without cases
And they want scratches on their phones
Second people
Who want to show their phones as a trend
Because now a days most of the phones come in white plain
background
They want something
Or They want to express their emotions
There is one audience
Who wants to show
I am like this
So basically they are expressing their emotions
If I say third audience
I will say
They are resembling a community
If I talk about my brother
My brother
Brought a roll from Gafar market
He has
A 3D printer
He has a CNC printer
So now a days
Models are available online
Of every phone case
So he goes to buy a new phone
He gets the exact same sheet
Printed and put it on his phone
So whenever his phone changes
And he changes his phone a lot
Every 3 months
His back will always be the same
Technology will change, camera will change
But the look and feel of the phone
Will always be the same
I use my phone
So that I always remember
If someone keeps their phone aside
I always remember my phone
That is his mindset
So I am able to think of these 3 people
You tell me what you thought
When I started
I was not able to define
It was a mistake
And I was not able to define it
Because at that time
It was not a must to adopt it
After this product
The audience we wanted to sell
I wanted to sell
It was not well known
There were very few skin men
Delhi, Mumbai
Nehru Place, Gafar
You used to get skin in Gafar
And they used to cut it off with a blade
They used to cut it off
With a blade
They used to scratch it
The problem was
It did not glow
I felt that the quality of the skin
Was not that good
And the design was not that good
So we worked hard
To add texture
And no one was able to copy it
Because the set up was worth crores
If I break down the layers of the business
We removed the need
That this is not a need driven business
There is no need for this product in the market
It is not that
No one wants skin
It is a humanity driven
Or emotional purchase
Who wants to purchase it?
It makes me feel good
I love the design and texture
It is not that
It saves from scratches
It provides protection
But the primary reason
Is that you feel
That you are a part of a community
That is the primary
Need of
Belonging I feel good
Like college students
Represent themselves
For example
We wear clothes
Like Gucci
Or I wear a watch
It is not that
It solves a functional purpose
Like logo or watch
It is the same watch
It tells me the time
It is not a functional product
It is an emotional purchase
In my opinion
Emotional purchase is a good thing
Because people say
Don't spend money
Why not?
Everything is so
Emotionally driven
Let me give you an example 22 boys
Are hitting the ball with a stick
And a country of 1 billion
Is watching them
Everyone is happy
Everyone is shouting
The whole country is sad
That they couldn't hit with a stick
There is no purpose
There is no logic
Everything is emotional
If we break down
What is logical 90% of the things we do
Are emotionally driven
In India
There is no lack of resources
There is a lack of mindset
The same mindset
And the same
If you go to India
To meet rich people
I go to clubs
Do you know what kind of people
I meet?
I make henna oil
I make a tyre cover
I make a machine
To clean the road
I make the threads
And what will happen?
Profit will be 800 crores
Profit will be 600 crores
In India, the same business
But I think
From today
The time of internet
From now
Vanity and emotional businesses
Will be successful
I think
Distribution was created
If we talk about a normal brand
They also have to sell their skin
Because everyone has money
A person can install a machine
Can bring the same technology
Distribution can also come in India
Distribution will be on every sale
Today I researched 60-70% traffic
Is coming on your website
Because of Shlok
Shlok has generated a lot of business
But today
If a new brand comes
They have to make their own brand
Maybe they run a ppc campaign
When someone searches skin
Or layer
They have to take a lot of tension
In which
Where you can earn a good margin
By selling a skin for 500
The other person
Can't earn even by selling a skin for 800
Because he has to spend a lot of money
Maybe the business doesn't work
Because people follow Shlok
People trust Shlok
People say that I don't care about 100-150
If I have to put a skin, I will put a good one
I don't want to take a loss
Let me tell you two things
Our mode
Our factory
Because we have increased the entry barrier
If you want to compete with us
You need factory setup
You need machines, latest technology
You need printing
The 3M paper
We source it from a different country
Our product is the best in India
It is best because
We have spent money
Entry barrier is of money
No one can make it better than us
No one
The other thing is
Distribution We have worked hard for it
It is like saying
You are coming to play basketball
You are tall 100% advantage
But I will use that advantage
If I have any advantage of distribution
I will reach my audience 100%
And I feel
Even empty distribution doesn't work
Let me give you an example
Logan Paul and Mr.
They are very popular in the US
Logan Paul has 2 million views
In the last video 2-3 million views
Mr. Beast has 150-200 million 300 million
Distribution is worldwide 150-200 million
Only in US
In Hindi 10-20 million
Mr. Beast has more than 100% distribution
But Prime
It is a 7 billion dollar business
And Mr.
Beast's fee stable
Is not that good
So I feel
Distribution alone doesn't work
Product should be good
I feel
If product is not good, then nothing
Product should be better than market
But I feel
There is a way to spread message
It makes a difference
People get to know
You are making something good
You are telling the truth
If you work hard, people will buy
It is easy to reach people
It is not that difficult to buy distribution
But it takes money
Most of the companies are in loss
If you promote in shorts
You will get 40-50 million views
Conversion Conversion is not coming
Distribution is there
Conversion is not coming
Conversion is emotionally driven
When an influencer is connected
With a product
You won't be able to buy it
Even if you give 10 lakh rupees
You will get 40 million views
People will see
But people know it is an ad
When an influencer is involved in a product
Or the owner
Like I made distribution
I was famous
And I built things
Over a period of time
Now the company is doing the opposite
They knew they were figuring out a product
They made their marketing
They knew what to make
Now the owner is coming
To make a video
We also saw what the situation is, and the owners
themselves are making it, so I think those days have gone
that you just sit down and buy the distribution, give 10-20
lakhs, spend crores, the distribution will come, the work
will be done, those days
have gone, because now people are used to sitting idle, the
owner himself will have to come and sell, or if he doesn't
come, he will have to learn social media, how content is
made, how people's minds have to reach them, that is very
important to me.
It is a big fight for everyone, and if you are doing your
business, then if possible, then instead of paid
distribution, focus on building a community, make your own
social media, where people trust you, not for your product,
but whatever you are delivering,
now try to gather a community together, so that in the
future, when you subconsciously integrate your product, it
keeps on selling.
People will say, let's talk about Elon Musk for example, we
have been seeing him working a lot in the personal brand.
100%, at this time, the value of words is very high, and
the value of connect is very high, so I think it will be a
major part.
This is a hard question, because our audience enjoys this
discussion. How much business is being made from layers?
Approximately, if we talk about the revenue point of view.
If I tell you honestly, our revenue is around crores, but
because there are a lot of investments, like I told you, we
have invested in a design agency.
In that, our entire design agency will change, that is, the
new products we are building, we have a design agency
outside India, a UK design agency, which basically designs
spaceships.
Together, we are designing a product, which we will launch
in April-May, because it takes 8 months to make a
differentiated product. So, all the money we are getting,
it is getting invested in new product development.
So, if you look at the actual profit on paper, then our
profit will be almost 0, and we will be in loss, because
more money is being invested in the next project. So, from
the revenue point of view, we are doing decent, because if
I tell you honestly,
we would have to go international.
In India, it is a luxury purchase. Skin is a very luxury
purchase, and the market ahead of it is outside India. And
after this, I don't want to buy a small mobile accessory. I
want to take a big jump in the consumer electronics space.
I am not selling a TV, I am not selling a speaker, but I am
selling a watch. When it will launch, you will know.
Everyone has said no, everyone has said yes, that is, if
nothing is said on one, then it is the same. Let's go ahead.
It can be a watch like this, or it can be a mobile, or it
can be a spaceship.
What do you say? We are selling cars to go to Mars.
Like I have a franchise business of Chole Bhature on the
moon.
It's been 8 years, we are selling franchises.
So, I understood, but is the revenue fluctuating? Is it
increasing?
Revenue is constantly increasing. I think when we started,
it was increasing quite well. Because we are not just
Techburner, we have done marketing in many other things
besides Techburner.
When I searched, Google ads were running. Ads are running,
then we work with other influencers and do multiple things.
And the community that buys, continues to reach them.
Launches keep happening, so even old customers keep buying.
I think one major reason for a business to be successful,
like overlays and layers, is that our customers buy again.
We don't have one-time buyers.
The person who buys from us once, that is a lifetime waste.
Normally, what is the cycle? How many months does a person
change their skin on average?
In 6 months, a person usually changes their skin. There are
many people who change their skin in 3-4 months. And there
are many people who like to change their skin. Usually, the
female customers I have seen, their frequency is more to
change their skin.
But our audience is dominantly male.
Are you focusing more on Instagram? No, I am not focusing
on Instagram to attract girls. We don't have a major focus
on Instagram. It is more on the lines that earlier, the
fashion style that I used to think of, I never visually
output it.
I used to think that people will find it weird that a tech
creator is wearing this kind of clothes. Or why is he
engaging in fashion? So, I used to get scared. I talked to
a lot of people and asked them how to do it. So, I used to
think that I don't stop
myself. And even this fear, let me tell you, I even have
business values.
Earlier, when I used to make YouTube videos, people used to
find it weird that I suddenly started talking about
business. Because they don't know that I have done so many
things in the past. It is the same thing on Instagram. Now
people are thinking that
I have become a fashion person suddenly. But for 2-3 years,
I have been involved in fashion. I have done designs, I
have designed clothes, I have done a lot of things. So, it
was a constant work in progress. But now people have
started to see it.
I think my focus is that for some time, I want to sell only
to boys. I don't want to sell more to girls. Because the
marketer knows that.
Why didn't you sell skins and cases? Because let's see, the
audience is the same. The skin audience was small and the
same audience could have sold more cases.
In cases, what is the brand of case in India that sells
printed cases well, which is very successful? You will not
be able to get it. Usually, the cases that will be there
will only be of iPhone. It will not be that everyone will
be selling. If there
will be, then the iPhone will be selling.
The reason is that the supply chain is very difficult.
There are so many challenges in the supply chain that if
you want to sell a good quality case for Rs 300-400, it is
a very difficult business.
And you will not make a profit in that. Because I tell you,
the case companies that sell so many cases, you have no
idea. People have no idea that tons of cases are burned.
This is a very wastage. When I was entering, I thought of a
case only. But I realized that it was a good decision for
the environment and everything. Plus, the supply chain is
so difficult that if we enter, we would have made a
business. But in that,
I didn't want to get into accessories for a long time.
I liked the skin of the case. And we wouldn't have been
able to add something like this to the case. The supply
chain of the case is difficult for a normal person. But if
you put on the whole manufacturing setup.
When an order comes, do we already have the skin ready? I
will tell you operationally that I am not so much into
operations. We have hired heads who lead operations. But
around 30% remains with us.
And our supply chain is so fast that if we get an order
now, we can ship it by the evening. Everything is packed
and shipped by the evening. But the problem is that we get
more orders.
And how much capacity do we have now? How much can we make
daily? I will have to check. Because now we have 3
machines. I don't know exactly, but we can easily do
2000-3000. But I will have to confirm.
I will tell you honestly that I personally don't get into
operations. Because I don't have the strength in
operations. For that, I have brought the right people who
know it well. And I think as a business owner, our biggest
skill is that we should know
what we don't want to do and what we don't know.
I have made a mistake by doing all this. And I have learned
this from experience that I should bring someone else for
what I don't know. I am involved in design, product
development and marketing. I know how to build a product,
what is going on in the
market, what is the demand of people, how to design, what
screw will be used, what will be the finish, what texture
will come, how to open in packaging, what smell should come.
I am deeply involved in this.
And I am deeply involved in the marketing part.
I think, I will tell you honestly, operations is a job that
anyone can do.
There are people in the market who can do it.
And why should I do such a job that people in the market
can already do?
But the product development and design is very unique to
us. No one else can copy that in the market. So that's why
I try to do the same thing that only I can do.
So how did you switch overlays? After skin?
I am not switching, both are working together.
No, I mean, why did you think that I do this too? We have
more alternatives to do.
But why did you choose jackets? Did you feel that this
business is not being made, a good business can be made in
a jacket?
No, no, nothing like that. Layers are running well. Layers
are running well. Layers are growing.
But let's see, tan wise, if we talk about making a bigger
business, then we can make a bigger business in the
clothing line versus skin. I will start with this point.
Yes, 100%.
So did you start clothing thinking this?
because we had to do it first.
I'll tell you honestly, we started with overlays before
layers. I mean, actually, in the beginning, we started with
overlays first. We started with layers later.
And in overlays, what happened was, at that time, the entry
barrier, as I told you, the entry barrier was huge.
If you want to make high-quality clothes, if you want to
make basic clothes, 100% cotton T-shirts, with a little bit
of print.
You can make it, anyone can make it.
There are so many factories.
But if you want to make clothes that beat international
brands, there are only a few factories in India that can
make it for you.
They have the machines.
They have the things that will provide you quality at that
level.
That was a big problem to solve.
We have to beat them.
But we don't even have that much money that how do you work
in such a big factory?
They take lakhs of orders.
Now we don't even have the budget for lakhs of orders.
It wasn't there at that time.
We were just starting at that time.
Then what did we do?
We decided how to do it.
We won't sell less quality.
We can't start selling less quality
We decided to make our own factory.
We do everything.
We have been running this factory for 2-2.5 years.
We had bought a factory before this.
It was 2-2.5 years old.
We were making it.
We were improving in every launch.
Then we bought a big factory.
And when we felt that our quality has been set.
This is going to beat any international brand.
We are selling at a price where no international brand can
compete.
Then we presented it well to the market.
Till then we didn't do any marketing.
Till then we did a little marketing in launches.
But it reached the masses when we actually made a product
which people knew that we made it.
And it is of good quality.
And we are selling it at the right price.
So that's why people saw it.
But actually this thing has been going on for 3-3.5 years.
And even now what happens is when we make more videos
people think that we have shifted the business.
It's not like that.
Majorly both things are growing together continuously.
And we keep shifting it month by month.
That this month is its launch.
This month is its launch like this.
So it will run continuously.
But yes, as you said
Kinz's market has an upper cap in India.
To expand its cap now as I tell you layers you think its
promotion is not going on.
But its promotion is going on outside India.
We are figuring out how to do it outside India.
So we are growing it more outside India.
And we are figuring out things outside India.
We don't even know about overlays in India.
So in India we are doing it.
So what is everyone's strategy in doing things like this?
See, how technical it is.
I feel that many people understand Shlok.
That's why I wanted to do it with you.
I have been connecting with you for a long time.
Because most people understand Shlok as a YouTuber.
They think he will set fire.
And no one knows how smart he is sitting behind.
Who has thought a lot strategically.
When are the watches coming? I don't want to tell you about
the watches yet.
You will know whether we will do the watches or not.
What will be the price segment? Will it be affordable or
super premium? We are figuring it out.
We are working very hard right now.
I want to say this.
And I can only tell you that we are working with the best
companies in the world.
And we are giving a lot of time to the product we are
building.
Usually the watch market, there are many people who I know.
Even just in general, the consumer electronics market is
very quick.
People don't know.
The goods come from outside India.
Same to same, it is sold in India.
By putting a brand.
And we are optimizing a little bit here and there.
But no one is working on the design, the whole experience,
the software end to end.
I am feeling that way.
And I feel that watches can replace smartphones.
It has become so powerful.
Because now a lot of things are coming in that space.
So what we will take out will be expensive.
Sustainability is my requirement.
I won't tell you the price.
I have a requirement in the watch.
Put that in.
Then I will start another new startup.
I have decided on my own.
Put a glucometer in the watch.
In China, many people are doing 80-90.
Because let's talk about CJM.
You have also come to fitness.
So you have started understanding biomechanics.
So the CJM that has come nowadays.
Many companies are selling it.
It is 80-90% accurate.
So I was doing some research.
There are some watches coming in China.
It looks like a needle.
It is doing it without a needle.
It is doing it with sweat.
And it is doing it in the watch.
Many companies have made it in China.
And it is also doing OEM for others.
If it is 80-90% accurate, just imagine.
I mean, I am telling you.
If the audience will understand, then fine.
If not, then do it further.
Normally I wear a watch.
My walk is being monitored.
If I give it my data, my fat, my height, etc.
Then it might be able to monitor my calories too.
Now it is able to monitor my heart rate too.
Now if it starts monitoring my glucose level too.
Then what will happen?
As soon as I eat, it will ask me, Have you eaten anything?
Because it saw that my spike has come.
I will say yes.
Now it will ask, what have you eaten?
I will tell it a little.
Based on that, it will calculate its calories.
Now it will tell me.
It will get to know after some time.
Because AI is coming here.
It will get to know from time
How do my fat burn go to my body? When I wore CGM, I took a
one month trial.
I mean, I wore it for a month.
So I got to know that fat burns are well absorbed on my
body.
Normally it is bad for people.
But it is not so bad for me.
My body behaves well with fat burns.
Similarly, if I wear a watch, then this data will start
coming.
If someone is under stress,
Then how are fat burns affecting his body?
Just imagine how big a data set can be made.
I mean, my idea is
Because I don't want to get into hardware.
I am a marketer, a software guy.
So I don't want to get into hardware.
If someone makes it,
I mean, I have investors ready.
That we will make such a product
Which is end to end.
What is happening logically?
We are going to the doctor.
There are many types of practical apps made these days.
After that, we have shared all the data of my watch.
So he is getting to know
At what time did my glucose fluctuate?
At what time did my heart rate fluctuate?
What is my resting heart rate?
What is my walking heart rate?
Based on that, he has done my full analysis.
Now if my watch feels
That if someone's resting goes so much
And he is eating this type of food
And this is happening because of it.
So maybe his cholesterol can be high.
So by default, my app will tell me
Get a cholesterol test done.
I did it.
We filled the data.
My one more data was added to my watch.
He got one more learning.
At this much cholesterol, this person's heart rate remains
this much.
And the food is absorbed like this.
I mean, there can be a fire in this thing.
I mean, what we call smart watch revolution.
I think this can be a fitness band revolution.
If anyone is watching, tell me.
I mean, I am saying, if you want to go ahead, go ahead.
I think it is 100%.
Because I have also tried those CGN monitors.
And it is very good and useful.
Even I am very much involved in health.
That I have taken so many things in health.
Now, for example, I did a mattress by sleeping on it.
I also found that very interesting.
I mean, it is hot and cold.
There are so many things.
I am also taking a lot of supplements.
I am figuring out a lot of things.
And in the watch, I feel like The problem I am seeing
If I tell you honestly
I see this problem
This is definitely a good feature.
According to me, the basics are not being done right now.
I think the first thing should be
A standard good user interface.
And all the things that are working accurately.
So, our focus is very different right now.
Because we are not using all these features in this segment.
We will not use it in the Apple segment.
So, according to me,
The demand of the current user The price point at which we
want to go
We want to meet it very well.
And if we make a fitness product
Then I will not make it in 3 months.
I will make it in 3 years.
And I will make such a product That after wearing that band
You don't have to do anything else.
Because I don't believe in half-hearted things.
That you are getting a sensor.
Let's put it on and do it.
There were a lot of things like this.
We also made a smart ring prototype.
We figured out how it happens in smart rings.
All the watches were in smart rings.
After that, we tried different prototypes.
And I can tell you that
Like you are telling one sensor.
There are blind sensors.
There are 10 things in the market.
But I
I focus on the experience and go to work.
And according to me
If I am aiming for a category Then I have to be number one
in it.
If I am entering the Apple race
Then my goal would not be that
Apple takes this much market.
It sells for 30,000 rupees.
Takes this much market.
I take out 25,000.
Put one or two extra features in a little less feature.
I don't go from that perspective.
If I am entering a market Then I will make sure that
We make the best product in that market.
Our product should be the best in the world.
And then we sell it at a premium.
That is my philosophy.
If I can't beat Apple
Then I won't enter the Apple race.
I will enter the product in 3-4 years.
Where I have done a lot of research with health experts.
Then I will go there and eat this.
You don't even have to tell
The watch will tell you
Eat this in the morning.
You will be healthy.
So health is a priority.
I will definitely do something in health in the next few
years.
But for me
Because people have no idea.
Because what happens now
I will tell you the biggest problem.
We all are sick.
We don't know.
All the people in Delhi are sick.
Everyone has no idea that they are sick.
The thing that you can't measure
You don't know how sick you are.
You have been sick since childhood.
So you don't know that you are sick.
You don't know what being healthy is.
The thing that people can't measure
If I tell you I'll tell you a number, if you are this much
sick and you can be this much healthier, then you will
improve a lot.
So I also feel that we take health for granted, we don't
even know what is healthy.
And if you go to the side of Japan, Okinawa and all these
blue zones, there are areas all over the world, there
people live 100 years comfortably, and they don't live 100
years, they are trekking at the age of 90, they have abs at
the age of 70, naturally,
good strong physique at the age of 70, their diet and
everything is good, lifestyle diet, a lot of things are
good, so essentially you live 3 lives in one life, I see it
like that too, so I think that technology is coming, it
will come slowly but it will
be very interesting, the watch will also play a part in it,
especially wearables will play a big part in it.
I have a lot of watches, but since I bought this, I have
been wearing this only, everything gets tracked somewhere,
the phone also comes here, a lot of other things come here,
so I feel that wearable is next level thing, it excites me
a lot, and all the
best, then I have told you, this is smart questioning, now
say it like this, stop it, we will tell you in the intro.
Please cut this part, it is not good.
Thank you, I got to learn a lot personally, and I think the
audience also got to learn a lot.
100%, I also had a lot of fun talking to you, knowing
everything, even the conversation before the camera, I
found it very interesting, and I hope the things you are
doing, the users, the consumers, they also got some help,
but yes, definitely a lot of
fun.
Thank you so much for coming, thank you.
So with this, this video ends here, I hope you enjoyed it,
like it, share it, tell me in the comments, how did you
like the video, bye, good day, good night, good morning,
good afternoon, whenever you are watching this video, Jai
Hind, Vande Mataram.