Hello, friends!
The Israel-Palestine war began over a month ago,
over 10,000 lives have been lost already.
Surprisingly, amidst this tragedy,
certain entities are benefiting significantly—
American weapons manufacturers.
Since the war began, the stocks of these companies
have surged by $30 billion.
The two major defense contractors in America
Raytheon and General Dynamics
have unabashedly informed investors
that the war in Israel
would be financially advantageous.
Other arms manufacturers like
Lockheed Martin and Northrop Grumman
have experienced substantial
stock gains over the past three years.
Lockheed Martin produces
F-35 Lightning II fighter jets used by Israel,
as well as Black Hawk helicopters,
Northrop Grumman produces submarines and combat vehicles.
Israel signed a $3 billion deal in July
to buy these F-35 fighter jets.
One might wonder about the source
of Israel's substantial military budget.
An obvious answer would be
that it is Israeli taxpayers fund.
But look at this news article.
In September 2016, during President Obama's tenure,
the U.S. and Israel signed a $38 billion deal,
as per this deal, the US provides military equipment
worth $3.8 billion to Israel annually.
Consequently, a staggering 92% of Israel's imported weapons now
originate from one country.
The United States of America.
But why does this matter?
A country buying weapons from an ally
country would not seem suspicious.
But the peculiarity of this situation is that
the weapons industry doesn't care about any alliances.
The weapons industry has only one objective
earning maximum profit.
This year, in January, the U.S. State Department announced
a record-breaking $205 billion in weapon sales
to various countries worldwide
in the latest fiscal year.
Weapons worth more than $200 Billion
were sold in a year by only one country.
Marking a 49% increase from the previous year.
These weapons went to 58 different countries,
including not only Israel but also
several Arab nations such as Lebanon, Saudi Arabia,
Qatar, Kuwait, the United Arab Emirates,
Bahrain, and Iraq.
Does selling these weapons make the world a safer place?
Or unsafe?
The issue extends beyond the United States;
last year, Israel also set a record in weapon sales,
surpassing $12 billion.
This substantial figure includes sales of
drones, missiles, rockets, and air defense systems.
Notably, $3 billion or the %12 billion
that is, 24% of this total export
was to Arab countries.
Israel ranks as the 10th largest arms exporter globally,
with the top four positions occupied by
the United States, Russia, France, and China.
The United Kingdom holds the 7th position.
What distinguishes these five countries is
their status as permanent members of
the United Nations Security Council.
A striking fact is that combining their weapon sales
constitutes over 75% of global arms exports.
After this fact comes to light,
how can one expect that
the United Nations would adopt a resolution
to curtail arms exports globally?
In May of this year, Oxfam International's
Head of New York office highlighted that
four out of the five permanent
members of the UN Security Council
are the world's leading arms sellers.
These weapons fuel conflicts worldwide.
This is truly hypocritical, complicit, and immoral.
Apart from them, Germany, Italy, and South Korea
also feature among the top 10 arms exporters.
The weapons industry isn't bothered by
what's right and what's wrong,
who is an ally and who is not.
This is evident in several examples.
While many consider Russia a close friend to India,
it is also one of the top three arms exporters to Pakistan.
Between 2017 and 2021
China was the #1 weapons supplier to Pakistan,
followed by Sweden
and Russia.
Look at this report from 2021.
Russia pledged to provide more weapons to Pakistan,
despite India's discomfort.
Turning to weapon imports,
the top countries importing weapons are
on this list of Top 10 Largest Arms Importers.
India is at number one,
followed by countries like Saudi Arabia and Qatar.
However, what's interesting here is that
in positions 5th, 7th, and 10th
reveal an intriguing dynamic with
China, South Korea, and America.
This suggests a complex game
of buying and selling weapons on the global stage,
Seemingly unaffected by a country's foreign policy.
In the realm of geopolitics,
the U.S. aligns with Israel,
while Russia and China form a separate bloc,
even in the current crisis, these two sides are evident.
Russian President Putin's opinion
on the Israel-Palestine war is that
it should be seen as a failure of the U.S. policy,
Asserting that the US neglects the well-being of Palestinians.
China, too, condemns Israel's actions in Gaza,
characterizing them as "beyond self-defense".
This might create the impression of a divide,
with the U.S., Europe, and Israel on one side,
and China and Russia on the other.
However, when it comes to weapon exports,
these seemingly opposing nations
find themselves on the same side.
These countries collectively export the most weapons globally.
By now you might be thinking that
these countries are truly terrible.
That we should be protesting the countries exporting weapons worldwide.
But if you are thinking so, you are missing the point.
A nation is formed by its citizens.
Americans aren't bad.
Neither are Russians, Israelis, or Chinese citizens.
The citizens aren't actually consulted.
The major players in this deadly weapons mafia
are not everyday Americans,
Russians, Israelis, or Chinese citizens.
Ordinary people in these nations don't reap the benefits of arms sales;
instead, private weapons manufacturers are the ones raking in profits.
That's right.
Almost all of the weapons sold globally by these countries
aren't sold by the governments,
rather they're sold by private capitalists.
Look at this list.
The top 100 weapons companies.
Out of the top 100 companies,
only a handful are government-owned,
such as Israel Aerospace Industries or
Aviation Industry Corporation of China.
Disregarding these exceptions,
the majority are private entities.
Lockheed Martin, an American company, holds the top spot,
followed by Northrop Grumman in third place.
In fact, 51 of the companies on the list are American.
What does this mean?
The massive profits generated from the sale of weapons
flow into the coffers of these private companies.
Ironically, the money used to purchase these weapons often comes from
taxpayers, as governments fund these acquisitions.
Many nations procure weapons either
from private companies in their country
or, when dealing with other countries,
they engage with private entities of that country.
Hundreds of billions of dollars of taxpayers' money,
are funnelled into these companies.
These funds are then utilized to purchase weapons,
which inevitably end up being used in
conflicts that affect ordinary people.
A report by the Stockholm International
Peace Research Institute in April this year
revealed that India's military spending
stands at $81.4 billion,
ranking it fourth globally in 2022.
At the forefront of military expenditures is America
with $877 billion,
followed by China at $292 billion,
and Russia at $86.4 billion.
The top 10 list also features the UK and France,
all five permanent members of
the United Nations Security Council
are on this list too.
Why don't these 5 nations collectively decide
to cease the wasteful spending on weapons?
A united commitment to refrain from attacking one another
could be a transformative step to
halt the financial drain on military budgets.
However, the irony lies in the fact that
the primary casualties of the weapons industry
are often the American citizens.
The frequency of mass shootings in America
is alarmingly higher than any other country.
This year alone, till mid-September,
over 500 mass shootings occurred,
with a tragic impact on children,
making "School Shootings" a
distressingly common phrase in America.
In 2021-2022, more than 327 school
shootings took place in American schools.
This is a direct result of the lax regulation
surrounding gun ownership in America.
Unlike in other countries where disputes
are settled with fists and kicks.
But in America, people do not hesitate to fire guns.
Only because of the fact that the American laws
favour gun ownership.
If the sale of weapons were prohibited,
no one would be allowed to sell weapons,
then these gun shootings would stop eventually.
But how would the weapon manufacturers benefit then?
This is why dozens of children lose
their lives in America every year,
politicians are often seen shedding tears,
but the gun trade isn't affected.
Disturbingly, between 2005 and 2020,
gun sales in America tripled.
In the previous year alone, Americans
purchased a staggering 16.6 million guns.
The government can easily
change this if it wanted to.
Governments do not need to bow down to the weapons industry.
Take Australia for example,
once known for lax gun regulations,
but in April 1996, when a 28-year-old man
k!lled 35 people with a semi-automatic rifle,
"Gunman k!lls 25 people
in Australia's worst massacre."
"The situation remains tense at the
Port Arthur side."
Following this mass shooting,
Australian Prime Minister John Howard took decisive action
to address the issue of firearms.
The National Firearms Agreement
was implemented a month later.
Between October 1996 and September 1997,
the government seized over 650,000 privately owned guns.
The gun owners were given monetary compensation
to surrender their firearms to the government.
People who had guns illegally weren't compensated,
but legal amnesty was provided to them,
they didn't face prosecution for
voluntarily turning in their illegal weapons.
As a result, today, in Australia,
such mass shootings are rarely seen, if ever.
Something similar happened in Serbia earlier this year.
Following two shootings in May
resulting in 17 d3aths, including children,
the government declared a one-month amnesty period
for citizens to surrender their unregistered weapons.
"Recent mass shootings which left 17 people d3ad
and 21 wounded,
have sparked public outrage.
Authorities have also declared
a one-month amnesty period
for citizens to handover unregistered weapons,
or face prison sentences."
Over 13,500 weapons were
voluntarily surrendered within a week.
Later, this date was extended,
and within 2 months, more than 100,000 illegal weapons
were handed over to the government.
It shows that with political will, governments can
effectively control the weapons and mitigate violence.
For those interested in delving deeper into American history,
there's an audiobook available on Kuku FM
about the American Civil War,
Kuku FM is abrilliant audio-learning platform,
with a diverse array of audiobooks
on almost every topic.
In the history and geopolitics genre,
there are several audiobooks.
Such as on the creation of Israel,
or the Israel-Palestine war
and the Russia-Ukraine war.
There are audiobooks on these topics.
Listeners can enjoy these audiobooks
when they prefer to rest their eyes.
For those new to KUKU FM,
a special 50% discount coupon is available in the description,
along with links to the mentioned audiobooks.
And now let's get back to our topic.
In certain regions, the influence of the weapons
mafia has expanded beyond arms sales.
Private companies are not only profiting from selling weapons
but have ventured into providing private armies,
commonly known as Mercenaries.
During the Russia-Ukraine war,
the Wagner group gained attention
for attempting to overthrow Putin from the government.
Considered by Putin as an anti-national force,
the group was subsequently disbanded.
But do you know how did this group form?
The Wagner group originated in Russia,
Putin had said that this group
received funding from the state budget,
a fact that was initially denied for years.
Putin eventually admitted to allocating
$1 billion to the group in a year.
Dmitry Kiselyov, the head of the state-
controlled Russian media group,
stated that the Wagner group was provided
a total of $9.8 billion by the Russian government.
Remarkably, taxpayer money was
used to finance private armies.
The logical question arises:
Why didn't Russia use its army?
Why opt to hire private mercenary groups?
The primary motivation behind this decision
is cost-effectiveness.
In a wartime scenario,
providing funds to a private company
allows the company's private army to
fight the war on behalf of the country.
Deploying the national army is very bothersome.
In the form of various financial obligations,
such as pension payments,
army officers' salaries, health insurance,
and compensations for families of martyrs.
Choosing to hire contract fighters is better because
once the country makes a payment to the company,
the company bears all other responsibilities.
Even if a mercenary of the private army d!es fighting,
they aren't included in the official casualty counts.
While headlines may report the number of
Russian or Ukrainian soldiers k!lled,
a third category exists,
private army soldiers fighting
who were neither Russian nor Ukrainian,
but were fighting on behalf of Russia.
Their d3aths may not garner
significant attention or discussion.
You might be wondering who would want to fight
as a part of a private company's armies.
Friends, mercenaries often hail from
economically disadvantaged countries,
driven by financial constraints and limited job opportunities,
they often join the army of these private companies.
These private armies are not only
contracted by governments
but also by private companies and warlords.
The Wagner Group, for instance,
engaged in conflicts beyond Ukraine,
including countries like Syria, Sudan Mozambique,
Mali, Burkina Faso, and Libya.
In these impoverished nations, they are
frequently employed in mining contracts.
The private mining companies that make money
by selling the resources of these poor nations,
hire these private armies so that
they could quell local protests,
Companies by Yevgeny Prigozhin mined for gold,
uranium, and diamonds, particularly in
countries such as Sudan, Mali, Libya,
and the Central African Republic.
These private armies k!lled hundreds of innocent civilians,
looting houses, harassing activists,
and even k!lling journalists.
The Wagner Group is not the only private military company.
Russia has also employed other private military companies.
Like POTOK, Don Brigade, Moran Security Group,
and Slavonic Corps, ENOT Corp, to name a few.
Russia isn't the only one to do so.
For instance, Yair Klein, a former Lieutenant Colonel in the Israeli Army,
established Spearhead Limited, a mercenary group
that supplied weapons, trained d3ath squads,
in right-wing paramilitary groups in Colombia.
Additionally, organized militias for
drug traffickers like Pablo Escobar.
Despite the Colombian government seeking to arrest him,
Klein, just like other wealthy individuals,
managed to evade legal consequences.
Israel is renowned for its cyber mercenaries
who engage in cybercrimes for money,
including hacking, forging blackmail material, disinformation spreading,
planting false intelligence, and surveillance.
Team George, an Israeli cyber mercenary group,
interfered in 33 presidential campaigns,
successfully influencing 27.
Facebook exposed and banned 7 cyber
mercenary companies in December 2021,
These companies had targetted almost 50,000 people worldwide.
Four of these were Israeli cyber-mercenaries,
like Black Cube and Cobwebs.
Apart from this, you would have heard of Pegasus,
an infamous spyware sold to governments worldwide,
this was being sold by an Israeli private company.
An Israeli private cyber mercenary group
called the NSO Group.
Talking about America,
between 1994 and 2007,
approximately $300 billion was spent on 12 private militias.
One of these private military company is Blackwater,
founded by former US Navy officer Eric Prince.
Blackwater hires fighters from various countries,
including the Philippines, Bosnia, Israel, and Chile,
selling its private services for money.
In September 2007,
Blackwater gained notoriety when its mercenaries
k!lled 17 innocent Iraqi civilians.
Although four individuals were initially being prosecuted,
they were pardoned in 2020
during Donald Trump's presidency.
Blackwater's involvement has contributed to
the escalation of numerous wars worldwide.
In December 2021, a United Nations report
accused Eric Prince of
violating the weapons ban in Libya.
The ongoing conflict in Libya,
is now characterized as a private war.
Look at this news article stating that
Blackwater was hired by the Obama government
to provide security in Afghanistan in 2010,
at a cost of $220 million,
public tax money was handed over
to these private armies.
Fast forward to 2021 when the Taliban
regained control of Afghanistan;
reports from the Wall Street Journal revealed that
Eric Prince was charging $6,500 per person
to facilitate safe evacuations from
Afghanistan on charter flights.
During the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina in America,
Blackwater secured a $73 million contract
to assist the FEMA staff during the
Katrina-aftermath recovery operation,
Not only this, Eric Prince has also made
significant political donations to Republican politicians.
This intertwining of financial contributions and business transactions
works quite well here.
The only difference is that
not only are the super-rich businessmen corrupt,
but they're dealing in weapons transactions,
k!lling people all over the world.
Eric Prince handed donations to politicians
and the politicians handed his company,
Blackwater, contracts worth $800 million.
In Iraq, over 160,000 Blackwater employees
served as guards for U.S. officials.
An internal report from Blackwater disclosed that,
among 195 shooting incidents in the last two years,
the company's employees shot the first bullet in 160 instances.
It's also quite common
for politicians to invest in stocks
of these private contractor companies,
thereby becoming direct shareholders.
This goes beyond a mere bribery situation.
Any benefit made by the company
would directly benefit the politician.
George Bush was the US President during the Iraq invasion,
his father was a Board member of the Carlyle Group.
This same group was awarded numerous defense contracts,
through companies like Vought and United Defense.
Furthermore, the then U.S. Vice President Dick Cheney,
used to be the head of the company Halliburton,
which received a $7 billion defense contract
without any competitive bidding.
The same company was awarded
contracts to restore the oil sector in Iraq.
Now, many people allege
that the real reason behind the Iraq war was
Iraq's oil.
Oil companies like Halliburton,
Exxon Mobil, Chevron, BP, and Shell
established themselves in Iraq.
As of December 2021,
there are at least 15 influential politicians in America
actively shaping U.S. defense policy,
who have personal investments in these military contractors.
They are directing U.S. military policy
while profiting from these arms-selling
companies by holding their stocks.
Can there be a more drastic conflict of interest?
By now, two key points should be clear:
First, in wars like the Israel-Palestine situation,
the weapons industry reaps significant benefits.
Second, politicians benefit off of it too
since they are personally invested in it.
especially those who have investments
in these weapon manufacturing companies.
Adding to this, the third point emerges:
politicians often derive political benefits from wars.
As poet Rahat Indori noted,
[Are tensions erupting on the borders?
Find out if its time for elections.]
When politicians have to answer for
issues like corruption and unemployment,
they can use wars to divert public attention.
Especially for dictators,
war serves as an effective distraction.
George Orwell's novel "1984" emphasizes the idea that
war should perpetually go on,
not necessarily to win,
but to continue fighting it
to maintain and consolidate power.
Think about it for yourself.
India refrains from attacking other nations,
that's a matter of national pride.
In India, the military expenditures are
primarily directed towards self-defense,
especially against neighbouring countries like Pakistan and China,
However, when analyzing China's behavior,
questions arise: Why does China
keep on encroaching on our borders?
Does a farmer in Shanghai benefit from the Chinese intrusion?
Or some school teacher in Beijing?
No.
This muscle-flexing and chest-thumping
mainly serves leaders like Xi Jinping,
helping them consolidate and sustain power.
In foreign policy, such politicians are labelled "hawkish",
while those advocating for peace are termed "doves".
Hawkish politicians often use
public tax money to fortify their positions,
In reality, during wars,
it's the common people who end up fighting each other,
not the politicians themselves.
An example from 2014 highlights this:
Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's son
had started his mandatory three-year army service.
However, this turned out to be fake news,
misleading the public into thinking his son
was directly involved in the conflict.
Critics have rightfully condemned
him for sending his son to
enjoy life at some American beach,
while sending ordinary citizens to fight.
These issues should prompt the media to
raise their voices and provide critical coverage.
Unfortunately, in many countries,
the media is often so corrupt
that it looks to benefit from wars,
eagerly chasing the prospect of increased
TRP by talking about the latest conflict.
Especially those TV channels
aligned with government's interest,
they find it convenient
to neglect the day-to-day issues faced by the common people
and focus solely on war-related news.
This highlights a stark truth about
the world's weapons industry:
an industry whose existence would be jeopardized
if global wars were to cease.
Perhaps this is why it is beneficial
to continue wars to ensure the continuous flow of money.
If you found this video informative,
you may also appreciate our video on World War I,
a conflict that occurred a century ago,
where common people were sacrificed
to save the interests of kings.
Click here to watch
the complete story of World War I.
Thank you very much!