- [Jimmy] As you guys know,
I like to give away money,
but in this video, we're gonna
do it a little different.
I'm gonna give people a choice.
Would you rather have
this $10,000 in cash,
or this key that goes
to something expensive?
(key slamming)
You have 10 seconds to decide.
- 10, nine, eight, seven, six, five-
(Javier groaning)
- Which is it?
(timer ticking)
Ten grand, or-
- Four, three, two-
- The key, the key, the key,
the key, the key, the key.
- Okay.
(team clapping)
- Yeah. We hate money! Woo!
- You just turned down $10,000.
You don't know what this
key goes to. (laughing)
- Okay. I'm not really sure
if I should have took the key,
but my gut feeling says
like, you gotta take the key.
So I gotta go with my
gut. Gotta go with my gut.
(team chanting)
- Guts. Guts. Guts. Guts!
(Javier laughing)
(team chanting)
- Key. Key. Key. Key.
- All right. So.
(upbeat music playing)
Right around this corner over here,
you'll see what this key goes to.
- Okay.
- Cover his eyes.
- Hold on, hold on.
- All right. Face that way.
- Javier.
Take your hat off.
(team clapping)
- No way!
- You just-
- A brand new car!
Guess how much it's worth.
- More than 10 grand?
- It's worth $26,000.
(cash register dinging)
- Woo!
(team cheering)
- Let's go.
- You wanna get a shot?
- Yeah.
(team chanting)
- Javier. Javier.
- Where you wanna go, boys?
- Hey, guess what?
You win something else.
- What is it?
- I'll give you your wallet back.
- My wallet?
- Javier, you took the risk.
You got the W, what do you wanna say?
- Listen to your gut.
I had a good feeling.
- Gut gang.
- Congratulations on your $26,000 car.
Throughout this video, we're
giving away many more cars
and hundreds of thousands of dollars.
This is just the beginning.
Next scene.
This next giveaway is two diamonds.
One of these diamonds is worth $25.
And one of these diamonds is worth 6,000.
Go ahead. You can touch
'em, do whatever you want.
One is worth $6,000, and
one is worth only 25.
- Okay. I have no clue, but
because I'm standing right here,
I'm gonna pick this one.
- I'm stressed.
So can you tell any difference
between the two diamonds?
- This one looks faker.
- What does that mean?
- It looks plastic. My
hands are like this.
- Why is this hand twitching
so much more than that?
- Because I feel like-
- That one's heavier.
That means that's the diamond.
- It's this one.
- So your choice is this diamond.
- It's my diamond.
- Yes.
- Oh gosh.
It's the fake one.
(box clicking)
- No way.
(buzzer sounding)
- The most important thing you
got out of this, friendship.
- Until you leave, then it's over.
(contestant laughing)
- For our next giveaway,
I want you to flip this.
This side says $0 and this
side says a thousand dollars.
Give it a flip.
- Woo!
- We want-
- Yeah, big money!
(team cheering)
(cash register dinging)
- Okay, hold up.
Now you can keep that thousand dollars,
or you can risk it to flip this.
This side is $0, and this side is $10,000.
(participant clapping)
- For sure.
- I want it at least above your head.
- All right.
- All right. And...
(cardboard clattering)
(team cheering)
(cash register dinging)
- Wait. What?
- Stay right here.
Do not move. Taylor, don't let him move.
- Dude. What was going
through your mind? $10,000.
- I didn't wait this whole time
for a thousand dollars.
(Taylor clapping)
- That's what I'm talking bout!
- I'm going big, or I'm going home!
- Once in a life time opportunity here!
- All right!
- Oh.
- You can risk your $10,000
for a chance at $20,000.
But this side still says zero.
(team chanting)
- Do it, do it, do it.
(Jimmy clapping)
- I am.
(cardboard clattering)
(team cheering)
- He did it!
- $20,000.
I'll be right back.
(team laughing)
- I don't know, man.
I don't know if I wanna keep going.
- There's no way he goes for this.
- [Person Offscreen] No way.
- [Jimmy] I think you're
crazy if you do this,
but $40,000 or zero.
- I'm gonna call my girlfriend
and I'm gonna FaceTime her.
- Babe.
- Hey babe.
- Your man just won $20,000. No joke.
- No!
- If it lands on this side, it's $0,
it lands on this side, it's 40,000,
or he could just walk away with 20 grand.
- Babe, 20 grand's a lot...
- I don't know, man.
I'm gonna be honest.
I came here to win.
- Ooh.
- And I felt I've done that.
(disappointed audience track)
- Oh yeah. I thought he was gonna say,
"I came here to win, so let's do it."
- I'm gonna settle for the 20.
(cash register dinging)
- I am curious if you would have won.
- Man, don't do that to me.
(upbeat music playing)
- Come on.
- You gotta see.
(Jimmy clapping)
- Come on.
- Are we listening to Taylor?
(cardboard clattering)
(team cheering)
(buzzer sounding)
- Listen to me.
- Our next bit is gonna
be an interesting one.
So this is Anna and as high as she counts,
I'll give her money. So just count to ten.
- One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
- So no joke. You can
count as high as you want.
And every single number you count,
I will give you a dollar at the end of it.
- Okay.
- The only stipulation
is, if you skip a number,
you go back to zero.
- Okay.
- Go ahead and start.
- One, two, three, four, five-
- Have fun counting.
- 87, 88.
- Steele, do not let her skip a number.
- 91 92 93- 104, 105,
113, 114, 128, 129, 130-
- [Jimmy] 140, 143, 144, 145,
- 131
- Works every time.
- Start over.
(Anna screaming)
- Next up is Juliana.
You can take $2,000 in cash,
or shoot a free throw for $10,000.
- Make.
- Make a free throw for $10,000.
It should go in the hoop.
- I'm gonna shoot a basketball.
- Wait really?
- She's puttin' her hair up!
(Taylor clapping)
- Okay.
I'm a little nervous. This is $10,000.
- Shh. I'm thinking.
- Okay.
(team conversing)
Chandler, stop talking.
(ball bouncing)
- Come on. Here we go. First time-
(electronic chord playing)
- Woo!
(team cheering)
(Juliana screaming)
- Yay! Yeah!
(team cheering)
(palms slapping)
- She stepped it up. She
knew what she had to do.
- I told you, I played before.
- Here you go. Plop that cash in here.
This is now your briefcase full of money.
Guys, is this for real?
- Congratulations on your money.
Chandler, let's do something fun.
Do you wanna bet $10,000 that you make it?
If you make this free throw,
I'll give you 10 grand.
But if you miss, you give me 10 grand,
which I'll donate to charity.
You don't have to do it.
- I want to, but I'm very
nervous that I'm gonna miss.
(Juliana laughing)
(ball bouncing)
- It's just a car. Rent for a year.
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
(buzzer sounding)
(team exclaiming)
Wow, I love how he almost
threw the ball at Chris,
like Chris did something.
(team exclaiming in slow motion)
(ball bouncing)
(Jimmy laughing)
- This ain't fair.
I got this new ring on
and it messed me up.
- Why don't you go hug him.
- Ryan, we need huggies.
- None of y'all are my friends.
None of y'all talked me out of it.
- I wanted to, but I'm so
confident in your skills.
- It's gonna be okay.
- Just think about charity.
I've always wondered if
I dropped tons of money,
how much could you catch? Let's find out.
And...
(crane whining)
Right here.
Okay.
We have Tim down there in the circle,
and we have tons of money.
Let's do a little sprinkle.
Sprinkage.
All right, Chandler, join us.
Whatever you catch, you
can keep, by the way.
(Tim grunting)
Oh, does this feel
condescending to anyone else?
(Chandler cheering)
What if we throw it at him?
- Hey!
- Hey, I'm ready.
- Let's go, boys.
(cash fluttering)
(team laughing)
Chandler, hit it off the ceiling.
- No!
- The money is literally
stuck in the ceiling.
- Yo, we gotta get it down.
- Are you guys curious? What
the girls counting are up to?
- Yeah, actually.
- 6784, 6785, 6786.
- Wow. I can't believe they're that high.
We're high as well.
- We should go down.
- Just get us to a point where
if we fell, we wouldn't die.
How much money did you catch?
- $1,929.
(cash register dinging)
- And according to Google,
that's when the Great
Depression hit. Yeah!
- Woo!
(palms slapping)
- Up next is Noah.
Now I want you to pick,
hat, shirt, or umbrella.
- Hat.
- He was very confident in that.
(team cheering)
(Chandler clapping)
- Let's go!
- Okay. And now we go up again.
Are you ready?
We ready for what?
- There's $8,071 in this box.
Whatever you catch, you can keep.
I'm literally about to
dump a ton of money.
It would've been 10 grand,
but the other guy took,
it was like-
- 1929.
- Oh yeah. The Great Depression.
Here we go.
- Ready...
(cash thudding)
- Oh!
- Oh, oh no.
- Oh, you're dropping it.
- I'm holding too hard.
- Okay.
We're dropping more.
- What?
- Just scurry away.
- Oh, god...
- Scurry.
- [Person Offscreen] What are you gonna do
with this money, man?
- I'm gonna see if he'll let
me buy his Tesla with it.
- Ain't no rainy days here.
- You really couldn't have told me
I was not making a good
choice when I chose the hat?
- You chose the hat so
quickly. I didn't even-
- Oh my God.
- Are you counting?
- Somehow Noah caught $1,920,
(cash register dinging)
exactly $9 less than the other guy.
- Now I do need to ask you though,
would you be willing to
take $1,900 for your Tesla?
- How about if you beat
a different challenge?
I might consider it.
- Okay.
- So gimme a second.
- I don't, I didn't know that
I could just challenge Jimmy
for his Tesla.
(palms clapping)
(both laughing)
There's no way I'll win
to Tesla here. Right?
- I have 10 cups and I'm
gonna grab a cheese ball.
If he guesses the cup with a cheese ball,
he can have a Tesla.
In this ZHC video, ZHC gave
me a customized MrBeast Tesla.
But at the end of the video,
I had Chris and Chandler play
rock paper scissors for it.
- I won.
- And Chris won.
Chandler. You sad about that?
If he wins, can I just
buy you a new Tesla?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Perfect.
(Jimmy clapping)
Noah, come on over.
There's 10 cups here.
One has a cheese ball
under it. If you pick it,
I will give you Chris's Tesla.
(Noah sighing)
All right, fine. It's not this one.
There.
- Okay.
(Jimmy thumping table)
- Now you have
a one in nine chance.
I'm not doing that again.
I'm gonna go over here.
- By the way. If you win it,
you have to clean it out.
There's a lot of trash in the back.
- You gonna pick?
- Oh.
(electronic chord playing)
- Oh!
- (laughing) Wait!
- No way!
(Noah cheering)
- Did he actually get it?
- I've given away my car, I guess!
- So I really randomly won?
- There is only one.
(cups clattering)
- Oh my God.
- How did you do that?
- That's crazy!
(Chris laughing)
- On the bright side, you get $1,900.
- Oh no. You get to keep your $1,900.
- I get to keep the money too?
- Yeah, you can keep it.
(Noah and Jimmy laughing)
(Noah clapping)
- One in nine?
- Got the Tesla for you.
- And it comes with all his clothes.
I cannot believe I just won a Tesla.
- You wanna get in your new car?
- Oh, absolutely.
- Hey Chris, do you mind
unlocking it for him?
- Oh, it's unlocked already.
- Oh my God. Let's go!
A Tesla's my dream car, too.
- Same.
- Now, your friend
literally only got $1,900,
and you walked away with a $50,000 car.
- He's the reason I was
invited here today, too.
So thank you, Tim.
- I'm sorry.
- I kind of want my new Tesla to be black.
- Huddle up. Huddle up. Huddle up.
Okay. Now that Chris
no longer owns a Tesla,
Let's go back to filming.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- All right.
- For this next bit, we're
giving away another car.
This is Cameron.
He was in this video.
(video popping)
But you're back,
(Jimmy clapping)
and you can win money this time.
- Woo.
- Listen to this sound.
(engine revving)
Sounds like a car. And
listen to sound number two.
(engine revving)
Also sounds like a car,
but here's the thing.
Only one of those sounds is an actual car,
and the other is fake.
If you guess which one's
real, you get a car.
- One more time.
(engine revving)
- Ooh. You can hear that shifting in that.
Sounds like a fart first.
(all laughing)
I don't know,
I really like the shifting
that I can hear from this one.
So I'm gonna go with number one for sure.
- I'm going to show you where
we got audio clip number one.
- Okay.
- Karl, come here.
- All right.
So I want you to show them.
I hate stuff like this.
- That was, oh my gosh.
No way.
- This is what you picked.
This right here.
(Cameron laughing)
I'm gonna show you what
you could have got.
- Oh no.
- This is what you could have had.
- Wow.
- Oh come on, jump up in that.
(all laughing)
- Karl!
You guys might be able to tell by now,
I don't handle people losing well.
Take over Karl.
(Karl laughing)
- Oh no. Look your car's coming.
- No!
- Drive by!
- [Cameron] No, I don't like that car.
(trombone buzzing)
- Bye Cameron. Good luck.
- No.
- Good luck with your trumpet.
- We got more to film.
- You know what they say?
Third times the charm.
I'm giving you a chance to
remake the $10,000 you lost,
again again,
and before he shoots this
free throw for $5,000,
let's go check on the girls counting.
They're probably close to $10,000.
- 9177.
- Wow.
- 9178.
- All right. So you're
getting close to 10,000.
(Anna cheering)
- Wow.
- Sheets of-
- I know, it looks like
someone's having a manic episode.
- Wait. What was I? 91-
- 43, 82, 71-
- 94-
- Six, three, eight, 99,504.
(girls chanting numbers)
- Hey Chandler. So they're at
a really, really high number.
Honestly. I'm kind of
surprised, but anyways,
you wanna shoot this free throw?
- Yeah.
(upbeat music playing)
(bell dinging)
Yes!
(cash register dinging)
- Okay.
- Yes!
- If you make this three
pointer, you get $10,000.
(ball bouncing)
(bell dinging)
(all cheering)
- Yes, yes! Yes, yes.
- You have now won 10 grand,
which makes up for the
10 grand you lost here.
Play the clip.
- Oh.
- Yes, yes.
- No, the clip of him losing 10 grand.
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
- Oh!
(all exclaiming)
Do you wanna risk your $10,000 for 20,000?
I know you do. Come on.
- [Chris] Yeah. Hoo! Hoo!
Hold up. We're grabbing a car.
(trombone buzzing)
Thank you.
(basket rattling)
(bell dinging)
(all cheering)
- Let's go!
(Chandler clapping)
- He made it.
- Gimme this thing.
- (Jimmy) Let me take this.
You just won $20,000,
(Chandler clapping)
which technically is 10,000,
'cause you owe me 10,000.
Ball me.
That's a trombone.
(trombone clattering)
If you stand behind this line,
which is really far away,
show the viewers.
- It's almost-
- 50 grand.
(ball bouncing)
- You think I can make this?
- No. (claps)
- Honestly.
Everyone's really quiet.
- Go broke or go home.
- It's more than broke.
If he misses this, he
still owes me 10 grand.
Play the clip.
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
- Oh!
(all exclaiming)
- It is a good clip.
Let's watch it one more time.
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
- Oh!
(all exclaiming)
Play it a hundred times on
the screen at the same time.
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
- Oh!
(all exclaiming)
- Tyler?
- Yes.
- Do you think it's dumb
for him to risk $20,000
for this shot?
- Absolutely not, because
it's not my money.
(Chandler slapping ball)
So let's do it.
(ball bouncing)
- Chandler! Chandler!
- Yeah!
(team chanting)
- Chandler! Chandler!
- Oh, that's off.
(buzzer sounding)
(Chandler groaning)
- I want to die.
- Buddy.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I need to just stop putting
you in these predicaments.
- Yeah.
(playful music playing)
- I'm just gonna start
just giving you money,
so you can't lose it.
- That would be great.
- (laughing) Okay.
- 11,150, 11,151, 11,152, 11-
- We can't just let 'em count forever.
Let's give 'em a time limit.
- Jimmy. If you keep letting
them count too much longer,
it's gonna cost you an arm and a leg.
(trombone buzzing sadly)
- We have some news we have to break.
You have one hour starting now. Okay.
And then we're gonna come back up,
and give you whatever you're at.
- Okay.
- All right.
- And you also have to restart?
- No.
(all laughing)
- Oh my God.
- From 11,248, 11,249.
- Good luck.
- Have fun.
- 11,251, 11,252-
- I hope you make a lot of money.
- Thank you. 11-
- Three six five eight nine 10.
(Anna screaming)
So here's how it works, Troy.
If you guess the cup with
the car key, you win the car.
- Oh.
- You got this.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Karl, I'd like you to escort Troy
where he can't see the cups,
and use this if he gets
a little aggressive.
- Right this way.
(upbeat music playing)
We're gonna teach your swing. Okay?
- Okay.
- Perfect. Just like that.
All right.
- All right. So we're gonna take this.
(key clattering)
Okay. We're gonna take this.
(cups clattering)
- Looks a little wobbly.
- Keep looking in that direction
and not that direction.
- Troy. Come see if you win a car.
- Okay.
- There's eight cups here.
Two have car keys.
I'm gonna go under here.
- Gosh. You're smart, Jimmy.
- Hover over the cup you
think has a car key in it.
- Don't touch it.
25% chance.
- This one.
- That?
- Yes.
- All right. You wanna lift it up?
- Oh, oh-
(all cheering)
- Let's go. Let's go!
(Troy screaming)
- Let's take him out outside
and show him his brand new car.
Tada!
- Woo!
(all cheering)
Come on!
- Look at that, man!
- [Karl] Watch out.
- Karl, no.
- Oh. (laughing)
- All right. Hop on in.
- I'm feeling really
good. I won a car, dude.
We good.
- Watching Troy win a car
kind of made me feel bad
for you losing 10 grand.
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
- Oh!
(all exclaiming)
- But you did have this
chance here to win it back.
- Oh, that's off.
(ball bouncing)
- Yeah. I didn't.
- Zach, come here.
We're going to let your
brother try to redeem you
and win your 10 grand back.
- Oh my gosh.
- You pick, red balloon or white balloon?
- White.
- Pop a white.
- Go for like the four right
there. You see the four?
- Oh, that's a good idea.
(balloon popping)
- Yes!
(cash register dinging)
- Okay.
Step back.
This is for five grand. Pop a red.
- Oh, red?
- Karl, you can just stand over there.
(Karl laughing)
- Go for the four right there.
- That one, or that one?
- That one.
- Oh. Okay. Wait.
(balloon popping)
(cash register dinging)
- Yeah. Let's go!
- Okay.
- I'm halfway out of the hole.
- Take a step back.
This one is for $10,000.
Chandley you might wanna hype him up.
- Come on, Zach. You got this.
There's four right here.
Just like we've been doing.
- And don't forget. None of
this money's going to you.
It's for him.
- Yeah. You got this.
- That's awesome.
- All right. Pop a red balloon.
I'm nervous.
- I am too.
(balloon popping)
(cash register dinging)
- Yes, yes.
- Let's go.
(palm slapping)
- Okay. Now Chandler,
you are now outta debt.
You lost 10 grand here,
(Jimmy gasping)
(basket rattling)
- Oh!
(all exclaiming)
and he just won 10 grand back.
But!
(balloon popping)
He can risk it for 20 grand.
- No.
- Jimmy, I'm going for it. Come on.
- Really?
This is for up 10 grand.
We're good right now.
- We're going for it.
- All right. (laughing)
Chandler, you might be at 10.
- Okay.
(balloon popping)
(Zach cheering)
(cash register dinging)
- We're rich!
- Well, Chandler got money.
- Wait.
- You were playing for Chandler.
- You got money.
- Chandler got money.
- Yeah.
- Let's do 30,000.
- Oh my gosh.
- We're not doing it anymore.
I'm good. (claps)
- I'm going.
- He's going for it. If you
hit this, you boys get $30,000.
But if you miss-
(dart thudding)
- Freak!
(buzzer sounding)
- You're an idiot.
- Oh shit.
(maudlin piano music playing)
- You're an idiot, Zach.
(hat thudding)
- We've got cheese balls, though.
Oh wait-
(balloon bouncing)
we-
- Bro, it's not that hard.
(balloon popping)
It's not that hard, man.
- At least you two are still
brothers hug it up, hug it up.
We have each other.
- But not 10 grand.
- I'm handsome.
(buzzer sounding)
- The girls' timer just
hit zero formation, boys.
(chanting grunts)
- [Karl] Could you imagine
hearing this coming towards you?
- We should probably stop it.
They might be weirded out.
- 14,439.
- Stop your counting.
What is your final number?
- 14,439.
- You just made $14,439.
(cash register dinging)
- Yay.
(all cheering)
- What are you gonna buy with it?
- I'm gonna pay my student loans off.
- Yes. Student loans!
(all cheering)
- Come on over here. This is $14,000.
(cash register dinging)
(girls screaming)
339 bucks.
That's loud. They're screaming very loud.
(girls screaming)
I've seen people less excited-
- Oh my god!
- to win a hundred grand on the show.
All right, there you go.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah. They're kind of heavy.
And you got this briefcase.
Here, you forgot a little bit of money.
(girls screaming)
I'm doing another one
of these in the future,
and I'm inviting random
subscribers to come compete.
So hit that subscribe button
because you could be invited
to our next, "Would you rather?" Series.
You could flip a coin for 20 grand,
steal Chris's Tesla,
catch raining money.
All you have to do is subscribe.
(explosion booming)
♪ MrBeast 6,000 ♪
(girls screaming)
(explosion booming)