Gaurav Chaudhary, of course you’ve heard the name, right?
Never heard of it?
You definitely would have heard of Technical Guruji.
Everyone knows Technical Guruji but technically, you don’t know anything about Gaurav Chaudhary.
I’m an extremely interesting person, so let’s review some of my interests today?
Right here, in my Discover feed on the Google app, I get everything I’m interested in. Pretty cool, right?
So let’s begin!
How to make a career in rafting?
Should I rather become a rafting guruji?
Just kidding! This is just an amusing interest that I have.
Oh! What’s this? Instead of people driving cars, cars will drive themselves
I’m definitely going to share this with my engineer friends!
So,  let’s see how interesting you and your feed are?