[Car engine starts]
Come inside.
[Glass shattering]
[Vansh] I could've never
imagined the day
when we would've had to deal
with the police to save our homes.
I thought only the slum dwellers
have to deal with such problems.
The government only
razes their homes.
We are decent people.
We vote, pay taxes.
Ration Card, Aadhar Card,
you name it we have it.
This can never happen to us.
Well, guess what.
It's happening with us.
Soon our homes will be razed to the
ground, while we watch helplessly.
When the government decides
to screw with you
then your consent
doesn't really matter.
You will be f****d, and how.
[Shouting]
[Vansh] I can never forget
the Summer of 2011.
That year, after my class
12 board exams I got a job.
And, when I had
saved enough money
I went to America on
my first backpacking trip.
America.
When I got there,
I understood what life really is.
[Door opens]
Vansh, didn't you sleep at all?
Now get ready soon, we've to go.
[Vansh]
After I returned I realized...
- [Yawning]
- ...how shitty life is in India.
Out here, we middle-class people
keep rubbing, grinding, boiling.
#lifesucks
- [Vansh] Morning.
- You're awake.
No, I am sleepwalking.
Don't walk while shitting.
Vansh, get me the iron
and the ironing board, son.
Yes, Grandpa.
Happy birthday, Papa.
- Bless you, dear.
- Bless me.
Happy birthday, Grandpa.
How many years has it been?
Still 18 years short of a century.
- [Vansh] You're joking.
- Did you add sugar?
If you want to complete a century,
then no sugar.
[Grandpa] Forget it.
[Man] Are you going
to the court today?
The government has declared my
birthday as a national holiday yet.
[Both chuckling]
Let's go, Vansh. We're
getting late. Come on, hurry up.
[Softly] Himansh, Papa's gift.
I'll arrange it by evening.
[Door slams]
Call the carpenter.
It just needs oil,
I'll do it myself.
[Door closes]
[Vansh] Out here you got
to fight for everything.
Like mom...
In order to save
a couple of hundred rupees
she travels daily one hour
to the wholesale market.'
So mister,
how old are your vegetables today?
These tomatoes are
from the British Rule.
2 kilos of potatoes,
2 kilos of tomatoes.
[Vansh] I don't want to live
like this. I want to go to America.
That's where the future is.
What opportunity does
anyone have out here?
[Vansh] Mom, did you talk to papa?
For your Washington University?
- Washington School of Business.
- Yeah, I know.
- And?
- Papa will break his FDs.
And next month my PPF
is maturing as well.
We'll manage, you chill out.
Chill out and all, huh.
If my son's going to America,
even I'll have an accent.
Good morning, Uncle.
[Vansh] If my father had
a business out here
then even I would've
done something.
But my dear papa blew it.
Walk faster. Faster...
[Both chuckling]
[Vansh] He had a well-settled
travel business.
But five years ago
it crashed because of some
turbulence in his mind.
What a loser.
Bro, there are a couple
more on the fifth floor.
Sharpen it properly.
Okay.
[Door opens]
[Vansh] So after
the business closed down
papa took up a job
in order to run the house.
Mom started her own
lunch-box business
and I am getting out of here
to make my life.
Go and sleep.
[Vansh] Goodnight.
I'll do a management program in
America and then settle down there.
In short, MCMC...
Every man for himself.
[Cooker hissing]
- Ganesh, the vegetables are done.
- Yes.
Why do you sound so low today?
- Focus, and do it properly.
- [Woman] Yes.
Lord!
[Cell phone ringing]
Yeah.
I am searching online
for a gift for papa.
You won't get any lunch today.
Did you drop the lunchbox again?
[Woman] Sorry...
Don't worry. I'll order
some lunch from Radhakrishna.
Listen, I am thinking of wearing
the yellow dress in the evening.
Wear the red one which
you wore at Amit's son's wedding.
You were looking nice.
I've already posted two pictures
in that dress on Facebook.
Sister-in-law will think that
I don't have any other clothes.
Okay, fine. Wear the yellow one.
You look nice in every color.
Did you talk to Hina?
I WhatsApped her.
They will come directly
to the hotel, don't worry.
Okay, bye.
- Tell me something.
- Yes, sir.
What's the difference
between these two phones?
Sir, this one has a face scanner.
And this one has a finger scanner.
This phone with the face scanner
is worth 100,000, isn't it?
Yes.
Papa will get confused.
I want something
that's user-friendly
and nothing complicated.
This one with the
finger scanner is better.
Yes, sir.
Should I order it for you?
Buying stuff online is very dicey.
Sometimes they send
a bar of soap in the mobile box.
- Mr. Sethi.
- Yes.
- The boss is calling you.
- Okay.
And, father's birthday is today.
- I will buy it at the mall.
- Yes, sir.
Did you read
Thapar family's complaint?
"Travelon ruined
our trip to Georgia.
What was supposed
to be a family vacation
turned out to be a trip
to hell and back."
Georgia immigration deported
them from Tbilisi airport
but, our travel agency
is not at fault here.
Why were they deported?
Their e-visa was rejected.
Why did you get them
an e-visa in the first place?
You could've double-checked
before the departure.
I could've never imagined that
immigration would reject
our government's e-visa.
Pretty unexpected things
are happening these days.
Mr. Sethi, our job is
to expect the unexpected.
So that our client's
vacation is not ruined.
Who could've imagined...
It doesn't matter
who is right or wrong.
But the buck stops on us.
- Just listen...
- Listen to what?
[Sighs]
Okay, let's go back in time.
When online booking
websites were started.
Those were the days when
travel agencies ruled the business.
You had your very own flourishing
travel agency,
and you were the boss.
And my dad was your employee.
When my dad worked
for your company
he treated you more
like an ideal, then a boss.
He learned everything from you
and started this Travelon.
And when your business closed down,
and you needed work
he immediately offered you
a job here, right?
Right, sir.
But that doesn't mean
that you make silly mistakes.
Do you understand?
I do.
Thank you for understanding.
And please make sure
these things don't happen again.
You can go now, thank you.
Mr. Sethi,
you should've taken an off today.
Anything special, sir?
It's his birthday today.
Oh! Many, many,
happy returns of the day.
- Thank you.
- Please proceed.
Thank you.
Your honor, Kala Kruti Society
has received water only
on 7 days in the last four months.
On the other days,
they used a water tanker.
But the Municipality has
sent them four months bill.
Supported documents, your honor.
Your honor,
when we didn't receive water
then what is this bill for?
I request you
to direct the Municipality
to take this bill back.
Mr. Phulke...
now you speak.
Water was not supplied, your honor,
because Kala Kruti Society
is an unauthorized construction.
But...
Objection, your honor.
This case is about over-billing
and not about
unauthorized construction.
Objection overruled.
Mr. Phulke, if the entire
society is unauthorized
then why hasn't
any action been taken.
The action has been taken, sir.
BMC has already sent
two notices to the society.
The first notice
on 5th September 1995.
And the second notice was
served on 9th June 1999, sir.
Is the Municipality's
responsibility
only serving notice?
This is why half the constructions
in Mumbai are illegal.
Can I say something, your honor?
Yes, please.
More than 100 families
have been living
in this society
for the last 22 years.
Comprising of young and old alike.
That doesn't make
the society legal.
According to Section 53
of Maharashtra
regional town planning Act 1966
Kala Kruti Society is
an unauthorized construction.
The court orders the Municipality
to completely raze down
Kala Kruti Society.
To be demolished
with immediate effect.
[Gavel pounds]
[All] Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to you.
Come on, Grandpa, blow the candle.
Happy birthday, dear Papa.
Yeah! Let's demolish this cake,
Grandpa.
[Woman laughing]
It's a beautiful cake, Bharti.
Thank you, Sister-in-law.
Papa...
This is a phone for you.
See, I told you.
You should ask Brother Himansh once
before buying a gift for father.
What happened, Bharti?
Even he bought a phone for papa.
[Man chuckles] So what?
Papa will use two phones.
That's not a problem.
Wow, Grandpa. Two phones.
This phone's equipped
with new technology.
It scans your face to unlock.
Face recognition.
Wow!
What will I do with two phones?
Yes, Grandpa.
Give me that phone
with face recognition.
[Women laughing]
Why do you need that phone?
I gave you a brand new
for your birthday.
I've given you a new phone
on your birthday.
Himansh, he is just joking.
I'll just go to the loo.
Even I'll go to the bathroom.
[Chuckles softly]
Let's eat the cake.
Parents are like old mobile phones.
They become outdated pretty soon.
So let it go.
I was just cracking a joke.
People in India don't
have a sense of humor.
[Unzips]
Whenever I am in a bad mood,
I think about the US.
Swear man,
I can't wait to get out of here.
Swear, even I am
tired of dad's lectures.
Look...
Look at Vansh.
Get marks like Vansh.
Stupid.
Look at Vansh.
He's found a source
to go to the US.
Vansh. Vansh. Vansh.
I am their son,
but you are their favorite.
Come on, let's exchange fathers.
[Both chuckle]
Why didn't Hina show up,
Sister-in-law?
She must be busy.
She's newly married after all.
Yeah, she just
got married recently.
And newly married couples
need some time alone.
[Coughs] Give it here.
- I am paying, Brother.
- I insist.
Whose idea was it
to bring everyone here?
Who is older?
Stop insisting, Brother.
I am paying the bill.
Why? Do you think
I can't afford it?
Take it.
[Woman] Did you win a jackpot?
You won't understand.
Then please explain it to me.
Hriday's gift was more expensive
than yours, so it hurt your ego.
And you paid the bill
which was 15,000.
Next week we've to pay Vansh's
fee for the American University.
We've to arrange
for 2.5 million rupees.
- We can't arrange for that, and...
- Fine, I made a mistake.
I got emotional.
I wish I could give
you guys the same life
that Hriday gives his family.
If Sethi Travels hadn't
closed down, Vandana
then I would've never taken up
this job that pays only 50,000.
You wouldn't have to make
lunch boxes every morning.
Hina could've had a grand wedding.
Vansh could've gone off to America.
I am a failure.
Himansh,
we've been married for 27 years.
Every morning you make tea for me.
And I wonder that
I couldn't have found
anyone who would've
made better tea for me.
[Chuckles]
I swear.
My gold medalist husband.
[Vandana] Stupid.
And my job is not a helplessness,
I like doing it.
You know
I received such great comments
on my lunch box WhatsApp group.
I made Punjabi curry.
Look what he said.
"The Curry was awesome."
And he spelled awesome with "OSUM".
See... he can't even spell.
Shweta gave me three thumbs up.
She never even gives one.
She's such a grouch.
Look this...
[Doorbell ringing]
[Knocking on the door]
[Grandpa]
Who's knocking on the door?
I'll check, Father.
[Doorbell ringing]
[Door opens]
[Himansh] Rishi.
Is everything all right?
Why didn't you guys
show up at dinner?
Where is Hina?
- Hina isn't here?
- No.
[Tongue clicks]
Please get me a Disprin?
[Himansh] Son.
Did she say she's coming here?
Where is Hina?
We had a fight last night.
She left home in a fit of rage.
I thought she would've come here.
You two had a fight last night
and you're telling us now.
- Phone...
- Yes.
I tried calling her, Aunty,
but her number's switched off.
You should've informed us
last night.
I'll try calling Akruti.
Hello, Akruti.
Is Hina at your place?
Okay.
Why did you let her go?
I tried to stop her, Uncle.
But you know how stubborn
your daughter is.
[Vansh] Let's call the Police.
Even the police won't take a
missing complaint before 24 hours.
Don't talk nonsense now.
But I don't think
she will go to a friend.
- Where else will she go?
- Hotels, guest houses, maybe.
There's no way
she could've gone to a hotel.
- There's no harm in checking.
- Okay, Papa.
Hina is at Parkhi's house.
- Let's go get her back.
- Yes, let's go. Let's go.
- Yes, let's go.
- Let's go.
And don't get angry or yell at her.
- Talk softly.
- [Himansh] Yes, Father.
Come, sir.
[Woman voiceover]
Please close the door.
[Lift door closes]
[Door opens and closes]
Hello...
What's the matter? The Sethi
family seems to be in a hurry.
Come on.
[Doorbell ringing]
[Door opens]
Hina, are you okay, dear?
Why didn't you come home?
Yeah, why didn't you come home?
Tell Rishi to leave.
- Come on, Hina.
- Papa, just tell him to leave.
Shut up, okay?
Go ahead, yell at me.
That's all you can do.
Go ahead, drink.
Drink and yell.
You told me to f**k off,
didn't you?
Now you f**k off.
See... that's the problem
with your daughter.
She was missing all day.
And now after giving us a heart
attack, she is showing attitude.
- Take it easy, okay?
- Why?
- She's my wife.
- And she's my sister.
- Whatever?
- Rishi. Rishi.
Rishi, son.
Please leave for now.
- But, Papa...
- I said leave.
Go.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
Come, Hina, let's go home.
[Grandpa]
I'll sue him for mental torture!
Tell that rascal
to stay away from my sights.
Or I will break his legs.
We all advised you not
to marry that alcoholic.
He's already been divorced once.
- Why did you marry him?
- Shut up, Vansh.
[Hina sighs]
I knew that you will all
give me the "I told you so" speech.
That's why I went to Parkhi's home.
At least she doesn't judge me.
I know I screwed up. Okay?
I know.
I thought I could change him.
Love would change him.
But I was stupid.
I am such an idiot.
Stupid.
No, dear.
Just forget what happened.
Marrying Rishi was a mistake.
But you're also making
a mistake thinking
your parents won't support you.
Huh?
Hina. Vansh.
You two must remember...
Doesn't matter what happens in
life, anything at all, any problems
you two have a home,
and always will.
Everything will be fine.
You are my strong child.
- Everything will be fine.
- [Vansh clears throat]
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Drink this tea.
Sorry.
I am not making any stories.
My wallet got stolen from
that restaurant around the corner.
Doesn't matter. Don't worry.
So boy, what notice
did you bring today?
Demolition.
Demolition?
You should always
wear a cap outside.
What's up, Chaubey?
This guy is from the Municipality
to serve another notice.
Come. Come.
What is this notice now?
Brother, why did you bring
notice so early in the morning?
Come with me, I'll treat you
to a nice cup of tea.
- Come on.
- Give that tea to Mr. Brijmohan.
He went to court to file
a case against the Municipality.
The judge has served
a demolition notice instead.
Now you will all have to pay.
Hey listen...
What's this about demolition now?
Madam, here you go.
There's a meeting.
Sir, here you go.
[Woman] On the 6th floor...
Yeah, yeah, the lift's for
you guys, right. Move.
What's wrong, Chaubey?
Who's making you run
a marathon in the morning?
This building is
going to be demolished.
I am warning you guys,
find another job.
Have you ever seen these
buildings getting demolished?
Nothing is going to happen.
Instead, they will grease
palms and set things.
The lift had to break down today?
Here you go, madam.
[Doorbell ringing]
[Door opens]
Madam.
Here.
Is this April fool?
Demolition order?
What is this new problem now?
What is this, Chaubey?
Emergency meeting.
[Tongue clicks] Oh no.
What? This house is illegal.
Why did you go to the court
in the first place, Father?
You knew all about this.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
You've started this new problem.
Why is everyone
screaming in the morning?
- Where is the fire?
- Here.
How dare they mention
my name in this?
We're out of mint and coriander.
Can someone go get it?
They are calling grandpa senile,
how mean.
They are senile.
I'll see them at the meeting.
Why buy a house here
when the building was illegal?
I didn't know at the time of buying
that the building is illegal.
Why didn't you ask me?
I could have investigated this.
Papa, I wanted this to be a
surprise for you, to mom, Vandana.
We're out of lemons as well.
Someone get that too.
- [Himansh] Okay, Vandana.
- Surprise, yes.
This is the mother
of all surprises.
I feel like my whole life is a lie.
Cool.
You know how these builders
and politicians fool people.
And you turned out to
be the biggest fool of all.
Papa, why are you yelling at me now
for a mistake I made 22 years ago.
- Why not?
- Himansh. Papa.
The demolition won't stop
if you fight amongst yourselves.
It's better if you call
for a meeting of the society.
Then you'll find a solution.
Or tell me,
I'll go attend the meeting
and you guys finish
packing the lunchboxes.
- No, I will go change first.
- This is the bits.
This demolition will never happen.
Go and get the ingredients
I asked for.
- I've to finish making the sauce.
- [Brijmohan] Illegal...
- Mom...
- Go, hurry up.
We are soon going to
become mincemeat in the meeting.
Vaibhav, we've been
served demolition orders.
We have an important meeting.
Aren't you going to attend?
Sorry, I have a shoot.
Bachchan sir is waiting for me.
So got to rush.
Next time.
We never saw him on TV and
Bachchan sir is waiting for him.
[Women giggling]
I am sure you all know that because
of Mr. Brijmohan's single mistake
we're facing a big problem.
Now we must together
find a solution.
What mistake?
Who is he to defend the society
against the Municipality?
Who are you?
Are you the Collector?
Or the Prime Minister?
Who made him the leader?
We've been living in this society
for all these years.
Why did you do such a thing?
I'll give it in writing that
we'll lose our home because of him.
- Because of me?
- Of course.
Because of me.
What are you saying, Mr. Gehi?
I was fighting for you.
And you sent me
this circular instead.
You have insulted me and I will
sue all of you for defamation.
[Indistinct murmuring]
What defamation, Mr. Sethi?
We're facing demolition now.
- I'll do that...
- How can you talk like that?
[Man] Please, sit down.
Please...
What are you saying?
We should listen first.
My brother-in-law...
My brother-in-law is an
advocate in the Supreme Court.
- Calm down. Calm down...
- It's okay.
Calm down.
Make him understand.
This is not done.
The entire building
will be demolished.
Look.
Nice, isn't it?
She has proposed marriage.
[Chuckles softly]
Pray that this happens.
- I am tired of jerking off.
- [Snickering]
[Woman] Silence!
Silence, sit down.
Sethi uncle,
we bought illegal homes.
We made a mistake.
But how can we complain, tell me?
How is it our mistake?
Was it a mistake that we trusted
the government and the builder?
We saved every penny
and bought a flat here.
How would we know that
the building is illegal?
And if the building was illegal
then why didn't the Municipality
raze it down.
We're paying property tax,
electricity bill
then how is illegal.
Look Brij,
your intentions are right
but what you did was wrong.
- Yes.
Last month when I wrote
a letter to the Police
and got rid of those junkies,
then that was right.
[Woman exhales]
When I got the garbage
cleared in front of our building
then that was right.
- But this is wrong.
- What's the point?
The garbage is still there.
And those junkies are back again.
But at least he tried.
It's 11 o'clock,
I must take Pluto to the doctor.
[Whispering]
Let's go from here, please.
This is so boring.
Hang on,
let's see what they decide.
Let's make out.
F**k this decision.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Listen, I am ovulating, okay.
And the office starts tomorrow.
You won't get a chance
for another week.
After that I am chumming.
[Audio not clear]
You want to be a daddy, no?
- Sure.
- Then let's go.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
Then let's go.
What's my mistake
if the garbage is back?
[Himansh] Papa!
Calm down. Please calm down.
Look, there's no point
in yelling and shouting.
- [Coughing]
- What's done is done?
Are you okay, Mr. Gehi?
You don't have to worry, Mr. Gehi.
They won't just run over
our building with the bulldozer.
It's not that easy.
They are just trying to scare us.
You see when uncle filed a case
he hurt the Municipality's ego.
So we'll find a middle way. Simple.
You know what, uncle.
Come with me and apologize
to the Municipality officer.
- [Man 2] Right.
- End of story.
Isn't it?
[Man 3] Correct.
Proposed by Mr. Motwani,
seconded by Secretary Nirmala.
Accepted.
Just a minute, Nirmala.
Motwani sir,
you want me to apologize.
[Motwani] Yes.
Then let me make it clear
that I won't apologize.
I will sue them, I'll take them
to the Supreme Court.
[Motwani] What's the point
of making things worse?
Everyone's talking just nonsense.
Get lost.
I am done.
[Man 4] Listen to me.
[Man 5]
When our house will demolish...
[Vansh] There can never be
a revolution in India.
Because the rich don't need it,
the poor don't have courage.
And the middle-class
don't have time.
And I don't have any interest
because I am out of here
in two months.
Mom is waiting for you.
Hi.
- Hi.
- When did you come back?
Yesterday.
So where are you heading to?
- Gym?
- How is Rishi?
- Okay.
- I heard that she came back.
So soon.
Yeah. Marriages these days
are like made in China.
They don't last
for more than 6 months.
[Giggling]
Meeting adjourned.
[Burps]
[Sighs]
Vandana, the food was delicious.
- You guys continue.
- Wait, Papa.
Wait.
What happened?
[Vandana chuckles softly]
Wow!
You're showing a lot of love today.
[Chuckles]
Well...
[Brij chuckles]
Papa, please say sorry.
Please.
When my children don't understand,
then forget the society.
And you're giving me sugar.
Do you want to kill me?
This is the limit.
The limit.
[Doorbell rings]
Go.
Uh...
Finish your dinner, Himansh.
Prince Charming is here.
Hello.
Are you back to your senses?
Sorry.
Hina, I am sorry.
Please talk to me for a minute.
Even after I blocked you
on WhatsApp, you didn't get a hint.
Papa, please tell her
to talk to me.
What mom-dad?
It's between us.
Fine. [Sighs]
[Door closes]
I have decided I'll go to rehab.
Whatever.
You can do whatever you want,
we are through.
Don't say that.
If you don't support me,
then who will.
I am not a walking stick.
But before the marriage,
you promised me
that you will help me
beat this addiction.
And didn't I try?
You did.
Rishi, I made a lot of sacrifices
for this relationship.
I fought with my parents,
quit my career.
Now I am done.
You can leave.
Hina.
[Door opens]
Leave.
I'll be back.
[Door closes]
[Exhales deeply]
- [Himansh] Vandana.
- Yes.
- Why is there no water?
- [Laughing softly]
What's the matter?
Is something funny?
Vansh, go check what's
wrong with the water.
Because I am the only
useless person in this house.
[Himansh] Go quickly.
What's wrong with the water?
The management committee members
Nirmala and Gehi have told me
to sever the water connection
- to your house.
- Why?
Until your grandpa
doesn't apologize
to the Municipality Commission.
- Okay.
- You won't learn, will you?
- I'll get you fired.
- Boss...
You'll get me fired.
Nothing will happen.
Just get water supply back.
Papa is in the middle of his shave.
[Chuckles]
Thank you.
Guess what
the society members
severed our water connection
because grandpa is not apologizing.
Don't apologize.
Today they cut off our water supply
tomorrow it will
be our electricity.
Soon they will cut our throats.
Just say sorry to the Municipality.
Yes, Grandpa.
When helpless be
like Mahatma Gandhi.
Hey!
You would've never said such
a thing if you had seen Gandhiji.
Courage.
He was courage.
I will file a police complaint.
I will sue them for harassment.
I will make sure all of them
are put behind bars.
Papaji!
Papa, please don't do that.
Even Gandhiji never
got anyone arrested.
Your generation has
forgotten to revolt.
You guys have no zest. No zest.
One has to come down on
the streets to bring a revolution.
Posting on Twitter and Facebook
won't bring a revolution.
But the water is back.
Himansh, go take a bath.
Yes.
- Papa...
- Go and finish shaving.
Whose anger are you
venting on the bag?
- [Man chuckles]
- Hey!
- Wow...
- Congratulations.
You didn't invite me
to your wedding
but I found out through Facebook.
Everything happened
so quickly that...
I know, I know.
Calling your ex-boyfriend
to the wedding is a little awkward.
What are you doing here?
You moved to the suburbs
after the wedding.
Actually,
these days I am at my mom's place.
Wow! You're pregnant!
What?
No. Nothing like that!
Then you fought with your husband.
That's why you were...
Listen, it's nothing like that.
You're just over thinking.
You haven't changed at all.
You still can't lie.
And you're still nosy
and annoying like always.
[Laughs]
You know what, give me your number.
Let's catch up some time.
The ex-girlfriend
has marital issues.
Show her some sympathy,
a shoulder to cry on.
And then hook up with her.
- Right?
- Wow!
Seriously,
I haven't thought that far, but
do I still have chances
for hooking up?
One cup of coffee won't hurt.
Actually,
how can a cup of coffee hurt?
[Man] Right.
See you.
Bye.
I will call you.
[Woman] Pluto.
How are you, Mr. Gehi?
How are you?
Mrs. Mehta.
[Indistinct chatter]
He doesn't want to do anything.
Same here.
Mr. Holkar.
This Sethi family has
made things worse for us.
[Woman 2]
Whatever, but they must apologize.
[Door opens]
Hello.
It's nothing, just one
of my neighbors. Forget it.
[Woman voiceover]
Please close the door.
[Himansh] The entire society
is boycotting us.
We cannot fight everyone, Vandana.
But who will explain papa?
What do we do?
Can I say something?
Let's invite everyone in
the society to our anniversary.
The entire society?
Do you know how much
that's going to cost?
Not the entire society?
Just the main guys.
Like Nirmala, the Secretary.
Motwani. Gehi. Srivastav.
Basically committee members.
But our anniversary is next month.
Wouldn't that be too late?
Let's celebrate in advance.
They don't remember
when is our anniversary.
Okay?
Yes, okay.
[Laughs]
What an idea. What an idea.
Then let's party on Saturday.
Okay.
Complete with booze,
kebabs, everything.
And your homemade yummy food.
Your food will calm down
their anger.
And things will be normal again.
[Kisses, laughs]
We did it last week too.
So... it's not like eating veggies
that we can eat only once a week.
[Both chuckling]
Tell me something.
Do you believe that our frequency
is anything like the other couples?
Not Mr. and Mrs. Motwani.
I see...
Have you noticed how
dry her hair has become?
And Mr. and Mrs. Gehi?
No chance.
That's why
they are so full of anger.
I am sure
they had sex last in 1983.
To celebrate India's victory
in the World Cup.
[Both laughing]
World Cup.
Forget the others.
You do something.
Hold me properly.
If you say in Marathi,
I can even jump from the window.
Just a minute.
- Where are you going now?
- Coming.
Aah!
[Himansh]
Are you bathing in perfume?
Coming.
[Vansh] Looking at the situation,
the Sethi family
moved the threat level
from serious to critical.
[Spraying]
No!
Nice, girl.
[Vansh] We didn't prepare so much
even during the board exams
compared to what
we did for this party.
- Looking nice, isn't it?
- Yes.
Where are you going, Papa?
You want me to share a meal
with them after they humiliated me.
Call me after they leave.
- [Door opens]
- Bloody rascals.
- [Door slams shut]
- Vansh, sit straight.
What time did I tell them to come
and what is the time now?
[Cricket commentary playing on TV]
This is wrong.
We should go.
Yes, we should.
But let it be.
They must be still
stuck in the office.
[Himansh sighs deeply]
You can sit here and chew nuts,
I am going to Vandana.
They will boycott us as well.
I'll see them.
[Doorbell ringing]
[Softly] They are here.
Vansh. Get up.
Fix the cushions.
Hina.
[Door opens]
[Laughs]
[Door closes]
Don't listen to me.
[Brij clears throat]
Come on, Vansh, Hina.
Let's keep everything back inside.
Let's wait a little longer...
No need.
They are not welcome now.
[Doorbell ringing]
[Door opens]
[Himansh] Mrs. Motwani.
Where is Mr. Motwani?
I'll tell you later,
first close the door.
- Close the door.
- What is this?
I called you at 7,
and you're coming now.
What to do?
I am very embarrassed to say this.
Actually, everyone decided
not to attend your party.
And who decided that?
The management committee.
Especially Nirmala and Mrs. Gehi.
And you know, the Society
has formed a WhatsApp group.
And only your family
is not in that group.
They keep saying bad things on that
group about your family all day.
You guys must do something.
And you? You call
yourself my best friend.
You should've told me
that no one's coming.
I made all this food.
Do you want me to feed
fritters to my family all week?
You must have made
chickpeas for the party.
- I made everything.
- Can I take some?
See you.
If anyone sees me here,
they will boycott me too.
Thanks for the chickpeas.
I'll send the plates over later.
Bye.
[Door closes]
[Vandana sniffs]
[Vandana] What?
Are you planning to keep it
on my head? Keep it in the fridge.
[Vansh] Poor papa.
Sometimes I feel bad for him.
I want to keep my hand on
his shoulder and say "Dad, Chill.
Let's roll a joint."
But he's an Indian father
after all
It will get scandalized.
[Door closes]
You know what, forget papa.
You go and apologize
to the Municipality.
Have you lost your mind?
Papa will never spare me for it.
But you don't have
to tell papa everything.
[Himansh] Hello, Karan.
Hello, Karan.
There's been a problem.
Hello. I've come down with viral.
I'll try to come to the office
after I recover.
Thank you.
[Himansh sighs deeply]
That was an award-winning
performance.
Why didn't you tell me before?
Even I would've tried in films.
[Vandana laughs]
What happened?
The society has added us
in the WhatsApp group as well.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, I've to buy some stuff.
- I'll call you after the meeting.
- Yes.
All the best, Himansh.
[Himansh] Thank you.
I will note all that, don't worry.
I hope we're not late.
- Whom do you want to meet?
- Mr. Khairnar sir.
- Sign here.
- Yes.
One plus three.
- She said the second floor, right?
- Yes.
This is the first floor.
Come quickly.
Wonder where they are going?
Where are they going?
[Motwani] I keep dealing with these
government employees often.
No need to worry.
We'll have to grease his palms,
and everything will be set.
Okay, Mr. Motwani.
You're experienced with such things
so you will lead. Let him speak.
- Okay.
- You know what, Sethi sir
you just apologize
on behalf of the uncle.
- I will deal with the rest.
- That will be right.
[Woman] Vandana Sethi.
Yes.
Actually,
we're from the Kala Kruti Society.
The illegal building, right?
Sir, when we bought our homes,
we didn't know it was illegal.
Yes, we didn't know.
Did you have the building's
occupation certificate?
You didn't.
Your building had a permission
to build five floors.
But he built 7 floors instead.
Sir, we've been living
there for 22 years.
- Where will we go now?
- Right.
But I have orders from the court.
One of yous went to the court
to complain against us?
Sir, you see his father...
is an old man.
And you know, at this age...
Yes, sir. You know old age problem,
senior citizen. You know...
He's 80 years old.
- He was a freedom fighter.
- I see...
Whatever happened
was unintentional, sir.
Okay, forget it.
- Sorry. On behalf of my papa...
- Okay.
What do you guys want from me?
Sir, we wanted you
to consider this matter
and remove that demolition matter.
We'll sit somewhere
outside and discuss...
I didn't understand.
What do you mean by consider?
No... [Stammering]
I mean...
Sethi sir was saying...
What were you saying?
What? What was I saying?
He's not saying anything.
Motwani sir was saying it.
Yes, we were considering that...
Are you trying to bribe me?
Look, I will have you arrested.
There's a little misunderstanding.
No, no misunderstanding.
I understand everything.
Don't talk about compromise
adjustment,
or anything like that here.
See this,
this is an abnormal growth.
It's a cyst in the breast.
Now in order to find out
what kind of a tumor this is
we'll have to do a biopsy, okay?
Sir, if the structure is illegal,
then it's the builder's fault.
Why are we being punished?
I see! Isn't it
your duty to find out
whether the builder
violated any rules or not?
The thief is to be blamed as much
as the guy who buys the
stolen goods. Understand?
Sir, the guy who buys stolen goods
is punished, and not the thief?
What kind of a Law is this?
The biopsy will determine whether
this tumor is benign or malignant.
If it's malignant,
then it's a breast cancer.
[Khairnar]
I have this court's order.
Demolition means demolition.
- Now you can go.
- Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
[Motwani]
And another important thing.
I've heard some rumors
about this MLA.
So no need to get too friendly.
I mean maintain your distance.
- Right.
- Okay?
Sister-in-law Vandana,
where is Mr. Sethi?
Himansh went to the office.
He can't get a leave every day.
It's all right.
And Mona, cut down on your ruse,
your lipstick, please.
- Why?
- Otherwise, how will we get that?
Get what?
- Sympathy.
- Yes.
[All] Right. Right.
We want the MLA's sympathy.
- It's called sympathy.
- I know.
And your earrings look too big.
Take it off.
- It's too big.
- And your chain too.
- Careful.
- Take it off.
- That's better.
- Sister-in-law, you're perfect.
We should look helpless and poor.
- Can we all go now?
- Yes. Yes.
You want help, don't you?
Then we will help you.
Let's find a way...
to stop the demolition.
First of all, get a stay
order from the High court
- for this demolition order.
- [Motwani] Yes.
Have you appointed a good lawyer?
[Holkar] No. Not yet.
[MLA] Then appoint one.
You must stop this demolition
in a legal way.
And we'll do it our way.
Sir, what do you mean by your way?
Our party has done
so much work in your area.
We fixed potholes,
installed street lights.
We got rid of the slums and made
footpaths for your morning walks.
We'll need a little donation
for all these good deeds.
How much, sir?
Yes, Motwani.
2.5 million.
Where will we get that amount?
Brother...
I'll come back and talk to you.
I'm in a meeting right now.
Yes. Thank you.
- Straight from the office...
- Yes...
- Water.
- Get some water.
Sit, Brother.
[Hriday clears throat]
Yes, tell me.
You see,
we want to send Vansh to America.
And you know about the expenses.
Dollar's rate is
at an all-time high.
Plus the Municipality's
served demolition notice.
So... I am a little stressed.
The matter is tight.
I am thinking about
taking out a loan.
Just tell me.
You see, the bank guys
are always after me.
They call up every day
insisting me to take a loan.
But... I thought
why don't I take
a loan from the bank
and why not you?
Instead of paying the
bank interest, I will pay you.
Even you'll make a quick buck.
And anyway,
you always have extra cash.
So tell me what interest
you will charge.
[Sighs]
You know what, Brother?
Why don't you take money
from the bank?
And pay the interest as well.
That will be better, right?
I thought he's my brother.
Not like the banks,
who take months to approve a loan.
And then if there's
ever a problem with EMIs
then I could've extended
the tenure.
But no, he's worse than the banks.
I was stupid who went
begging to him for a money.
What are you looking at?
Huh?
Vandana.
What is this?
[Himansh] Don't worry.
We'll deal with it.
We've fought many battles in life.
We'll fight this one too, and win.
We'll get the best treatment.
[Vandana sighs]
The cost will be
around 1.5 million.
Where will we get
that kind of money?
We have FDs, PPFs (investments)!
No, they are for sending
Vansh to America.
We cannot send him
to America anyway.
We need to save
some money for a home.
What if we lose this home tomorrow.
But Himansh, he wants to go.
Those who can't afford America,
don't they do MBA?
There are some very good
colleges in India as well.
He can finish his MBA here.
I am feeling very guilty.
He will be heartbroken
because of me.
You don't get everything in life.
Vansh has to learn.
Don't tell the children
about this just yet.
They will be scared.
We will tell them after
the test results, whatever it is.
Remember your aunt's daughter.
Why don't we take
a second opinion from her?
She is a gynecologist.
She is a doctor.
[Vandana sighs]
Himansh,
I Googled it.
There are only 30% chances
of surviving cancer.
30% is a lot.
Even if the chances are 0%,
I won't let anything happen to you.
What is the bad news?
Son, you know we love you.
We try to fulfill Hina
and yours every need.
We can't, because we have
some shortcomings of our own.
Come to the point.
Son, this house is in dispute now.
The Municipality
isn't ready to listen.
The future is very uncertain.
So?
We can't send you to America.
What?
Tomorrow if we have to move,
or change homes
we need some money in the bank.
But you promised me.
We weren't facing
demolition back then, Vansh.
I knew it.
I knew you guys would do this.
You don't love me.
Uncle should've been
my father instead.
Shut up!
- You just shut up.
- What else can you do?
You can ask me to shut up.
There's nothing else you can do.
You can't run a business
or earn money.
All you have is a big ego
which you carry around everywhere.
And this?
How much is this worth?
2000 rupees.
[Laughs]
These are fake.
They are fake.
Real ones cost 10,000.
10,000.
- It's fake.
- [Door opens and closes]
[Sighs]
I already smoked two joints,
but I am still not high.
Should I talk to dad?
No. I know my dad's ego.
If I take money from my uncle,
he will disown me.
Even I don't want to go to America.
I can't keep a maid there.
And I will have to wash
and clean on my own.
[Chuckles]
You want to go to America,
but you can't afford it.
My dad can afford it,
but I don't want to go.
Life is a b***h. Unfair.
Even Bill Gates said that.
Hi.
Hey.
Can I click a picture of you guys?
- No.
- Yeah, sure.
You guys smoking weed.
No.
Enjoy.
She was checking you out.
And you're making faces like
every other girl on Tinder
right swaps on your picture.
She's going back to Kanpur.
Why?
She was a paying guest here,
couldn't find a job.
- Oh, God!
- [Scoffs]
Life's unfair.
Bill Gates said it, I know.
[Growls]
[Doorbell rings]
[Door opens]
- [Hina] Hi.
- Hi.
How bad is that?
This.
Two more weeks of bed rest.
After that, I'll be ready
to stick my feet in others affair.
[Hina chuckles]
- Is this for me?
- Yeah, that's for you.
Thank you, please come in.
[Door closes]
Wow...
So finally you got
into fashion photography.
I mean, I grew tired of telling you
to get a commercial job,
make some money, make a career.
- But you never listened to me.
- Hey. Hey.
You're not my girlfriend anymore,
remember.
Fair enough.
So, what do you want to have?
Red Wine.
Do you still drink red wine
or you quit after marriage?
I only changed my marital status,
not my taste.
I see.
But your taste in guys
changed before marriage.
Otherwise compared to me,
interesting and that boring Rishi.
[Hina chuckles]
Listen, enough about me.
You tell me about yourself.
So what's happening?
- Who are you dating these days?
- Me.
After you walked out on me,
I went back to my first love.
- And who is that?
- Photography.
Listen, I won't drink.
Why?
Because after one drink
we'll discuss my marriage.
And I really don't
want to get there.
We won't discuss your marriage
even after four drinks.
I promise you.
Okay.
Cheers.
- You know what?
- [Man] What?
What's worse than
being single and lonely?
[Man] What?
Being married and lonely.
Marrying Rishi was
the biggest mistake of my life.
I screwed my whole damn life.
Fuck it.
Shit happens.
You made a mistake.
So forget it.
Don't keep him wrapped
around your finger.
As in?
As in...
Give me your hand.
You don't need him.
Divorce him.
Move on!
And don't ever think you are alone.
This is fine.
[Man 1]
And what about the other file.
[Woman 1] Wait, I'll give you.
[Man 1] It's signed.
- Vandana Aunty.
- Hello.
- Hi!
- You must congratulate us first.
Congratulations.
- But what's the good news?
- Good news?
The good news is
that there's good news.
- Wow.
- Great.
[Vandana] When did you find out?
We just found out.
Just now.
So by March or April.
Yes, if all goes well.
Brother Mohsin,
don't give her any stress.
- And take care of her diet.
- Okay, I'll take care of her.
[Mohsin chuckles]
What are you guys doing here?
We're here to see Dr. Kulkarni.
Is everything all right?
All well?
- Yeah, okay.
- Everything is okay. [Chuckles]
- Okay.
Okay, take care.
- Bye.
I feel something is wrong.
- Why?
- I felt.
I get dozens of
customers every day.
Where will I get change?
That's not my problem,
that's your problem.
Madam, we don't get change
- from the bank either these days.
- What happened?
How much change can one guy carry?
What happened?
Yes, I have, wait.
Here you go, mister. Now go.
- Thank you, madam.
- Thank you.
Guess what,
I met your parents at the hospital.
At the gynecologist.
- Gynaec?
- Yeah.
I asked them if everything is okay.
They said yeah, everything fine.
They were a bit nervous
and embarrassed.
Why would they be embarrassed?
Exactly.
[Tongue clicks]
These accidents
can happen at any age.
- Chill. Relax.
- Hurry up!
Okay I'm coming.
See you later. Bye.
You're out.
Why are you cheating?
- You're out.
- You're cheating.
Vansh, I need to speak to you.
I don't want to talk, get lost.
You're out.
What?
Mom and dad were at the gynaec.
Zulfiya just told me.
Mom said they are going
over to Jyoti aunty's house.
Mom is pregnant.
They went there for an abortion.
Have you lost it?
Do you know mom's age?
If she can still have sex with dad,
then why can't she get pregnant.
Yuck! You're talking
about my parents, okay?
Our parents.
And biologically
they can get pregnant.
They can...
I wonder how they didn't
get bored of each other yet?
Maybe they love each other.
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Not everyone is like you.
It's Mom.
Abhay.
Please don't be judgmental.
We're just friends.
Hello.
[Door opens]
I'll make a nice
cup of tea for you.
No need, I'll make it.
No, take rest.
- How much rest...
- Mom.
Yes, dear.
What happened?
Papa, it's okay.
Everyone makes mistakes.
We are not kids anymore.
You both can tell us.
What mistake?
You tell us not to lie,
and you don't follow it yourself.
If you had told us
that mom is pregnant
then we wouldn't
have been so stressed.
Bloody fool,
have you lost your mind?
Then why did you two
secretly go to the hospital?
Tell us.
We went to see Manju aunty,
for a second opinion.
A second opinion on what?
The doctor's suspect...
breast cancer.
Mom!
They just suspecting,
nothing is confirmed.
We just got a biopsy done,
and find out in two days.
- I don't think it will be...
- Mom.
- Don't worry.
- I am sorry.
- No!
We just got a biopsy, so...
No need to be scared.
Be strong. Himansh.
Yes, don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
I'll get tea for all of you.
Yes.
No.
Where is your grandpa?
He's gone for a walk.
Good. Don't tell him.
He will be scared.
Vandana.
An emergency meeting
has been called.
Look, friends, the total legal fees
to defend this case in the high
court will be 1.2 million rupees.
And 2.5 million
to the MLA separately.
So in all, we need to
gather 4.5 million rupees.
Four million.
But how is it possible?
Mr. Motwani,
what's the guarantee that
the MLA will stop the demolition
after getting the money.
We'll have to take that risk,
Mr. Srivastav.
And anyway,
what other option do we have.
The building has permission
only till 5th floor.
And our flat is on the first floor.
It's 100% legal,
so why should we pay?
Please tell him.
And I am selling my home,
why should I pay?
And, I don't have that kind
of money. I can't afford it.
Why are you wasting money
on another lawyer?
I will defend this case for you.
Please let it be, Mr. Sethi.
You're the main
cause of this problem.
You've already lost the case
in the session's court.
So I don't think we can
give you any more chances.
Uncle, no need to take the trouble.
We'll arrange for a lawyer.
The Sethi family is at fault here.
So why we should
pay the legal fees?
This is your mistake,
so you will pay the fees.
We cannot afford this expense.
[Indistinct chattering]
Wait... Look, mister.
Sooner or later
this matter would've come up.
So how long will you
blame the Sethi family?
This is not right.
But...
[Vansh] Even sorrows have levels.
What was the biggest tragedy
of my life in the morning
doesn't matter anymore.
I can fight with mom
argue with her,
stop talking to her.
But I cannot live without her.
[Song playing]
- [Crying]
- [Hina] Mom.
Yes, dear.
Will anything happen to me?
No.
God.
Head massage.
How will I look like without hair?
What do you mean?
Hair starts falling
after chemotherapy.
Shall I wear wig then or cap?
What delicious food
have you made for tiffin?
Rajma and fenugreek
leaves and potato vegetable.
Great.
You always wanted to
do this Tiffin business.
[Tongue clicks]
But I wanted to
do business of my own.
My parents never supported me.
Why?
In those days ladies were
not allowed to be independent.
Your father also did
not want me to do anything.
Tch, tch, tch!
And you married such a chauvinist.
[Chuckles] Love marriage.
In those days
all gents were the same.
But even then I did cooking course
after much argument with him.
Thank God for that.
You did cooking course
so our lives were saved.
Otherwise we'd have to beg after
shut down of father's business.
We would have been in trouble.
Sorry. [Chuckles]
Vansh, you go to America.
Mom, please. I am not
even thinking about America.
No, but I am thinking.
I did not get my family's support
so I could not become a chef.
But you will get
your family's support.
You go to America.
Mission America is over. Okay?
Why? Just because
we do not have money. Right?
Don't worry. We will do something.
We will take a loan.
Hierarchy of needs, Mother.
Hierarchy of needs.
- What are you saying?
- [Chuckles]
There was a man
named Abraham Maslow.
He had said that basic needs are
the most important
needs of a human being.
Like food, clothing,
shelter and mother.
Remaining needs like career,
America,
clubbing, shopping dating
are required but later.
So first we will sort out mother
and then we will sort out America.
- Okay?
- Not okay.
Don't sacrifice your future for me.
What will I do of
my future without you?
[Kisses, sniffs]
[Kisses]
[Bell dings]
[Vansh] Everyone says
that during crisis
one should have faith on God.
But how do we keep?
God is not a doctor.
But how can we keep faith
on doctor? Doctor is not God.
[Landline ringing]
[Woman] Vandana Sethi.
May I come in, Doctor?
[Male Doctor] Come.
Sit down.
Has everyone come with mother
taking a leave?
It seems you all did
not sleep the entire night.
Your biopsy reports have come.
Reports are absolutely normal.
You do not have cancer.
[Vandana Sighs]
It is just a small tumor that
will get dissolved with medication.
My child.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
If you don't mind may
I have the next appointment?
Thank you, sir.
[Doctor] Sister.
- Thank you, doctor.
- [Doctor] Next patient, please.
Tell me, madam.
What do you want us to make?
An affidavit.
Leave them and come here.
Come. Sit down.
Kalakriti Society.
- The municipal one.
- Yes.
It will be done.
I will get such a stay order that
demolition will not take place.
Thank God.
- Stay there happily.
- Thank you. What is your fee?
30,000 bucks.
- For the entire case.
- [Chuckles]
Per hearing. In about 10-12
hearings the case will be finished.
Around 3-4 lakhs
of the entire case.
What are you saying, sir?
Be a little reasonable, sir.
Uncle holds great regard for you.
I too have regards for
your uncle so I said 30,000 bucks.
Best to best would be 28,000 bucks
per hearing. Is that okay?
Sir, we have a budget of
one lakh for this entire case.
We are middle class people. Our
society has only this much funds.
Do you have funds
to pay for this tea?
Or I will have to pay for it.
That is not the case.
Look...
[Gehi] What a strange man he is?
- He is a very rude man.
- Very.
- Uncle was right.
- Mannerless fellow.
Hi. I am Rizwan. I am a lawyer.
Shake hands.
Greetings. Can I sit down?
- Please.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
- We are finding a lawyer.
I know everything.
Kalakriti demolition,
municipality... I know everything.
I know everything.
I will fight the case for you.
What is your fee?
Don't worry. Pro bono.
- Porno?
- [Laughs]
Not porno but pro bono.
That means free of cost.
I will fight your case
and we will win.
We will win and I promise.
Shake hands.
[Rizwan chuckles]
Rakesh, three coffees from my side.
Could you now please give me
the detail of entire case?
Yes. We were... 22 years ago
we bought this building.
[Door opens]
[Vansh] The favorite word
of Indians is 'Free'.
Whether it is mobile data,
pirated films or lawyer.
We want everything for free.
With the arrival of
Rizwan a new ray of hope
arose in the minds
of people of the society.
He became the latest
celeb of the society.
Everyone started
flattering his highness.
- Cheers.
Make her eat sweetmeat.
[indistinct chatter]
Whether it was Rizwan's magic
or Pawan Giri's good luck
that after waiting for years
finally he got engaged.
Now that mom's health was perfect
then the signal for going to
America changed from red to green.
Mom convinced father
to take loan from bank.
I'll wait outside. All the best.
Hi.
Do you have money?
I will not come to deposit it
in the bank.
Buy a house as well.
Don't mention about this
to anyone in society.
Otherwise a complaint
will be filed against me again.
Did anything happen?
Something can happen only
when they allow it to happen.
My landlord does not
allow my friends to come home.
The aunties of your building
pass sneaky comments
if one wears a short
dress and goes down.
If I get late then
your watchman also judges.
And I thought I am from small town.
Now I know why the government
wants to break your building.
Because all of you are
so boring and narrow minded.
All of them are not like that.
But mostly they are of this sort.
Did you get a job?
Yes, finally.
- Sani TV. Have you heard the name?
- [Tongue clicks]
It is a very lame channel.
No one has heard the name.
But at least I have the job.
Yes. Sure.
But how do you know
that I was finding a job?
Just like that.
Neighborhood gossip.
Did you get the visa for America?
How do you know that
I am going to America?
Neighborhood gossip.
[Woman] Token number 10.
That's me.
Uh... Shall we hang out sometime?
I am going to America.
Can we hang out before
going to America?
Yes, ma'am. [Clears throat]
Here.
Ma'am, documents.
[Woman] Which university?
Washington School of Business.
You have got a scholarship.
Yes ma'am.
The entire tuition is waived off.
I want loan for travel
and living expenses.
The credit score
of Mr. Sethi is very low.
What does credit score mean?
Mr. Sethi made a default
twice on the last loan.
Ma'am, maybe that time
father was suffering
losses in business that time.
Everything is normal now.
There will not be a default now.
Your building does not have an OC.
We cannot pass the loan
on the surety of home
till all the papers are legalized.
Please take a look.
All other documents are sorted.
What can I do?
Property papers are not clear.
Credit score is low.
There must be some way out, ma'am.
All the rest...
There is no way out
without any security.
I am so sorry.
Token number 11, please.
- What happened?
- They are rascals.
They will give loans
to those who have crores
but will not give it to us.
Don't take tension.
We will try something else.
Take this.
I just cannot think about anything.
Hi. Hi, Dad.
- Sit.
- Hi, Uncle.
Vansh, you too come along.
No, Uncle, I will go by rickshaw.
Your father will not scold
for dropping you home.
- Come and sit.
- You never know about him.
[Door opens and closes]
- Thanks, Uncle.
- Wear the belt.
I tried a lot but the
bank officials did not agree.
No one can do anything
when luck does not favor you.
Nikhil, you go to America.
I will come to the airport
to bid you farewell.
Keep quiet.
I will give you the money.
No, Uncle. Leave it.
If father comes to know
then he will thrash me.
He will thrash you
only if he comes to know.
Tell him that a friend gave
you a loan. The matter ends there.
Do you want to
go to America or not?
Come on smile.
Smile.
[Chuckles]
By telling people we both
can make some improvement.
- Hi, Aunty.
- Hello, Son.
Shall I talk to mom in private?
Yes. Okay then, bye.
What is it?
Uncle has given
for going to America.
Have you gone mad?
You will create a fight at home.
Mom, send me to America
but not on a guilt trip.
When Himansh asked for it
then Hriday did not give.
Okay he has given it now. Big deal.
Papa will get upset.
He will not like it at all.
Okay, his feelings are
important but now my future.
What will I say? Who gave it?
Jyoti aunty.
Is my sister like a joker of cards?
You just fit her in any situation.
Who else will give?
No, no. If you put the cheque
in the bank then
Himansh will come to know about it.
Mom, I will put it
in my personal account.
Father is not going
to check my bank statement.
You are very smart.
You have planned everything
before coming to me.
- Mom.
- [Sighs]
[Tongue clicks] Why are you
calling? First close the matter.
Let me call Jyoti to tell
that she is giving money to you.
- Let me take her in confidence.
- Mom, you are the best.
I am not the best.
I will go in hell for you.
Your son will go to America.
Let her pick up the phone first.
- Your Jyoti aunty is giving money.
- Yes.
Your sister is very sweet.
She is always ready to help.
Yes.
- Whom are you calling?
- Jyoti. To thank her.
She has gone to watch a movie.
If you call in between
then it would be bad manners.
Call her later. After two hours.
Okay fine. But make
one thing very clear to her.
We will pay back
her loan in 2-3 years.
Yes, of course. We have taken the
loan so will surely pay it back.
Yes. Give me.
I had told you to let me first
talk to Jyoti and then tell father.
- Why are you always in hurry?
- Mother India, chill.
I could not get through
Jyoti's number so how can I chill.
Everything is sorted out.
- What has sorted?
- Sorted.
I am sorted here.
Pick up the phone.
Everything will be done.
Come on let's eat food.
How will everything be done?
I hope no problem comes up.
Hey Birju, newspaper.
Open Page3.
[Boy] No, I did not take.
Look at this.
I had told you that
I would solve your problem.
He is from opposition.
He got the photo published
in press. He is playing politics.
Sir, we did not know
about it at all.
Then you should have
searched the internet.
Then you would have come
to know that he is their area head.
Search it on the internet.
Do whatever you wish to do.
Look, my party just
wants to help you.
[MLA] Why? Are you their relative?
Opposition is using you.
[Rizwan] These people from
government will neither help you
nor let anyone help you.
If anyone can help you
then it is just government.
The government is ours.
Listen, do not get
trapped in what MLA says.
It is my job to do social work.
I will save you. I will.
Look sir, we do not need your help.
We are simple people.
How can we understand our politics?
- Sir, please leave this case.
- What?
We will hire another lawyer.
You all have very less time.
Sheikh sir, please.
Father had mentioned
to check background
and then appoint lawyers.
But you all did not listen.
I am again late for office.
I shall leave now.
[Woman]
Did you see the entire movie?
- Good morning, Mr. Sethi.
- Good morning.
Boss was asking for you.
[Karan] Make it more presentable.
Mr. Sethi.
Good morning, Karan.
How come you are in office today?
The problem of the demolition
of our building is going on.
And then my wife's cyst
and the biopsy.
Do you know Rosy
in the marketing team?
Her divorce is going on.
Sunil at the front desk.
His brother is in jail.
In fact my girlfriend also
broke up with me last week.
There are problems in everybody's
life but work is also important.
Look, everyone is doing.
It is good that
you came to office today.
It will be very good if you
continue to come to office on time.
Okay. Please.
[Song playing]
[Sighs deeply]
[Cell phone ringing]
There is no peace at all.
Vandana.
Vandana, your phone.
[Vandana] I am taking a bath.
[Song pauses]
Hello, Jyoti.
I am fine. How are you?
I was about to call you
to thank you.
Jyoti, thank you so much
for the loan that
you have given Vansh for his fees.
No.
Okay, I will ask Vandana
to call you.
Bye.
[Himansh] Vansh, Vansh.
Vansh.
[Brij] Hey!
- Did you take money from Hriday?
- [Brij] What happened?
Did you take money
from Hriday or not?
- Yes.
- Didn't you? Why did you lie?
Why?
Why are you screaming?
- Dad, he took money from Hriday.
- So what?
- It is a big deal for me.
- It is not his fault.
- Even you are taking his side.
- Himansh...
No. Come with me.
- Come with me.
- Papa, but...
Come.
- [Brij] Why's he getting so angry?
- Calm down.
- Why are you getting so angry?
- Come.
[Brij] What has happened?
- [Vandana] Your BP will increase.
- [Hina] Papa, please.
- [Vandana] Listen to me.
- [Himansh] Come.
- Papa, what...
- Calm down.
Do not trouble me.
[Door closes]
What is the problem if I helped
him a little? He is my nephew.
- It is a problem.
- What problem?
The problem is that you are
disgracing me by instigating him.
- You are playing a game with me.
- What game am I playing?
You refused when
I asked money from you.
How did you ask for money?
- How did I ask it?
- I am your younger brother.
Have I opened a bank here?
You were irritating me
by continuously
asking me to take interest.
I do not need your money.
Vansh, return his money.
Brother, because of your ego you
are spoiling the child's future.
You worry about your child
and not of mine.
- Vansh, return the money to him.
- [Hriday] Amazing.
I will not return it, Father.
What?
Why should I return the money?
He is not our neighbor but family.
Who else but family helps
during such times?
Son, there are certain
rules and values of life.
- I do not have them, Father.
- But you are my son.
But I am not like you.
I will take help and
will go to the US. I have decided.
Fine.
Then do not ever come back.
I will not back.
I don't want to come.
Once I go to US
I will not even call.
And I'll go with mom.
- I am there for you.
- [Sniffs]
[Man] Now your demolition
notice has come.
You tell me if will you get
your daughter married in a family
who do not have a house to live.
That is fine.
But if you could give it
a second thought.
We are sorry for now.
Uncle, you did not come
in flag hoisting ceremony.
Who is winning?
Who else but Sethi uncle.
Who else will win, Mr. Gehi?
[Chuckles]
What do you want?
We all have taken a vow
on independence day.
We want to be free
of the fear with
which we are living
for the last 22 years.
We will strongly
oppose the willfulness
and dictatorship
of the municipality.
We have come here to request you
to please be our leader
in this fight.
Today, you are giving me
a lot of respect.
We have always respected you.
That is why we want you
to fight in high court and win.
We all are with you.
Earlier you never respected Birju.
Maybe they did not
get any other lawyer.
If not now then when will
your experience be of any use?
- Please take up this case.
- Yes.
- We are like your children.
- Right.
Set up my office
in the society office.
Everything will happen
according to your wish, Uncle.
On Monday we will file
a petition in High Court.
- Be ready by 9 o'clock.
- Yes, yes. Sure, Uncle.
Now can I finish my game?
Yes sure.
Best of luck.
Don't defeat him.
- Okay, Uncle, thank you.
- We won.
Here the municipality is defeated.
[Man laughs]
And now the builder is defeated.
Today I have to file
a petition in High Court.
I will try to get
the date for this month.
- Best of luck.
- All the best, papa.
- Mom, I am going. Bye.
- Have breakfast and then go.
I will get late.
Okay I will take this.
- Love you.
- Why are you getting nervous?
You will surely get visa.
Hail to Lord Ganpati.
Himansh...
wish him.
You will get it. Okay?
Bye.
[Door closes]
New look.
Are you going to see a girl?
- Visa interview.
- Oh, nice.
Saturday night
there is a play in Prithvi.
I have heard it is nice.
Do you want to go?
I am busy.
Why do you act pricey all the time?
Look, first there will be a play
then movie, dinner,
drinks, kiss and sex.
Then it will be time for me to go.
Then emotional drama,
crying to stop me.
Emotional blackmail.
Who wants it, right?
What an imagination you have? Wild.
Thank God you did not imagine
our marriage and children.
I am sorry.
Your building is
about to be demolished
and you are going to the US.
They all have created
their own problem.
And now they are trying
hard to solve this problem.
Offerings will be made.
People will pray to God
that it is not in our hands
so please come and make us
win this court case.
And you have problem
with God as well.
No, buddy. They are spending
so much on offerings and prayers.
Instead of that if they
would have hired a good lawyer
they would have won the case.
Why are you taking tension?
You will get another house on rent.
Yes, of course.
Landlords are always keen
to keep young and single girls.
With such great difficulty
I found this house.
How will I find it again?
I am dying to be
single and mingle alone.
You have such a great life. There's
no one to stop you. Full freedom.
You should have the change.
When it is my birthday
or I am having fever
then I remember mom and dad
and not freedom.
[Man chanting in Sanskrit]
[Vansh] As and when
people got scared
the people in the society started
showing a lot of faith in God.
Not only in God.
Everyone knew that only
one person can save them in court.
Birju, will we win this case?
My son will go and live in
his in-laws house with his family.
He cannot take me there.
If we lose
then I will have to go to Uganda
to my son leaving Pluto.
They are saying that
if we lose the case
then the marriage
will get cancelled.
If there is no house
then how will we have a baby?
They will leave me
in this old age home.
Don't worry.
No one has the daring
to throw us out of our homes.
Pluto will stay with his mother.
We will win this case.
You will get married. Don't worry.
Mohsin and you will become parents.
You have my word for it.
Stop worrying.
Thank you.
[Zulfiya sniffs]
[Exhales]
Hey, I got it.
I got my visa for America.
- What?
- Yes.
- Did you get it?
Show it to me.
[Cheering]
- Father, look at it.
- Congratulations.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Himansh, he has got the visa.
That is amazing.
It is very good, amazing.
Now I will just talk
to you in American accent.
Okay, Mom.
[All laughing]
[Himansh clears throat]
Papa, this case is
like world cup final.
You are the last batsman
at the crease.
You will have to hit
a century to win.
Stop this cricket commentary
and tell me clearly
what you want to say.
Will we win this case?
Do you have a doubt?
I am a little nervous.
Eat your food. [Clears throat]
Eat food.
I was suggesting that
if another lawyer was consulted
then the case would become stronger
Don't you have confidence on me?
I just have tension.
Like last time...
Say it clearly that
you don't have confidence on me.
Last batsman...
Why are you saying things
in such a twisted way?
- Father, have food.
- I am no more hungry.
[Sighs deeply]
What was the need
to talk while eating?
Those who do not have confidence
on themselves
cannot have on others too.
It is a matter of getting worried.
And only those people worry
who are emotional.
He will never understand.
Thank God I am not
emotional like him.
Stop it, Vansh.
Himansh, have food.
Ask your dear son to eat food.
I don't want to eat it.
Eat food. Don't do all this.
Vansh.
Himansh.
- Himansh.
- Hmm!
Till when will you both
go on with this drama?
Vansh, apologize to father.
Why should I apologize?
Himansh, you are elder
to him so forgive him.
- Let him apologize first.
- Say it.
For what should I apologize?
What have I done?
You always support him.
He does not want to apologize.
[Door closes]
How long can a person
be angry with his son?
I really need some fresh air.
Where are you going now?
I am going with my friends.
Please don't wait for me.
Hey...
- [Door closes]
- [Muffled bellowing]
My family is like a ticking bomb.
Anyone can blast anytime.
The house is no more a home
but has become a war zone.
Shh! [Kisses]
All efforts to rescue from
that war zone have started.
How?
Tan tan tan tana!
With a divorce of Rishi and me.
What the fuck is this?
We had decided that
you would divorce him.
I started the deal. Sign on it.
We will get it signed
from Rishi as well.
Then you are free. [Kisses]
Not we but you had decided.
[Sighs] You know I need some
sort of commitment.
I am not a spare part
that you can use temporary.
I want a long term commitment.
Abhay, try to understand
my situation.
Everything is so complicated.
I cannot give any commitment now.
[Sighs]
- I get it.
- What?
Everyone in college was right in saying
that Hina is a gold digger.
- What the f**k?
- It's true. Admit it.
You dumped me and got
married to Rishi. Why?
Just because he is fucking rich.
- Shut up. Okay?
- He might remain f**k all
and I maybe caring but
you will never leave him for me.
Because love does
not give security.
For that you need money.
Lots of f*****g money.
F**k you, man.
[Door slams shut]
F**k up. F**k, Rishi.
F**k all of these boys.
Focus on yourself in the time
that you have got.
What should I focus now on?
You were an amazing MC.
With your hosting skill you would
put the entire college
festival on fire.
You sacrificed a
good career for Rishi.
Who will now give me a job of a MC?
Don't talk like losers.
Did you try?
Call up event managers.
Just get back into the game.
Just be who you are.
You are kickass.
I am elder to you
but you are intelligent.
From childhood I am saying so.
[Chuckles]
Shall we go home?
For one more fighting round.
Where do you want to stay?
On the footpath.
Somehow we will have to stay there.
Vansh, where is my coat?
I am getting late.
[Himansh] Yes, Father.
Here it is.
You will surely
win this case, Father.
I have more confidence in you
than in myself.
I am getting late.
[Man chanting in Sanskrit]
Here also.
- [Cheering, applauding]
- We will win this case.
Your honor, I agree
that illegal and
unauthorized construction
is a grave offence
and should be punished.
But your honor,
those builders should be punished
who constructed the building
going against the law.
Action should be taken
against municipal officers
because they did
not take action on time.
That is why I feel the
decision of the session court
is quite arbitrary
and it should be quashed.
And we should be given a stay order
against this impending demolition.
Your honor, I request
the honorable court
not to grant a stay order.
In last 22 years
municipal corporation sent
show call notice many times.
But neither the builder nor
the residents of Kalakriti society
took it seriously.
That means
their intentions are malafide.
Our intentions are
only to save ourselves.
What is our fault, your honor?
Your mistake is your negligence.
I agree with you. All I ask is
is the quantum of
punishment justified? Is it fair?
There are old people, children
and pregnant ladies
in this building.
Therefore all I ask of this
honorable court is compassion.
Your honor,
if court starts showing compassion
then no criminal will be punished.
They are not criminals, your honor.
We are not criminals.
It is quite clear
that who is a criminal.
I once again, your honor,
beg to this honorable court
to grant a stay order
on this pending demolition.
So you agree that Kalakriti
society building is illegal.
Your honor, I have told you that...
Shh!
If building is illegal
then demolition will take place.
The order of the session
court will be maintained.
The court gives
two months time
to the residents of Kalakriti
society to vacate their homes.
The court gives order
to Municipal Corporation
to demolish Kalakriti society.
Thank you, your honor.
Thank you.
Okay, so we are starting
this new program under CSR.
For people living
below the poverty line.
We will give them limited
number of free tickets
who are in need to travel
in an emergency.
Got it.
I am thinking this department should be
headed by our very own Mr. Sethi.
Mr. Sethi. Mr. Sethi...
- I'm sorry. There is an emergency.
- We are not done yet.
There is an emergency.
I have to leave.
- But the meeting's still going on.
- Sorry.
Great. This time everyone
has given on time.
[Cell phone chimes]
You did a good job
in collecting money.
What happened?
Hurry up.
[Woman]
Tell us what happened in the court?
Do you need water, father?
[Woman 2]
Vandana, where is Himansh?
Uncle, what happened in the court?
He should have been here.
[Motwani]
It is the decision of the judge.
We have no other option.
[Overlapping chatters]
[Girl] Catch her.
Mother!
What hospital?
Shastri! Shastri!
No, no.
Vedant Heart Care.
He'll get 5-star treatment
at Vedant Heart Care.
I know the doctors personally.
I'll handle it, don't worry.
I am here.
We'll take care of everything.
Don't worry.
[Hina panting]
[Hina] What are they saying?
We are also waiting.
See, the reports are showing that
both the arteries of your father
are blocked.
We need to do
an angioplasty immediately.
So do it.
What is the problem?
The fourth-generation stent
required for the operation
is not available.
Should we shift him
to another hospital?
That won't help.
There is shortage of it
in the entire city, Mr. Sethi.
- How is that possible?
- Right.
Ever since government
dropped the prices of stents
distributors reduced supply.
You mean, the patients suffer
in their tiff?
What about grandpa?
Look, we are trying to get
spare stents from other hospitals.
But until then, we'll have to put
him on anti-platelet medication.
And when we get the stents,
I'll let you know.
Till then,
we'll shift him in the ward, okay?
Hold on a minute.
Um... Nikhil, call up
Batra Hospital and find out.
Call your dad to speak
to his cardiologist.
And you two, call up other
hospitals and find out.
- Okay.
- Ashok.
Father-in-law had a heart attack.
- We're here.
- The cardiologist...
Stent! Stent!
Can you arrange it?
- Listen to me.
- Stent?
Do they have any spare...
- And nobody picks up!
- [Hriday] Fine.
This is why I hate this country.
I even told my brother
as he's a heart specialist.
Really?
There are no stents available
even at his hospital.
Give your father my regards.
They tried very hard,
in the court.
But the judge turned out
to be a rascal.
I should get going.
Hriday must be waiting.
[Vandana] Sure.
Thanks.
[Motwani] My husband
got really sick last night.
- His BP shot up.
- Oh boy!
I gave him two tablets
and finally he was better.
The stress of the house, moreover
the BMC put up another notice.
They'll come here in a few days
to disconnect power supply.
What have you all decided?
What will you do?
Where will you go?
Chirag has been telling us
to go to him, to Toronto.
But starting everything from square
one in a new place... Not possible!
Tch! I know.
Dear, you and Mohsin
should shift immediately.
Stress is not good for you
in this state.
Absolutely right.
But Aunty, where do we shift to?
We took a loan to buy this house.
We're still paying the EMI.
Where do we get
a second home from?
[Zulfiya sighs]
- Vandana.
- Hmm?
What did you decide?
[Mrs. Motwani]
Okay, Aunty, we should get going.
Okay, bye.
- Take care, Zulfiya.
- [Door opens]
Thanks.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Okay.
[Door closes]
[Sighs deeply]
Vansh.
Let's pack our bags.
Come on.
Get the suitcase down.
Coming.
[Door opens]
[Machine beeping normally]
Did they find stents?
Doctors are trying.
Okay.
You should go.
Sure?
- Eat something.
- Sure.
Himansh.
Are you okay, Dad?
Dear, listen to me.
Among the two brothers
you are the older one.
Then act like one, okay?
Swallow your anger.
Hmm?
Okay, Dad.
Get some rest.
- Did you fill the bag?
- Yes.
Have you taken everything?
- Undies, new toothbrush...
- Yes.
Bathroom slippers.
Clothes, check. Footwear, check.
Undies, check.
Toiletries, check. All check.
Wow! You have become
very organized.
[Sighs deeply]
Come on, social media.
Show your magic.
[Button clicks]
[Cell phone ringing]
Vansh!
Vansh, your phone!
[Vansh grunting]
Oh shit!
Is it dad?
[Tongue clicks]
Hello. Yes?
Yes, tell me.
Yes.
Yes, yes. One second.
We got the stents.
Yes, I did put it up.
Yes. Yes, sir.
I'm in Mumbai.
Ma'am, Dr. Tandon?
First floor, second cabin.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- [Woman] Don't worry, it's gas.
- There!
Ask him to take Digene
and he'll be fine.
No heart problem.
Hi, Doctor.
We found the stents.
- Really?
- Yeah.
How did you guys manage?
Ma'am, long live Twitter.
Long live my brainy brother.
- Hello.
- Strange.
Yeah, one second.
Which ones?
We need PMS
fourth-generation 5.5mm.
- PMS fourth-generation 5.5mm.
- Correct.
I'll transfer the money right now,
when will we get it?
Tomorrow.
It's too risky.
It's too late.
- We need it today.
- He's in Delhi.
Try. It can't wait till tomorrow.
I'll call you back.
F**k.
If we take the earliest flight
to Delhi...
We won't reach before late night.
Swati Chauhan.
- What Swati Chauhan?
- Swati bloody Chauhan.
Your classmate?
- Yeah.
- The hot Swati?
She's happily married.
Airhostess
Mumbai-Delhi-Mumbai sector.
What!
Hi, Swati.
Where are you?
- She's in Delhi.
- No!
Yes!
Yes, Dad. Did you get
the account details?
- Transfer the money right away.
- Okay, fine.
Yes, Swati.
So, he'll be at T3 terminal
in front of The Mocha Coffee Shop.
Yeah. I'll pick it up
from here.
- Where are they?
- What happened?
Just trying.
She's not picking up.
[Vehicle approaching]
- Is she the one?
- This one.
- Hi.
- Hi, Swati.
- Hi!
- Hi! Thank you so much.
Good seeing you.
[Door opens]
All good! All good!
He's absolutely fine.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
[Doctor]
You should thank these kids.
It's unbelievable how they arranged
for stents in just one day.
- Long live Twitter, right?
- Yeah.
Long live my brainy brother.
[Doctor] Of course! Of course!
Right.
Well, you all may rest. Anyway he's
going to be in the ICU for 2 days.
- Okay?
- Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Very good.
Learn something from him.
- [Chuckles]
- He also helped.
I know.
Okay, you all should go home.
I'll stay here.
No, no, I should stay.
You all should go.
No! You should listen
to me sometimes.
[Chuckles]
Go home, everyone.
- Come on.
- Come.
Let's go.
- Come on.
- Come.
[Sighs]
You two should go ahead.
Take the car. I...
will come with Vansh.
[Himansh] In September, 2010
I put a final lock here
on Sethi Travels.
So today is like
an anniversary?
I come here every year
on 23rd September.
Every time I look at this shop,
I'm reminded of my past.
That excitement, the chatter
of the many employees I had.
Day in and day out, talking
to the airline executives on call.
Making package tours,
be it for Switzerland or Bangkok.
Sethi Travels would be packed
with customers.
Does mom know that you come here?
Some pain is very personal.
Then why are you
sharing with me?
Since you're going to America.
You made the right decision
of not returning the money.
You are practical.
I wish I can ever be practical.
It's okay, Dad.
You're fine.
I could not modify
my business with time.
So I started incurring losses
one after the other.
I never let go of my staff.
Because they were family
for you, right?
They were not just staff for you.
These emotions bring you down.
You are not emotional,
you'll do well in life.
Take this. I deposited
a top-up of 2 lakh rupees in Forex.
No, Dad, this is not needed.
Uncle...
I know he gave you money.
But I'm your father.
You are unbelievable!
You don't talk for a month and...
then you make me emotional.
[Cell phone ringing]
You customized this?
No, you get these with your name
on it in the market.
Obvio!
[Chuckles]
- Nice.
- Hey.
I spoke to Epic Events.
Most probably,
I'll have a gig this weekend.
Thanks for pushing me.
Well done, tiger!
Okay, don't get too senti.
We're getting late, come.
I'm senti?
[Tongue clicks]
Vansh!
Keep this box.
- What is this?
- Thepla.
Mom, the custom officers won't
allow this thinking it's smuggling.
If they don't allow, eat it there.
Keep the box safely.
Dad, it's locked.
Yes, I'll put one more.
Many thefts happen at the airport.
What is there to steal in it?
Instant noodles and Thepla.
Keep the keys safely.
- Come, let's go.
- Shall we?
One minute.
Himansh, water!
Mom, I'll miss my flight.
What are you doing?
[Vansh] Mom! Come on out now.
[Hina] Come on, guys.
Selfie time.
- One selfie together.
- Okay.
Dad, smile.
[Clicks]
Dear, you wanted to leave
without saying goodbye?
No, Aunty.
I was looking for you.
Really? [Chuckles]
Bye!
Focus only on your studies.
Don't worry about your parents.
We'll take care of them.
And when you meet him
after two years
he'll speak with an accent.
And a hot blonde next to him.
Just as my son did
once he went to Toronto.
Anyway, we're getting late.
The contractor is waiting...
- Oh, yes! Right!
- ...in the society office. Come.
- All the best, dear.
- Bye! Come on.
- The car is here.
- Bye!
- Take care.
- Thank you.
Hello.
[Car door closes]
- Bless you.
- Greetings.
- You took everything, right?
- Yes.
- Take care of each other.
- Okay.
Just as your father
takes care of mine.
Okay?
[Boot opens]
Leaving?
Yeah.
You never took me on a coffee date.
[Boot closes]
Send a friend request.
I'll accept it if I feel like.
I'll send it if I feel like.
[Chuckles]
Take care.
[Car door closes]
Keep updating me on grandpa's
health, on WhatsApp.
[Vansh] Take care.
Take care.
Bye.
Take care, tiger!
[Car door closes]
[Man 1] Come on, send the bulldozer
over there.
[Indistinct chattering]
Santosh, why is the car
stopped since so long?
Ma'am, there's traffic jam
right ahead.
At this hour?
It's the PM's visit today,
so they're clearing all of this.
They should be cleared. They've
built illegal huts everywhere.
[Kids crying]
[Women crying]
[Man blowing whistle]
[Woman wailing]
[Woman] We're ruined!
Excellent reports.
Very nice.
If the reports are so good,
please discharge me.
We will do that.
Don't worry.
Excuse me.
Grandpa, all okay?
Gosh! What okay?
Nothing is okay.
Yeah, yeah, all good.
He just needs to rest.
Okay, thank you.
[Sighs]
- Vansh!
- Hi, Dad.
Did you miss the flight...
Vandana!
He refused to go in.
He didn't even check in.
Didn't check in?
What... What is this?
- Why did you...
- There is such a huge crisis here.
How could I leave?
The college fees
had been paid in dollars...
Dad, the fees
will be fully refunded.
Yes, we'll lose just a little
over the airplane tickets.
Little? What do you mean
by little?
The college authorities
will save me the seat.
Until the crisis of our home
is solved, I'll stay with you all.
After that,
in the next semester, I'll be...
Vansh, do you know
the value for money?
Is it more than
the value for family?
No, right?
Right?
Shall I meet grandpa?
Hi, Grandpa.
- [Vansh] Surprise!
- Wow!
[Brij] You... You came back?
Yes!
- W-What...
- I didn't like it without you.
Huh?
How did that happen?
Did you see?
He's exactly like your son.
[Vansh] I always told myself
that I'd never be like dad.
Well, guess what?
I'm his carbon copy!
I'm the same from within
what I would call him.
Emotional fool.
[Man 1] I don't know
what's going to happen.
Look, we have just two options.
First, we vacate our houses and
hand over the keys to municipality.
Or give a last try. Supreme court.
We have already lost the case
in session court and high court.
What can we do in Supreme court?
I have one house and
we will do everything to save it.
Just think that we will have
to go to Delhi again and again.
Hotel expenses will be incurred.
We will have to pay lawyer's fees.
How will we manage it?
The fees of Supreme court's
lawyers for one hearing
is more than what
we earn in a year.
Then should we buy another house.
Mr. Bolkar, do we have
money to buy another house?
Mr. Bolkar's son
is in excise department.
He will buy another house.
What do you man to say?
Is my son corrupt?
- How can you say this?
- Why are you saying this?
What are you saying?
This is not the time to fight.
Mr. Aggarwal did
not have that intention.
Can't we speak anything?
Calm down.
Sex! Sex! Sex! Sex!
Sex!
- Vansh.
- [Vansh] They don't listen.
Thank you.
Thank you for your attention.
Will we get a solution
by fighting amongst ourselves?
Look, the point is that
nothing will happen by
just going to Supreme court.
What does that mean?
Aunty, why will court, government
and municipality listen to us?
Neither we are vote bank
nor do we have any power.
No one listens to a common man
in this country.
But if we have public support
then we have chance
to save our homes.
Son, sit down.
It is not a child's play.
Father, you all tried
but nothing happened.
At least listen to
what he wants to say.
- Vansh, you continue to speak.
- At least listen to him.
- Come on, speak.
- Speak, Son.
All I am saying is
that nothing happens
in this country
without public drama.
Even in Nirbhaya case till
the public did not hit the road
rape laws did not change.
What should we do, buddy?
Shall we do hunger
strike at Jantar Mantar?
There are many other ways. We will
make our story reach to people.
We will tell the entire country
as to what is happening with us.
We will tell them that
whatever is happening with us
can also happen with them.
How will we do this?
- Leave that on us.
- Yes.
We will shout so much that
they will have to listen to us.
Yes.
[Pawan] Vansh, don't let it fall.
My father will kill me.
What a mess?
[Mohsin] They have made
this a Jurassic park.
It looks like a government office.
That's why
they're not able to do anything...
[Vansh] They have created the
problem so now we have to solve it.
[Mohsin] Let's be positive.
We have to do it. Come on friends.
Social media, TV coverage.
What else?
Banners, pamphlets, newspapers.
WhatsApp messages,
blogs, group messages,
Street plays, newspaper fliers...
[Woman 1] Who reads it nowadays?
How did '#MeToo' do so well? They
must have done something right.
Of course.
Because men supported it. Simple.
- No, buddy.
- Men never supported it.
[Vansh] It worked because it
was hard-hitting campaign.
Hey guys.
Hi, Vaibhav.
Can I be of any help?
Are you free today?
Did Mr. Bachchan leave you today?
- Pawan, what are you doing?
- [Woman 2] What's up, Vaibhav?
I am just like you guys.
If this building breaks
then where will I go and stay?
Even I am scared like you all.
Vaibhav, just come.
We will help each other.
Grab a chair.
You will not fit
into one so get 10-12
- We can use his tweeter followers.
- Exactly.
How many tweeter
followers do you have?
- 18,000
- That's it.
Your attitude is like
that of having one million.
[Vansh] He is already seven feet tall.
How much more will you pull him?
- Click a photograph first.
- Okay.
[Vaibhav] Guys,
please look serious.
- [Hina] Stop smiling.
- Actually.
I think you should
use hash tag also.
We do not have hash tag.
Kala Kriti Society...
But what Kala Kriti society.
Justice for Kala Kriti.
- That is too high society.
- Justice...
Bachao Kala Kriti.
Bachao is too...
I know. It should be spunky.
Hash tag KKS
It is not a cricket team. KKS
- Terrible.
- Save, save.
Water is saved but not society.
Save Kala Kriti Society,
it's good one.
- It is good.
- Actually good one.
- Save Kala Kriti.
- Hash tag Save Kala Kriti.
[Mohsin] Save it.
It is a god stand, guys.
Yes. Save Kala Kriti.
Not bad.
[Woman 1]
Done. Let's have tea now.
[Man 1 on TV] 23 children.
You are the hospital head.
No TV channel covered our case.
- Any Retweets?
- Not really.
We need a strong emotional
picture for our social media page.
The demolition types.
Something like this.
- No.
- No. We need a face.
A sad face whose house
is being demolished.
Drama, you like that.
[Man 2 on TV]
Concerned doctor?
23 children. What will you tell
to their parents?
The concerned doctor
has been arrested.
So callus is your answer.
If we come on the
channel of this person
then we will trend
in the entire nation.
[Man 1 on TV]
Chief minister himself...
Do you have his number?
I can find it.
Oh shit. I got to go, guys.
Where?
I have my first gig.
- Be successful.
- All the best.
Bye.
How is this one?
- No, buddy. What is this?
- Show me.
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's put his photograph. He seems
to be like a refugee these days.
Very funny. You will understand
when your engagement will break.
- Aww!
- [Smooches]
What about this?
It is great.
- Vansh, no.
- Why?
- It is picture of Syrian war.
- I know.
Because it is unethical.
There is full emotion in it.
Do whatever you want to.
I don't care.
Are we saving our homes
or becoming ethical?
Like it or not? I like it.
- I vote for it.
- Me too.
What do you guys say?
[Vaibhav] I am up for it.
- Sorry.
- Unbelievable.
Majority wins.
It is a good picture. It will work.
[Yawning]
[Sighs]
Oh.
Hello, Himansh,
Hina has not come back yet.
It is 1 o'clock.
I tried.
The phone is not reachable.
[Door opens]
She has come. Go to sleep, Himansh.
Hina, you are so late.
[Both laugh]
- Was it good?
- It was very, very good.
10,000 bucks.
For you.
It is yours. So keep it.
Mummy, keep it.
[Chuckles]
Oh God.
You know I had forgotten that
I enjoy anchoring so much.
- Did you eat food?
- Yes.
Do you know that
they have promised me
to give me another gig next month.
I am so excited.
I am calling since morning.
Please make me talk
to Somen Chatterjee once.
Just once.
Just for two minutes. That's all.
Hello.
What the f**k.
What happened?
Nothing. I am trying from landline
and still they are
disconnecting the phone.
Am I selling credit card? They
disconnect the phone so easily.
[Man 1] Call up the secretary.
I am calling the secretary itself,
Who else am I talking to?
You are just playing carom there.
Do some work?
The problem is
that people like Somen
think themselves to be Shah Rukh.
Our parents are the problem
who decided to buy
this house 22 years ago.
And today we are in trouble.
We do not go on a date
without searching
about the girl on internet.
And they bought a house.
We should sue our parents
for ruining our future.
- I will get a lawyer for free.
- [Cell phone ringing]
Put few more extra
sections from my side.
Yes, Mom. Okay, fine.
Hey, your drunkard
has come with his father.
[Harish] Rishi was staying in rehab
for last 2 months.
Now he does not touch alcohol.
He has thrown the entire
stock that was at home.
I asked him to keep some for me.
[laughs]
It's all good now. Come home now.
- I want divorce.
- What?
Please give another chance.
Look, dear,
marriage is not like a job.
That you do it today
and leave it tomorrow.
Himansh, make her understand.
This is my decision.
What will he explain to me?
I am sorry.
I promise I will never drink again.
They are young.
They do not have experience.
We are elder to them so
we should make them understand.
Yes.
Vandana.
If she is saying so then
she must have said it
after giving it a thought.
[Harish] Your daughter is talking
about breaking the marriage
and you are not saying anything.
What kind of a father are you?
Mr. Harish, if I was
a dominating father
then I would have never
let Hina marry Rishi.
Let's go, Rishi.
Dad, wait. Let me talk to her.
If I talk to her
then she will agree.
Rishi, we are leaving now. Come on.
[Chuckles softly] Bye.
[Door opens]
Hi, Uncle. Snacks?
I have been insulted
so I am not hungry.
Make them eat the snacks.?
[Door closes]
[Chuckles softly]
Papa, snacks.
I will keep them inside.
Life changes a lot after marriage.
Isn't it? But no one tells.
Look at me.
I don't understand that
what has happened with me.
We will not get abortion done.
What will we do then? Will
we sleep with the child at home?
We will stay on rent.
Okay calculate.
The rent of the new house,
EMI of this house
hospital expenses,
medicines, salary of the maid.
And I will have to take
maternity leave for a year.
There will be many expenses
and the salary will be only yours.
How can we afford a child?
Everything is so
uncertain right now.
How can we bring another
life in this world?
Into this chaos.
See, this is the
situation right now.
What if the situation changes?
What do you mean?
What if our house is saved?
The society is making
an appeal in the Supreme Court.
That will take time.
We have the time.
It is only 10th week now.
We can wait for a month or two.
Okay, we will wait for 1-2 months.
What if the Supreme Court
still gives the same verdict?
What's up guys?
Oh!
Now we have come. We will
not go even if you ask us to leave.
- Correct.
- No chance.
What are you guys having?
Everything is empty here.
We are having a conversation.
Intense. At least you drink.
Hello Mr. Chatterjee.
Come this way.
I have a table reserved for you.
I will catch hold of him now.
No, Vansh, this is not
the right place to talk.
Don't listen to him.
Desperate times call
for desperate value. You go.
- Come on go.
- Don't. Don't.
Hi, guys.
Good evening.
Hi. Hope you are having fun.
Few days ago I found Alladdin's
lamp and I rubbed it.
And Gini came out and asked me
as to what I want.
Do you want a Ferrari car?
I replied, "Hey brother, 28% GST
80/-per liter petrol...
Are you mad?"
[Laughter]
Gini told me to take 100 million
dollars loan with no interest.
I said not possible.
If I take loan then I'll
have to leave the country.
[Laughter]
I love this country.
Gini asked me as to what I wanted.
I told him to get me
a 2 BHK flat in Mumbai.
He looked into my eyes
and said that if I had a flat
then would I be staying in a lamp.
[Laughter]
This is not a joke. But a reality.
My house, our house
where our family stays
is about to be demolished.
For last 22 years we
are staying in that house.
I was born in that house.
But now that house is...
why?
Because the government has
declared that the building is illegal.
If someone knows about a good
footpath or flyover then tell me.
Not under construction.
Ready to move in.
We do not have time.
Low maintenance, free parking. View
should be good. View is important.
If you cannot help us
to buy new houses
then at least help us
to save our existing houses.
Especially you,
Mr. Somen Chatterjee.
You are Gini and we are Aladdin.
Our voice needs your loud speaker.
Please sir, if you could
raise this issue on your channel
then it'd be a great help.
That would really help us, sir.
If you guys want to help us
then you can also go on
social media and like our page.
It is called hashtag
Save Kala Kriti.
Maybe your likes
will save our homes.
That's it. Thank you, guys.
[Applauding]
Wait, wait! That was not bad.
- Thank you.
- What is your name?
Vansh Sethi.
- Whatever you said is true. Is it?
- of course.
Do one thing. You take
my card and call my secretary.
Maybe we can do a debate
on this topic.
I am not promising anything.
It may or may not happen. But...
Mann Ki Baat...
You did it.
Why didn't they take
you for the interview?
You also wanted to appear on the show.
Motwani will handle everything.
Vandana.
[Somen on TV] Good evening and
welcome to 9 o'clock debate.
Today we are focusing on illegal
constructions across our cities.
Hello, Rohit,
Can you stream News Studio channel in Canada?
Your father is going to be on TV.
...on the Kala Kriti
Housing society.
The housing society...
- Increase the volume.
- ...is in trouble.
We have with us Vansh Sethi,
Mr. Mukul Motwani.
- Should've worn a better T-shirt.
- [Vansh] Thank you.
The high court has declared
that your society is illegal.
There is an eviction notice.
What is the problem?
The problem is that
we have bought these houses
I mean our parents have bought
these houses
with hard earned money.
But everyone buys houses
That can't be an excuse.
Yes, it's not an excuse.
Over 20-22 years, these families
have been living here.
Suddenly there is a notice
and we are asked to leave.
But does that mean that
they can avoid justice?
- No.
- Brother,
actually we are saying that
- this is injustice.
- It's injustice?
Yes. I mean we are honest citizens.
We are paying our taxes on time.
- [Somen laughing]
- All. Everything.
Sorry what did you say?
- We are paying our taxes on time.
- Before that.
- Yes.
Honest citizens.
- [Laughs] Honest citizens.
- [Mukul] Yes.
Really?
I would like to request
my producer to put up a photo
of this housing society.
Social media page please.
Viewers, focus on the photograph
of the social media page.
The photo they have
is of Syrian Civil war.
Is this your social media page?
Hashtag, Save Kala Kriti Society.
Do you use a photograph
from a war torn country
and trying to pass it
out as photo of your society?
We are not trying to say...
Aren't you ashamed?
Aren't you ashamed of yourselves?
To manipulate the public like that
into sympathizing with your cause.
which by the way is wrongful
in the first place.
Sir, we are not
trying to manipulate.
No, one second.
What I am saying is that
if you have done something illegal
then you should suffer for it.
Which is why I am
starting a new hash tag
and my hash tag is Demolish
Kala Kriti Society.
Not save Kala Kriti society
which is what these people want.
By doing things illegal.
I am saying hashtag
Demolish Kala Kriti Society.
- Break down this society.
- Oh God.
We have not done anything illegal.
Don't interrupt me.
Please send me
your tweets and opinions
on hashtag Demolish
Kala Kriti Society.
I will see you after the break.
Brother, you've got to understand
our point of view.
We are not trying
to mislead anybody.
- We came here for public support.
- Yes, I am with your cause.
- No, but you did not...
- We have to speak in debate.
It is not even our fault, sir.
The FSI gave permission
to builder for five floors.
The builder
ended up making 7 floors.
So the builder has done
something illegal.
Yes.
- You guys are innocent.
- Correct.
[Man 1]
We are going live in 5 seconds.
- 5.
- I'll tell.
[Man 1] 4, 3...
Welcome back from the break.
We are discussing the issue of
the illegal Kala Kriti society.
And I asked about your tweets
and opinions on this issue.
And we have got literally
hundreds of tweets.
The first one is from Purohit 2016.
And Mr. Purohit says
if they are criminals
then they should
suffer like criminals.
- Sir, we are not criminals.
- Don't interrupt.
I completely agree with that.
If you have done something criminal
then you have to face the law.
And we have got other tweets
as well coming in.
Demolish Kala Kriti
Society is trending, guys.
He says that
they should get no respite.
I agree with them.
No respite for them.
They should face
full force of the law.
I think that is what
India is saying today.
And I hear you loud and clear.
Thank you for joining
me on this debate.
Coming after right after
the break another debate.
This time we discuss
I will see you after the break.
[Vansh sighs deeply]
That went well, right?
I will just go to loo
and coming back.
Switch off the lights.
It will get cool.
[Mukul] No problem.
We at least tried.
[Siren blaring]
[Car doors open and closes]
- Disconnect water connection.
- What is the scene?
Court has ordered
to disconnect your
water, electricity
and gas connections.
How can you disconnect in this way?
Sir, we have not
received the notice.
How many times we will give notice?
How many times?
What are you saying?
We will file a complaint
against you.
- Right.
- Come on do complain.
Whom do you want to complaint?
Come on do it.
- No...
- Calm down.
Look, you are committing
a crime by interfering
in government work. And not us.
We're appealing
in the Supreme Court.
Supreme Court?
Go to the terrace and
disconnect water connection.
It is Diwali after two days
and then you can do your job.
Diwali or Eid?
But we have to work every day.
Disconnect water connection.
[Indistinct chattering]
Get aside.
We have to work every day.
Listen to me, sir.
- Don't touch me.
- Sorry sir.
Sir. Sir.
We are at
the Kala Kriti society today.
There has been some chaos
between the residents and...
- Sir, please wait for a minute.
- Disconnect water connection.
- Don't touch me.
- Sir, please listen to me.
- Let us do our work.
- Please, listen to me sir.
- Please.
- Hurry up.
Move aside.
- There are children staying here.
- Many things need to be done.
- There are old staying here.
- Please understand.
- It is court's order.
- 32.
- Okay.
Please, sir.
Please listen to me, sir.
Tell me the number.
Hurry up.
Many things need to be done.
Listen to me.
- Please sir, take care of him.
- One minute wait.
What can I do?
Building is illegal.
Listen to me, Inspector.
Sir, what are you doing?
What is this, sir?
- [Door bell ringing]
- No. No.
[Door bell ringing]
Tell me.
We have come to disconnect
gas connection.
We have to disconnect
What happened, Inspector?
[Man 1] We have court's order
to disconnect gas connection.
Let us do our work.
Call up Mrs. Nirmala.
What are they doing, Mother?
[Man 2] Nirmala,
they are cutting gas connection.
It is court's order.
We will have to do it.
They are saying
it is court's order.
[banging]
Pluto.
[Knocking on door]
No one will say anything. It is
court's order so don't interfere.
Try to understand.
What are you doing?
- Hurry up and disconnect it.
- What are you doing?
How can you enter
someone's house like this?
Don't turn it off.
How dare you touch my wife?
- It is court's order.
- Leave him.
- But how dare you touch her.
Why are they shouting there?
- Go and see.
- What happened, Mr. Sethi?
Quiet!
- Quiet!
- Leave him.
Please, I request.
- Leave me.
- Listen to me.
How dare you slap my son?
Quiet.
Everyone keep quiet
or else I will fire.
Take him out.
Arrest him.
Listen to me.
Take them away.
What have we done?
I will not spare you.
Come fast.
Hurry up.
Don't push him.
Put them behind bars.
- Sir, please listen to me.
- Keep quiet.
- Put them behind bars.
Why are you putting us behind bars?
[Man 1] I went to disconnect
their gas connection
but he raised his hands on me.
- [Woman 1] File the report.
- Okay.
- Sit down.
- Okay, we will sit.
They are sitting there. Himansh.
Hey, who are you all?
- Who are you?
- Madam, please release them.
Madam, he has BP and heart problem.
We will pay the amount of bail.
Please, madam.
This is non bailable offence.
After Diwali when the court
opens then get their bail done.
Madam, they belong to
good family and are educated.
They are not criminals.
He raised a hand on police officer.
They seem to be true criminals.
Madam, by mistake he touched you.
Madam, we apologize on their
behalf. Please release them.
Please don't create chaos here.
Don't create chaos here.
- Madam, please listen to me.
- Madam, can't bail happen?
- Madam, can't we bail them out?
- Madam, please come outside.
Why are you doing this?
- Poonam.
- Vandana.
Poonam.
Himansh... Vansh.
At least let us meet them.
Mom, Rishi... Rishi's father
is very influential.
He can help us.
Few days ago you asked for divorce
and now you will ask for help.
What will they think?
What kind of people are we?
Mother, to save them
is more important
or what they will
think is more important.
Listen, what do you think
of yourself? [Slaps]
Will you tease her?
[Slaps]
Let her talk to her father-in-law.
Yes. All these rules
and law are for us.
Influential people get
their work done quickly.
Let her try, please.
Come on. Tease in front of me.
So, you have come here
to ask help from me.
And not to stay back in this house.
They want help from us
and not relationship.
Look, I can help them
to get released.
I just have to
make 2-4 phone calls.
But in return of that,
will you come back to Rishi?
You are keeping a condition.
Just as you are
thinking about your son
we are also thinking about our son.
Brother, we had come here to
ask for a favor and not do a deal.
Let's go, Hina.
[Hina] Uncle, none of your contacts
and influence is working.
Father and Vansh will
have to stay in jail all night.
Okay, I will call you later.
My battery is dying.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello, I am sorry I could
not send tiffin to you today.
Some problem is going
on in our society.
In the mean time please
make alternative arrangement.
I will start soon. Thank you.
Hello, Nirmala aunty, you said
that you would talk to the lawyer.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
During young days
once I had gone to jail.
Really?
Neighbor Khosla
said bad words to mom.
Father and I went to
his house with a sword.
In those days we had
a sword in our house.
- Sword. Wow!
- Yes.
Then?
Police made a case and put father
and me behind bars for two days.
Oh!
It is the tradition
of our family that
father and son duo is
behind bars together.
It is a genetic disorder.
[Chuckles]
It was my fantasy.
[Hina] What?
Candle light dinner.
And you married the most
unromantic person of this world.
Your father is romantic
but in his own way.
Eat.
[Man 1] This is your food.
Have it, sir.
[Clears throat]
- Take it, Son.
- First you take.
You eat this as well.
It is not delicious so I eat it.
Don't become sentimental.
Eat it. I am having mine.
You will have trouble
in stomach at night
and no one will be able to sleep.
I am not hungry, dear.
[Scoffs]
You are a very bad actor. Eat it.
[Man 1]
Get up and four of you come out.
- What is this, sir?
- Come out.
- Father...
- Rishi.
[Woman] What is this, sir?
Why did you do like this?
Don't do it again.
Tell Mr. Shirke
that I have done it.
- Thank you, madam.
- There is nothing to be grateful.
Let's go.
Did you all have food?
Yes, five course
meal with champagne.
But, Son, how did
you get us released?
Uncle, you do not know my father.
Anyways, I think you
should talk to chief minister.
Something might work out.
Our MLA does not pay heed to us
then what will we talk to CM sir.
It will be done, Uncle.
When will dad's contact be of use?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[Bolkar] Such a sweet boy Rishi is.
Nowadays no one does for
their near and dear ones.
Thank you so much.
I am really sorry
for what dad said.
He shouldn't have.
I have explained to him
that our problem and
family problems are different.
Take care.
Thank you.
Bye.
[Door closes]
You are right but what can we do?
We are also helpless.
The government cannot
go against the court's order.
Sir, you have special powers.
By passing an ordinance in your
Vidhan Sabha (legislative assembly)
please authorize our society, sir.
[Chuckles]
There are many such
illegal buildings in Mumbai.
If I authorize one then we
will have to do each one of them.
Please do it, sir.
No one purposely
buys illegal houses.
With due respect, sir,
if government can legalize slum
built till 2000
then why not our houses.
Exactly.
Because we are not vote bank.
[Stammering]
He is trying to say that
you will only think of our welfare.
You are not trying to understand.
If I authorize your society
then anyone will construct illegaly
anywhere they feel like.
Due to this the fear of law will
be erased from builders' minds.
So you want to make us target
and set an example in the society.
You don't know what
you are talking about.
Look, only Supreme Court
can grant relief to you.
No, that we are trying, sir.
But if you could put in
a kind word from your end then...
Sir, at least you can get our gas
and electricity connections
reinstalled as a Diwali gift.
Sir, there are so many
lights and decorations here
but there is darkness in our homes.
That we are managing somehow but...
Look, Mr. Harish Shah is
friend of our party president
that is why I met you all.
But government cannot
do anything in this.
Goodbye.
Sir, Jalgaon's committee
is waiting for you, sir.
This is the file, sir.
Please.
Call up the office
and tell there is no electricity,
water and there is crisis at home.
Anyone will agree.
Vandana, I am already
in bad books of Karan.
I haven't been to the office
for so many days.
I will make Diwali offering, pamper
him and his anger will cool down.
You did not have a bath on Diwali.
While coming from hospital
I will have a bath.
You too have a bath there.
Where? In the hospital?
We have spent so much then
let us enjoy the privilege.
I will leave.
[Door closes]
- Happy Diwali.
- [Woman] Happy Diwali.
I am very late for prayers.
Actually, sir, that will not work.
Please activate it, madam.
I am already late.
- Sir, it will not be done.
- Why?
Karan sir has asked me
to give you this.
- What is this?
- [Woman] Sir, termination letter.
You did not inform before
taking leave for two days.
Boss is very angry.
Let me meet the boss.
[Woman] He has refused.
Can I call him?
- No, sir, he has refused.
- One time.
Please, Mr. Sethi.
Even I will lose my job.
Sir, your belongings.
Sir.
Happy Diwali.
Thank you.
[Vansh] Every morning
on WhatsApp forward messages
there is gratitude message.
Count your blessings.
Thank the universe.
F**k off.
The truth is that sometimes
life sucks so much
that there is nothing
to thank for.
- [Firecracker bursting]
- As it is today.
But on the most depressing Diwali
my mother finds a reason
to carry on.
Honestly her optimism
is exhausting.
Vansh, Hina, come.
Himansh, come and offer prayers.
By offering prayers will
Goddess Laxmi come home?
Will she give me keys to 3 bedroom
hall flat and ask me to have fun?
I have lost my job.
Your business got shut.
In few days we will
lose this house as well.
Why should we celebrate Diwali?
It is Diwali today
so let's celebrate Diwali.
Today we do not have anything.
Tomorrow we might
lose our house also.
But at least we are together.
Mom, nothing will
happen with pep talk.
Why don't you understand?
How will we run the house?
I will run the house.
I have earned 30,000 this month.
I will do more events
and earn money.
Papa, why are you
looking at me like this?
I know I am selfish,
detached types.
And are involved
in my problems only.
But can run the house as well.
Actually even I can get
a job worth 40,000.
Did you see?
We found a solution to the problem.
I don't know when will
you stop taking stress?
So many times I have explained
that it is not good for health.
Stop explaining me.
Come on let's offer prayers.
Vansh, play the religious
song on internet.
- Battery is dead, Mom.
- Even mine.
Sing with me.
[Chanting prayer]
It is too much.
Is this the time to come?
- I'm waiting...
- Sorry.
Where were you all?
Is everything fine?
- All is well.
- God promise.
- Leave all that. Let's play cards.
- Yes.
- It is Diwali.
- Did you bring money?
Let's play on credit this year
and next year with cash.
Okay, it is a loan till tomorrow.
Son, you are distributing wrong.
- Papa, you distribute.
- No, you do it.
I will distribute.
- You know it then do it.
- I will distribute.
You should have been
UN Peace Keeping Force.
Then who would be in
Sethi Peace Keeping Force.
Great.
This time I will win.
Everyone saw their cards.
Why did you all see?
No one is going to play blind?
[Childrens chattering]
- They had said 13 number.
- I think it is this one.
- Mr. Chaubey.
- Yes?
Greetings. Welcome.
- How are you?
- Is everything okay?
[Man on TV] Greetings.
You are watching News Express.
On one hand the entire
nation is celebrating Diwali
and there is complete darkness
in Mumbai's Kala Kriti society.
Can you please put this on charge?
Three days ago municipal
corporation officers...
Thank you.
...disconnected electricity, water
and gas supply to 120 households.
According to our
sources very soon
bulldozers will be
run over these houses.
- Sister...
- It was not needed.
Let's take you over
to our reporter Mithila
who is present
in Kala Kriti society.
Mithila. Can you tell us how
did these helpless people
pass this dark night?
Yes, Rajesh.
As you can see residents of Kala
Kriti society are really suffering.
Let us ask them
about their condition.
We have not had a bath
for last 2-3 days.
And we are feeling itchy as well.
Why are you asking children?
Ask us.
We pay lakhs of rupees as tax and
this is the way we are treated.
For last three days there
is no water in the house.
Gas supply was disconnected.
Look at our condition. We have not
had a bath for last three days.
We have not been
able to cook food.
Do we look like living in slums?
Our maid is better than us.
She stays in slum but
at least has a bath every day.
You know Mrs. Srivastava
is very frank.
Yes.
- But she is not bad at heart.
- That's true.
We are leaving
this place and going.
We cannot take so much stress.
People are falling
sick in the society.
The government has won
and we have lost.
Now tell us what we should do.
- We are going from here.
- We will not stay here.
[Man 1] This is not to be done.
- We will leave.
- One minute. I'll just come back.
[Man 2]
We don't have drinking water.
[Indistinct chattering]
I hope you will not be in trouble.
No, madam, we will manage.
Take it.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you. Okay, we will leave.
I will help you.
Please take your phone.
[Himansh]
We want to ask the government...
that why is it doing this with us.
There is only one reason behind it.
All laws are being imposed
on common man like us.
I want to know that when will law
arrest those corrupt politicians
who have built their
homes on illegal land.
Go to them. Seek answer from them.
Why are only we answerable?
You can see that people
are quite offended.
I want to ask a question.
We pay electricity bill,
water bill and property tax.
When we pay property tax
for this building
then how can it be illegal?
You do something.
Media can do so much.
People are really offended here.
[Indistinct shouting]
Government! Down! Down!
[Girl] Government! Down! Down!
He is doing a lot
of hard work for you.
Let him do as much hard work
as he wants. But I want divorce.
I am shifting tomorrow morning.
Yes, you should.
I have a lot of things.
Will you help me to pack up?
My dear Kala Kritians,
thank you for the contribution
you all have given.
Thank you very much.
We have arranged this dinner
with money contributed by you all.
We have appointed a new lawyer.
He will file an appeal
in Supreme Court.
As soon as we get
the date of hearing
Himansh, Mr. Motwani
and I will go to Delhi.
One more thing.
Tomorrow morning water tanker
will come at sharp 7 o'clock.
Please be ready to take water.
Tomorrow morning at sharp 7.
As of now enjoy dinner.
Come, child.
Come, Uncle.
[Door opens]
Nice.
Thanks.
Close the door.
What should I do?
Pack those books.
Okay.
Where are you moving?
Did you find a house?
No, not yet. I am still finding.
I will stay at my aunt's place.
[Chuckles]
She is a monster.
What about you guys?
Where are you shifting?
I don't know.
It seems as if I had
gone for a movie with mom.
I was five years old.
Because of rush in the
theatre I left mom's hand.
Mom got lost.
I mean I got lost.
[Sighs]
For two minutes I got scared.
I could not understand.
I felt as if...
it's all over.
Even today I am feeling the same.
Where will we go? What will we do?
I am very scared, bro.
It's going to be fine.
Come, give me a hug.
Come.
[Vansh sniffles]
[Vansh sighs]
I had read on internet
that stress is reduced by mating.
Did it happen?
[Tongue clicks]
I will have to try again.
[Chuckles]
Do you want to go home, sir?
Do rest of the patients stay here?
[Laughing]
All his reports are good.
I will get his
discharge papers ready.
By evening you can take him home.
Okay. Take care.
- Thank you, doctor.
- [Woman] Okay.
Hurry up before they
change their mind.
- Yes, Father.
- Hurry up.
I will get the discharge
papers prepared.
Hurry up.
[Mukul] Everyone will get water.
Everyone please adjust.
What are you doing, Mr. Gehi?
Six buckets for one family.
This is not fair.
Two buckets are enough.
Pawan, make father understand.
Mrs. Gehi, please come.
Please don't waste water.
Come and have a bath at my place.
Easy.
Bolkar family,
you please come ahead.
Why are you filling
water from the tanker?
Get the tank filled with the pump.
Without light only
superman can pump water.
Please take water. Many
people still have to take water.
Mohsin...
Hey heroine,
how can you come in between?
- She is with me.
- Please calm down.
How can you stand queue directly?
She is pregnant and her
husband is standing in queue.
No problem.
I will take when my turn comes.
- No problem.
- It does not look good.
Hello, Himansh.
There is water problem here,
no electricity and so much stress.
You know it. What will we
do if father becomes unwell again?
Please move ahead.
[Vandana] Himansh,
we all want him to stay here.
But he needs rest.
If you say then shall
I talk to Hriday?
[Mukul]
Give buckets to the children.
[Woman] What can he do.
Water flowing speed is slow.
[Woman 2]
We had called for two tankers.
Where is the second tanker?
[Woman 3] Sweety, get two buckets.
And big one.
Himansh,
why am I not going to my home?
Papa, my house is yours too.
That is fine but I want
to sleep on my bed in my room.
What problem do you have?
I have no problem, Papa.
Even I can take care of you.
Look, Son,
I have friends in Kala Kriti
and the case is
also going on there.
I want to go home and you
are throwing me out of the house.
I can't understand.
Papa, who am I to throw
you out of the house?
What is the matter?
Already there is
so much stress there.
Municipality has disconnected
water, electricity and gas supply.
Now don't be stubborn
like children.
Disconnected electricity,
water and gas supply.
Why didn't you tell me?
What would have
happened if I told you?
What could you do?
Can you do one thing?
Become 100% fit, please.
I am fit.
Yes, Papa, you are completely fit.
But come to our home for few days.
Why are you being so partial to me?
After all even I am your son.
Come, let's go.
Come on.
[Anu] Sit carefully.
[Mr. Aggarwal] Okay, Mr. Srivastva.
Kitty, be careful.
Do not bang your head.
[Mr. Aggarwal] Bolkar sir.
Sister-in-law.
Mrs. Nirmala, forgive me
as your younger brother
if I ever made a mistake.
What are you talking? Take care.
Let's go. We are getting late.
See you soon.
- Bye, dear.
- Bye.
Mr. Aggarwal, Anu,
how can you go like this?
What do you mean?
[Sighs]
Today you are going.
Tomorrow Mr. Bolkar will
say that they are going
and then Mr. Srivastava.
If all go one by one then
who will save our
homes and fight for it.
But, sister, how is it possible
to stay here?
There is no water and electricity
here. Children cannot stay here.
You all are there to fight.
Why? Why should we be
responsible to save your home?
If we stand in unity
then municipality cannot
throw us out of our houses.
How can anyone fight alone?
Tell me.
[Mukul] Yes, Mr. Aggarwal.
If we fight this battle
together then we will surely win.
- Yes.
- Mr. Aggarwal, this is your home.
- You cannot go like this.
- But...
Everything will be fine
when all will be together.
- [Mukul] Come on, buddy.
- Sister is right.
We all will fight together.
Come, kitty. Come out.
- Absolutely.
- Everything will be fine.
Do you want to say anything, sir?
- What should I say?
- Anything, sir.
It will be a help
to Kala Kriti society.
We will upload on social media.
I have become old.
Let me stay comfortably in my home
otherwise my children
will leave me in old age home.
Mrs. Mehta.
This is not a pet but my child.
If we do not have homes
then where will I leave Pluto?
The government will not only
take our home but our baby as well.
It is a murder.
I request everybody...
to help us.
[Vansh] Thank you.
[Mohsin] Who will go next? Pawan...
Speak up.
My engagement broke.
I don't know whether
I will get married or not.
Mr. Chaubey.
I am not just a watchman
but a family.
The government is not
doing right with them.
Do you want to say anything,
Nirmala aunty?
We all are a family and
now everyone will be separated.
I do not want so much.
Give me 1500-2000.
Go to bank and
get passbook updated.
Just see how much is
there in FD's and savings.
We have enough that in case we need
to stay on rent then we will
be able to pay rent for few months.
Give me the ticket, Son.
Positive reactions are
coming on social media, Father.
- Everything will be fine.
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Let me see the comments.
- [Vansh] Look at this.
Yes, Hriday.
If papa has got up
then can I talk to him?
I am leaving for Delhi
with society members
for hearing of Supreme court.
[Fire crackling]
[Man crying]
[Cell phone beeps]
[Cell phone chimes]
[Indistinct murmuring]
[Cell phone beeps]
Papa,
we lost the case.
We did not get the stay order.
We lost the case.
[Vansh] Life is strange.
Without break it keeps
on giving setback.
It makes us cry and then
does not give time to cry.
Kale, tell them to keep
both their dozers ready.
We've to head to
Kalakruti Society for demolition.
[Engine starts]
[Car door opens]
Let's go.
[Car door closes]
Please relax. Please.
Please. Please.
But Manchanda sir,
listen to what he's saying first...
Relax. Relax, guys.
Speak, Son.
There's no point in shouting.
We must stop them in a planned way.
This is our society Kalakruti.
This is our gate.
And there is just one access
road leading to this gate.
Obviously, the Municipality will
come through this road.
[All] Yes.
So we must block them
in three layers, okay.
[All] Yes.
They will bring their
JCBs for the demolition.
We will park our
cars outside the gate
so that their JCBs get blocked.
This is a society,
not a fort to block them...
Listen to him first.
If they crush our cars,
break down the gate,
then we'll form human-shields.
Yes, we'll hold our ground.
They can Lathi-charge as well.
But we don't have to be scared.
We've to fight.
They will have to run
over us with the bulldozer.
She is right.
- All hail.
- Kalakruti Society.
- Three cheers for...
- Kalakruti.
Let's go.
- Three cheers for...
- Let's go.
- Kalakruti.
- Three cheers for...
Does everyone have placards?
Take your placards.
All the ladies will stay
in the front for the human chain.
Zulfiya, you stay at the back.
You'll not stay in front, Zulfiya.
Hold the placards high up.
You must shout slogans.
We might fight against
the municipality.
- Side, sister-in-law.
- [Honking]
Come on.
[Honking]
[Man 1] Side. Side.
Side. Side.
Left. Left. Left.
Right. Right. Right.
Centre.
Come. Come. Come.
Come.
Close the gate.
Move. Move.
Give the rope.
We don't need any more.
Vansh. Vansh.
Close it. Lock.
[Mukul] Check the lock.
Scenes of high drama
can be witnessed
outside Kalakruti Society now.
The situation here seems
like a war has been declared.
The residents of Kalakruti
Society are prepared
to do anything to save their homes.
We must wait and see what the
Police and Administration will do
to get them out of their homes.
Ma'am, what is your opinion?
We're pretty disturbed, and
we will fight till our last breath.
Until we don't get our homes back.
[Siren blaring]
All ladies ahead. All ladies ahead.
Come. Come.
Come in front.
Sir, how can you...
- Sir...
- Calm down, please.
Calm down.
Wait, wait...
Yes sir. Please speak.
You think you'll park your
cars in our way and we'll go back.
[Shouting]
We won't move. We won't move.
I have orders from
the Supreme Court.
No Law can go against humanity.
We have a JCB standing here,
the entire Police Force.
And it's too hot today.
So please move out of
our way and let us do our job.
You move out of our way, sir.
We won't move. We won't move.
Look, you cannot scare us.
We won't get scared.
We won't move even
if you call the military.
We won't move. We won't move.
Look, you're using illegal
means to save illegal homes.
- This is contempt of court.
- Exactly.
You can be arrested	 for this.
Don't forget.
Sir, we know all the legal options.
You can do what you want.
- What's going on...
- We won't move.
We won't move.
[Nirmala] We won't move even if
you hang us by the noose.
Municipality-Down-Down!
Municipality-Go back!
They won't move.
We would've done the same thing.
I'll call sir, what else.
Everyone, stay calm.
No one will charge
until I don't say so.
I want to speak to sir.
Me?
It's Khairnar speaking.
Municipality-Down-Down!
We're screwed and sir is busy.
What are your plans?
How long will you stop them?
- Stop them as long as we can.
- Yes.
And our hands have been
forced to do this, we're angry
- because we are being wrong.
- It's wrong.
Please help us, we're not
criminals. We're ordinary people.
- We're the common people.
- Please Tweet the Chief Minister
Call his office.
Please help us.
Madam, please use your
news channel to tell the world
tell the minister,
tell the President, what's...
Tell the entire country
what's happening with us.
Yes! Yes!
We won't move. We won't move.
[Man on TV] The Police are present
in large quantity
and yet the residents
of Kalakruti don't seem to budge.
Deputy Municipal Commissioner
is trying to explain the people.
But the residents of
Kalakruti Society isn't...
What is the name of
this Deputy Commissioner?
Khairnar.
Call him.
Purohit, what's going
on in your election area?
You can't even
get a small job done.
Khairnar, what's going on?
No, don't use force.
Media is present there.
It will create a scandal.
Be gentle.
Explain them gently.
And get them out of there.
Yes sir.
These a******s sit in
an AC cabin and give orders.
And we've to clean their mess.
Come on,
now let's clean this mess up.
- Just a minute.
- Municipality-Down-Down!
- Speak.
- Listen you all.
We have orders from above to
use force. But follow court orders.
To hell with your court orders.
We don't accept your orders.
Please move.
Just a minute.
You can kill us if you want.
Because we cannot
live without our homes.
Yes, we cannot live without it.
Look, this is your last warning.
Move these bamboos
and open this gate.
And this is our last warning.
Go back.
Yes, go back.
Municipality-Down-Down!
Why is it taking so long, Khairnar?
It's been two hours.
Does it take so long to do a job?
Hurry up,
get those people out of there.
Finish this matter.
Bloody a*****e, he'll understand
when he comes out on the field.
Bring the JCB ahead,
move these cars.
[Engine accelerates]
Commissioner, I don't want any
violence. No Lathi-charge, okay?
- Right, sir.
- Please take care.
Right, sir.
Municipality-Down-Down!
[Car crushed]
Move them. Move them.
What are you doing?
We won't move. We won't move.
Move them.
I said no violence.
Hey Stop it. Please move.
JCB, break it down.
[Khairnar] Move. Please move.
[Earth-mover clanking against gate]
Move out of the way.
[Gate smacked]
Move back. Move back.
- Move back. Move back.
- We won't move.
Please calm down, and move back.
- Please, I request you.
- We won't move.
- What are you doing?
- [Slaps]
[Tumult]
Lathi-Charge! Lathi-Charge!
Stop! Stop!
[Man 1] Move back. Move back.
Go back! Go back!
Stop! Stop!
Hey stop it!
Grandpa. Grandpa.
Move. Move.
[Man on TV]
Today is a black day, gentlemen.
I told you do not use force.
Do not force.
Have you lost your mind?
Now call bulldozers off.
Immediately. Call them back.
At once right now.
Where is the Chief Minister?
Move. Move back.
He's fine.
Give him some fresh air.
Take your force back.
Move back.
Take the JCB back. Take it back.
Get the stretcher.
Lift him up, come on.
Take this.
If anything happens to him, then
the Municipality'll be responsible.
Come on, hurry up.
Municipality-Down-Down!
Stop here.
Open the door.
Open the ambulance door.
[Siren blaring]
Take it inside.
Take it inside. Come on.
Go inside.
Go, go.
The Administration, Media,
Court, you appealed to everyone.
And they all have the same opinion.
That illegal construction
has to be broken down.
Now you're making a
joke out of Law and Order.
Sir, Law, and Order
are making a joke out of us.
The whole country is saying
that this is an injustice.
- And you're not listening.
- Listen.
What is your name?
Vansh Sethi.
Vansh...
we live in a country
that has some law.
This is not some Banana Republic.
I am requesting you personally.
Please surrender your house keys.
Nothing can be done now.
And these demonstrations,
Satyagraha, stop all this.
And what if we don't
hand over the keys.
Ma'am, don't mistake
my government's sympathy
for its weakness.
Nothing can be done now.
Just do as I said.
Please.
[Man 1] Come, ma'am, please.
Brother, what have you decided?
Where will you live now?
We'll rent someplace.
And the expenses?
Sister-in-law told
us about your job.
And even the lunch
business has shut down.
And starting a business
in a new area will take time.
I have some saving.
Heena and I will
support them too, Uncle.
We'll do something together.
[Clears throat]
I don't know how to say this,
Whenever I try to do
something you get angry.
You misunderstand me.
But I am still saying it.
We have a property, which
is lying vacant for a long time.
Sister-in-law,
why don't you guys move there?
[Bharti]
You've already spent a huge sum
on hospital bills and lawyers.
We're saying this because
we understand your position.
Sister-in-law, Brother,
do give it a thought.
[Sighs]
[Bird fluttering]
Oh, no!
This is just one room.
One bathroom, that too Indian.
How are we going to live here?
Let's rent someplace.
- Papa, say no.
- Wait a minute.
Think about it, children.
If you try to rent a two-bedroom
flat in a proper building
it won't cost anything
less than 50,000 rupees.
Plus brokerage and
two to three lakhs for deposit.
All those expenses and we have
only 700,000 rupees in the bank.
Now you guys tell me,
how long can we live there?
And Bharti said we can
stay here for as long as we want.
We won't have to pay a nickel.
Beggars can't be choosers.
[Door opens]
[Hina giggling]
Guddu, take a look at this as well.
But this is Burma ply, Sethi uncle.
No, this is Burma Teakwood.
No, but this is 10-15 years old.
I can't give you
more than 600 for this.
No, that's too less.
This is from Vansh's childhood.
That's nowhere close
to the original price.
[Guddu] I've given you the best
rates for all the stuff.
- [Himansh] 45,000 Rupees.
- [Vansh] 45 for all the stuff.
[Himansh]
Guddu, you're paying us peanuts.
45,000 rupees for all this stuff.
Rosewood table 1200 rupees. 12?
Dresser, 1000.
Dining table, double-bed.
You call these decent rates, Guddu.
We've known you since
you were just a kid.
Listen... Listen to me.
You up the prices a little, and
we'll negotiate again.
You know what, let's settle
for 50,000 rupees. Fix it, please.
Okay, what's in the kitchen?
[Himansh] There are a lot of
things in the kitchen.
But the kitchen is separate.
This does not include the kitchen.
[Guddu] But at least
let me take a look.
[Himansh] Yes, go take a look.
But sir,
this is all iron and steel.
This will be sold per kilo.
Don't touch that. Keep it down.
I don't want to sell this.
Now leave.
I said leave,
I don't want to sell it.
Himansh, I won't sell this.
Vandana, we don't have a place for
all this stuff in the other house.
No, I don't care.
I don't know what I will do
with them, but I won't sell them.
These lunchboxes...
When we had nothing, we ran
our house with these lunchboxes.
How can I sell them?
This crib.
Vansh played in it, so did Hina.
Did we keep it safe all these
years just so we can sell it?
This table...
I used to sit here and
check my children's homework.
We cut so many birthday cakes here.
Played games on this table.
Scrabble, Monopoly.
The morning tea which
you used to make.
This is not just
a piece of furniture for me.
This is our life.
How can I sell them?
How? [Crying]
I am sorry.
It's okay.
[Vansh] You know what they say
"Good things happen
to good people."
Bullshit!
Truth is... terrible things
happen to good people.
That is just how the world is.
Cruel, unfair, and random.
Happy endings are only in stories,
not in real life.
Hey.
Stop.
You're not supposed to carry.
[Grunts]
Abortion...
When will we get an abortion?
[Mohsin sighs]
[Sighs]
- Mr. Chaubey.
- [Mr. Chaubey] Yes, madam.
Inform everyone to come
to Nirmala madam's house at 9 pm.
[Mr. Chaubey] Yes, madam.
We'll be just wasting
space with that.
Let's appeal again.
Supreme Court.
- Review Petition.
- What?
We must leave for Delhi tomorrow.
What are you saying?
What happened?
I won't let it go so easily.
What won't you let go?
I won't leave my home so easily.
It will cost some money,
but let's try again.
Mrs. Nirmala,
call Mr. Gehi and Motwani
and call for an urgent meeting.
I am coming.
Go after him.
Look what's going on?
[Vansh] Dad.
We're too late now, Himansh.
Nothing can be done now.
Sethi sir, you're right.
But what's the point of going
through all the trouble again.
We've tried everything.
Going to Delhi again,
paying lawyers.
But the conclusion
will still be the same.
Try to understand.
Maybe filing a review petition
might do something.
It will be a different
judge and a different judgment.
Forget it, Sethi sir.
My stuff is getting
loaded at the back.
Our tickets to Canada
have arrived as well.
And we're going to
gather everyone around
to hand over the keys
to the Municipality.
Okay.
Vansh, please explain to Sethi sir.
This is absolutely impossible.
No, it's okay.
It's okay if you can't come along.
I will go alone.
Sethi sir, please talk...
- Sethi sir...
- No problem, thank you.
Okay, sir,
see you tomorrow in Delhi.
Okay, thank you.
The lawyer got a hearing
date for tomorrow.
Book a ticket for me
to Delhi tomorrow morning.
What about the lawyer's fee?
How are we going to do it?
He's defending our case for free.
If he wins,
he will get a lot of publicity.
And, what about our stuff, Papa?
I mean, there are chances
of getting the same verdict.
If the demolition crew come down
then how will we sell
it at the last minute?
Son, think positive.
We'll keep it in the
society office for now.
The others have
kept it there as well.
I'll call Rishi as well.
He'll come and help.
What have you thought
about him, dear?
We think you should
give him a chance.
He's trying his best
to convince you.
You guys don't understand.
If I patch up with him now
he'll think I am going back
because I don't have a home.
He'll think it's my helplessness
and not my choice.
I don't want that.
You've grown smart in my company.
Eat your food.
Vansh.
Take a selfie.
Now?
Maybe this is our last lunch
in this house.
Think positive, Vandana.
[Vansh clears throat]
Hashtag last lunch.
[Mukul] Mr. Gehi,
did you talk to her?
Why did Nirmala call us
at this hour?
[Gehi] I don't know either.
Our packing is not complete yet.
Mrs. Nirmala.
Your voice has grown weak.
Knock on the door instead.
[Knocking]
[Vansh] Aunty.
[Woman] Someone call her.
[Gehi] Her battery must be dead.
Hello, welcome.
Come in. [Chuckles]
You look like Ms. Nirmala today.
Don't stand outside, come in
Come.
- Come.
- How are you, sir?
Come.
Hello. Sit, sit.
Hello, sir.
How are you?
[Exhales deeply]
Please be comfortable.
Look, there are two kinds
of people in the world.
You've all seen the Titanic.
Now, remember the last scene.
The ship is sinking.
Most of the people are running,
crying and yelling.
But in this entire confusion
only four people are
merrily playing the violin.
Thinking that they
are going to sink anyway
so why don't we go
down singing and dancing?
Now you guys decide
whether you're the
panic-stricken lot.
or the ones going down merrily?
Today is our last night
in this society.
So those who want to cry
alone in their homes, well adios.
And those who are going
down singing and dancing
there's rum,
vodka, and whiskey there.
[Chuckles]
Choose your poison.
But for God's sake
don't ask for ice.
[Laughter]
Obviously, vodka, rum, whiskey.
Come on, guys.
Love you, Nirmala aunty.
Thank you.
Come on.
Very nice.
Thank you.
You love it.
Yes I love it.
[Laughter]
- Chaubey.
- Yes.
Keep that back.
Where is your glass?
Go get your drink first. Go.
He's already drunk.
[Nirmala] You are too much.
He's not the employee
of the society now.
Hello, everyone.
Hey, Rishi.
[Mukul] Did you get ice, or not?
If you didn't,
then you won't get a drink.
Shut up.
- Come, son.
- Come, sit here.
Did you smell alcohol, bro?
[Laughter]
Look, you are all
society members, by law.
But he's by love.
Great!
The boy's worked really hard.
[Mukul]
He's a very hard working boy.
First, tell me what
you're going to drink.
- Nothing, Aunty. I am good.
- [Nirmala] No?
Mrs. Nirmala,
he's become one of those...
- What are they called?
- What?
- Total tea... types.
- [Laughs]
- Tea-totallers.
- Exactly.
[Laughter]
Well, I am not a teetotaler, son.
Make one for me.
If my son had been here, he
would ask me to make one for him.
[Mukul] Your turn next.
You have to tell...
- Hey you.
- Come.
- What?
[Hina] Vansh.
Vansh.
Yeah. [Clears throat]
- What's up.
What's up.
Actually, mom-dad are right here.
You can take her home.
You'll get some privacy out there.
- And anyway, making out reduces...
- Stress.
Yeah.
- Have heard that
- Yeah.
Rascal, when did you two do it?
When did we do it?
Friday.
We were stressed out
about the demolition
and you two were getting laid.
It reduces stress.
Rascal.
Let it be. Now you don't
lecture me on this subject.
I've to make a drink.
- Nice catch.
- Thank you.
I chased after him and
caught him by his collar.
Only after that did he marry me.
[Laughter]
Mrs. Bhonsle.
The truth is out.
One minute,
one minute, settle down.
Now let's play a game.
Now everyone must say
what's in their heart.
- Okay.
- And you must tell the truth.
Oh, God.
[Laughter]
Me first. Me first.
22 years ago, when I came
to this society to see the flat
it was a love-at-first-sight
situation for me.
- With the society?
- No.
With a very beautiful girl.
Wow.
- And she lived in this building.
- Wow.
- Who was she?
- I'll tell you, madam.
I'll tell you the entire story.
And I booked a flat here
because of that beautiful girl.
Romantic.
[Mukul]
There's a twist in the story, son.
Now next.
Look at my fate,
after I came to live here
I found out that she is married.
Oh no.
Who was that girl?
You're asking me this,
Sister-in-law Vandana?
[Vandana] Tell us.
That girl is you.
- Sorry, Sethi sir. Sorry, Sethi.
- Heard it.
So sorry.
[Laughter]
Mr. Motwani, were you married
or unmarried back then?
[Laughter]
What...
Mr. Sethi.
What can I say?
Sethi sir,
say whatever you like today.
Everything is allowed today.
Sure?
Come on, Sethi sir.
Will anyone feel offended?
Say it.
Himansh, say it.
What are you going to say?
Say it.
You guys are rascals.
You cut off my water connection.
I reached office late.
Who does that?
Sorry, Mr. Sethi.
It was a mistake.
We did wrong.
[Mukul] Genuinely sorry, Sethi sir.
Apologize to me as well.
I organized a party at home
but no one showed up.
And all my food was wasted.
And plus we were taken
out of the WhatsApp group.
- Very bad.
- She is absolutely right.
And it's not a small mistake.
It's a big crime.
You made me miss Vandana's
delicious cooking.
And it's really worth regretting.
I second that. I second that.
Sorry, Vandana.
Done. I'll come over next time.
[Laughing]
[Vaibhav] Can I say something?
You're all my family now.
So it's not right to hide that I
don't have a job for two years now.
I'm sitting idle at home.
You're not the only one.
Even I don't have a job.
And, even I'll be completely
useless from tomorrow.
- Right.
- We'll struggle together, cheers.
[Mukul] Two's better than one.
Not bad.
Himansh, let's go.
You have a flight to
catch tomorrow.
[Vandana] No.
What's the hurry,
sister-in-law Vandana?
[Mukul] The night is young.
- No one's going anywhere.
- Let us go.
[Vandana] Not at all.
When will he sleep,
and get up in the morning?
We are...
[Turns on the music]
Why did you put on the music?
So you two dance.
Come on.
Let's dance.
Come on let's dance.
[Song playing]
Dad.
[Door closes]
Come.
The residents of Kala Kruti
Society have finally given up.
They don't have any option left.
They are locking
their homes and leaving.
They must hand over their keys
to the Deputy Commissioner
so that the demolition
process can be initiated.
[Car Squeaking]
[Car door opens]
Excuse me. How do you think
you can carry this out, sir?
- What is your plan?
- Stop the JCB here.
Please tell me, sir.
I'll go see Zulfiya.
You won't need cops this time, sir.
This time we'll cooperate.
Okay.
Sir, we have a humble request.
The Supreme Court's
revised decision
will be announced at 12 o'clock.
Can you please wait until then?
- It's just a request, sir.
- Please. Please.
Only till 12 o'clock.
Thank you, sir.
Now, all of you stand in a queue
and surrender your keys.
Everyone form a queue, please.
Everyone form a queue.
Send them one by one.
[Khairnar] Flat no. Name.
Sign here. And keep the key here.
Sign. Keys.
Sign here.
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Khairnar. What's the report?
We've started the procedure, sir.
And start the demolition
after the handover.
Good.
Wrap it up quickly
or else we might run into
another problem like last time.
Remember?
[Sighs]
Thank you so much, Aunty.
Thank you so much for coming here,
really thanks for being here.
Really means a lot.
I wish Mohsin was here, but...
Are you mad?
There's no need to say thanks.
Thank you. Really means a lot.
[Woman]
Zulfiya Sheikh, your husband?
Thank you, Aunty.
I'll take care of her.
[Sighs]
I am sorry.
Motwani's.
- That's all 120.
- Yes, sir.
You guys can stay.
It's not 12 o'clock yet.
Mr. Sethi, I've tried my level best
but we've to accept that
the chances are very less.
Yes, sir. [Sighs]
Some tea?
No, thank you, sir.
Any message from dad?
After the last judgment, would
you like to give a new argument?
Your Honor,
the arguments are still the same.
We would like to make one last
request to the honorable court
to reconsider its last
judgment on humanitarian grounds.
Then, in that case, there
is nothing new to be reconsidered.
Your Honor, the applicant,
Mr. Himansh Sethi
would like to say something
to the honorable bench.
Why?
Do you have a new argument?
No, sir. I don't have an argument.
I just wanted to say something
that's on my mind.
Make way. Make way.
Did your papa call?
I saved money by staying hungry.
And bought a flat on EMI.
Felt like I've
finally settled down.
But then we found out
that it's illegal construction.
[Himansh] It wasn't our fault, sir.
We trusted the builder.
Why did the government give
permission to the builder
for that illegal construction?
And if the builder
didn't have permission
then why did he sell the flats?
Whereas the builder and the officer
are involved in this entire scam.
Then why are they
not in this court, sir?
Who is standing in the court?
A middle-class common man.
And all the members
of the Kala Kruti Society
kept paying every taxes.
We paid property tax,
electricity bill
water connection bill, gas bill.
If the construction was illegal,
then why accept it, sir?
A house is built of sand,
cement, stone.
Few rooms and pillars.
But in that house
when your mother-father, wife,
children come to live in that house
then that makes it... a home.
Sweet Home, sir.
And now our sweet home
is being destroyed.
Sir, your decision...
will make 500 Indians refugees
in their own country.
[Monitor beeping]
Come, lie down.
Look, it's 12 o'clock.
We must start our job.
Sir.
[Mukul] Sir, please wait another
10 minutes.
Come on, start.
Sir, please wait
another 10 minutes.
The court will give its decision.
Come on, start, start.
- Sir, please wait.
- Come on, start, start.
[Engine starts]
[Cell phone beeps]
Papa's message,
we got the stay order.
Stop!
Yes, sir.
Stop. Stop.
Demolition cancel.
[Cheering]
- We got it.
- We got the stay order.
We got it.
[Cheering]
What happened?
Stop. Stop.
We got it.
Dad.
Mohsin, we got the stay order.
Doctor, stop the abortion.
Please stop it.
Zulfiya, our home is safe.
We stay in the same house.
We don't have to abort the baby.
I love you.
Go back.
Go back. Go back.
Let's go back.
Thank you so much, sir.
Thank you so much.
That was such a close call,
for you and me.
How yours, sir?
If today I had
demolished your building
my wife wouldn't have
let me in the house.
[Laughing]
Thank you so much, sir.
God bless, sir. God bless.
[Himansh] Here you go.
[Vansh] Papa.
Hi.
Well done.
[Clapping]
Sethi, you were amazing.
The judge was amazing.
He was such a nice man.
No need to be so modest now.
You are our hero now.
Long live-Himansh Sethi.
Long live-Kala Kruti.
Hip-Hip-Hurray.
- Son, did you take my bag?
- Yes.
Long live-Kala Kruti.
- [Doorbell rings]
- [Door opens]
Hello.
So cute.
So, guys, I'll be leaving now.
- Where are you going, Son?
- Home.
Alone?
- Will you come along?
- Obviously.
Wow.
Come here...
Well done.
[Vansh] Thank God everything
became normal.
Normalcy is a strange thing.
When everything is normal,
it seems boring.
And everything is not normal,
we understand its value.
Cheers.
And everything is not normal,
we understand its value.
Okay. All right.
Breathe in. One. Two. Three.
Inhale.
[Inhales]
[Laughing]
- No, no... serious. Okay.
- Okay.
[Inhales]
[Gasps]
What?
- Kicking again.
- Kicking.
[Both chuckling]
My God.
[Woman] The court's decision
arrived, and your homes are saved.
Now, shall we fix the wedding date?
So, when do you
want to get married?
As soon as possible.
Our entire routine was ruined.
Once everything is back to normal,
we'll come over to Canada.
[Man 1 on call] Okay, Mom-Dad,
please stay out of trouble.
Well, no one invites trouble
for himself intentionally.
And, you also stay out of trouble.
Look they are here.
[Man 1] They call us every Sunday.
Dear Kala Krutians.
We're facing trouble again.
See, we got a stay order
against the demolition.
But we must pay a fine
to legalize our society.
- There's always something.
- How much?
- 720 million rupees.
- What? 720 million rupees.
See, out of the Supreme Court
and into the fine.
We've made the calculation
and per flat owner
share will be 6 million.
6 million?
It's hard to say whether
this is penalty or extortion.
[Man 2] It's definitely extortion.
Well, everyone has to pay.
[Indistinct chattering]
Look...
Listen to the further process.
Listen, we're going to
contest against it in the court.
We're going to appoint
a lawyer tomorrow.
One request, please appoint
a decent lawyer this time.
- And not some amateur.
- [Mukul] You're right.
You think we don't know
what we're doing.
How dare you say that...
Think that we'll have do that.
It's the same problem
for all of us.
[Indistinct chattering]
[Vansh] They say that beyond
fear lies victory.
Sorry boss, for us
there's more fear lies ahead.
In short; hashtag FMML
Hashtag Fuck my middle-class life