Hello, friends!
One of the world's most courageous military commanders
widely recognized as the most powerful king in Europe.
was Napoleon Bonaparte.
However, he remains one of history's most controversial figures,
with some praising his capabilities
while others criticize his hunger for power.
Questions about the immense loss of life attributed to him persist:
What is the truth?
Was he a hero of the masses or the vilest of villains?
Director Ridley Scott is set to release
a film titled 'Napoleon' on November 24th.
Scott, known for directing acclaimed films
such as 'Gladiator,' 'The Martian,' and 'Prometheus,'
the trailer of the film promises an intriguing portrayal,
featuring Joaquin Phoenix as Napoleon.
Phoenix notably played the role of
Joker in the film of the same name.
So I thought this is the perfect time
to get to know Napoleon Bonaparte's story.
Napoleon was born on 15th August 1769,
on the island of Corsica.
Look at the map, it is an island
situated between France and Italy.
Noteworthy for being the backdrop of the song Matargasti,
from the film Tamasha starring
Ranbir Kapoor and Deepika Padukone.
Corsica, during the 1700s,
was under the rule of a country that doesn't exist any longer.
Republic of Genoa.
This was the flag of the Republic of Genoa.
Several territories that are now part of Italy and Greece
were under the control of this country.
One such territory was Corsica,
but the Corsicians were fed up with Genoan rule.
They were fueled by a burgeoning sense of nationalism
and a desire to live in a free country.
Pasquale Paoli emerged as a leader in
the Corsican struggle for independence,
and a young Napoleon embraced Corsican nationalism,
inspired by his childhood idol Paoli.
By the 1760s, Corsica found itself embroiled in war,
while the Republic of Genoa,
burdened by debt and war,
decided to literally sell the island of Corsica to France in 1768.
This decision caused unrest among Corsican freedom fighters,
but there wasn't much that they could do.
Resisting the might of France's imperial power proved challenging.
The turning point came in 1769 when
the French army clashed with Corsican forces.
During the Battle of Ponte Novu.
Following a swift victory, France
claimed Corsica as its territory.
Shortly thereafter, Napoleon Bonaparte was born.
His father Carlo,
was a lawyer who initially fought
alongside Corsican freedom fighters.
But after the French army's triumph
Paoli had to flee the country.
And Carlo switched allegiance.
The shift was notable, as Carlo became an
ardent supporter of the French royalty.
He used connections to make advances in his career.
He secured the status of Nobility.
By 1777, he became Corsica's representative
to the court of the new French king, Louis XVI.
This transformation bothered Napoleon.
He harboured no fondness for his father.
He viewed his father as a coward and deserter.
But it was his father's connections that
Napoleon and his brother Joseph secured scholarships,
enabling Napoleon to enrol in the French Military College.
At the college, Napoleon was surrounded
by the children of French aristocrats,
he faced ridicule at school
due to his distinctive accent.
Unfazed, he refrained from socialising with his peers,
viewing the French as colonizers.
His dream was to witness his country, Corsica achieve independence.
Napoleon's isolation drove him to find solace in books,
particularly drawn to Enlightenment-age
philosopher Jean-Jacques Rousseau,
the primary reason for that was
Rousseau wrote about Corsican freedom,
and considered the Corsicians brave in his writings.
In addition to philosophy,
Napoleon exhibited a keen interest in mathematics, history, and geography,
excelling in these subjects.
Among his favourite reads was Plutarch's 'Parallel Lives,'
a compilation of 45 biographies featuring historical figures
like Alexander the Great and Julius Caesar.
Napoleon found inspiration in Caesar,
often drawing comparisons.
Upon completing his schooling,
Napoleon joined a military academy in Paris,
specializing in artillery.
Graduating as the second lieutenant
of the Royal Artillery in the French army,
during all of this, he would often return to Corsica
continuing to idolize Pasquale Paoli.
However, the landscape changed in 1789
with the onset of the French Revolution.
I have made a separate video on the French Revolution
in case you haven't watched it,
you can watch it after this.
During this period, Corsica fell under the
jurisdiction of the new French National Assembly,
leading to the pardon of Pasquale Paoli.
After a 20-year exile, Paoli returned,
and was greeted warmly by the people of Corsica
including Napoleon.
Subsequent elections in Corsica
saw Pasquale Paoli emerge victorious,
becoming the President.
Despite Napoleon's 'traitorous' father having passed away by the time
and Napoleon holding Paoli in high regard,
Paoli harboured resentment toward Napoleon's family,
Consequently, Paoli declared that such
traitorous families could not live in Corsica,
prompting Napoleon and his family
to relocate from Corsica to France
in June 1793.
Following this, Paoli severed ties with
the French Revolutionary Assembly,
aligning himself with their enemy, the British.
This is why, in 1794,
the Anglo-Corsican Kingdom was established,
expelling France from Corsica
and rendering it a puppet state under British control.
However, this arrangement lasted only two years.
In 1796, France launched an attack,
reclaiming Corsica from British rule.
Meanwhile, France was embroiled in a civil war,
marked by various factions of
French revolutionaries and counter-revolutionaries.
People, divided into various groups,
were fighting among themselves.
In 1793, a political group named Jacobins,
came to power and formed the French government.
The group was led by Maximillien Robespierre.
During this tumultuous period,
Napoleon expressed his support for the
Jacobin government in a political pamphlet.
This caught the attention of Robespierre's brother,
it greatly impressed him.
This gave a boost to Napoleon's career prospects.
In September 1793, an event occurred that
further elevated Napoleon's popularity.
Toulon, a French naval base,
witnessed an uprising by a group
and subsequent attacks by the British forces.
The French Army dispatched Napoleon
to take command at this location.
Napoleon was then serving as
Senior Gunner and Artillery Commander.
Napoleon proposed a strategic plan to win
this conflict
and shared it with his commanders.
The plan included capturing a fort,
securing a hill for artillery dominance,
and launching attacks on British ships.
His plan was executed
with Napoleon fighting with remarkable bravery,
and suffering significant injuries.
but after three months of struggle,
the French army emerged victorious.
The General of the French Army, Dugomere,
speaking about Napoleon, stated
'I have no words to describe Bonaparte's merit:
much technical skill, an equal degree
of intelligence, and too much gallantry...
Napoleon is an amazing man.'
In recognition of his contributions, Napoleon
was promoted to the rank of Brigadier General
at the young age of 24.
During this period, France remained
embroiled in a civil war,
and Maximilian Robespierre sought to implement reforms.
Such as universal male suffrage,
granting voting rights to all men above 18.
While women were not granted political rights,
significant reforms were instituted for them,
including the right to divorce
an option that was previously unavailable to women.
Additionally, women gained access to
the right to education and work opportunities.
Robespierre's influence extended to the abolition of slavery in France
and the French colonies,
leaving a lasting impact reflected in
numerous roads and metro stations
named after him in France.
However, Robespierre's tenure was marked by controversy,
particularly because of the Reign of Terror.
In an effort to quash opposition to the French Revolution,
thousands were executed on suspicion alone,
leading to the d3ath of at least 20,000 French citizens.
Simultaneously, the government initiated the
dismantling of Catholic Christianity in France.
confiscating church properties
and promoting a singular Supreme God,
to be revered through acts of service to the people.
Amid these challenges and instability,
a coup unfolded in July 1794 against the Jacobins government,
resulting in its complete overthrow
and Robespierre's execution.
In August 1794, since Napoleon
supported the toppled government,
he was imprisoned.
He vigorously defended himself,
securing his release from jail after only a few weeks.
The orchestrator of this coup was
the well-known figure, Paul Barras,
who had known Napoleon since the Siege of Toulon
and gradually developed a favourable opinion of him.
In October 1795, Napoleon was entrusted with the task of
quelling a revolution,
despite the French army facing
a numerical disadvantage of 1 to 6.
Employing 40 cannons and limited infantry,
Napoleon successfully suppressed the uprising within 2 hours,
This pleased Paul Barras,
who then gave him the title of General.
Napoleon became a national hero.
At just 27 years old,
he assumed the role of General in the French Army.
Shortly thereafter, he took command
of the Army of Italy,
not the Italian Army,
Rather the French forces operating in Italy.
They were known as the Army of Italy.
The troops lacked motivation, discipline, and supplies.
Napoleon addressed this by delivering compelling speeches,
emphasizing the importance of discipline for victory
and condemning looting and pillaging in conquered territories,
asserting that only cowards engage in such actions.
Napoleon's armies didn't loot or pillage territories.
Despite this, Napoleon did indulge in
one form of appropriation—art.
That's right.
His passion for art stemmed from his
desire to establish a universal museum in Paris,
showcasing a vast collection of
artworks from around the world.
In later years, he even renamed
the Louvre Museum,
naming the museum after himself.
Getting back to the Army of Italy,
Napoleon led them in a famous battle against the Austrians.,
the Battle of Arcole.
This famous painting depicts this battle.
Napoleon's tactics involved
rapid troop movement, varied formations,
and surprise attacks on the enemy.
Using these, Napoleon's troops won the Battle of Arcole.
In 1798, as France contemplated
invading the British Isles,
Napoleon, upon his return to Paris,
refused to fight in this battle.
He argued that the British Navy was formidable
and it made any invasion impractical.
He proposed an alternative campaign
in the Mediterranean.
Advancing southward to capture Egypt
and blocking the route of the British to India.
Afterwards, Napoleon planned to
assist Tipu Sultan of Mysore
in his struggle against the British.
Commencing his Mediterranean campaign with 40,000 soldiers,
Napoleon and his soldiers set sail for
Toulon, boarding numerous ships.
In addition to the soldiers,
he brought along over 160
scientists, scholars, and artists,
aiming to document valuable knowledge acquired in new territories.
The army progressed southward,
capturing the island of Malta
before landing on the Egyptian coast in Alexandria.
Battles such as the Battle of Alexandria
and the Battle of the Pyramids, unfolded.
"Following the footsteps of Alexander, the Great,
and Ceaser,
and destined for greatness."
Resulting in victories against the Ottoman army and local kings.
The French flag flew over the Citadel of Qaitbay
Look at these photos from present-day Egypt.
Napoleon established the Institute of Egypt
to systematically study the country's
history, culture, and resources,
concurrently promoting Enlightenment ideals in Egypt.
However, the success of Napoleon's plan was short-lived.
Within a few weeks, in August 1798,
a formidable fleet of the British Navy attacked the French,
leading to the destruction of numerous French ships
and the d3ath of a French admiral
in the Battle of the Nile,
depicted in this historic painting
showing numerous destroyed French ships.
A year later, in August 1799,
following continued defeats,
Napoleon clandestinely abandoned
his army and fled from Egypt.
Although Napoleon's military campaign was a substantial failure,
Let alone reaching India and helping Tipu Sultan,
Napoleon lost his hold on Egypt too.
And Malta, which was captured first,
was recaptured by the British.
You'd be wondering why I'm mentioning this failure.
For two reasons.
Firstly, despite its military setbacks, the campaign
was scientifically successful.
Notably, the discovery of the Rosetta Stone,
a slab inscribed with the same message in three different languages,
the key to our understanding of the ancient Egyptian hieroglyphics.
The Rosetta Stone had been previously discussed
in the video on the Indus Valley Civilization.
For further insights into this remarkable
artifact, you may refer to that video.
Additionally, French scientists made significant discoveries
about the types of trees and plants indigenous to Egypt.
They explored the topography of Egypt,
studied architectural designs,
and documented the utilization
of Egyptian jars for food preservation.
The second reason why this seemingly
unsuccessful campaign holds importance
lies in Napoleon's reception upon returning to France.
he was welcomed as a hero,
You must be perplexed by how
Napoleon, who lost the territories,
and abandoned his army,
is welcomed as a hero?
This was due to the extensive pro-Napoleon
propaganda that had been ongoing for years.
A multitude of mediums, ranging from newspapers to paintings,
official bulletins, songs, and poems,
Napoleon was being praised throughout France.
There were 6 newspapers in France back then,
some of them were established by Napoleon himself,
while Napoleon tookover the control over the others.
These newspapers printed about various battles.
The narrative in the newspapers would be set by Napoleon himself.
Napoleon presented himself as a knowledgeable person.
Several positive paintings and sketches were used
to depict his heroic battles.
When he chose the scientists for his Mediterranean campaign,
the newspapers printed seven pages
writing about each minute of the meeting.
Napoleon's speeches to his soldiers were widely published,
along with his childhood stories,
both factual and fictional,
Imaginary stories of Napoleon's childhood were created,
of the great deeds he never did.
An intriguing narrative emerged around
Napoleon's love for Josephine,
this romantic relationship has been
portrayed in depth in this film.
Director Ridley Scott claims that
Napoleon's conquered the world
to win over Josephine's love.
But when he couldn't
he conquered the world to destroy her.
Destroying himself in the process.
I won't talk about this film's plot too much in this video,
you can watch the movie to know more.
Returning to the discussion of propaganda,
let's examine these propaganda paintings.
One notable piece, commissioned by Napoleon himself,
depicts his Mediterranean campaign,
portraying him helping the sick in Jaffa
and drawing parallels to Jesus Christ.
Another example is this painting
illustrating the Battle of Marengo
fought between the French and Austrian armies in 1800,
where Napoleon is depicted crossing the Alps on horseback,
you'd note that this painting is inspired by Alexander's sculpture.
But why is this a propaganda painting?
Because this isn't how Napoleon crossed the Alps.
Look at this painting from 1850,
this is how he crossed the Alps.
On a mule guided by a farmer.
These propaganda paintings served a specific purpose:
to show Napoleon as the hero crossing the Alps on a horse.
The aim of the propaganda was to
advance Napoleon's ultimate goal
his final ambition.
To be on the throne.
When Napoleon returned to France from Egypt,
there was widespread conflict and corruption reports in France.
Napoleon orchestrated a coup in November 1799.
This led to the expulsion of the existing government
and the establishment of a new Consulate government,
with Napoleon as the First Consul of the new government.
Two individuals were appointed as aiding consuls,
and a new constitution was introduced in France.
Most French citizens didn't disapprove of it
due to the widespread influence of propaganda,
portraying Napoleon as a figure transcending politics,
acting solely in the French national interest,
and championing Enlightenment ideas.
To solidify public approval on the new Constitution,
a referendum was held in France,
and the results, announced by Napoleon's brother
Lucien, the Minister of Interiors in France
that 99.9% of the 3,013,000 voters
supported the new constitution.
It shows that 99.9% of the French citizens favoured Napoleon.
Was that true?
Absolutely not.
In reality, approximately 1.5 million votes
were cast in favour of Napoleon.
French historian Claude Langlois presented evidence in 1972,
revealing that the 1800 referendum was a complete fraud,
with slightly over 50% of the votes cast
were in favour of Napoleon.
Two years later, another referendum took place in 1802,
where Napoleon posed the question to the public:
Should he be appointed Consul for Life?
Once again, the public voted
with "99.7% voters"
supporting Napoleon to hold power for life.
Even after two fraud referendums,
Napoleon sought further validation.
In 1804, a third referendum was conducted,
asking if Napoleon should become the King of France.
And the result of the referendum was that,
"99.9% of the voters"
voted in favour of Napoleon becoming the king.
Napoleon wasn't greedy for the power,
but became the King to appease the masses.
I'm kidding, that's not how it went.
Napoleon wasn't one to hide his greed for power.
He openly embraced his love for power,
famously declaring, 'Power is my mistress.
I have worked too hard at her conquest
to allow anyone to take her away from me.'
Back then, this hunger for power,
was a characteristic accepted among
kings and nobles of the time.
Over the next decade, driven by Napoleon's love for power
he engaged in a series of battles across Europe,
interspersed with peace treaties,
such as the one signed with Britain in 1802.
However, the resumption of wars was inevitable
as both Napoleon and the British thirsted for power.
Many European nations engaged in wars with Napoleon
not only for power but also for their survival.
Many European kings and monarchs felt
threatened by the French revolutionary ideology.
They considered Napolean a threat to their kingdom.
In the French Revolution video, I explained that
the ideology of Nationalism was introduced by the Enlightenment thinkers.
Such as Rousseau and Voltaire.
These were the ideologies of left-wing revolutionaries.
While the right-wing adhered to
supporting monarchies and social hierarchy,
preserving the existing system.
The left-wing ideology championed equality,
freedom, and the aspiration for national freedom,
evolving into the foundation of Republicanism.
This nationalist fervour
was quickly spreading across other
European nations during that period,
leading to the emergence of revolutionaries
challenging the reigning monarchies.
In response, these monarchs formed coalitions,
sparking a series of coalition wars
between 1792 and 1815,
where monarchies collectively waged war against France.
In this context, Napoleon's role can be seen as
that of a liberator,
propagating the slogans of freedom
and revolution throughout Europe.
When Napoleon's forces entered Italy, he declared
to the Italian people that the French army
had come to break their chains.
He told them that he bore no ill will against the masses,
rather they were there to liberate them
from kings and emperors
who had oppressed them.
This is why in Milan, Italy
Napoleon was viewed as a hero.
For liberating them from Austrian rule under King Francis II.
Italian revolutionary and poet Yugo Foscolo
in 1802, said this about him:
"I will name you, therefore, Bonaparte,
with the unheard-of title of Liberator
of Peoples and Founder of Republics."
Additionally, in 1803, on of the
most renowned music composer,
Beethoven paid tribute to Napoleon by
naming his Symphony No. 3 after him.
He named the Symphony No. 3
Bonaparte.
Beethoven considered Napoleon a hero
for promoting democratic ideology
and opposing monarchy in Europe.
However, how could he be a hero when
he crowned himself the king
and conducted fraudulent referendums?
When Beethoven learned of Napoleon declaring himself a king,
he angrily proclaimed that
Napoleon was just a man, not a deity,
susceptible to the lure of power
and capable of oppressing people.
Beethoven subsequently removed
Napoleon's name from his symphony.
Indeed, Napoleon's decisions deviated from
the principles of the French Revolution.
In 1802, he enacted two laws that
reinstated practices of slavery.
Furthermore, his views on women were regressive,
emphasizing the importance of women
based on the number of children she bore.
Napoleon revoked many rights granted to women
during the French Revolution,
reinstating priority given to men in divorce laws.
Although the French Revolution had
championed freedom of expression,
Napoleon gradually imposed restrictions on it.
Dissenters who spoke against him were exiled,
and free newspapers were systematically shut down.
Despite bringing stability to France,
Napoleon's rule maintained a dictatorial character.
If he genuinely aimed to propagate
the ideas of the French Revolution,
he could have reinstated democracy in France.
I began this video, by talking about Corsica.
How Corsican independence was Napoleon's childhood dream.
Yet as a king, he never pursued the liberation of Corsica.
Instead of bringing democracy to France,
Napoleon appointed his brothers as
kings in the conquered territories.
In May 1808,
France initiated a war against Spain,
resulting in the Spanish King Carlos IV stepping down,
and Napoleon installing his brother Joseph as the new ruler.
Before this, Joseph had been
the king of Naples and Sicily.
Napoleon's younger brother Jerome
was crowned the king of Westphalia,
a region in present-day Germany.
Additionally, when the Kingdom of Holland
fell under Napoleon's control in 1806,
Louis, another of Napoleon's brothers,
was made the king of that region.
However, amidst this hunger for power,
there is a positive legacy
left by Napoleon worth noting.
Several decisions he made had far-reaching
benefits for the future of France and Europe.
The Napoleonic Code of 1804
stands out as a landmark legal framework, providing France
with a comprehensive and written set of laws.
The second achievement was the establishment
of equality for males under the law,
despite the setbacks for women's rights
and the reintroduction of slavery.
The equal rights given to the male citizens by the law,
remained unchanged.
Furthermore, Napoleon's era marked
the end of feudalism in France,
In the territories he occupied,
the same laws were enforced.
Third, Secularism.
During Napoleon's rule, the French
government adopted a secular stance.
There was religious freedom in France,
allowing individuals to practice their chosen religions.
In 1801, Christianity did return to France
when Napoleon signed an agreement with the Pope.
But the relationship between the Church and the Government
never fully went back to the way it used to be.
The power balance shifted more favourably towards the government.
While traditional positions of the
Catholic clergy in the Church were restored,
the government retained control over the selection of bishops
and supervised the church's finances,
significantly diminishing the influence
of the church in European affairs.
Fourth, establishing a banking system.
The Bank of France was founded by Napoleon in 1800,
It brought hyperinflation under control
and stabilized the currency.
Fifth, he introduced a modern and efficient tax system,
ending the exemptions previously granted to nobility and kings,
ensuring that everyone contributed to the tax base.
Sixth, in the education system,
Napoleon set up primary, secondary, and high schools,
along with establishing the University of France.
Uniformity was introduced to the education system,
teachers were trained,
and a centralized recruitment process
for teachers was initiated.
The government also regulated technical schools,
civil service schools, and military schools,
leading to a rapid improvement
in the overall quality of education.
Seventh, water distribution.
In 1808, Napoleon modernized Paris's water
distribution system by upgrading old pumps,
constructing a new canal
to direct water to the city,
and building 15 water fountains.
He ensured that Parisians would never starve.
Storehouses and granaries were modernized,
and eight new markets were constructed
wine market, wheat market,
everything happened in an organised manner.
In conclusion, despite Napoleon's hunger for power,
he wasn't a clueless ruler.
Napoleon emerged as a highly intelligent and effective administrator,
implementing several positive reforms for the French people.
Some people draw comparisons
between Napoleon and Hitler
which, in my opinion, are entirely inaccurate,
as Napoleon did not propagate hatred
against any religion or community,
nor did he employ strategies of divide and rule.
While Napoleon's actions resulted in the d3aths of millions,
but he was driven by his thirst for war and power.
Finally, let's talk about how Napoleon d!ed.
Despite his numerous victories,
he also faced defeats.
Such as Napoleon's Egyptian campaign, as discussed earlier,
Napoleon had installed a Continental System,
a comprehensive economic blockade against Britain
by all French allied countries.
When Russia violated this continental system in 1812,
Napoleon launched an attack on Russia.
The Russian forces refused to fight.
They would retreat and set fire to the battlefield,
leaving nothing for Napoleon's troops as provisions.
Even so, Napoleon's army reached Moscow,
but the city was empty,
and after a month of waiting for the Russians to surrender,
to no avail,
Napoleon's hungry army had to retreat from the barren city.
The next year in 1813,
a coalition comprising the United Kingdom,
Russia, Prussia, Austria, Sweden,
and other countries collectively attacked Napoleon
in the Battle of Leipzig,
dealing a significant blow to France.
This led to Napoleon's exile
to the island of Elba in 1814.
However, in 1815, he made a dramatic comeback,
rallying his soldiers and marching towards Paris.
Despite briefly reclaiming the throne with public support,
his rule lasted only three months.
The United Kingdom and its allies
waged another war against Napoleon,
culminating in the Battle of Waterloo,
the final battle of Napoleon.
Following this defeat, Napoleon was
exiled to the remote island of St Helena,
where he passed away six years later
in 1821,
marking the end of Napoleon's remarkable story.
What do you think about Napoleon?
Comment below now that you know the entire story.
I hope this video provided you with
a basic understanding of Napoleon,
it'll make the movie more interesting,
since you'll recognise the characters shown in it.
Consider watching this film in cinemas.
It seems quite captivating to me.
I'm definitely planning to watch it.
And now, to understand the French Revolution better,
you can check out this video by clicking here for the detailed explanation.
Thank you very much!