Hello, friends!
On 21st August 1911,
it was a Monday morning in the French capital, Paris.
It was quite bustling.
People were going to work in their offices
when suddenly, three men came out of the Louvre museum.
The three had spent the previous night in the museum.
And now, they were carrying an
important property of the Louvre Museum.
that was hidden in a blanket
while they tried to escape.
They went to a nearby railway station
and caught the train at 8.45 in the morning
and disappeared.
The whole world was unaware of the fact that
they had stolen a painting.
Not an insignificant painting.
The world's most famous painting.
The Mona Lisa.
Today, the value of this painting
is close to $1 billion.
What is the reason behind this?
What are the secrets hidden in the Mona Lisa?
Why is this the most famous painting in the world?
Let's understand the mystery of the Mona Lisa
in today's video.
Mona Lisa was painted in 1503
by an Italian artist Leonardo da Vinci.
And this man was so amazing,
that you won't even believe it.
Not only was he a painter,
but also an engineer, scientist,
sculptor, architect, and theorist.
He had knowledge of so many subjects
be it painting, cartography,
astronomy, anatomy,
botany, hydrology,
geology, optics, or even palaeontology.
An entire video can be made on his life.
So, without talking about him too much,
let's get to Mona Lisa.
Which was his most famous painting.
But who was this person in the painting?
People have always been curious about
the identity of the woman in the painting.
The first revelation about this was made by
an Italian artist named Giorgio Vasari,
who wrote the autobiography
of Leonardo da Vinci in 1550.
According to Vasari, this woman was
Lisa Gherardini.
She was married to a silk trader who lived in Florence,
Francesco Giocondo.
He believed that Francesco had
commissioned this painting of his wife
and that's the origin of the names of this painting.
The first name that we all know,
Mona Lisa,
derived from Madonna Lisa.
Traditionally, in Italian,
the word Madonna was used to mean Madam.
So, Madonna Lisa meant Madam Lisa.
The word Madonna was later shortened to Monna.
Monna with a double N.
When this was written in English
an N was dropped
and Monna became Mona.
So Mona Lisa means
Madam Lisa or Lady Lisa.
And then comes Mona Lisa's other name
which is La Gioconda.
After her marriage, Lisa Gherardini
became Lisa Giocondo.
Interestingly, in Italian, Giocondo means
light-hearted or cheerful.
Meaning, bright and joyful.
And today, Mona Lisa is very famous for her smile.
So that's where it got its name,
La Giocondo.
In French, the word Giocondo is written with a J,
like this, Joconde.
So that's why when you go to the Louvre Museum in Paris
and see the painting of Mona Lisa,
in French, it would be identified as La Joconde.
Now, the interesting thing is that
in 1550, despite this revelation,
people were not ready to believe that
Vasari's narrative was correct.
Many theories started to emerge
about this woman being someone else.
Some people said that she
was Leonardo da Vinci's mother.
Some said that this was a painting
of a queen from the Italian aristocracy.
The most interesting theory was that
in this painting, da Vinci painted himself.
That this painting is not of a woman.
but in fact a self-portrait of Da Vinci.
Where he imagined
how he would have looked had he been a woman.
This theory was promoted by
artist Lilian Schwartz in an article in 1987.
She used digital tools to
try to show similarities between
Leonardo Da Vinci's face
and Mona Lisa's image.
With this logic, any two faces
can be seen as similar by placing them on top of each other.
But today, we can say with a lot of certainty that
the woman painted here
is indeed Lisa Giocondo.
A professor living in Florence
researched this for 25 years
and found the archives
and in 2004, he discovered clear evidence
to prove this fact.
He also found that
the da Vinci family had a close relationship
with Francesco Giocondo's family.
He also found a record that
Lisa's marriage was registered on 5th March 1495
when Lisa was 16 years old
and Francesco was around 30 years old.
He found that Leonardo da Vinci's father
and Lisa's husband knew each other very well.
And it's possible that
this painting was commissioned not by Lisa's husband,
but by Leonardo's father.
Pallanti says that
when the Mona Lisa was painted,
Lisa was 24 years old.
And that there might have been
two reasons for painting this.
The first reason is that in 1503,
when Francesco and Lisa bought their home,
or the second reason is that
in December 1502,
when their second son was born.
The second reason seems more probable
because three years before this, in 1499,
Lisa lost her daughter.
If you look at this painting closely,
you will see a veil over Lisa's hair.
Many people call it a mourning veil.
It is a veil that is worn when
someone in the family has passed away.
Now, one question arises here
if Da Vinci was Italian,
Mona Lisa was Italian,
then why is this painting in France today?
Well, the thing about this is that
in the year 1516,
the king of France, King Francis I,
invited Leonardo da Vinci to live in France.
And so, da Vinci moved from Italy to France.
And took with him the Mona Lisa.
Historical records aren't clear about this,
but it's believed that da Vinci
hadn't completed the painting yet.
15 years after starting the painting,
he was still working on this painting,
trying to modify it and make it better.
Meanwhile, in the year 1519,
Leonardo da Vinci passed away
during his stay in the French palace.
And the king kept this painting
as a part of his Royal Collection.
About 150 years, in 1797,
when the French Revolution happened,
this painting was taken out of the palace
and handed over to the Louvre Museum.
I have made a separate video on the French Revolution
in case you haven't seen it yet,
its link is in the description.
The interesting thing is that
this is the reason why
the Mona Lisa was stolen in 1911.
I had talked about this at the beginning of the video.
The mastermind of this theft was Vincenzo Peruggia.
He stole this painting together with his two friends.
He was an Italian Nationalist.
He believed that this painting belonged to Italy.
Not in France.
And so after stealing it, they took it to Italy.
Stealing such a famous painting was a risky job
especially when the value of
the painting was in millions of dollars.
So, obviously, Vincenzo wouldn't have felt safe after this theft.
But if you want to feel safe and secure about your money
then consider stable investment options
like investing in fixed deposits.
In short, FDs, have been a safe and stable investment for years.
And the sponsor of this video
can help you a lot with this.
Stable Money.
Stable Money is an app
that revolutionises FD investments.
You get access to information from more
than 200 banks and financial institutions.
They have partnered with many banks and NBFCs,
you can see the interest rates of various banks,
and compare options.
And without creating an account in those banks,
you can invest money in
the FDs of those banks through this app.
The best thing is that the barrier to entry is very low.
You can start investing with ₹1,000.
You will have the flexibility
to withdraw your funds whenever you want to without any penalties.
When you invest money through Stable Money,
this money goes to the banks directly,
and they give you FD receipts as well.
Download this app to try it out.
You will find the link in the description and pinned comment.
The first 500 people will get a cashback of ₹250
for investing more than ₹25,000 in FDs through this app.
You can check it out.
Now, let's get back to Vincenzo,
the Italian nationalist.
We will talk about what happens next later in the video.
But before that, let's know the speciality of this painting.
Why is it so special?
First of all,
the Mona Lisa was not painted on paper, canvas or cloth.
Instead, it was painted on poplar wood.
In those days, it was the favourite wood of Italian painters.
Secondly, this painting isn't large.
Look at the photos.
This is where it hangs in the museum.
You can see its size in comparison to the people.
This painting is only 77 cm by 53 cm.
But still, it is considered so special
because, in its time, in Italy,
this was the first painting
which focused so closely on the person.
This is a half-length portrait.
These types of shots are very common in photography today.
But no one used to make such paintings in those days.
If you look at the overall colour grading of this painting,
you will see a lot of brown and yellow shades.
It looks like a very dull painting. It is so yellowish that at one point, a professor declared Lisa a cholesterol patient. But there are two reasons behind this. First, a varnish layer has been applied to this painting so that moisture does not affect the painting badly.
It looks like a dull painting.
It is so yellowish that once a professor
had declared Lisa to be a patient with high cholesterol.
But there are two reasons for this.
First, there is a layer of varnish on top of this painting.
So that there are no ill-effects of moisture on this painting,
since it was painted on wood.
So it's necessary to protect it from humidity and moisture.
And secondly,
over time, there was bleaching.
Originally, when this was painted,
it used to be more bright and colourful.
Some people tried to recreate this painting
to see how it would have looked originally.
Da Vinci used a very special painting style in this painting,
known as Sfumato.
The technique of blending.
The background you see in this painting
is a landscape.
It is the Arno Valley in Italy.
There are no clear boundaries or outlines
between the background and Mona Lisa.
In some places, Mona Lisa's hair is blended with the landscape.
Blurring the outlines and blending the colours
is the technique of Sfumato.
This is the secret behind Mona Lisa's mysterious smile.
Look at Mona Lisa's smile carefully.
The more you look at this smile,
the more serious this face will look.
But now look into Mona Lisa's eyes.
Suddenly, you will see Lisa smiling more.
If you look at any part of the painting,
be it the background, Mona Lisa's forehead or her eyes,
you will see the effect.
Lisa's face starts smiling more
when you don't focus on the smile.
To perfect this smile,
da Vinci spent the most time.
He spent many nights in a hospital in Florence,
where he used to go and remove the skin of d3ad bodies.
He wanted to study the facial muscles and nerves
and how they work together to create a smile.
He wrote in his book that
"the muscles which move the lips
are more numerous in man
than in any other animal."
It was very difficult for him to dissect the muscles of the lips
because the muscles here are tiny and numerous.
During this experiment,
da Vinci studied horses as well.
He compared human expressions to that of horses.
In the notes, he wrote,
"Notice whether the muscle that
raises the nostrils of the horse
is the same as that which
lies here in man."
Hardly, throughout history, any other artist
has dissected the faces of a horse and a human
and done these experiments.
His obsession with Mona Lisa's smile
didn't end here.
After this, he did research on optics as well.
He found that the light rays
don't merge together into a single point on our eyes,
rather they spread out over the entire retina.
The centre of the retina,
known as the Fovea,
helps us see the finest details.
On the other hand, the rest of the retina
picks up shadows and black-and-white imagery more.
Using this knowledge,
he focused on the shadows in such a way that
even when you see the Mona Lisa in your peripheral vision,
as in, if you are looking this way
and Mona Lisa is on the other side,
even if you are not paying attention to Mona Lisa,
the effect of her smile is still there.
When you look at her smile closely,
you will see that its central line is a flat line,
is why when you look at her smile,
it looks like she is not smiling at all.
But on the other hand,
the shadows created using the Sfumato technique,
have such an effect that
when you look elsewhere,
your peripheral vision sees that smile
and its shadows are reflected.
And then you feel that Lisa is smiling.
How would it feel if I told you that
the Mona Lisa is not one painting,
rather two paintings.
This is not a conspiracy theory,
it's the truth.
Mona Lisa's painting, as we know,
a similar painting was created
at the same time.
The story of this second Mona Lisa began
in the year 1504
when another legendary artist named Raphael
made a rough sketch using pen and ink.
This sketch looked something like this
and if you compare it with the Mona Lisa in Louvre,
you can see a huge difference.
In this sketch by Raphael,
you can see two columns behind Mona Lisa.
Here, the researchers believed that
Raphael must have made his drawing based on the Mona Lisa painting.
So, it was initially brushed off.
But this theory was disproved by
a German art historian in 1993.
And Professor Pallanti, whom I had mentioned earlier,
who had been researching the identity of the Mona Lisa for 25 years,
confirmed that Raphael actually
lived right in front of the Giocondo family in Florence.
So, does this mean that Raphael
made an original painting
on the same subject,
with the same woman in the same pose?
This seems quite unbelievable.
Another answer to this question could be that
another Mona Lisa painting exists
which inspired Raphael to make this drawing.
And this second Mona Lisa painting was revealed to the world
in 1914.
A novelist living near London,
John R. Eyer,
had a new version of the Mona Lisa.
This is the new Mona Lisa painting.
The same painting based on which
Raphael made his drawing.
This second Mona Lisa
is 3.5 inches longer
and 5 inches wider than the one in the Louvre.
If you compare these two paintings,
you will notice three things.
First, the woman in this new Mona Lisa
looks much younger.
Second, the head in this new painting
is tilted a little forward.
And third, the expressions of this new Mona Lisa
are very straightforward and clear.
There is nothing mysterious about her smile
that is in the Mona Lisa in Louvre.
The two columns in the background
are the ones seen in Raphael's drawing.
Due to these reasons,
a new theory is coined by the experts.
That Leonardo da Vinci was actually working on two Mona Lisas.
Leonardo da Vinci painted both these Mona Lisa.
But the Isleworth Mona Lisa that was later discovered
was the first version of da Vinci's painting.
He was experimenting with his style then.
And this is why the Mona Lisa in that painting
looks younger than the other Mona Lisa.
This theory remains a topic of debate to date.
In 2010, the Mona Lisa Foundation
started an investigation on the Isleworth Mona Lisa
to find out the secret behind it.
And they came up with another theory.
They said that the face and hands of this new Mona Lisa
were indeed painted by da Vinci.
But the background was painted by an inferior artist.
Perhaps, a person working in Leonardo's workshop
had finished this painting.
Both these theories remain mere theories
because no solid evidence has been found on either side.
Coming back to the theft of the Mona Lisa,
it was found that the mastermind of this theft, Vincenzo Peruggia,
was an employee in the Louvre Museum.
One day, he hid in some corner in the museum
and spent the night there
after which, the next morning, he walked out with the painting.
He believed that since Leonardo da Vinci was an Italian,
this painting should be in an Italian museum.
When the news of the theft spread,
it made headlines all over the world.
Scores of detectives were put to work
to look for the thief.
But no one could find him.
For two years, Peruggia hid this painting at his home.
He wondered what he could do with it.
The whole world was looking for it.
Finally, he became impatient
and tried to sell the painting.
He tried to sell this painting to an art dealer in Florence
To Giovanni Poggi.
Giovanni became suspicious
and saw the stamp on the painting to confirm that
it was the stolen painting.
He was being sold the most wanted item in the world.
Because of this, Vincenzo was caught
and was sentenced to 6 months' imprisonment.
The painting was sent back to the Louvre Museum
and was hung up on 4th January, 1914.
Today, this painting is displayed there,
behind bulletproof glass,
in strict climate-controlled conditions
where humidity is maintained at 50% +/- 10%,
temperature is strictly maintained at 18°C to 21°C.
Perhaps the most interesting part in this story is that
only after this theft
did Mona Lisa's popularity start increasing.
And it became the world's #1 famous painting.
That's right.
Before the theft, the Mona Lisa was not very famous.
People who were interested in art,
knew about the Mona Lisa but
the common folks did not know about the Mona Lisa.
So, if you go to the Louvre Museum
and see the painting of the Mona Lisa
and you see a crowd of people around it,
then you can blame Vincenzo for this popularity.
If you liked this video, you will also like the video on Koh-i-noor.
You can click here to watch the video
where I have explained the mystery of Koh-i-noor.
Thank you very much!