You need to be a little careful.
The law will be enforced any day now..
I am not selling my property, Majumdar
Then form a Trust.
Even that takes time.
All the other landlords are doing it.
Pakhi..
Where were you lost?
How long have you been up?
I have been up for ten minutes,
but you were staring into space,
moving the fan like a statue.
How are you feeling now?
I am feeling fine, thank you.
Did it hurt?
Did I ever tell you
the Bheel Raja story?
No
A long time ago, there lived the..
Mighty Raja of the Bheel tribe.
No one could ever harm him.
Everyone was afraid of him.
The English made many
attempts on his life.
They cut him with swords,
they slit him with a thousand arrows,
but he just wouldn't die.
Then they heard that the Raja..
Confined his 'life' in a parrot.
But there were a thousand
parrots in the forest.
Which one would it be?
Then they sent a spy.
A beautiful one.
The Raja fell in love with her
One fine day she found 'the' parrot.
She got hold of it and...
Then?
Then he died
Pakhi, you are my that parrot.
If anything happens to you..
Stick to the left side.
Slowly.
We don't want to have an accident.
If we get into an
accident then you were driving.
If not then I was driving.
Watch out!
You will get me fired.
Watch out
.. that motor...
What are you doing?
Shh..
Doctor Uncle
Pakhi, you can go home
He is fine now
Ok
Move.
Why
You almost killed
the poor motorcyclist.
You don't know how to drive.
Me?
Then who? Me?
What's wrong?
The filament got damaged.
Filament?
The thing that lights up.
Isn't that electricity?
The electricity lights the filament,
the filament lights up the bulb.
Oh, yes. I knew that.
So whatever it is,
Install it everywhere.
And give the bills to Majumdar.
You aren't being serious.
If the Zamindari Abolishment Act is
passed, you will be left with nothing.
The Act wont be passed, Majumdar.
It will.
There aren't any landlords in
government who will support you.
Why do our fathers keep arguing?
My father feels that Zamindar
uncle doesn't understand him
and Zamindar uncle feels
that my father keeps yakking.
Yakking?
Yes?
My name is Varun Srivastava
Where have you come from?
You stay here.
Babu, someone has come from Delhi,
some 'english' place.
He is an archeologist.
Wants to excavate our temple site
He thinks there is an ancient
civilization buried underneath.
So?
He's coming home for dinner tonight
Ask him yourself.
Varun Shrivastava.
Yes?
Don't look back
The driver who drove into you,
his name is Babu Singh.
Ok.
And what is your name?
Don't try to be smart,
because you are not.
Ok.
Which one are you?
Mr. Srivastava
You are very punctual
This is my daughter, Pakhi
And Pakhi,
he is that gentleman I told you about.
Namaste
She wants to be a writer
She's not bad.
She has written her name
on all my books.
Baba, I am good.
I am sure
So, Archaeologists.
I always thought they were old men.
Busy amidst the cobwebs
of archaic buildings.
I guess that's why the
name starts with 'Archaic'
Where are you staying?
At the Circuit House.
Nearby the temple.
What happened to your head?
My motorcycle had
an accident with a car.
In Manekpur?
Yes.
Who was driving?
I was driving.
If you drive both of
them at the same time..
I was driving the motorcycle.
Coffee?
Yes
And some bad amateur
was driving the car.
Couldn't spot a motorcycle
on such a wide road
I don't think these
amateurs should be allowed..
Sorry. I'll get some cold water.
Sorry about that
Baba Nagarjuna.
Real name Vaidyanath Mishra
Lives in Darbhanga, my native village.
Where did you say, you are staying?
I'm impressed, Varun Babu.
This mansion instead
of that guest house.
Are you understanding anything,
Debdas Mukherjee?
I can understand everything.
My parents talk exactly like this.
Learn Bengali
You'll have to learn one day
Have you seen Baazi?
No
You should watch it...
Now that's what you call a movie.
Dev Anand plays a gambler.
And a moment comes
when he has to choose.
A hell lot of money
or his sister's life.
Or he has to quit everything,
for his love.
He's an amazing actor.
And an even better fighter.
You want to see how he fights?
Like this, while swaying..
No matter how many goons attack him
they will not spoil his hairstyle.
These ruins have remained
untouched for the
last five hundred years.
Nobody is allowed to build
or demolish anything here.
This famous Radha-Krishna idol is..
..the legacy of my
Roy Chouhdry ancestry.
Its at least three hundred years old.
This..
This is where we start excavating.
And we can put up the camp here.
We would need some labourers.
Definitely
So this is where we dig
Do what?
Digging
Good
Now, do you guys know how to dig?
What have we got all this for?
Very good
But why are we going to dig?
Well.. because this is land and..
News from the capital.
In a historic decision today
the government of India..
..announced the
Zamindari Abolition Act.
One of the prominent lawyers
from the High Court..
Mr. Rao added that
according to this Act..
The Landlords will be allowed no more
than fifteen acres for themselves.
Will they seize the orchard?
Yes.
What will they do with it?
Divide it amongst the villagers..
Free fruits for all.
My stomach is growling.
No one eats before
the first fish is caught.
Tradition, you see.
Of course.
You are looking in the
wrong direction, Varun babu.
Are you mad?
I was just looking.
I saw how you were 'looking'
How was i looking?
Its that 'look'
Things happen.
Nothing happens
your hunger has gone to the brain.
Why are u getting upset?
I am just adding to the
stuff you are already cooking up..
I am not cooking up anything.
You are not cut out
for this painting stuff?
Neither are you Raja, nor Ravi Varma.
You carry that blank
canvas everywhere.
But you never put any paint on it.
My dear friend, Debdas
One day I will paint my masterpiece.
And the world will watch.
I want to learn painting.
Why the sudden interest?
Its not sudden.
I've always been interested.
You keep talking about.
I've always told you,
I wanted to learn
You never told me.
I did you never listen to me.
Fine. Ask Majumdar Babu,
he'll get someone
Ask Devyani also
Devyani only wants to cook.
And there's no need
to look for anyone.
Varun Babu is a great painter
Finish your tea.
How do I look?
Very beautiful. Now go.
Now what?
Just go
Have you tried to paint before?
I mean, when you used
to study in Shantiniketan.
You know that I used
to study in Shantiniketan?
No. As in since you
are the Zamindar's daughter.
I learnt a little.
So what do you want to learn from me?
You tell me.
Lets begin with landscapes.
They are easy to grasp.
Then once you get a hang of it..
No. After mangoes and apples,
the first thing
they taught us was Landscapes.
Can't we learn portraits?
You don't think I know
how to paint a landscape?
Shall I show you?
You know how to paint.
I don't know how to paint leaves.
Leaves!
They are really easy
Show me.
Sure
Take some green
Take some black
What is this?
Leaves
This?
Its Modern Art.
You don't know how to paint, do you?
So you are a teacher to him?
For the class to run,
someone has to be a teacher
Someone is too smart for his own good.
I always wanted to learn painting.
And this is a good opportunity. No?
Of course.
My father calls me Pakhi Express
Because I'm always in a hurry
What do you want to do?
I want to write.
Lots and lots of books.
Sometimes, I feel like running away
to our house in Dalhousie.
While the snow keeps falling outside,
Inside I keep..
- Writing, writing and more writing
The Raja there has a big palace.
Jandhrighat palace.
That Raja is very rich.
Much more than my father.
And he also has an
ancient unique Ganesha idol
Is it?
Made of pure gold.
At least five hundred years old.
Do you like what you do?
This is all I know.
I've never known
anything other than this.
If you get a chance
to do something else,
What would you do?
Tell me..
I want to see Chandratal before I die.
Where is that?
Beyond Manali. Deep in the Himalayas.
Clear blue waters, And not a sound.
None at all?
No
And?
I want to paint a masterpiece
that the world will remember.
Really?
Yes. Don't tell anyone.
And if I tell?
It's a flat tyre.
Will take sometime.
What happened?
Pakhi?
Why didn't you tell me?
Pakhi is a good girl.
And you will have to break her heart
She will be shattered when you leave.
And if I say that I love her?
You aren't allowed to love, Mr.
Srivastava
If you want to love,
you need permission.
And that stone-hearted
uncle wont give it to you.
Varun Babu
No class today?
Yes. Our work is about to finish.
There isn't enough time.
We can learn here also.
No. Not here.
No problem.
Tomorrow?
No.
The day after that?
Next week?
I leave next week.
There's a lot of pending work here.
Everyone's waiting for me.
So am I
It would be better if you leave.
It would be best, if you die
They can dig two feet more by morning.
That's not great,
when will the other work happen?
Why are you doing this to me?
Come on get back to work.
What's the matter with you today?
With me? What's the matter with you?
Why are you doing this to me?
It's like you don't want to see me.
Like I'm nothing to you.
Do I mean anything to you?
I leave next tuesday.
And, the time that we spent together?
You wanted to learn painting
And you didn't know how to!
Why did you agree?
You could have said No then.
I was stupid.
Do you love me, Varun Babu?
Please say yes.
Don't think so much. You
did the right thing.
No need to be my guardian angel.
Eat your food
Uncle sent a telegram asking
why is it taking so much time?
Biswajeet Roy, Treasury Department.
What department is this?
There is an official
seal on the letter.
This is ..
The East India Company gifted
that to my grandfather.
Its at least two hundred years old.
Even more
Pal Babu
Put all of these into our van
What are you doing?
All of this is India's heritage
It will go to the National
Treasury and then maybe to the Musuem.
This is my family
heritage. You cant take it.
Whatever the East India
Company gave you was not theirs.
It was all stolen.
If you wont co-operate,
then we will have to arrest you.
Arrest me?
In Manekpur? In my own village?
Pardon me
I'm a government servant not yours.
The world has changed Varun Babu
Its improved for you and ended for us.
I was so used to this way of life.
That even after you
and Majumdar warned me
I didn't think I would lose everything
The country got free
from British yoke..
But that freedom cost us dearly.
You still own a lot of
assets that are very valuable.
I can help you
There are a lot of buyers out there
The government wants to destroy us.
They think we were
friends with the English
But our hands were tied
We gave money to
the Indian National Army
Was it our fault if the Government
didn't accept their fight to freedom?
Call them
Sell everything.
Put that away
Did you hit me?
The Zamindar is ready to sell
Inform uncle
Once the labourers leave tomorrow,
we will start digging
in this direction
All this mud can
be removed and put here
We have to finish this in three nights
Its the first car
I owned very dear to me
Hope you take good care of her
I will
Meet my friend, Varun Srivastava
Hello
Mr. Mukherjee
He's bought my car.
To Calcutta?
Yes today itself
Can Deb go with him?
Ask him, I have no problem
Zamindar Babu,
I'll also be leaving
in a couple of days
The month is up? So soon?
Our work is done. We didn't find anything
All the best
Thank you
Zamindar Babu, I really love Pakhi
I want to marry your daughter
What does your father do?
My parents are dead
I don't even remember them
I have an uncle
He raised me. Taught
me everything I know
Call him here
He wont come
Why not?
He wont allow it
Won't allow what?
Zamindar Babu, we will get
married and go some place else.
I really love your daughter
I'll make sure she stays happy always
I would give my life for her
Please write...
'Zamindar Soumitra Ray Chaudhry
cordially invites you to the..
Engagement of his beloved daughter..
Pakhi Ray Chaudhry
with Varun Srivastava.
Done?
Yes
Mr. Roy Choudhry? - Mr. Bajpai
How was the journey?
Good. Thank you
Some kind of celebration going on?
My daughter is getting engaged
Congratulations
You're getting married to Pakhi?
And what will you tell Bajpai Uncle?
I don't know
So why are you doing all this?
Do you want to completely ruin her?
What are you hiding from me?
Nothing
There is something
Where is the engagement?
At the temple
When?
Tomorrow
Tomorrow?
And our work?
Its your work now. Get it done.
No, its our work
Bajpai Uncle
Congratulations Varun
Heard
Don't bite the hand that feeds you
Uncle, I have to get married sometime
I never got married
How would I have taken
care of you boys, if I had?
I know what you did for us
Taught us everything
I did everything you asked me to
Does she know what
you do for a living?
Why you're here?
Suraj was killed
He was trying to escape
He had two daughters and a son
You know that
This is the life we live
Is this what you want to give her?
I want you in Calcutta tomorrow
We cant afford the luxury
of relationships in our work
You still tried
Don't think I cant tell your
father-in-law what you really are
Good morning gentlemen
Happy?
Congratulations, lets go
Fake, they're all fake
Not a single original note
Dinner is ready
Should I go home?
Yes
Do you need anything else?
No
Ms Pakhi
You know Varun better than anyone
If you wont help then it is
difficult to nab their whole gang.
What happened in Manekpur,
has happened many times before
This gang has robbed millions
from Zamindars and Rajas
Many families have been ruined
Your father wasn't the
only one who died because of them
My father didn't die
because he was robbed
He was heartbroken
He trusted Varun.
If he were alive,
he would want Varun to pay, isn't it?
I don't want revenge, Mr. Singh
I just want to forget him
Ok
If you need anything or..
If you feel like sharing something,
You could contact me on this number.
What are you writing?
Some story?
Yes
What story?
Its just a story
Is there a boy in the story?
And a girl?
Yes
Do they love each other?
No
Are they going to fall in love?
I don't know
The boy wants to know something
The girl isn't talking to him
Is she angry?
Yes
Because he's leaving?
Because he's asking too many questions
So what is she saying?
Don't ask so many questions
So?
Has he stopped asking questions?
He's a fool
Doesn't even understand a thing
Has the boy told the
girl how beautiful she is?
That there's nobody more beautiful
than her in the whole world.
No
Has the girl told the boy
that she loves him the most?
No
So when is she going to tell him?
When?
Dalhousie police station
Can I talk to Inspector K N Singh?
Who s' speaking?
Pakhi Ray Choudhry
KN Singh speaking
He had once told me
that the Raja of Jandhrighat
owns a valuable idol of Ganesha.
Made of pure gold
Maybe their next target
will be in Dalhousie.
Thank you
Ok
Guesthouse available on rent
Its tuberculosis
Its life threatening
You should move to a warm place
You will live longer
Everyone dies some day
What should I live for?
You could write another book
My life is being taken
by what I am writing
There's two men at the gate
For the guesthouse
What should I do?
Show it to them
Who stays out there?
The Lady of the house.
Hello
Ms Pakhi, this is Inspector K N Singh
Yes
I called to inform you that
the gang leader has been arrested
He's confessed that Varun and Debdas
should be reaching
Dalhousie any day now.
We have booked all the
places where they can stay
They will eventually
reach your cottage
As soon as they do, please call me
Excuse me, Mr. Vijay?
What happened?
How do you plan to ship the idol?
By truck
It's on its way from Delhi
And security?
Six of our people
will accompany the truck
And if you wish,
you can send some people too
So how can I help?
We need to take measurements
of the idol for the shipping crate
So if you don't mind,
could we start work tomorrow?
That's it?
We can stay here if you'd like
Come tomorrow
I'll inform everyone here
K N Singh speaking
This is Devender Singh
It's them
Thank you
How many men do you have?
Twelve
Do they all have weapon?
We have .303
I want them all, immediately
Bajrangi, get them ready
He's not answering the phone
Must be asleep
Listen..
Give me a cigarette
We're being followed
You go left, I'll go right
Ok
See you here in fifteen minutes
Follow him
Come with me
Shoot
Have you given him any medicine yet?
Not yet Doctor
How far is it from here?
Five minutes
Is he breathing okay?
Mr. Singh?
He's been shot
Won't be able to get very far
He's in town and he's wounded
Spread the word
Put up his sketch everywhere
I want this man
Keep looking till you find him
Dead or Alive?
You told the police!!
My friend died because of you
I wont let you die so easy
I didn't think you
had any emotion in you
You still don't know a lot, Pakhi.
Please leave, Varun
I need a place to hide
You wont get it here
Leave or I'll call the police
You wont
Close the door, Shyama
Are you mad, Varun?
Did the police stop you?
Did they ask you any questions?
No
Don't try to fool me, Shyama
Your sketch is up everywhere
They're looking for you
You've been accused of
killing a police constable
And they say that
you killed your friend
You killed Deb?
There are shoot-at-sight
orders for you.
Who are you?
He is an avatar of Lord Vishnu, Shyama
With ten names and faces.
I didn't kill Deb on purpose
He was my friend, like my brother
And the police constable?
They were firing at me,
So I fired back It was a mistake.
What was I supposed to do?
I don't believe you
It's the truth
You should have said the truth then,
a lot would have been saved
I couldn't betray Deb and Bajpai Uncle
He raised us,
when we were this little.
I couldn't just abandon them
But you could abandon me
You could betray my trust
You wouldn't understand
You've seen nothing
You've lived in luxury all your life.
You wouldn't understand anything.
Keep it
Use it in the kitchen
Should i call the police?
No.
Why are you trying to save him?
Hello?
Chaubey?
Its Nandu
I will leave tomorrow morning
I'll have to spend the night here
You can call the police, if you want
Zamindar Babu..
Is dead.
How?
You killed him
Like you killed Deb
It wasn't your fault
I am going home
I won't tell the police anything
I came here to run away from my past
To forget everything
Why did you come back to my life?
Why did I allow you to?
Why don't I just kill you,
when you are asleep?
It must give you so
much joy to see me like this
You see that tree?
I stare at it, day and night.
At its leaves that fall
It's like the Bheel Raja's parrot..
It has my life inside it.
The day the..
Last leaf falls..
Is the day I will breathe my last.
This is where you have brought me to
I hope you are ashamed
of living like this
But I know you don't care
As always, all you will do is hide
Nandu!
Its still unsafe outside
I will have to stay
here for a few more days
Tea
I don't want
What are you trying to prove? ..
Nothing
When you should have done..
I went away, I know.
You were surrounded by people.
I know what you want.
Is it? What?
Once wasn't enough for you.
Of course, since you're
looking beautiful these days
I am not joking
I don't know how to make jokes
Why don't you eat something,
then we can..
Just leave
Pakhi
Don't say my name!
Don't shout, you'll get another attack
See, I told you
Why are you..
Shut up
Sometimes I feel like murdering you.
I hate you so much.
But i don't have the strength anymore
I just want to release Varun
from you,
from myself,
from this life
May I come in?
I tried calling, quite a few times
No one answered is everything ok?
Just a little cough
Did you see him or meet him?
Who?
Varun
Why would I meet him?
You said he might come
The guesthouse is still empty
The 'For Rent' board is still there
Yes
Can I look inside?
Do you have a warrant?
Sorry?
I don't have one right now,
but I can get one tomorrow
Then please come tomorrow
Why are you trying to protect him?
I am not protecting anyone
He's responsible
for your father's death,
and he shot one of my men
He will spend the
rest of his life in jail
He might even hang
I'll be back tomorrow with the warrant
I'll have ten policemen
with me who I am leaving outside
If he tries to escape
at night, they will shoot him
If not, then tomorrow I will shoot him
I already shot him once,
He's badly injured but he got away
Not this time
Do you know my real name?
What?
Atmanand Tripathi
You look beautiful when you smile
KN Singh is going to kill you
You know what Deb
would have said to that?
What?
There isn't a KN Singh or Rahman
alive who can ruin Dev Anand's hair
You are not a hero
He wont be able to touch me
I have escaped from much worse
He'll bring the warrant tomorrow
I'll leave tonight
Don't look away Pakhi
Look at me
I know you don't believe a word I say,
But today I'm not lying
I cannot forgive myself
for what I did to you
Only you have the right to do that
But I hate myself
and I will keep hating
myself as long as I live
Did you ever love me Varun?
I did
I still do
You were my only chance
to lead a better life
And I threw it away
Everyone in my life used me
Only you loved me
And I couldn't love you back
This isn't the life
you should be living
Depending on that
last leaf isn't right
It isn't your parrot
And if it falls?
It wont
That's my promise.