- We dumpster dove 100 dumpsters.
It's Chris versus Weddle.
They will take turns to see
who can find the most valuable stuff.
See this guy?
He's a professional appraiser.
He's gonna tell us what
everything's worth.
And whoever makes the most money,
wins $10,000 at the end.
Who wants the first one?
- I'll do it.
- Okay.
- I'll take one for the team.
- Here's your ladder.
You don't have to do
this if you don't wanna.
- No, I need the money.
- [Jimmy] Okay.
- Lamp!
- [Jimmy] Oh, wow.
- Dude, if our appraiser's a moth,
this is gonna be like
worth thousands of dollars.
- This hampers not bad.
- Oh wait, grab that jar of stuff.
- [Jimmy] Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew.
- It's smelly.
(Weddle gags)
Oh, that's smelly.
What if I just
do this right here.
Enjoy your trash, man.
- That was mean!
- [Chris] No, it was an accident.
- I feel this trash can's done.
- What would you pay for it,
if someone brought this
into your pawn shop?
- $2.
- What is this basket valued at?
- Five bucks, it's in-
- [Jimmy And Weddle] Wow!
- pretty good condition.
- What?!
- Mr. Chris, this dumpster's yours.
Cannonball.
Oh gosh.
- Oh god!
- Oh gosh, dude he found-
- [Weddle] What is that?!
- That is luggage
filled with cat poop.
- And it's got folded scrubs
and underwear.
Oh, a straightener!
That's nice.
- Don't, don't.
No!
- Oh, dude, these are nice slippers!
These are L.L.Bean slippers.
- What?!
I shouldn't have let him go first.
- Whoa, look at this!
- Still in the case.
- A phone case!
- This iPhone case is still in the box.
What's it worth?
- Best I can do is $4.
- This thing?
- 10 cent.
$10 for those.
Assuming it's working,
I'd give you two bucks.
- What's this luxury suitcase,
with cat poop, worth?
- I'd give you five for that.
- Whoa.
After one dumpster each,
Chris has made $21.
Weddle has made seven.
All right, Mr. Weddle.
Here's your second dumpster.
- Oh, that's not too bad.
Nope, oy!
Oh!
Calculator!
Yes.
(Weddle yells)
- You found a head
scratcher and a calculator.
- It works.
- Whoa!
I can give you 20 bucks for this.
- Woo!
- What is this, 1990?
You got one on your phone.
- [Jimmy] What is this
head scratcher worth?
- Two bucks.
- That brings your total to $29.
- I'll take it.
- Chris, you are currently losing now.
- But how much am I losing by?
- $8.
- And how many dumpsters has Weddle done?
- [Weddle] Two.
- And how many have I done?
- Hey, let me check the
math with my calculator.
- Hey, the nineties called.
That sucks.
- All right, Chris.
Dumpster number four.
- Before I got in the dumpster,
I found this ring.
- That counts.
- LED light rings.
- [Jimmy] A bagel.
- It's still in the wrapper.
- I don't think you can
take this to a pawn shop.
- I don't know what this is.
(sword unsheathes)
- [Jimmy] Oh my god!
- I found a sword!
Is this a murder weapon?!
Dude, I literally thought
that was just trash.
What?!
(man speaks in foreign language)
- What would you say this ring is worth?
- 50 cent.
- What'd you say this sword is worth?
- 25 bucks for this.
- What do you think those
four ring lights are worth?
- Two of them look burnt out.
$2 for the other two.
So $4.
- What's the mattress worth?
- Uh, that's a box spring.
- Okay.
- [Chris] Oh, he is a professional.
- Five bucks.
- We saved the most
valuable item for last.
A full bagel.
Not eaten, in a bag.
- I'd give you 50 cent.
- Weddle is at $29.
You're at $56.
You are killing the game.
- A sword.
- All right, to the next one.
(upbeat music)
- [Weddle] I'm claiming this sofa.
- This is dumpster number five.
(Weddle squeaks and spittles)
- You guys better your
get cameras for this.
- [Jimmy] Oh!
- Box of stuffed animals.
- I'm here to help.
This is actually kind of valuable.
So what would you say this is worth?
- Three, four bucks for that.
- What would you say these
stuffed animals are worth?
- Eight bucks.
- And finally, what
everyone wants to know.
This guitar, it's slightly gross.
What would you say it's worth?
- If the electronics are working,
I'd give you 90 bucks for it.
- Ooh.
- Oh!
- Sadness.
- What about the sofa?
Its a soft sofa.
- It's very soft.
- And wet.
- It might be worth 10 bucks.
- Okay.
Weddle is now up to $140.
Chris is still on $56.
- Apparently, we like guitars
more than swords around here.
- And calculators.
- I got jibbed.
- Who cares? Next one.
- Chris.
- This has nothing in it.
- That's nothing.
- I see something.
You know what, I'm really
sad Chandler's not here.
He would appraise these
frosted flakes for a lot.
That's not a bad hat, actually.
- This right here is Chandler 2.0.
We FaceTimed Chandler,
because he's preparing for the hospital.
'Cause he has surgery coming up.
Since he's getting ready for
surgery, he can't be here.
So we're gonna FaceTime him,
and he is now Chandler 2.0.
So when we were dumpster diving,
we found a bag of frosted flakes.
What's that worth?
- Uh, at least $3.
- Here's your $3 frosted flakes.
- Oh great and almighty Chandler.
What is this lamp worth?
- $35!
- $35?
What about this soggy, wasted, worn hat?
- That's $15 right there.
- [Jimmy] Oh. Pillowcase?
- [Chris] A nasty pillow case.
- [Jimmy] It can be used to make a ghost.
- A dollar.
- I agree with the dollar.
The rest of it...
He's definitely not a professional.
- [Jimmy] We didn't go into
quite a few of the dumpsters,
because they were either
empty or extremely gross.
- There's nothing in here.
But to my left,
there's a really comfy looking love couch.
- What would you say the value is?
- 13 bucks, it's a little nicer
- All right.
- than that other couch.
- I don't think there's anything in mine
other than just actual trash.
- Oh.
- Can you appraise this?
- I'd give you a dollar.
- Nailed it.
(upbeat music)
- Before you hop in the dumpster.
- Yeah, yeah.
- What is all this outside it?
- [Weddle] Look at this nice couch!
- Another half chair.
All right.
- Whoa.
- [Jimmy] Monitor.
What would you say this is worth?
- 45 bucks.
- [Weddle] Nice!
- Well, what do you think
this monitor's worth?
- 30.
- [Jimmy] What about
this flipped over couch?
- Five bucks.
- Okay.
- Fair enough.
- $221.
- Woo!
So far, you are killing Chris.
- I want to go home.
- I didn't know it spins?!
- Yeah, it does spin.
- Do you wanna add value
now that you know it spins?
- Nope, it's already-
Nope, he said it.
- I'll add 10 bucks.
- No!
I want to go home.
- Next dumpster.
- Ew, get away from that.
- No.
- [Weddle] Oh, this is looking like a dud.
- [Jimmy] Nothing.
That's a hardy nope.
- Oh my gosh.
- Oh!
- I see some shoes.
- Got some really good dress shoes here.
I got a pair of mismatched vans.
More nice dress shoes, man.
- Wow this-
- Oh, this is a good haul.
- At least 15 bucks.
I'll give 13.
12.
Yeah, those are a little more worn.
I'd just give those 10.
- With a pop socket!
- Pop socket makes it nine.
- Nice!
- [Weddle] Yeah, what's
Chris at, what am I at?
- The totals are on the top of the screen.
- Oh, okay.
- What if-
- He was like,
you guys are idiots,
Ethan put it right there.
- [Jimmy] Oh, it's literally nothing.
- [Chris] Good dumpster!
- There's nothing here.
Nothing.
Only one of you is
walking away with $10,000.
I'm gonna raise it to $12,000.
- Huh!
- Yeah, I see Q-tips,
I see (indistinct).
- Are these chairs?
It is a chair.
- It works.
- What do you think the mattress is worth?
- 25 bucks.
- [Jimmy] Beat up chair.
- That's at least 15 bucks.
- Propane tank.
- 12 bucks.
- You can get 'em refilled.
On Pawn Stars they have to call their guy.
Call your guy.
Are you sure?
- Don't give it to 'em.
- He's saying 20.
- Okay, I'm fine with that.
- [Man] Times that by
two, there's a second one.
- Oh!
- Oh, there is a second one.
- That's more.
- This
is probably worth about 25.
- Hey, I'll take it!
- Woo!
- Chris
just demolished you.
- I did.
I did just get destroyed.
- 29 looks like a bust.
Nothing in here except for a pillow.
I don't really want to go after a pillow,
because there's a big ticket item.
(Chris groans)
- Mr. Appraiser, what
do you think it's worth?
- 40 bucks.
- There's nothing in here either.
There's really nothing in here.
- Look how empty it is in here!
- I think I'm gonna get outta here.
Oh wow.
Some milk.
- You have $330 so far.
You have $231.
- Yep.
- We called in Chandler 2.0 again.
Chandler, you have $100 credit.
Who do you want to give it to?
You can give 50-50.
You give it all to one.
Chris is winning,
by a hundred exactly.
- Well, let's make it a tie.
- [Weddle] Ooh.
- [Chris] Good luck with your surgery.
I hope it goes terrible.
- Thank you, oh great and
almighty Chandler 2.0.
You can go.
- Because you did that,
your surgery will go well.
(upbeat music)
- The only thing my dumpster has in it
is ants.
- This is dumpster 45.
That's dumpster 46.
- I want those cherries.
Tomato cherries.
Got 'em.
- [Jimmy] Ooh, is that a pen?
Pen for the-
- That looks good.
- middle school.
- Weddle found some cherry tomatoes.
What is that worth?
There's an ant in it.
- [Appraiser] That actually
increases the value.
I'd give that 10 bucks.
- Nice!
- Chris found the pen.
- [Appraiser] Uh, five bucks.
- So there's two dumpsters.
You guys have had a long day.
- We have.
- I want you to pick,
and I'll search both for you guys.
- Oh, wow.
- Really?
- Okay.
- I call this one.
- All right, I'll get that guy over there.
- All right, you guys
wanna just sit there?
Can someone get them some water?
Here you go, gentlemen.
- Oh, wow.
- Here's some water.
Here's some money.
Just feel free to split it.
- Wait, aren't you also the appraiser?
- Yeah.
- Wait a second.
- There's a giant furniture thing.
I can't get it out.
Oh, Chris, we found the mother load.
(bomb explodes)
Oh!
- It's knowledge!
- [Chris] Who would throw
away all these books?
- Hey, hey, more about me.
(men laugh)
Go sit down.
I got this.
- [Weddle] Sorry, I can't.
- [Jimmy] Do you see anything
I should be searching?
- [Weddle] Oh god, um...
- [Jimmy] Oh, here's a package.
It's empty.
- What's over there?
Something looks wrapped up.
- It's empty.
- [Weddle] It's empty?
- Our appraiser apparently
had a lunch date
with his grandma.
- What a loser.
- Dork.
- So I'm taking over for the appraiser.
Chris, you found a lot of books.
- [Chris] Yes.
- This book is worth $10.
(bell dings repeatedly)
- It's a book of jokes!
- [Jimmy] How much would
you pay for those jokes?
- $100.
- Let me try out one of the jokes,
and then you tell me what
it's worth, all right?
- Yeah, and if they're funny
- All right, let's find out
how funny this is.
- then we're good.
- Why was the belt arrested?
Because it held up a pair of pants.
- Based off that joke.
The books worth 30 bucks.
These cushions are $2.50 a pop.
- What kind of coat does a house wear?
A coat of paint.
(Chris laughs)
- All right, it's now $25.
The total from this dumpster was 96 bucks.
Let's see what Weddle's got.
Having fun?
- I got bubble wrap!
- But that's not even real bubble wrap.
Look, you can't pop it.
(bubble wrap pops)
- [Jimmy] Someone found bubble wrap.
What is it worth?
- [Chandler 2.0] A dollar per bubble
that is still intact.
- [Jimmy] Well, how about 50 cents?
That seems more reasonable.
I'm gonna round up,
I'm gonna say 40.
- Nice, keep it competitive.
- Wait, hold on.
How many is in a line?
- If you do this, you're gonna regret it.
- All right, $40.
- So these are currently the numbers.
You're at $421.
What do you wanna do?
- I wanna give him a dollar.
- I'm at $385.
- Okay.
Yours just went down a dollar.
- Yeah, that's fine.
Now it's $420.
Nice.
(whimsical music)
I found a bike back here earlier
and I've been waiting.
- It's a rust bucket.
It does work though.
- What a dream!
- I got chargers!
And I got this sofa.
- Chris, bring your bike on back here.
- Oh, I'm not done yet.
I found this.
It's near the trash.
- $70 for the bike.
$40 for the ladder.
- I'm killing it.
- And a couch.
- Okay, so, that's $3.
This is a nice couch.
60 bucks.
- Okay.
- [Chris] There's a leg missing.
- The leg is missing.
It's not 50 bucks.
Chris is at $530.
You're at $430.
- I am.
(whimsical music continues)
- So this is dumpster number 55.
- A duck!
- Oh my goodness.
How much would you pay for it?
- Oh my god!
- 25 bucks for it.
- Whoa.
- Ducks!
- That means you just got $75.
- I would only pay like $10 for this one.
- All right, that's everything in here.
- If you had $100, who
would you give it to?
- The yellow hat.
- That's what I get for-
- Yellow hat guy?
- [Weddle] Wait, you throwing away the TV?
- Yeah.
- Oh no, he threw away a TV.
Here I go.
Hey Jimjam!
Oh!
- 70 bucks.
- All right.
(whimsical music)
(bell dings repeatedly)
- 69!
- Number 69!
Nice!
(whimsical music continues)
(bell continues to ding repeatedly)
- Oh, what is that?
- Oh!
- Doesn't smell at all.
- I could give that to a kid!
- Can I give it to my girlfriend
as a present?
- Yes, you can.
- Worth 50 bucks.
- Nice!
That's a nice TV right there.
- This TV's pretty thick.
- I'd give you 90 bucks for it.
- [Chris] 90 bucks, that's fair.
- That was a spicy meme.
- I'll give you two bucks for that.
- I'll take it.
- Wow.
Who wants to get in the dumpster?
Pay you like 50 bucks
at the end of the day.
- It's a full box of lettuce.
Nice water bottle.
- Ooh!
What do you think about my salad?
Here, I'll toss it.
- [Jimmy] There we go.
- Eight bucks.
I'd say 25 with the customization.
- There we go.
- You are losing, Chris.
So take your pick.
- Okay, got her, this one.
- Really, that one?
- Hey, this is a mattress topper.
These are worth a lot of money.
(upbeat music)
- Chris had a massive haul.
- He has a living room.
- What would you say this is worth?
- $13.
- Big table?
- Easily worth 55 bucks.
- All right.
- 55? Okay.
- 18 bucks for the gas can.
- 35 bucks for the-
- 35?
- 19, 20 bucks.
I give it 20 bucks.
- We'll do 20.
- 20.
- Wow.
- Chris, you are currently in the lead.
Weddle, there's only 15 dumpsters left.
And as of right now,
- I know.
- Chris would walk away with 12 grand.
How do you feel now that
you could win $12,000?
- Better.
- This dumpster is so big,
we're actually gonna count it as four.
Weddle and Chris get to
go in at the same time.
(indistinct overlapping chatter)
- For your plants.
- [Cameraman] Chris,
why are you out of this
big dumpster already?
- I'm terrified of rats.
And I saw a rat.
And so I refuse to go
anywhere near this dumpster.
- I'll carry the torch.
This lot will close at,
what does that say?
- [Man] 8:00 AM on 9.16
left cars will be towed.
- Here you go, Chris.
- [Chris] Thanks.
- Let's start off with Chris.
What is this worth?
- Well, seeing as it's only worth anything
on one day outta the year,
I'll give you 10 bucks.
- And my planter?
- Seven.
- Sweet.
- Pretty good.
This crap?
- Chains are actually pretty expensive.
So I'd probably give you 20 bucks
for a broken chain.
(Weddle laughs)
- There's a sprocket and a little filter.
All right, I'd give you
five bucks for that.
And five bucks for-
- I'm gonna give you $5
'cause he knows what a
sprite, sprok, sprocket is.
- It's a sprocket right there.
- Eight for that.
- Chris is currently in the lead by $37.
So if this trend continues,
Chris is gonna win the 12 grand.
There are three dumpsters here.
Two of them are Weddle's.
One of them is Chris.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- Hey!
- [Chris] Ooh!
- Listen. Listen, dad.
- [Jimmy] Wow.
- Oh my god!
- Heelys!
- Heelys.
- We have like 20,000.
- That's too much.
- That's two bucks.
- Weddle got 60 bucks for his bubble wrap.
- But my bubbles were better!
I had better bubbles!
- I'm not saying
there's cheating going on, but-
- What do you say this TV is worth?
- It was a hundred bucks.
- All right, Chris.
- Heelys?!
Are you kidding me?!
- Five bucks for 'em.
For the box.
Just the box.
- Let's move on to Weddle.
- [Weddle] All what's this worth?
- An umbrella? 35 bucks.
- $35.
- I'll give you eight bucks for the box.
But the stuff in the box-
- We got a candle.
- Eight bucks for the candle.
(bell dings repeatedly)
- Nine more dumpsters
stand between you guys and 12 grand.
- Nine!
Hey!
That's a Victoria's Secret purse.
- They call us ranch,
'cause we be dressing.
- I see it's Hidden Valley.
So I don't even know how you found it.
(both laugh)
Three bucks.
For the one that doesn't look used.
- E.C.U. t-shirt.
- Wash 'em, and I'd give
you 10 bucks for the pair.
And what about our clothes hamper?
- All right, five bucks.
- All right.
- Again, you want to
put your kids in a room
but you don't want to deal with 'em?
- $15.
- $15, nice.
We have-
- Eight bucks for these two.
- Those two.
- 10 bucks.
- Nice.
- Since Chris is winning.
You can pick.
- Nice.
What is this bread worth?
- $2.
- What's this worth?
- Nine bucks.
- Nine bucks, okay.
What's this? This is for a microwave.
- Six bucks.
- Universal fit.
- Here's the scores.
Five more.
96, 97, 98.
Chris gets all the evens.
(bright music)
You each have one more dumpster.
$12,000 is on the line.
- Appraise me.
- Appraise him.
- Is there a disc in this?
- Don't open it.
Don't open it!
- No disc.
- Why did you open it?
- Wouldn't say trash, but three bucks.
- Three bucks.
- Three bucks!
- There's shoes in here.
Don't open it.
It's a nice shoe box, so two bucks.
- It's a poop box.
It's a litter box.
I've got hangable blinds.
- Seven.
Six.
That's probably seven
bucks a piece, honestly.
(tense music)
- $1,479.69.
Weddle, $1,415.
$57.79 stand between you and 12 grand.
Final two dumpsters.
I'm thinking of a number
between one and two.
Pick a number.
- One.
- One and a half.
- Obviously he picks two,
'cause it's the only thing left.
- Okay, that's what was in my hand.
- I would've won anyway.
- Which one do you want?
- This one, it's got its roof on.
It's a mystery.
Oh, that's an empty one!
- That's worth a lot.
It's busted.
- It's pretty.
- First is a Just Fab's shoebox.
If you've ever wanted to feel Just Fab,
look at it, who's just fab?
You are.
- A dollar.
- All right.
- Leather phone case.
- That's a good 25 bucks, right there.
- There you go.
On eBay, iPhone XS
boxes are going for $40.
- [Weddle] Just the box?
- Just the box.
- Yeah.
- So, 30 bucks for the box.
- And next, police caution tape.
You can hang it on your
door for Halloween.
- A dollar.
- Mr. Appraiser, come on over here.
- A shower curtain.
- Three bucks.
- Fair enough.
- Two bucks.
- Olive oil.
- Olive oil bottle.
69 cent.
- Nice, finally.
- Nice, nice.
Before we reveal the totals,
I wanted to teleport us to
the warehouse real quick,
with all the items they found,
so you could see.
Chris, on this $1 bill
is written your total.
This is your total.
Weddle, please read us your total.
- I found $1,421.59
worth.
- Chris,
what was your dumpsters worth?
- $1,531.69.
I haven't won in so long.
It feels so good.
10 smackeroonies.
- Yeah!
- That's $10,000.
This is $1,000.
$1,000.
$12,000.
The viewers wanna know,
how are you gonna make
him feel not terrible?
- I'm gonna take him to the mall,
and I'm gonna treat him like a king.
- Wow.
- Are you actually?
- Yeah.
There you go.
- Oh!
- All right.
- Whoa!
Oh, he keeps-!
- Hey, we're gonna stop this joke!
- He's gotta stop!
- All right, let's go to the mall,
and let's ball out, buddy.
- Woo!
♪ MrBeast, oh ♪