My name's Rangeeli.
The name's Rangeeli.
I have a sharp tongue.
My work is neat and clean.
And I am sharp
to count the bills.
No one can trick me.
I am a storm.
So should I say all that again
or come to the point?
Whoever you are.
Rangeeli or whatever.
Why should we care?
Tell me something.
How dare you enter
our house shamelessly like that?
Hasn't anyone taught you?
When elders are talking,
you should not stick
your big nose in it.
Never mind.
Now that you have asked,
let me answer it.
What happened is
I was walking down the street.
And I heard the sweet
melody of a Lord Krishna prayers.
So I thought let me
enjoy that.
Look,
God doesn't discriminate.
Everyone is welcome to his abode.
Say it aloud,
Glory to Lord Krishna.
Stop the nonsense.
Let me make it
clear to you.
This is our home
and not some temple or charity home
where you can just barge in.
Get lost.
Firstly, I feel only you do
the talking here.
Okay, Let me get to the point.
A little birdie told me
that you need a hard-working,
smart maid.
But I do not work for anybody
or everybody.
Before I start working,
I make sure I know each member well.
Actually with God's grace,
I am here anyway.
So I'll stay here
for a few days.
And better your lives too.
You are mistaken.
We don't need a maid.
Mister, you should never be hasty
when it comes to your needs.
If I leave,
I'll not come back
for anyone or anything.
Very good.
So you better leave.
We don't need you. Out.
Hey!
Liar, liar.
You shouldn't lie.
Well, the moment I saw this house,
I understood there is a lot that needs
to be fixed in this house.
It is full of filth.
I mean I'll have
to clean every corner of this house.
I have had enough of your nonsense.
Get lost.
Don't you get it?
We don't need a maid.
Get lost.
- Out...
- Don't touch me.
Vinu.
Did you see that?
She is a mere servant.
But has the attitude
of the boss.
You are the elder
of this family.
Your face...
From your face,
I can say that you
call the shots here.
Tell them to hire me.
Dadiya.
Just Dadiya.
Dadiya, there is no dearth
of work for me.
But the thing I am facing
a financial crunch now.
In short, I need work, desperately.
I am a girl from a poor family.
So I am looking for work
in order to sustain myself.
This girl is amazing.
On one hand,
she is begging for work.
On the other hand,
she is disrespecting my mother.
Stay within your limits, girl.
All this coming from an uncouth like you...
Enough. I have shown
you enough respect.
I have had enough
of your ranting.
If you want respect,
learn to speak respectfully.
You are so silly, Rangeeli.
You are expecting her
to show respect.
Dadiya, tell me.
Will you hire me?
No.
We do not need a maid.
Leave.
Don't say that.
Look, I can do all the chores.
Cleaning, mopping,
doing the dishes.
From oil massage
to polish the shoes.
I can do everything.
I will apply the orange peel
to your face
and make you look so radiant
that you will put
these young people to shame.
Please, Dadiya.
Will you hire me?
Please.
Listen pretty girl,
I find you to be the prettiest
and the most sorted in this house.
I am sure,
everyone listens to you.
Tell them to hire me, please.
I said,
we don't need you.
Stop your nonsense
and leave.
Heard that?
We don't need a maid.
Take your things and leave.
- Come on.
- Stop, Aunty.
Dadiya, it is a virtuous thing
to help the needy.
I wonder why I feel
we should hire her.
You are right.
But hiring someone
without verification
or without knowing her
is not right.
Yes, Dadiya.
It's 'Janmashtami' today.
An auspicious day.
And it is not right to turn a needy
away on a festive occasion.
You have a point.
Hey, girl, come here.
You can stay in our house.
[Sanskrit chants]
But you will talk less
and work more.
You will work very hard
with complete earnestly.
Can you do it?
You're amazing, Dadiya.
Don't bother.
Get up.
Make her understand.
If she wants to stay here
then she should talk less.
I dislike people
who talk much.
Let's go, Nishu darling.
It's Dadiya's orders,
so I will accept it.
But remember this.
Stay away from me.
Do not give me
that attitude.
I am least interested
in messing with you.
'Thank You, Lord Krishna.'
'You made them
change their minds'
'and got me the permission
to stay here.'
'Now I will avenge every injustice
and oppression I have suffered.'
'Just as Lord Krishna slew Kansa
and eliminated the evil.'
'I have to eliminate evil
from this house.'
'I have to find out
the reason'
'why my husband
betrayed me.'
'That's why your devotee Siddhi
as entered'
'this house in this disguise.'
'And I am not leaving
this house until'
'I find the answers to my questions.'
'This girl doesn't seem
to be what she appears to be. '
'Why do I feel'
'she wants something from here?'
'I got her hired
so that I can know all her secrets.'
'I must find out everything
about this girl.'
Vinayak.
[Sanskrit chants]
Siddhi, you?
Destiny gives
everyone a chance.
Yesterday, it gave you the chance
to commit a crime.
And today, it is giving me
the chance to punish.
I am Siddhi.
And I have come back
to exact revenge.
[Sanskrit chants]
You remember your sin, right?
You tried to kill me
by pushing me off the cliff.
because I am dark-skinned
and not pretty.
You tried to kill me
because you desired my pretty sister.
You were my husband.
But you discriminated against me
because of my skin colour.
You disrespected
the sacred bond of marriage.
[Sanskrit chants]
I am sorry.
I wanted to get rid of
my dark-skinned wife.
You are ugly
to say the least.
And I am the dream man
of every girl of Agra.
I love your sister Maya
and not you.
I never expected such a betrayal
from you, Vinayak.
So, you will get an unexpected
punishment too.
You tried to kill your wife only
because she is dark-skinned.
You have committed
a crime.
You have disgraced
the sacred bond of marriage.
And now you will have
to admit your crime.
Thank you.
I could get into this house
only because of you.
This has been possible
This is your battle.
I am just supporting you.
What are your plans now?
I have planned it all
and I will be executing it soon.
Oh, my.
The kitchen is so dirty.
Dirty dishes?
Raghu, Mamta, where the hell are you?
Just a sec.
We have a new maid now.
What's her name?
Chhabili?
No, it's not Chhabili.
It's Rangeeli.
Damn it.
I guess she must be
sleeping soundly.
Very good.
She made such tall claims.
But she is good for nothing.
Sushma, it's time
to do what you do best.
Today, I'll do something
that makes her shudder even
at the sight of me.
There was a girl with Vinayak
on the cliff that day,
who was whistling like this.
I don't know who she is
or why she was
supporting Vinayak?
And that's why I have come
here posing as a maid.
Because a wife
can bear anything
except for betrayal
by her husband.
This smoke
will teach Rangeeli a lesson,
she'll never forget.
If that girl is colluding
with Vinayak,
I am sure she is still
in touch with Vinayak.
I must find out
who that girl is.
I swear.
There must have been an
earthquake the day you were born.
Because your intentions, mind
and heart and your actions are evil.
That's why you tried to
suffocate me with this smoke.
Should I tell your mother
about your misdeeds?
Shut up.
Never mind complaining about me.
Get ready to face the music.
Let's go.
Hey, you snob, where are you...
Do you see these dirty dishes?
They are craving
a thorough cleaning by you.
And this mess here.
Only Rangeeli is going to clean it.
Do you understand?
You are the maid.
Don't try to be the boss here.
You think you can freeload, right?
You have a sharp tongue.
So now start using your hands
and clean the house.
The maid wants to be the boss here.
Great.
The belch tells me
that you have stuffed yourself.
You have stuffed yourself
but you want to keep your maid hungry.
Let me be clear.
I'll eat and then do the work.
Glory to Lord Krishna.
As you wish.
- Maya.
- Here, have some milk, Rangeeli.
Thank you, pretty madam.
I knew it.
You are the only one
in this house who understands me
and can help me succeed
in my efforts.
Hold on.
She can't have the milk.
Let her finish her work first.
I am going to have it.
Aunty...
'I got it to find out
Rangeeli's secrets.'
'But the stupid woman
drank it instead.'
Oh, God.
What the hell was in the milk?
What happened to her?
She's smoking like Chandrayaan-3
from her ears and mouth.
Do something, Maya.
I'll die.
Have some water.
And have the sweet kept
as the offering.
You will feel better.
Yes, I am going.
Oh, Lord.
I don't know why
she was fluttering around.
You know what?
Let me clean up this mess.
How did you know that
the cleaning items are kept there?
You have never been
in this kitchen before, right?
Tell me the truth.
How can anyone know
so much in such a short time?
'Maya, I feel you'll catch me.'
'But I have come here
to save you from my evil husband.'
I am sure you know something
about us and this house.
Nothing like that.
Anyone can guess
where these things could be.
And as far as
she is concerned,
let's assume that God has sent
me here to punish her
for her evil deeds.
How do you know
that Aunty's evil?
You don't even know her.
Anyone can guess
that she's a malicious woman.
Can you please move,
I have to clean this.
'She is very sharp.'
'I need to keep an eye on her.'
'On one hand,
is your hatred,'
'which I could never see
in your eyes or heart.'
'You hated me so much
that you tried to kill me.'
'And then there is me.'
'I want revenge.'
'But I still love you
just as much. '
'I feel like giving
you a tight hug right now.'