- Chris, can I borrow your phone?
- Yeah, sure.
You need to text somebody.
Oh, you dropped it.
- Yes.
And notice how it's okay?
- Yeah, it's fine.
- But what if we dropped
it from a hundred feet?
- Let's not.
- Or a thousand feet, or even 10,000 feet?
- How are you gonna
drop it from that high?
- We're gonna start things off
by dropping a Mac Mini
onto a Mac from five feet
- Mac Attack. Big Mac!
- Mac on Mac.
- On the Mac. Mac squared.
- All right.
As you can see with the
slow-mo, it crushed the Mac.
- I liked not only the
slow-mo, but the 360 cam.
- Now we're gonna drop a
watermelon from 15 feet.
- All right.
I don't know how we got from
Mac computers to watermelon.
- All right, Chris.
The watermelon's about to fall.
So we just dropped the watermelon and boom
- Figure out.
And it exploded into like a
million pieces. That was--
- A million?
I don't think so.
- That was more like a hundred thousand.
You thought that was cool, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, here's a car falling
on a car from 50 feet.
- Whoa. It squashed it!
- Wow. They have so many different angles.
- They do have so many.
- What's more impressive
than them lifting up the car
is getting that many cameras.
Now we're gonna drop a car
from 65 feet and see how
high it launches a human.
- Wait. A human?
- A fake human.
- Oh, okay.
Is that Naruto?
- Yeah!
- It does look like Naruto.
- Yo.
- Wow. It still hasn't fallen yet. Boom!
- He's so excited.
- I know. I love how happy they get.
And speaking of Naruto,
I may have a really special
clap coming up soon. Shh!
- Wait, what?
- Now we're gonna throw a piano
off a building from 80 feet.
- I'm ready.
- Two, one. Boom.
- Piano!
- Bro, if it doesn't make
the do, do, do sound.
- Cartoons lied to me.
I'm supposed to hear the sound
of all the keys going ---!
- I know.
Whoever did the experiment,
thank you for opening our eyes.
- Thank you.
- Cartoons lie.
Now we're gonna drop a
hundred thousand bouncy balls
from 85 feet.
I love how this is just a how
ridiculous reaction video.
- Pretty much.
- Oh my gosh.
Give me the side angle.
- Whoa, yo.
Oh, that's so cool.
Oh and they're seeing
who can catch the most
in remote control cars.
- If you guys weren't in Australia,
I'd literally be in every video.
- Oh, that's right.
We have to fly across the entire world.
- Exactly, bro.
You could offer me a billion dollars
and I still wouldn't fly to Australia.
- Jimmy, I'll give you a billion dollars.
- I'm not flying Australia.
Now we're gonna drop a
PlayStation from a hundred feet.
- Wait a minute.
- Oh my gosh.
Wait, that's a really cool shot.
- I've seen this guy drop an iPhone down.
- Woo.
- On the PlayStation5 Guys
- Look at that.
That's how you get the skin off of it.
- My male testosterone is spiking.
- I'm angry.
I could have eaten that PlayStation 5.
Does it still work, is the question?
- Nah,
- Ain't no shot.
Dropping a sword 120 feet.
Oh, do you think it stabs into the ground?
Like anime style?
- Let's see.
The swords falling.
It's still falling.
Oh!
- In the middle!
- Oh through paper.
- Wow. That's hard to stab
through that much paper.
That's crazy.
That's like, he's coming
from space and he is like...
- Now we're 125 feet up
and we're gonna drop an
iPhone covered in concrete.
Let's see it.
All right, what happens? And boom.
- Oh. Oh, they got disintegrated.
- The concrete did, did
the iPhone shatter though?
- Wow. Look at the metal on this thing!
- Not only is it shattered,
it's like cut into,
- Oh, okay.
- 'Cause all the rocks.
- Dang. Okay, now let's
go ahead and try turning
this thing on.
- Yeah, go ahead. Try it.
- No response at all.
- Shocker.
- Good to know. Good to know.
You do not need a concrete
case to protect your phone.
Now we're up to 150 feet.
- That's a lot of feet.
- All right. It's coming up on the cliff.
- Whoa! Oh, those people are close.
Oh, that's a giant!
- Yo, look at that shot.
Now we're gonna drop a car on an ax.
- So we saw a sword get
dropped onto something.
Now we're seeing something
get dropped onto an ax.
That was a good camera angle.
I like that first one, to like tease us.
Get us ready for it.
And this is the one that just makes us--
- Ooh!
Bro. That tower's crazy.
- That's so cool.
Kind of missed a little bit though.
- Yeah.
- I'm not gonna lie.
- Actually just do it again.
All right. Now it's an
airplane versus trampoline
from 200 feet.
- What? Where do they get an
airplane from and a trampoline?
You know, they're just
sitting in a big office
with a bunch of bean bags and
somebody's like, airplane.
And they're like, all right,
what we dropping it on?
And somebody's like, trampoline.
And they're like, all right, run it.
- Let's do it tomorrow.
- Tomorrow, run it.
- Now we're gonna take a water balloon
and drop it from a 300-foot skyscraper.
- Every kid has wanted to do this.
This kid had the balls to do it.
- They say if you drop a penny
off the Empire State Building,
it could kill someone.
- Yep.
- So what if you drop
a water balloon off it?
Let's find out.
Holy!
- Wow.
Okay, good.
He's got a second angle.
- That sounded like a rock.
- It'd be so fun just to drop
a thousand at the same time.
- Oh yeah.
- On Carl, as he is walking by?
And then just run away
and never say we did it.
I can't wait
until we get to the 10,000
foot drop at the end of
this video.
That's gonna be insane in the membrane.
- Now we're gonna take a
giant rock and drop it.
467 feet.
- Wait, the wrestler,
Dwayne the Rock Johnson?
- You can literally see it on your screen.
- Oh my God.
Wait, he's got so many
movies he's gonna be in.
Don't do it!
- I refuse to play the
clip until you stop.
- It's a funny joke.
- Get him out. Get him outta your system.
- Alright, all right.
- Jumanji. Action. Bald. Big.
- Let's see it.
I wanna see it.
- All right. It's falling.
It's falling.
Oh my God.
- Still falling.
Holy crap.
- Oh my gosh.
- Ahh!
- That's it. We're outta here!
- This guy is throwing
$10,000 out of an airplane.
He's making it rain.
- Wait a minute.
- So does Honey.
Honey is the number one
shopping tool in America
and scours the internet for
coupon codes when you check out
online to make sure you
get the best deal possible.
- But wait a minute, Jimmy,
this sponsorship couldn't have come
at a better time because I
wanted new roller blades.
- That's convenient then.
It's as easy as going to
your favorite online store
adding roller blades to your cart
and then watching Honey
search the internet
for coupon codes and then
automatically applying them.
- But wait! What if I'm on the go?
- I'm glad you asked.
Honey is available on mobile too.
- Why am I here?
- How much does it cost?
- I'm scared.
- Tell me!
- Shut up!
How much my ears hurt.
- How much?
- How much does it cost?
- How much?!
- Nothing, Honey is free to install.
- That's !
- So go to joinhoney.com/beastreacts
That's joinhoney.com/beastreacts
and install it right now.
- Do it!
- Now we are in a
helicopter dropping Legos.
What's gonna happen?
- Oh, a Lego red arrow.
- Yeah.
- They did this solely for the thumbnail.
- Okay, he's dropping it.
- Oh no you fumbled the bag so hard.
Fumbled it so hard.
- We won't even know what it's
like when it hits the ground.
- Oh no.
- Even he's like, "Oh, I messed up."
Imagine renting a helicopter
going through all that trouble
and then you just hit it on the side.
- A whole day's work and
then just ruined instantly.
- Yeah, that was still epic.
You know what?
I still give it a nine outta 10 for epic.
- I was gonna say eight.
- Now we're gonna drop another car.
But from 500 feet.
- This is different 'cause it's higher.
This doesn't look like it
was like a planned thing.
It looks like this guy just picked
up this car and is gonna drop it.
Oh no. Wait. This is Top Gear.
I love Top Gear so much.
- I'm not an nerd.
All right. Let's see it fall.
It's still falling.
Adds enough time to cut to
other people while it falls.
- It's still going.
- Boom. Did that satisfy
your male instinct?
- Ooh!
- Now we're gonna drop a giant
inflatable ball off a dam
into the YouTube employee watching.
That's a dam as in the
thing that holds back water?
- Oh, I was gonna say...
- Not the bad word.
If I see a yellow single
on this video, I will sue.
Okay.
- I'm so intrigued for
what's gonna happen.
- Imagine he just fell off the,
- I was thinking the same
thing 'cause he put a lot
of effort into that.
- He was willing to go all in.
Imagine he falls off with it, but then he
he's riding the top of it
and he bounces up and somehow survives.
- He bounces all the way back
up to the dam and he is like,
all right, let's do it again.
- Or just bounces up and
down until it stops bouncing.
He's just like, all right.
- I love watching it.
Just like,
it can't really do that much.
- Oh no, it didn't speed.
I love hearing Australian people talk.
Okay. That angle is way--
- That's funny.
All right, now we're 1500 feet in the air
and this mannequin's gonna get
kicked outta the helicopter.
- Oh, it's MythBusters.
- Ladies and gentlemen, this
is a Mythbuster's control.
- All right, so what are we myth busting?
What happens if you fall
out of a helicopter?
- I think we already knew.
He said it was a control though.
Maybe this is just to see
like the speed of how fast
a human drops.
- Dang.
- Oh, he hit,
- He hit hard.
I think it's time to say it.
- Say it.
- Mannequins take a lot of flack.
They do things that we
don't wanna do as humans.
- Yeah, that's true.
- And I think it's time
someone stands up for them.
- It better not be you
because there's a shipping
container with a thousand
mannequins jammed in it right now.
- You're right.
I do own a lot of mannequins.
You know what?
I'm no better than the rest of you.
Now we're gonna drop a Nokia from the sky.
Now here's the thing.
We all know Nokias are indestructible.
- Oh, the old, old joke
that everybody's heard
a hundred thousand times,
what do you think is gonna happen?
- Seeing how it's 1500 feet in the air?
I do think it's gonna break.
If this still works?
- What if it breaks the ground?
Where is it?
- What if just goes through Earth?
Did they lose?
- Whoa, my, they're all laughing.
But anyone could have been
just destroyed by that.
- Decked in the head.
Yeah. No, it doesn't work.
And now the moment we've
all been waiting for
- A Toyota!
- We're gonna go to the
highest of the highest heights
higher than everything
dropped in this video.
- And what are we gonna drop Jimmy?
- A Toyota. The most durable
- Of course.
Good.
- Oh well the car's falling.
- Look at it. It kind of survived it.
Look, it's drivable.
Go ahead and crank her up.
- And now the final clip,
an iPad is about to fall
30,000 feet.
- 30,000 feet?
How did they get it up there?
- Weather balloon.
- Whether or not I asked
is the real question.
- You did.
- I did.
- This is the highest thing
dropped in this video.
- Whoa!
- Now she's tumbling.
- Look at her go!
- 30,000 feet.
Wait.
- That smacked the ground.
- In a previous video
we said we'd shout out
someone random that subscribed.
Here's that person.
- Packer Anderson!
- I hope that satisfied
your alpha instinct.
That was things falling from high places.
Subscribe if you're not.
- Sigma.