This is the story of :
"Mr. Sharma and Mr. Verma"
One is smart while the other is stupid
"Mr. Sharma is careful."
"Mr. Verma falls in
trouble every now and then."
"Mr. Sharma does long term planning."
"Mr. Verma does not
think of too far ahead."
"So what do you think,
who do you want to be?"
"Mr. Sharma or Mr. Verma?"
"Think now, act now."
"Invest in smart savings
plan and secure your future."
"Be a Sharma."
I don't know.
Something is missing in this ad.
We will finalize the logo by tomorrow.
Is it the color..
- I don't know.
I can't put my finger on it.
- Okay.
Is it the.. design.. - Anyway,
let me think about it on my flight.
And I will let you
know when I get to Delhi.
But Vineet please, we need
this perfect by this week.
We are already
running behind schedule.
I want it absolutely right, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Thank you.
- We will get back to you.
Hello Zenobia
Nice of you to join us so early.
Sorry, ma'am..
- I know, lots of traffic, right?
Here's your flight ticket to Delhi.
And this is for Los Angeles on Monday.
Change this flight to Sunday.
I need some more time
Yes ma'am.
Aren't you getting late?
- For what?
Your flight to Delhi.
Its at 4:30, right?
Okay, tell Varun that I will finish..
..this report on the flight
and send it back to him. - Okay.
Cc Mr. Mehra on the third
stage of the Hot-ends deal.
And please ask FedEx..
..about the status on my roeters.
Tell Niharika, that its sea
green and not marine blue.
Okay.
Call Vineet from Trikaya.
Actually, forget it.
I will do it myself.
Ask my driver to bring the
car to the porch. - Yes, ma'am.
Lower the volume
Yes.
Yes, on the way.
Airport.
We'll have to cancel the party.
No, I have to go to LA on Sunday.
Yes, it's preponed.
Yes, you also know how it is.
Okay, we'll talk about
it when we meet. Okay.
Okay, see you.
Love you. Bye.
Aunty, aunty, give me Rs.2.
I want to eat something.
I'll eat some food.
Please, aunty.
Aunty, what's that on the television?
Look, remember we saw it back there..
..it is on the TV now.
Sweetheart, may you
get a handsome husband
Give us some money, come on!
Give it.
Cheapskate.
Blow the horn.
Oh, my! I don't believe this.
These are the worst kind of people.
Sorry.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
What the..
Constable.
- What is it?
What is the problem? The traffic
is jammed from both the ends.
Madam, the traffic jam
is going to get worse.
A huge rally is going to pass by.
- Rally?
Yes.
- But I am getting late.
I am sorry, madam, but everyone
will have to take a diversion.
Okay.
- What?
Everyone! Take the lane to your left.
Great.
'Welcome to Chhatrapati
Shivaji Airport..' - Your ID, please.
Sorry.
Excuse me, please. Sorry.
Ma'am, please. Do you mind?
Please. Please.
- Are we standing in the line for fun?
Flight to Delhi.
- Ma'am, you have missed your flight.
That's not possible, check it.
Sorry, ma'am, but
the gates are closed.
I can't help you.
You are late.
What do you mean by I am late?
Sorry, ma'am, airline rules.
Airline rules!
Do you know how much
business I give your airline?
Me alone!
- I really can't help you, please.
When is the next flight?
- 11 o'clock at night.
What?
Listen, I need to go right now.
Aren't there any flights before that?
Not before 11 o'clock.
Only if you want to
travel by any budget airlines.
Budget airlines.
One outlook money please
Rs.30, madam.
No change, madam.
You must have. Check again
I really don't have change ma'am
How much?
- For 1000.
Just a minute.
Here is your change, ma'am.
You are welcome.
25.
Do you want a different magazine?
Will they get married?
What do you think?
Saif-Kareena.
How would I know
Well, If we don't know..
Why waste money on this magazine?
Sir, you should have
checked-in the bags.
But why, they're not that large!
And check-in or cabin, finally
all are going to reach Delhi.
What's the big deal. Relax.
Yes, hello.
I have already boarded.
No, keep talking.
I am only traveling by
the plane, not flying it.
Yes.
What?
I said 15 and not 12.
How much? Yes.
Tell that boy we are
here to do business..
..and not to waste time.
And we are not scared of him.
Tell him that's the final rate.
And also add that 'no
room for discussion' clause.
Yes.
Useless.
These Mumbaikars think
we Delhilites are fools.
So? Delhi?
- Delhi.
"..and pay attention to us."
"During the flight you.."
That's a nice shirt. Is it readymade?
Must be. Who gets
clothes tailored nowadays?
'Fasten your seat belts.'
'And follow our instructions.'
Forget it.
When our lives are in danger..
..she will be the first one
to jump out with her tray.
And we'll be searching for
the front door, middle door..
..and back door and
reach the heaven's door
Heaven's door. Front door.. Get it?
'It will come down from the
panel above..' - That's okay.
'..and the effect of oxygen..'
Have you ever tried the oxygen mask?
Gives a nice high.
The mind feels light.
Try it sometime.
So I explained to my wife,
"What are you so concerned about?"
"You mind your own business."
"As far as uncle is concerned,
there is nothing to worry about."
"We will lay a mattress on the
terrace next to the parapet."
Where?
- Parapet
No, on the terrace.
Do you want to get uncle killed..
..by hanging him from
the 30 feet high parapet?
You aren't paying attention
What do you do? You're in a
job or run your own business?
I am at.. the IIT..
- so you're still studying.
That's why you're
not paying attention.
Passengers are requested not
to open their seat-belts..
.. and stay at their seats..
..till the plane comes to a
complete halt. - Hold this.
See you.
Yes, hello.
- Excuse me, sir, please be seated.
What's the big deal.
We've landed after all.
- Yes, Hello.
I have just landed. Where are you?
'Flight IT8..'
Vikram, I can't go on Monday.
But if it's my birthday and
I don't want to do anything..
..then I just don't
seem to understand..
Listen, hold on.
That's my bag. I'll call you.
Okay, I have got my bag.
Yes, I am coming out.
The battery is very low
I will see you there.
Yes, I am coming out. At exit no..
Welcome to Jaipur
International airport.
I am in Jaipur!
Vikram, I am in Jaipur!
I don't know, let me call you back.
I realized after
I landed at the airport here.
I don't know, there's some
major technical problem..
..or something like that,
at the Delhi airport.
All the flights are landing in Jaipur.
It's freezing here.
They did make the announcement..
..but I was asleep on the flight.
Hang on a minute.
It's freezing.
Listen, don't worry.
I will hire a car and come to Delhi.
Because there is no
other choice, Vikram.
There are no other
flights till morning.
Vikram, don't get
over-protective on me now.
I can't handle it.
I am hanging up now.
My battery is down.
Okay.
What happened?
Madam, the machine has broken down.
The card isn't working.
You will have to pay cash.
The plane is not working.
Your machine isn't working.
Is everyone's mind working?
That's working properly.
How much?
- 4000.
Here.
This is three..
- Wait.
Will do.
Here, the receipt to your car.
- Thank you.
You will find it in the parking
lot behind the second gate. Yes.
Okay.
- Madam. Greetings.
Welcome to my land.
Like there was a choice!
See you.
Excuse me.
I have to go to Delhi.
How long will it take to reach Delhi?
Six hours.
- What?
And if you drive faster?
This is my speed.
For the past 11 years.
- Very good.
Hey, what are you doing?
I haven't slept for
the past 32 hours, madam.
I have been driving non-stop.
What choices do the poor have?
Just keep toiling hard all day long.
Look, will you be
able to drive safely?
Or should I hire another car?
Hire another car.
- What?
Are you crazy?
You cannot do that.
You hire another car..
..and I will take another fare.
Where would you like to go, mister?
How dare you speak to me like this!
Look, I will file
a complain against you, okay?
Start the car.
You took the money, didn't you?
So do I owe you my life!
Madam, its you! Are you okay?
- What okay?
I hired this car to go to Delhi.
And now he's saying he won't go.
He's saying, "Hire another car".
You said so yourself.
Sir, where do you want to go?
Are you drunk?
Come here.
Why don't you take her?
You can't force me to.
It's my car.
I decide who I want to take
Or not take.
It sure is your car,
but I've hired it.
You talk as if you've bought it.
One call can make you rot in jail.
Don't you know how to talk to a lady?
Go ahead.
You too slap me.
The entire world can do
whatever they want with the poor.
I will crush your jaw
with a single punch.
Then you can drive your car in
the reverse gear all your life.
No, please, don't.. don't argue.
Don't worry, I know how
to deal with such rascals.
Why won't you go? Start the car.
I will come along as well.
Don't worry.
Let's go. Delhi.
Don't worry, I am coming along.
Come on. Now just drive the car.
And don't even dare to stop the car..
..or your breathing
till we reach Delhi.
But.. - Actually the Roadways'
bus is running late by two hours.
So I thought he will stay in control..
..if there's a man with you.
But you'll have to pay extra fare.
There you go again!
Should I remove my belt?
You.. you can just drop
me on the way. - Where?
There.. on the way,
near Chandni Chowk. - What?
Are you from Delhi?
No.
Why?
Does everyone traveling to
Delhi have to be from there?
You're right.
He could be from Kashmir as well.
My husband is.
- From Kashmir?
Delhi.
- I see. Delhi.
Where in Delhi?
Chanakyapuri.
- Chanakyapuri.
Where in Chanakyapuri?
Ninth main.
- Ninth main.
Where in Ninth main?
Bungalow no. 44, have you been there?
Bungalow no. 44, Ninth main,
Chanakyapuri, Delhi. No.
I have never been there.
Do you want to get us
killed at this young age?
Open your eyes. He was dozing off.
Stop the car. Stop the car.
Don't worry, I have travelled
between Delhi and Jaipur many a times.
I can drive on this
road with my eyes shut.
Even he was driving
with his eyes shut.
Sit properly.
You get worried very easily.
It's not your fault.
Those who belong to New Delhi
are the nervous sorts.
I am from Old Delhi myself.
You must have heard of Chandni Chowk.
The 'Gurdwara' (Sikh Temple)
there is very famous.
That's where my home is.
But I work in Karol Baug.
It takes me 11 minutes everyday..
..to reach Karol Baug on my scooter.
I have my own shop.
Ladies' dress material and saris.
I mean American silk, Indian silk,
Dhaka Silk, georgette..
..poplin, you name it!
Retail and wholesale. Both.
It's in the alley in front
of Nathuram Confectioners.
Incase you want to drop by someday
Which alley?
- Nathuram Confectioners.
No, the alley in front of it..
- Please look ahead and drive.
Only if this guy lets me.
Sit properly.
Madam, I was wondering..
if you don't mind..
What do you do?
I'm into banking.
Bank. Which bank?
- What do you mean?
I mean the bank that you work in..
..which bank is it?
It's not like you think.
It's investment banking.
Securities.
- I see. I get it.
You must be posted in
the head office branch.
No.
You know what? Forget it.
I get it.
You must be thinking..
..that how can this
man from Chandni Chowk..
..understand about banking?
- I don't mean it like that.
No, no, it's okay.
By the way, madam,
I am not like I seem to be.
I am more cunning than a 'Lomdi'.
'Lomdi'. Wolf.
- Fox.
Fox, wolf, same family.
They are cousins.
Its okay if you don't want to tell me.
If that's so, then let me tell
you in detail what I do. - Okay.
Basically, we help in the capital
formation of businesses.
By the way of outright
purchase or security sales..
..which the issuer offers.
We do this through
standby or separate selling..
..to the US market
specializing in dollar investments.
Got it.
- I got it.
It means our professions are similar.
Investment banking and poplin?
Look, you sell American dollars..
..and I sell American georgette.
Isn't it?
- Now I have heard it all.
Music.
Which music do you listen to?
I know, you must
listen to English music.
I can say that just looking at you.
"Moments alive just passing you by"
"And you know that its cupid's time"
"Because its never coming back"
"Just gone a flight"
"Last time is beating,
time is beating, time is beating."
How far have we reached?
You woke up.
Seems like you are used to
falling asleep on journeys.
Where are we?
- Actually we just crossed Shahpura.
We'll soon be reaching Behrol.
Then Dharuvera then Gurgaon.
Shahpura?
We are headed to Ajmer!
- Ajmer.
No chance! Why would we go to Ajmer?
Please ask someone.
- Don't worry.
Just relax and sit comfortably.
Two hours later you will be
comfortably sitting on your bed..
..and watching television.
But why haven't we
crossed the Behrol bridge yet?
And where did this
rough patch come from
It says Mumbai 950 kilometers.
Where are we going?
You are driving
in the opposite direction. - No chance.
Why would I drive in
the opposite direction?
I took a diversion 10 kilometers back.
I took a big u-turn and
then two small u-turns.
You are heading in the
opposite direction. - By God!
They've changed all the
roads in the past two years.
Mark my words..
..this government won't
last for long. - Be quiet.
Just shut up.
Excuse me. Hey, you.
Driver.
What is his name?
Shivrattan
Wake him up.
Hey, get up.
Madam is asking something.
Oh honey! why are you getting annoyed?
What happened?
- What are you blabbering? Wake up.
This man is taking us
somewhere else all together!
Where am I taking you? All
of us are going to Delhi.
You just stop the car. Stop it.
What's the big deal.
Where are we? - Just a minute,
madam. I will find out.
God!
This is the worst
car I've traveled in.
What is he doing?
Is he serious?
Seems like he used to
drive a steamroller before.
You be quiet!
What? Where are we?
- I don't know, madam.
He said, "I have been
driving for 11 years".
So? You have been driving for
the past 11 years, haven't you?
I used to drive on the
Shimla-Manali road, madam.
Why am I not surprised?
Why are you asking this fool?
He was sniffing the road.
Get in the car
Don't worry, madam.
We've only lost our way, that's all.
What's the big deal.
It will start right now.
Yes, hello? Vikram, I..
What?
No. Not now.
God, I can't believe this.
What happened?
The battery is dead.
So what's the big deal! Use my phone.
Take it.
Talk. Go on.
I will go take a look.
Bablu, I suggest that
you check the carburetor.
That's where the problem always is.
Your theory would have
been helpful in the 1980s
A car with fuel-injection
system doesn't have a carburetor.
It doesn't!
That's why it broke down.
Our car broke down.
Vikram, don't get hyper.
No, I will be there. You stay put.
I'll call my friend.
He will come and fix it.
He is a mechanic.
- When will he come?
He will be here in 1-11/2 hour.
Want some?
I just called to tell you that..
..it can take a little longer, okay?
Just relax, we are fixing it.
Okay, I am hanging up. See you. Bye.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
Is it fixed? - very soon.
I showed the fool how to do it.
Don't worry, here, take a bite.
This snack clubbed with red
chilly pickle is my specialty.
Ready to eat in two seconds.
Noodles still take
two minutes to prepare.
I am not hungry.
How much longer will it take?
Around 1-11/2 hour.
- What?
For the mechanic to arrive.
Mechanic?
- What's the big deal.
There's a problem with the carburetor.
Bablu has called his friend.
Bablu, our driver.
I named him that.
What are we going to do
for one and a half hours?
Great.
It's been resolved.
Now.. we travel by
truck to Delhi, is it?
Not all the way to Delhi, but at
least Dharampal will drop us..
..to an inn ahead.
It's the truck driver's name.
I don't know.
I swear that's his name.
I asked him. Dharampal.
I don't know whether I
want to go by a truck or not.
I will wait here.
Here? What will you do here
for 11/2 hour in this cold?
And with this fool.
I suggest that you come along.
We will go there and give him a call.
..and tell him where to get the car.
And we can have dinner as well.
Come on. Come along.
Come on, madam. Come.
I've left all my luggage in the car.
You think it'll be safe there?
You are getting worried unnecessarily.
Your luggage will be absolutely safe.
Three of my bags are there as well.
Bablu will bring them along.
Just relax.
- Right.
First time.. in the truck.
- Yes.
It's quite high.
- High and safe.
Isn't that so, Dharampal?
This vehicle has the pride
of a king, isn't that true?
Rules over the roads
There goes a tiny tempo..
And there goes that ant sized scooter
It's been ten minutes.
You are absolutely quiet.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling shy of
the beautiful madam?
No, no, it's not that.
- then what is it?
Why don't you tell a
story of one of your journeys
Like the.. Modi's crazy companion.
It was a show on the radio.
What did it come on?
Radio.
- Yes.
What story should I tell you, sir?
Tell me anything. A story
will make the time fly by.
Once I was driving on
the UP-Patna highway.
And a diesel tanker was lying
toppled in the middle of the highway..
..after ramming into a buffalo.
My truck crushed him.
And his neck came
under my truck's tires.
You mean the entire head.
- Oh, no, the head was gone.
Both his horns sank in his body.
And there were streams of blood.
Just like that.
He died on the spot.
The veins in the neck
must have been severed.
I don't know. - Once I saw an
ovine being slaughtered like that.
You do know what an
ovine is, don't you? Sheep.
Actually the butcher's
knife wasn't sharp enough.
He gave a single blow.
And his head hung like this.
It's okay, you can throw it out.
You think so.
How much?
Let it be, madam.
Why are you embarrassing me?
My wife is pregnant.
Just pray that everything goes well.
You are giving such big news now.
Sly guy.
I..
Let's..
- Dharampal.
Yes. - Do you always listen
to English songs on the radio?
No, madam.
I played it for you.
- For me?
Yes. I thought you must
listen to English songs.
And she thought you listen to them.
Okay, God bless you.
Call me and tell me what happened.
If it's a girl I'll distribute sweets.
Come on, jump.
You must have never jumped
from a truck before today.
All the best. - Thank you.
- Okay, Dharampal, I will call you.
That's so sweet.
And I was wondering..
..since when did truck drivers
start listening to English music?
Careful.
Are you okay?
- Ya.
You're wearing very high heels.
I was wondering..
..why do women wear such high heels?
But these heels are not
meant for walking on these roads.
Don't mistake this road to
be an ordinary one, madam.
I have heard that people
come here in their Mercedes..
..to eat at this inn. Potatoes
with ladyfinger, potatoes with cumin..
..potatoes with egg plant, potatoes
with fenugreek, potatoes with..
..cauliflower, peas
and cottage cheese and..
..they even have cold drinks.
So, madam, what will you have?
Anything.
- Anything?
"Anything" isn't
available in this menu.
You will have something.
Anything will do as
long as its not very oily.
Which I guess is asking
for too much in this place.
Lets see..
Son. Yes. Come here quickly.
Oh, thank you.
- Great.
He brought a blanket for us.
What is your name?
- Sunny.
Sunny.
Great, Sunny.
Do one thing. Do you eat non-veg?
- No, I don't.
Oh no! Do one thing.
We'll have two plates of Dal,
Two plates of potato with cumin,
Two plates of chick pea curry
two plates of yoghurt salad
And four flatbreads to start with.
Smear the breads with lots of butter.
No, do one thing. Butter two nicely,
And just put a dollop of
butter on the other two. Got it?
That's too much. - But I am so
hungry I could eat an elephant!
And listen. Sunny, right?
Do you see the lady?
She is from Mumbai.
She works in movies, she's an actress.
You must have seen her on television,
haven't you?
If she's pleased with your service..
..she will take you to Mumbai.
And cast you as a hero in her
upcoming film "sky full of stars"
In which film?
- She'll cast me as a hero?
What hero? I'm
saying "sky full of stars"
Go, get the food. Yes.
Go quickly.
What was that stupidity?
You wont understand.
Just watch how well they serve us now.
By God!
Next time you want good service..
..don't use my name, okay?
What's the big deal.
Son, turn the fan this way.
- Fan?
Let it be, it's cold.
Wow.
It's delicious.
What are you doing?
Wiping the bread.
You must have an oil-remover cream.
Apply that on the bread.
It's great, just great.
How is the food?
- It's okay.
Thank God.
You didn't taste the Chick pea curry.
It's too oily.
It's locally made butter.
It's very good for health.
Try some.
Eat it.
- Why did you serve it on my plate?
I hate people touching my plate.
Fine, don't eat it.
No one's forcing you.
What's the big deal
Great.
Great. That was delicious.
Why are you laughing?
Go get water, chilled water.
What happened?
My God.
Looks like armpit hair
I can't do this anymore.
- It's okay.
It's clean now after all the steaming
and boiling it's gone through.
Don't worry, just relax and eat.
Please call that driver.
Bablu.
- Yes.
He must have fallen asleep by now.
Give it to me.
Shankar, see if there's a snake.
Snake.
Cockroach.
Just a minute.
There you go. It's dead.
Stop laughing everyone.
Madam is scared of cockroaches.
I am not used to all this.
And cockroaches are the worst things.
Shut up, enough of laughing.
You call him.
Your phone?
I gave it to you just now.
- Yes.
It must be right here.
Where did it go?
I am really very sorry.
I didn't realize how this
phone slipped from my hand and..
That's okay, it keeps falling.
It's still within the warranty.
Will it get repaired? I will get
it repaired once I reach Delhi.
Once it fell in the commode.
I thought it's gone for good.
But those people fixed it in two days.
How will we call the driver now?
I was thinking about the same thing.
Jhujhar Singh.
- Yes.
Can we find any transportation here?
Some scooter or anything.
We don't have a scooter,
but there is a bicycle.
Bicycle. Even that will do.
Should I ask him to fetch it?
- Yes.
Go, get the bicycle quickly.
Get it quickly.
Should I come along?
Where will you go? You sit
here comfortably and relax.
I will go find out.
Is it working?
- No, there is no sound.
Uncle.
- Yes.
Should I go along as well?
- Go on, son.
Come, come, climb on. Very good.
Don't you know how
to sit on a bicycle?
Yes, that's correct. Bravo.
Tell me.. why don't you go to school?
Do you want to clean
utensils all your life?
Tell your uncle to get
you out of this inn..
..and send you to school.
Send you where?
- To a school.
You're a smart kid.
"Mr. Sharma does long term planning."
"Mr. Verma does not
think of too far ahead."
"So what do you think,
who do you want to be?"
"Invest in smart savings
plan and secure your future."
"Be a Mr. Sharma."
It's bad manners.. to
stare at someone like that.
Shankar, you were going
to the loo, weren't you?
Go on. Go inside.
What was that sound?
- It's the wolf.
Wolf?
- Yes.
Wolf. Like a real wolf.
There's a jungle around.
They wander around.
Aren't.. aren't you scared?
There is nothing to be
worried about, madam.
They don't come up
unnecessarily like the snakes.
Snakes?
- Yes, snakes do come here.
And they come in large
numbers in the monsoons.
I saw one just the other day.
It was this long. it passed from here.
But those innocent
creatures don't hurt us.
Instead, they eat up
the mice in our inn.
How was the food madam?
Stop, stop.
I must have lost
10 kilos of weight. I swear.
Jhujhar Singh.
Make some tea.
Where is the car?
- What?
The car?
- The car was towed away.
There was a leakage
in its fuel injection.
So they towed it away.
- Now?
Now what? We will hire another ride.
But.. how can they do that?
They should've sent another car.
That's right. But this is India.
You will have to go to
Delhi and lodge a complaint.
That's why I brought our luggage back.
Where is my bag?
- What?
My bag.
- Which bag?
My black suitcase.
Oh! That's what I kept
wondering on the way..
..what have I missed..
What?
You left my bag in the car.
What's the big deal, we
still have the receipt.
We'll call the car-owners and
they will deliver the luggage.
Receipt?
It was in the car.
- Really?
Did you take it?
But we do know.. the
name of the driver. - Bablu.
Yes.
- Wow.
What will I do with that name?
All my belongings were in that bag.
My clothes, my files, everything.
How can you do this?
You have only lost your belongings.
So what.
Things like these happen sometimes.
You shouldn't let it
bother you so much.
Because I believe
that the only thing..
.. that matters in life,
is life itself!
And we're still alive.
You are rinsing your mouth..
..with my French Alps Spring water?
So what's the big deal.
You're arguing with me
for a bottle of water.
I will buy you
another one. Jhujhar Singh.
Give madam two
litres of mineral water.
What's the big deal.
- What's the big deal!
What's the big deal!
What is a big deal for you?
When wolves come in and
attack us and eat us..
..that will be a big deal for you.
And you, madam.
Everything is bad news for you.
Even your good starts
with not too bad, you know.
That's it, I have had it.
You are the worst person
I have ever met. - Really?
What have I done?
What did you do?
- Yes, tell me, what have I done?
I missed my flight because of you.
Because of me?
- Yes.
You stopped your stupid
rickshaw at that green signal.
And then I had to forcefully
plug my ears on the flight..
..because of your non-stop blabbering.
I never realized when the flight
landed in Jaipur. - That's great.
You are accusing me for the
problems at Delhi airport.
And then he
forcefully barged in my car.
I took a lift for you..
- You drove in the opposite direction.
I took a lift for you.
For me?
- Yes.
So that.. That evil Bablu..
How could I have left a lonely
helpless woman with him alone?
What?
Lonely helpless woman?
- Yes.
Do you have any idea who I am?
This lonely helpless woman..
heads a company worth 200 crores.
635 employees report directly to me.
I wouldn't let fools like you..
..wander anywhere close to
my office's building compound.
Who wants to wander in
your office's compound?
And.. and I don't understand..
..how can so many
men work under a woman.
Of course, because for men like you..
..women should stay at home.
So that you can go
out and fool around.
I am fooling around.
Am I fooling around?
By the way, sister, my wife
stays at home the entire day as well.
But I didn't chain
her down, understand?
Do I look like a sister to you?
Oh! Well, now it seems
like it's a crime to call..
..a woman 'sister' in India !
Forget it.
You Mumbaikers won't
understand a Delhilite's feelings.
I know many Delhilites, okay?
But none of them eat
with their mouths open.
And they don't use abusive language.
That, too, in front of women.
Oh yes, if we say it
in Hindi, it's abusive..
..and if she says it in English,
that's acceptable
Just.. shut up.
Okay..
I think.. I yelled too much at you.
I mean I just..
Bablu was saying that Nua
station is 25 kilometers from here.
There's a train that leaves
for Delhi everyday from there.
We'll catch that in the morning.
Okay, thanks.
It's just that my
migraine had become severe.
And..
I just.. I just..
Excuse me.
What's the big deal!
It looks like armpit hair.
You're driving in
the opposite direction.
Ma'am you've missed your flight.
See if there is a snake!
Vikram, I am in Jaipur.
Jhujhar Singh was saying
that he has a camel-cart.
It will give us a lift to
a jeep. And from there..
What are you looking at?
It's so beautiful, right?
I've never seen such a sunrise.
What is so special about this sunrise?
Sunrise happens everyday
But you don't realize how
beautiful it is everyday.
And if I wasn't here with you, then..
..I would have never seen this.
And I am really sorry.
I yelled at you last night.
Actually I had got a bad migraine.
Its okay.
Sometimes, when we lose temper,
we blow our tops off.
Here, toothbrush.
But I have to confess.
Seeing you so worried, I was scared..
..that you might start crying.
I never cry.
- I never cry either.
I make people cry.
- And I make them laugh.
In fact, you know what you
should do when you feel like crying?
What?
- You should laugh out loud.
What rubbish!
- Believe me, it's true.
If you laugh at the sorrows..
..then they never bother you.
That's why whenever I feel
like crying, I laugh out loud.
Interesting.
Yes.
- Thank you.
If I don't get tea in the morning,
then I lose my mind.
Yes.
It reminds me, your headache..
- Migraine.
Yes, that. I have a
guaranteed cure for it.
A saint from the South gave it to me.
- I see.
Look.
Wow. What is this?
It's an ayurvedic ointment.
Flowers of henna are soaked in vinegar
And then mixed with elephant's poop..
- Okay, okay
It's a guaranteed cure.
- It might be.
But my head just got better
hearing of 'elephant poop'.
Thank you.
- As you say.
I am used to having heavy breakfast.
Will I get something here?
- That's more like it.
Shankar.
What's for breakfast?
Fried flatbreads and potatoes.
"He dreams with open eyes."
"our heart
- its crazy"
"the entire world has changed,
but it refuses to budge"
"He has gone crazy."
"All day long, he has fun"
"He has fun."
There's a "Nua" station,
I am taking a train from there.
Okay. Yes, I will be there.
Just meet me at Delhi
station at 2 o'clock.
Okay, fine.
It's the.. camel driver's phone.
Please, I will tell you later.
Okay, bye.
"There's restlessness in the heart."
"and yet its jumping with joy"
"sometimes it behaves itself"
At other times, it becomes naughty"
"There's restlessness in the heart."
"and yet its jumping with joy"
"sometimes it behaves itself"
At other times, it becomes naughty"
"He plays pranks openly."
"He has fun."
"He wanders around aimlessly."
"Like a kite on the loose"
Only God knows how we'll reach Delhi.
"He has fun."
We have reached Nua station.
- Yes.
Finally.
I get hungry..
whenever I see a station.
I have already digested
the morning breakfast.
I suggest that we first go
and eat something.
No.. you go.. I'll take a leave.
- you're leaving?
Aren't we are
traveling to Delhi together?
No, I will take a first AC..
- First AC.
These first AC fares are too high.
Why are you going in first AC?
I suggest that it's a
three-four hour journey.
Let's travel in the general bogie.
- I know.
That's why I will buy my ticket..
..and you buy yours.
And anyway, my husband is
coming at the Delhi station. - Yes.
But how will you travel alone?
I can manage that much.
Okay.
And, I am really sorry..
for the phone. - That's okay.
What's the big deal.
I should be apologizing
for the water and your bag.
I am very sorry. For all
that I may have said or done..
And if you ever come to Karol Baug..
..then don't forget to drop in.
Do pay me a visit.
- Okay.
Yes.
- Okay. Goodbye.
First AC, Loharu express to Delhi.
One ticket please.
Madam, 324.
My money.
My.. my money.
Where did he go?
Hey, get something to eat.
Get something to eat.
Hey.
- You!
Hey!
- Come on.
Hey.
- You!
Hey!
- Come on.
Hey. My money is stolen.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Come on.
- Hey!
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Someone cut my bag.
All my money has been stolen.
Yes.
Even yours?
Who's the fool?
Oh!
What job am I stuck in?
I should've worked in my
uncle's tractor agency.
I would've done much better with that.
Some fool pulled the chain.
That's only when
I get my hands on him.
See, he delayed the train.
Someone pulled the chain.
You did.
You are a disgusting person.
Don't you know that spitting at
public places is a criminal offence?
It's a bigger offence to pull
the chain and stop a moving train.
But if I hadn't done that you
wouldn't have boarded the train.
What if we are caught?
- No chance!
I pulled the chain from the AC bogie.
Didn't you notice, the TC is
searching for someone else?
Let's go, let's go.
Will we get a place to sit?
Where there is a will,
there is a seat.
Come, come.
Here, here, right here.
It's a window seat, 56, sit, sit.
Sit down.
I don't have a ticket.
- What?
You don't have a ticket?
I was just joking.
That's alright.
I have been traveling in
trains since I was 20 years old..
..and I never bought a ticket.
Never made any reservations.
Direct setting with the TC.
Don't worry, enjoy the view.
But what if we have to pay a fine?
You won't have to pay
any fine, I am there.
Don't worry.
Are you Bengali?
How did you know?
Looking at your
wife's dangling earrings.
How else?
Only Bengali ladies wear
such dangling earrings.
Am I correct, sister?
- Yes, absolutely correct.
What a beautiful sari!
Is this a 'Tanth' sari?
- Yes, it's a 'Tanth' sari.
They did the right thing.
Changed Calcutta to Kolkata.
You don't get the same
taste in 'Rasgulla'..
..that you get in
'Rosogulla' (Bengali sweets).
Isn't it?
- Yes.
Now whenever we say Kolkata..
..it feels like
someone's saying Calcutta..
..with hot 'Rasgulla' in his mouth.
Try it. Kol-kata.
Why don't you try it?
Hello, are you married?
Do you.. have children?
- No kids.
Oh, God, it's important to have kids.
You must have kids.
- Yes, soon.
Soon will make your life lonesome.
She has been married for five years.
I advise you that..
..don't miss the happiness
of kids for your career.
Because life may not always be kind,
..but everything good
happens for a child.
Who told you that I am career-minded?
Just because I look like
this and I dress like this.
You are arguing again.
All okay?
- Yes, everything is okay.
It's just that children
are a big responsibility.
And I am not ready for it.
And can I live my life on my terms?
If you don't mind?
- I was talking about myself.
I had two children in
two years of marriage.
And I had planned for four.
- Four children?
Oh, God. Your poor wife.
She isn't poor.
Vibha could make the
witches look kind!
you don't know her.
Aren't you ashamed?
You are mocking your wife publicly.
I am mocking my own wife and not his.
Sister, you have two kids.
Two sons. 'Rosogullas'. Very sweet.
But don't mind me saying, the
joy of having a daughter is unique.
Like the saying goes..
I believe that a son is a
son till he gets a wife.
But daughter is a daughter
till the end of life, right?
By the way.
Your pocket was picked
as well, isn't it? - Yes.
Then how did you buy the ticket?
You forgot the secret pocket.
No thief can get there.
I have stashed Rs.800 in there.
- What?
Rs.800 in your secret pocket.
"Let's go to Dilli."
"Life's so short, wonder
what will happen next moment."
"Your journey is calling out to you."
"Stop grieving."
"Let's learn to be happy."
"Catch this train that's departing."
"Life's so short, wonder
what will happen next moment."
"Your journey is calling out to you."
"Stop grieving."
"Let's learn to be happy."
"Catch this train that's departing."
"This is your world,
no matter how it is."
"Why curse it?"
"Let's live these golden moments."
"The dawn has arisen."
"Let's go to Dilli."
Water. Water. Cold water.
Which station is this?
- It's Jhunjunu.
The 'Ghewars' (sweets)
from here are very famous.
You must have
certainly eaten 'Ghewar'.
How would you have eaten 'Ghewar'?
This must be your life's first
train journey. - Of course not.
I have traveled by train..
..when I was nine years old.
From Mumbai to Allahabad.
- I see.
It was my uncle's wedding.
We had a.. What do you call it?
An entire coupe to ourselves.
Fun and mischief all along the way.
Eating something or
the other all the way.
Then you will surely
like the 'Ghewars'.
I will get it, do taste it.
- No, thanks.
Goldie, you will eat it, won't you?
Sister
You will taste it, won't you?
- Yes, I will.
I will be back soon.
You taste it, too.
- No thanks.
Papdi. Kachauri (snacks).
- Tea. Tea.
Vada. Hot vadas (snacks).
So.. how many did you sell today?
Ticket. Ticket.
Your Ticket.
Ticket.
Are the Jhunjhunwala's from your town?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Madam is calling you.
Come here. Come on.
A while ago,
when I was praising your 'Ghewars'..
..she was getting furious.
Madam, your ticket.
Now she wants them too.
I suggest that you pack two kilos.
- Listen.
Your ticket.
Madam, your ticket.
56 is yours?
No..
- Actually, madam..
Sir..
Is she with you?
- No.
No, he has gone out?
- Husband.
No, colleague.
He has the ticket?
- No, he doesn't have the ticket.
That means you don't have a ticket,
I suggest that you get down here,
Come..
- Panth, sir.
I was looking for you in S5.
Would you like to have 'Ghewars'?
Come on. Come on.
- Madam..
She is with me. Come on.
Papdi. Kachauri.
Mr. Panth.
- No.
What's the big deal.
Hold this box.
- No. - Hold the box.
Mr. Panth, can we travel by
train taking up enmities with you?
You don't understand.
- We can never do it, Mr. Panth.
You are our benefactor.
- Okay.
Take.. the 'Ghewars'.
Taste it.
But I am diabetic.
I can't eat too many sweets.
It's done?
- Of course.
He wasn't listening,
he was showing attitude.
Later he took Rs.400.
I will surely return this money
in Delhi.. - What are you saying?
Can't I do this much
for my special customer?
Customer?
- Remember !
My sari shop at Karol Baug.
Now wont you be buying saris from
my shop on birthdays, marriages..
..and every special function.
It's all marketing. Marketing.
This is the level of this
corruption in this country. - Yes.
Anyone can do anything with money.
Nothing good can happen to India.
How can it?
When the train left from Nua station..
..I boldly pulled the chain.
But did anything happen?
Did anyone catch me?
Did anyone harm me in anyway? No.
I bought 'Ghewar'
at Jhunjhunu station..
..and now I am
distributing it to everyone.
The system, my friend. The system.
The problem is with the entire system.
That's why no one is
afraid of doing anything wrong.
Look, just because
they get a uniform..
..they think they
have got the license.
From the police officials to
the TC, all of them corrupt.
They have a rate card.
They won't think twice before
selling their fathers for a bribe.
Rascals.
Inspector. Mr. Mishra.
I was saying that we only
just pulled the train's chain..
..and not a chain from a woman's neck.
Don't you agree?
- Just a minute.
What do you mean by that?
Sir, I have the right
to make one phone call.
You too will get a
chance to make a call.
Seems like you watch a
lot of English movies.
How.. is she related to you?
She.. is a friend. Co-passenger.
We boarded from Nua station..
- Yes.
And..
- I see. Co-passengers.
Yes.
Look, you will have to
pay a hefty penalty.
Uncle.
- Uncle?
I only have Rs.500 left.
If you could settle
the case with this..
Rs.500 is no good.
I have to maintain the entire office.
Actually.. - This is no good.
Listen, listen to me.
Someone picked my
pocket and hers, too.
This won't do any good.
You will have to pay Rs.5000.
See, when I offered him he refused.
Hey, shut up.
There's a huge difference in..
..pulling the chain and
stealing the tracks from the yard.
Characterless.
Sit there quietly. Look, actually..
Release Pappu or else
I will shoot you right here.
Billu. Billu. Are you here to free us?
Shut up. Otherwise
we'll be in trouble.
Look, you can't do this.
How dare you arrest my friend?
Hey. Shut up.
Sit down.
Release me.
It's office time.
Excuse me.
Actually.. can we.. get a lift?
Thank you, brother.
Come on, let's go. Come on.
No one in my family robbed
anything smaller than a goods train.
And you got arrested
for stealing tracks.
If you wanted to get arrested..
..then you should have
atleast done something big.
Pappu. Pappu.
You are like the innocent girl..
..that every man in the
village takes advantage of.
Useless.
It's not my fault, brother.
It's that rascal
Shusheel Kumar's fault.
His men must have
given my information.
Who is Shusheel Kumar?
That tailor's son.
- Yes.
See that.
That scoundrel, the son of a tailor.
He has become so bold that
he is trying to challenge me.
Brother, these days
he runs his own gang.
Rascal.
- Listen to that.
Just out of the womb,
and already making gangs.
He will learn his lesson..
..when I get my hands on
him and wring his neck.
Sit in the car.
Bhanwar Lal,
take the car to his village.
Are you okay?
Let's go there. We will
knock him there itself.
Brother, Asangarh is on
the way to Delhi, isn't it?
I will shoot that rascal first.
Here, in his chest.
He dared to lock horns with
Bhairon Singh Gujjar, that rascal.
What?
We will skin him alive.
- Two pieces.
And that, too, diagonally.
- Great.
Brother, where are
you going to drop us?
Who is he?
Brother, he is..
Brother, look.
Shusheel Kumar's uncle's car.
Bhanwar Lal, follow him.
Turn, turn, take a u-turn.
Don't let him go.
Drive faster.
I was locked in jail because of him.
Drive faster, Bhanwar Lal. Faster.
Bhanwar Lal, drive carefully.
Brother, is it
important to go to Asangarh?
Stop the car.
I was just saying it's very
important to go to Asangarh..
..otherwise how will
Shusheel Kumar learn his lesson?
Where did such a big car disappear?
It was right here.
Why don't you keep track?
Brother, there it is.
There goes the car.
Turn, turn, turn the car, reverse.
Yes, there it is.
Hey, it's torn.
That's okay, it can
be stitched easily.
First we will thrash the tailor.
Then we will make him stitch it.
Bhanwar Lal, tail him, tail him.
- Yes, bravo.
Bhanwar Lal, don't let him go.
Even if you have to fly this car.
Oh, no.
That isn't Shusheel
Kumar's uncle's car.
That car belongs to
Lallan from Teragarh.
Stop.
Sometimes, the car disappears..
..at other times, we
follow the wrong car.
You wasted so much of my time.
Take it in reverse.
Take it straight to the local bar.
Hey, tailor, I am going to..
Ok, let's have one strong beer.
Brother.
I was saying if you
could drop us here..
And anyway, there isn't
much space in the jeep. - Yes.
Please drop us here.
Throw them out.
Get out.
Thank you, brother.
Okay, it's alright. Mention not.
Thank you.
Come on.
Here's your bag.
Carefully, brother.
Do teach a lesson to
that Shusheel Kumar.
Come, let's go.
You are just..
You take a lift from
just about anyone.
I wonder where they left us.
Keep walking, keep walking.
Faster. Faster. Don't look that way.
"my heart beats like
the train's engine"
Madam, stop, stop.
You don't have to catch a flight.
Relax.
Look, brother, you..
Are you madam?
- Look, this doesn't suit you.
Foreign stuff is really great.
Please.. don't trouble her.. Leave it.
I have contacts in police station.
You don't get it?
You lost your laptop as well.
Thank God, they only took my laptop.
Are you okay?
What okay? My shoes are broken,
my clothes are torn.
I am carrying an empty bag.
And I haven't been to the
bathroom for the past two days.
So.. what's the big deal
This is a open jungle. You can..
- Really?
We will find a small hotel there.
I was thinking that.. what if they..
..steal your bank's
information from your laptop?
They cannot do anything.
Laptop's specialty.
Face recognition, password protection.
That's good.
Then they won't be
able to sell it either.
You really think I care.
Yes, let's go.
Just a little further.
Come on.
We have arrived.
It's a long story, Vikram.
I will tell you when we meet.
Just get me out of here.
Vikram, don't shout..
I am tired, I am fed up
and I just want to go home.
It's some Red Tomato.. Palace.
Jhunjhunu junction. Gol Chowk market.
Okay.
Just please come soon,
I can't take it anymore.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, love you. Bye.
Here, yours is 301.
I will go find out the menu.
It's been so long
since I ate the 'Ghewar'.
hungry? Eat this.
Would you like anything?
See, she's hungry.
So tell me what
today's special menu is.
Chilly fritters, onion fritters,
snacks, potato with ladyfinger.
Barbecued chicken. And sweets.
Sweets with cream.
And there is a special
arrangement in the basement.
You mean there's a
buffet in the basement
Sir..
Today there is a special program..
..in our honeymoon
hall in the basement.
Only for gents.
I see.
Greetings, Sir!
Hello.
This looks like pure
'Pashmina' (Cashmere Wool).
It must be expensive.
Chew it.
It's brother's paan (betel leaf
with tobacco and betel nuts).
Chew it.
Great. The betel-leaf is really nice.
Come, I will show you some real fun.
Send the bags to the room.
Let's go.
- Come, come, come.
You are our guest.
"Love is my spell."
O enchantress!
"It will knock you out."
"No one can escape..
..my charming eyes."
"Laila, I am Laila."
- Brother, greetings.
"I am such a seductress."
"Everyone wishes to meet me alone."
Wow!
- Great.
"Take care, Laila is here to
knock you off your senses."
"Just my glimpse can
give you sleepless nights."
"My attitude is mesmerizing."
"My name has created uproar around."
"My gait is alluring,
everyone's crazy about it."
"Only the Lord knows who
will dwell in my heart."
"Laila, I am Laila."
"I am such a seductress."
"Everyone wishes to meet me alone."
"Laila, I am Laila."
"I am such a seductress."
"Everyone wishes to meet me alone."
"I am captivating.
Whoever gets a taste of me.."
"..falls head over heels for me,
brings the world at my feet."
"Whoever watches my enchantment,
says.."
"You're charming, Laila."
"I am captivating.
Whoever gets a taste of me.."
"..falls head over heels for me,
brings the world at my feet."
"Whoever watches my enchantment,
says.."
"You're charming, Laila."
Laila!
The programs in these small cities..
..are so unique.
Just play a Hindi
movie song, dance around.
And it's a full house.
It was fun.
You freshen up. I will wait outside.
I already freshened up.
Please sit.
Your husband was
supposed to be here, wasn't he?
I will go take a look.
Vikram will be
arriving two hours later.
Then I will take a
look two hours later.
Shall I order food?
- How much are you going to eat?
I was talking about you.
For me.
No, thank you.
Just imagine, if your wife..
..finds you in a strange hotel,
in a strange place..
..with an unknown girl,
what will she say?
'She won't say anything.
Really?
Yes, my wife is beyond these problems.
It doesn't make a difference to her.
Okay.
What is your residence number?
- 6283314.
What.. what are you doing?
Calling your home to
tell her you are fine.
It's not a problem, right?
No, no, there is no need for that.
Yes. Hello, am I speaking with Mrs..
Actually.. - I told you
there is no need for that.
Actually we aren't talking
to each other these days.
If I make the call it
would mean my defeat.
She should apologize.
Your phone
Yes, Gopi.
What?
This matter will go on for long.
Mr. Pandey and Mr. Bhaiyya
won't spare each other.
But what happened here?
And so suddenly?
- Yes.
Madam, it's a long story.
It's a political matter.
Mr. Pandey's brother-in-law,
Mr. Bhaiyya.
They both are from rival parties.
They have been looking for
an opportunity for a clash.
Today, they got the opportunity.
That too, in my Red Tomato.
Here, in this hotel.
What are you saying?
In the honeymoon hall in the
basement, during the program.
Someone spat betel-leaf
residue on Mr. Bhaiyya's kurta.
Oh, no. Then?
"My gait is alluring,
everyone's crazy about it."
"Only the Lord knows who
will dwell in my heart."
"Laila, I am Laila."
Laila's darling.
What's this! Spit.
Hey, someone spat on you?
Who could it be!
There he is. Chewing like a cow.
It must be him. Stop him.
After that, Mr. Bhaiyya thought that..
..Mr. Pandey's men must have done it.
He slapped him hard.
And after that,
it erupted into a quarrel..
..and from here,
it reached all the way to Gol Chowk.
There is complete chaos.
What now?
- What can happen?
It has engulfed the
whole of Jhunjhunu.
Gangs are coming from outside.
And there's a curfew
in the entire city.
Curfew.
How will Vikram come here now?
That's great.
When people don't know
how to eat betel-leaf..
..why do they eat it? Isn't it?
Sajjan Singh will come
there with the money.
Keep it in the blue drawer
without letting mother see it.
Don't start counting
it in front of everyone.
Understood? I will talk to you later.
Stop. Stop.
Are you in a hurry?
Take a u-turn, sir.
It's closed ahead.
There's a gang-war going
on between Pandey's gang..
..and Shrivastav's gang in Jhunjhunu.
That's why. Understand?
Now leave. You can't go
any further than this.
Move.
O God! Why did it all
have to happen today?
I am sure you must have
spat that betel-leaf residue.
Am I the only one who chews
betel-leaf in the whole of Jhunjhunu?
Tomorrow, if the
government collapses..
..she will blame me for that as well.
Sit down, don't worry,
Why shouldn't I be worried?
There's a riot outside.
What's the big deal.
You know, ever since I met you..
..I am trying to figure out
what would be a big deal for you.
When they come in and attack us..
..will that be a big deal for you?
Vikram.
Thank God.
Boyfriend.
- Husband.
Are you okay?
- I am now.
Let's go.
- Sir, there is a riot outside.
How can you go?
The riots have ended a long time ago.
You civilians really are..
We fight the enemies at the border..
..and you fight amongst yourselves.
You civilians should be ashamed.
You don't have any sense. Let's go.
This is my husband.
Lt. Colonel Vikram Singh Rana.
And he is the one who brought me here.
Hello.
- Not him. Him.
'Hail the youth, hail the farmers.'
Don't fight amongst yourselves,
understand?
Let's go, the riots are over. Come.
Mr. Pandey, Mr. Bhaiyya.. it's okay.
And you know, he fed the
TC Ghevar (a sweet snack).
Hey, you don't know, he was
asking for Gulabjamun (a sweetmeat).
You went through all that.
Oh, God.
- That was great, nice meeting you.
Thank you, nice meeting you too.
- Well done, well done.
Let me tell you one thing.
I wonder what would have happened..
..to my wife if it wasn't for you.
What would have happened?
I would have reached
Delhi on time yesterday.
Isn't that right?
- You are just..
Later.
Well, at least call home now.
They must be so worried.
There is no need for that.
We are almost home.
What kind of a person are you?
Such an ego. And that too, male ego.
It's just not done.
- It's not like that..
She is right. Why
don't you just call home.
I insist. Give him the phone.
What happened?
- My phone.
I can't find my phone.
Did you leave it back at the hotel?
Yes, that's right.
Should I take a u-turn?
- No big deal.
That's a nice attitude.
You have developed a great attitude.
Here.
- No, no, really..
Call her, that's okay.
I insist, call her.
- Okay, if you insist.
Hello.
Yes, it's me.
The flight was diverted
from Delhi to Jaipur..
You won't understand.
I am coming.
I am not making any excuses.
You are just.. Listen.
This is not my phone.
I can't talk to you for too long.
That's okay, you can talk to her.
- That's okay. - Yes.
No, no, I am almost there.
I will come see you.
You don't know, once Vibha starts,
she doesn't stop.
Thank you.
Stop on the left.
Your home is here.
- No, it's in the alley inside.
Then I will take it inside.
- No, no..
The car won't go inside.
I will walk on foot.
By God, let it be. I mean it.
It's very far inside.
Very far for you, but near for me.
Sure?
- Yes. 100 percent.
Shall I stop here?
- Yes.
Go ahead and take right. That's it.
Stop here, here.
Okay.
- We've reached Delhi, thank you.
Nice meeting you.
- Thanks, sir. Salutations, sir.
Okay.
I..
Okay, colonel. See you.
- Look after yourself.
Thanks for the lift.
Why is she getting down?
What happened?
So I guess this is it.
Yes, this is my Chandni Chowk.
No, I mean.. the end of our journey.
Yes, the journey has ended.
We have reached Delhi. Who knew..
- Yes.
I was saying..
..I apologize for any..
No, please.
Whatever it was I have to say..
it was very interesting.
Mr..
Brother.
I think you didn't
read my name on the card.
It's okay. My name is Manu Gupta.
Mihika Banerjee.
Nice to meet you.
Very nice to meet you.
Goodbye.
Oh! I am so tired.
What is that?
Flowers of henna are soaked in vinegar
and then mixed with elephants poop..
Headache formula.
- Are you serious?
Yes, A-one formula for
Head aches and body aches.
It belongs to him.
And I am going to use it.
- Please use it.
Oh, no.
Listen, your ad office had called.
Oh, no, I forgot to call them.
Vikram, where is your phone?
There it is.
- That's it.
Hi, Vineet.
Sorry, I couldn't call you back.
No, I was tied up in something.
Listen, I have figured out
what is missing in that ad.
Whether it's Mr. Sharma or Mr. Verma,
it doesn't make a difference.
I think that should be the end.
Yes, okay.
And listen.
I am in Delhi on Monday..
..so if you want to drop by,
you can come at anytime, okay?
Okay. Bye.
You were supposed to
go to the US on Monday.
What happened?
- I am not going.
Are you sure?
- Yes.
Why?
- Because you are going to..
..throw my birthday party on Sunday.
And the next day, I will be hung over.
So I will go after that.
You have changed.
Listen..
Look there in the pocket.
I brought something for you.
Take a look, it's in my jacket.
- Really? - Your birthday gift.
Yes. Found it.
Oh, my, God. Vikram, it's beautiful,
You like it?
I am so lucky.
I have the most
wonderful husband in the world.
And I want to celebrate my birthday..
..with my friends
and family at my home.
There's still time
before we reach home. - Yes.
Let's make a list.
- Yes. Great.
Tell me, who do you want to invite?
The usual suspects.
- Okay.
Sangeeta.
- Sangeeta.
Kunal.
- Kunal. - Jeet. - Jeet.
Why don't we call him..
Your friend from this journey?
Why not invite him?
You have the best ideas.
Where is my phone?
- Yes.
It must be the last dialed number..
Call him back.
- Of course.
The number you have dialed is invalid.
What happened?
They are saying it's
an invalid number.
Show me.
You seem to have
dialed a wrong number.
Please check the number.. - Yes,
its an invalid number you have dialed.
Why would he do that?
Why would he?
Vikram, turn the car around please.
Are you sure? - Please. - Yes, just..
just turn the car around.
Where are you going?
- I want to find out something.
Should I come along?
- No. I am fine.
Are you sure?
- Yes. - Just two minutes.
Excuse me, do you know
where Manu Gupta lives?
I don't know that.
But please taste these kebabs.
No, thank you.
Excuse me, do you
know where Manu Gupta..
..who has a shop in Karol Baug, lives?
Mr. Gupta.
- Yes.
Go into the alley right in front.
It's the first house on the left.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Manu uncle's home.
- Yes.
It's the last house.
- Okay, thank you.
Hello, does Manu Gupta stay here?
Someone's at the door for you.
Just coming
Its you!
Your wife.
She's still angry?
No, she wasn't my wife.
She is the nurse.
My wife..
Come in. Come on.
Come in.
She is my wife, Vibha.
Vibha, look who is here.
Mihika.
The one I was telling you about.
Two years ago,
she got high fever and..
..it went up here.
To her brain.
And since then, she is in coma.
Why..
Why didn't you tell me?
I never told anyone anything.
Why are you standing? Sit down.
What's the point in telling anyone?
The more I tell people,
the more they'll sympathize.
And the more they sympathize,
The more it'll hurt me.
And I don't want to live like that.
The truth is that when
something is not in our control..
..its foolish to let it affect you.
I believe.. change what you
can and accept what you cant.
What? I said, accept it.
But your children.
I have two daughters.
Shraddha and Archana.
They live in Meerut
with my elder sister.
I stay out of the house
half the time for work.
So they are better off with her.
They do come here
sometimes on Sundays.
This is my family.
Wife's here, children are there.
And I, from here to there.
A wandering traveler,
And what do the doctors say?
What would the doctors say?
The doctors have..
.. stopped saying anything,
just like her.
All of them are quiet.
But I am sure that one day my
Vibha will be cured 100 percent?
How sure?
100 percent.
You are a shameless woman.
There's a guest at Home who
has come for the first time..
..and you didn't
even ask her for water.
She has grown lazy.
I will get water for you.
Now I understand..
What the big deal was.
What did you say?
Just that..
..when something so devastating
has happened in someone's life..
..then nothing else
seems like a big deal..
It's just a point of view.
See..
No matter in what
condition my wife is in..
..at least she is with me.
And you know.
Vibha isn't an ordinary wife.
She's the only wife in the world..
..who doesn't argue with her husband.
So you too learnt to
laugh at your sorrows.
Here.
- Thank you.
But there is one thing
I still didn't quite get..
Why did you suddenly.. return
Actually tomorrow, which is a Sunday
There is a party at my home.
And Vikram and
I wanted to invite you for it.
Me? - Look, you tried to
avoid us even earlier.
But I found your home.
- No, I..
No excuses this time.
Do come.
You do remember the address,
don't you?
Chanakyapuri, Ninth main,
bungalow no. 44.
Yes, I do.
- Exactly.
No, actually you..
It's such a big party.
And I will look out of
place amongst your friends.
There are very few places..
..where you will be out of place.
And many places where
I will be out of place.
So, do come.
Actually, it's my birthday.
Happy birthday to you. In advance.
- No.
I will shake hands with you tomorrow..
..when you come home and wish me.
And.. you've already
given me my birthday gift.
Birthday gift.
Your favorite ointment,
I see. Yes, you can keep that.
For your migraine.
So.. I will see you tomorrow.
Please, do come.
Okay, I will take your leave.
But how did you come here?
- Oh, I walked.
But the car is on the road.
They won't let
Vikram park on the road.
He will have to go ahead and park.
Let me drop you.
- No, no. No problem.
I'll go on my own.
- No big deal.
I'll drop you on my scooter
Okay. - And it will be
faster for you as well. - Yes.
Vibha, I will be right
back after I drop her.
Don't get up.
Can she hear us?
No, she can't.. hear.
But I can talk.
Right?
- Yes. - Come on.
Let's go.
I hope you can get on it.
By the way, Happy
Diwali (festival of lights).
Sit tight.
- Yes.
You must not have sat on a
scooter before, have you? - No.
What happened?
- Nothing, it just stopped.
It will just start.
Are you serious?
- Yes, it's just..
It happens sometimes during winters.
Its okay, what's the big deal!
Well said.
It started.
- Look, its started. I told you.
Now let's go to New Delhi.
But seriously, I must admit, guys.
My meeting with Manu Gupta..
..was nothing short
of a big deal for me.
Meanwhile, a small thing
happened at our Dharampal's house.
A sweet daughter.
Meaning, a daughter stays a daughter,
till the end of life.
Maybe Pappu and gang are
searching for Shusheel Kumar..
..on Google search now.
Provided, they can
crack my laptop's password.
Shivratan, who couldn't
blame the rich enough..
..finally found a shoulder to rest on.
And back at the inn, Jhujhar
Singh began Sunny's lessons.
What did he start?
Lessons.
Speaking about lessons..
If you are traveling by train
without a ticket due to any reason..
..then don't panic.
Talk to the TC traveling on the train.
He has the right to
issue a fresh ticket to you.
Spitting around is a bad habit.
Meanwhile, Gujjar was
fed up of running around..
..and now he is thinking of
finding a nice girl and settling down.
Uncle.. Mishra is still quite
tied up in managing the station.
Mr. Bhaiyya, Laila and Mr. Pandey..
..have literally spit out their enmity
..become friends and
have come to Mumbai.
To take part in a reality dance show.
Goldie is still happily..
blaming the system.
And Manu.. is still
laughing at his sorrows..
..and celebrating happiness.
And me.. Well, Vikram and
I have decided to start a family.
And the best thing is that
Vikram has been transferred to Mumbai.
So I guess now it's 'Chalo
Mumbai' (Let's go to Mumbai).
"Let's go Delhi."
"Life is short, why criticize?"
"Have fun if you are right."
"Stop thinking so much."
"Loosen up a bit."
"Life is short."
"Don't waste it
worrying about problems."
"Stop thinking so much."
"Loosen up a bit."
"Give me a high-five
if you want to rise."
"Because life short."
"Give me a high-five
if you want to rise."
"Because life short."
"Stop worrying too much."
"Let's go Delhi."
"Live life to the fullest."
"Today will be gone forever."
"Why do you worry so much.."
"..when all of us
have to leave one day?"
"Live life to the fullest."
"Today will be gone forever."
"Why do you worry so much.."
"..when all of us
have to leave one day?"
"Stop crying and be cool."
"Handle yourself or
you may make a mistake."
"Stop crying and be cool."
"Handle yourself or
you may make a mistake."
"Stop worrying too much."