Bonjour !
bon
jour
bonjour !
Bonjour means good morning
Bonjour can be used from morning
till noon (12 pm)
but
if you want,
even after 12 pm
i.e., any time of the day
you can use 'bonjour'
just like we use 'namaste' in Hindi
'namaste' can be used in the morning,
in the evening,
even at night
In the same way,
we can also use 'bonjour'
Now a pronunciation tip!
There are two letters in this word
which are often mispronounced by people
Which are they?
'j' and 'r'
'j' should be pronounced as 'zh'
so
'bonjour'
Now you might have noticed
Even 'r' has a different pronunciation in this word
What did I say?
'bon-joorh'
The different sound produced by 'r' is
rh
bonjour
You'll get some special notes in this video
So, watch this video till the end
AU revoir !
Don't forget to visit
www.novafrenchcampus.com