these are the lowest chance things to
ever happen in the world like this guy
who found himself randomly on Google
Maps or this person's car that's about
to get crushed by a massive Boulder but
randomly stopped but first we need to
react to this crazy ax throw okay so
they're throwing the axes whoa okay oh
that's pretty cool we need to go try to
recreate that how can you even cut metal
what are the odds very low because
that's the whole point of the video wait
he's gonna hit it out he's not
oh
I don't believe he doesn't even have an
emotional reaction he didn't believe
that just happened wait what is he doing
here
oh oh the Boulder's still going oh
but Boulder's coming at your car don't
beep move get out of the car perfect
timing
Carl
[Music]
what I was like what part of this is
perfect that firefighter woke up with
his hat on put his uniform on he's like
you know what I think this building over
here is about to collapse let me go get
the fire truck he's like I need to get
to town I know you're about to fall
man's dreams comes true he said he wants
to catch it well does he catch it oh
oh oh my God better have let him keep
that oh of course I hope he kept that
why would they not I don't know was
there like a shortage of footballs I
don't know they have a shortage of wins
but not footballs that's messed up he
bounces the ball on the pigeon
oh my God wait he hit a bird wait so
it's not out because it bounced off the
driveway or did what sport is that that
was rugby what's rugby it just looked
like they combined like four Sports into
one that's like a top three sport in the
world the pigeons aren't usually in that
sport okay no be dripping
[Music]
oh it's not stopping that looks like a
prank
save them either the other guy who said
that wasn't his day when you hold a
bowling ball like that you know how to
play okay what
what that's pretty cool well if you ever
did that I would think much more highly
of you even more highly much more highly
wait Boomerang hat no he's like take my
hat let me see this
oh was that on purpose no he made it
seem like it was on purpose though well
if I was an artist I would practice that
what's a nutmeg it's when you hit it
between the legs oh double oh my God and
it didn't clip any of their ankles wow
that was cool that's rare here's
something even more rare
that's funny they give me flashbacks to
Mysteries gaming the problem is eggs are
usually in fridges so when you pull it
out and you throw it you're like oh this
will just crack it does it it's
literally the equivalent of hitting
someone with a rock you have to thaw out
eggs before you Pelt your friends just
you know who's parking I don't know if
this is where you park whoa is that as
smooth
parking all right I don't know what to
say
oh is he gonna summon lightning what
that has to be edited well is that
edited nope really that really happened
yep what how do you know Walt you were
there I was Walt was there bottle cap
I'm into those
um what
and it's still spinning what is the
physics bird joins a ride
bro
so bad oh my gosh she got a new necklace
wow accidental hole in one and you
accidentally hit a whole one whoops I'm
good
oh that's hot all right that makes sense
does that count surely that counts for
the other person oh wait oh you hit the
other person out of the way oh yeah so
she did get a hold of one bus breaks
just in time oh
oh my God
I don't know everyone cheered him on I
say we give him a raise yeah go ahead
baseball grape juice what does that mean
no way
oh wait he caught it in his oh and then
he chugged it yeah you have to at that
point right wow you don't have another
Choice you're left with that only option
bro that's the coolest thing I've ever
seen how did I do that what'd you do
is that a destruction room what am I
looking at I don't know why does that
look like Fallout like what is going on
in there finding yourself on Google
Street View but I know him what's his
name simcopter is that really him I've
met him in person did he wear that shirt
I don't want to find out it can't be him
and with the shirt it's me
geometry
double kill oh my God that parent
unironically hates their kid
Annihilation
that's funny bottle shot
[Music]
oh but that coke bottle is better
basketball than you let's see the next
video
in the mouth
wow okay world record
wow oh my God I'm jumping off to
celebrate I'm landed in the basket
bro come on all right you know what yeah
I could yes if you duct tape my charger
to the floor and put my phone on the
floor I can slide it on you know what we
need to ramp these back up we're getting
more in the one in a million range not
the one in a billion this better be good
oh there we go now we're talking
boom that's awesome boss clock what is
that
oh right at the 10 seconds I mean it's
more just the cool walk away he did that
with a mission he had a plan but wait
what did he get free free drink look at
that face that's a man who wants his
free drink I'm making a Diet Coke oh
baseball is he gonna yam it oh no this
is where he hits the bird oh wait no he
didn't hit the bird what is this wait
that's a home run it went out of the
stadium that's out of the park right wow
what happened it was a home run really
why do they try to hit it over the fence
why don't they just hit it into the roof
well the roof isn't full of holes but
your mom is oh got what I needed
that's disrespectful off the head office
Noggin whoa how's this affecting my
taxes or LeBron's Legacy
wait he's like oh thanks for all the
food they're like get him water
what happens here
could you believe that and he wasn't
looking he didn't even see it happen wow
poor goalie Tyra returns to Cinder this
is where it like rolls off and rolls
back on it's on a race oh my God it's
going for a distance
wow what he's like hey I'm back do you
miss me is this LeBron James there he is
wow LeBron never doubt Lebron stop
doubting him this is nothing that you
practice right maybe when you're goofing
around at the end of a practice right
you know what I'm gonna say those
commentators were not
agreed the same three trucks with the
blinkers synced oh that's cool that's
beautiful and then let's follow that up
with the crash truck
bro after
and tried his best
it was halfway transformed kid can't
make it
that's fine they better count that
oh they better count that that's the
most unlucky rare amazing catch all
right I'll be the judge if this is an
amazing catch all right let's see how
amazing it is foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay I'll be honest it's amazing so he
finally gets it and then he bobbles it
again all right you know what that was
pretty amazing and so are you for
watching to the end subscribe