...This is not being followed. This poses a danger to the lives of the people sitting behind as well as my life
And when I go home, it becomes a danger for my family as well
This extremely important document that I am writing and handing in...
Greetings, friends!
It has been more than 10 days since the you-tuber "Flying Beast",
that is, Gaurav Taneja raised some critical flight safety issues in Air Asia Airlines on his social media
Due to which, he was even suspended from his job as a pilot
But even today, there has been no response from the airline regarding these specific issues
Whether these issues persist or not and what the airline is doing to avoid them- nothing at all!
This is something that concerns all of us
If we book a flight on Air Asia today, a question arises- Is our safety in danger?
Come, let us understand these issues in detail
I spoke to Gaurav about these issues
One of these issues is so critical that it might be the reason behind the rising cases of corona virus in the country
Come, let us see
-Gaurav,  coming straight to the point, the people that you are up against will try their best to divert the issue
But I would like to keep this to the point
Let us talk about the three safety issues that concern the people
The first safety issue, as you had pointed out, was that of paid leave
Could you please elaborate on that?
This issue is precisely about sick leave and how it has been made punitive
If a pilot is sick, then how is he punished for taking a sick (leave)
In most jobs you work for five days- from Monday to Friday- and Saturdays and Sundays are off
For pilots, they pilot the flight for 6 days and get the seventh day off
These are the off days
On the other hand, there are sick leaves
No matter which job you have, you can take a sick leave if you are unwell
and there are a specified number of sick leaves in every job per year- for example, around 10-15
The same goes for the pilots
Now Gaurav says that if you take a sick leave in Air Asia, then it is counted as an off day
-This is a normal month with the dates written. Assume a pilot had flights from the 4th until the 9th
He flies for 6 days
He should get an off on the seventh day, as per the regulations
So, he got an off on the 10th
And then, he can work again for 6 days
Let me explain with the help of an example- Suppose, the pilot got sick on 9th, right before his off day
and he got so sick that he was not in the condition to go to work
If he takes a sick leave on the 9th, then he would have a flight scheduled on 10th, despite it being an off day
and the company would assume that 9th was your off day and that you were resting
So, counting six days from the 10th... it can make you fly again until the 15th
A very important thing to understand here is that
Are you taking a holiday when you are sick?
Are you enjoying?
On my off days, I do gym, I shoot my videos and edit them and I spend time with my family
Basically, it is a time to let go off my fatigue
But when you are running high fever, are you recovering from fatigue?
You are suffering in your sickness
You are not recovering from fatigue
The company assumes that you are recovering
When in fact, sickness adds on to your fatigue
Now, assume that when that pilot came to fly on the 15th,
then he had no time to recover from his fatigue from the 4th until the 15th
Imagine how fatigued the pilot will be on the last day, if he is flying on 15th
Imagine if he has to get up at 3 in the morning to report for a flight (and) do four sectors
Furthermore, if its a normal job and your're a little fatigued, then it's fine- it can be endured
But if a pilot flies a plane for 15 days in a state of fatigue,
then it becomes a safety risk for all the passengers on board that plane
if he is unable to fly the plane properly
-And here, I'd like to show you a study by the FAA- the Federal Aviation Administration, which is
the regulatory body in the US, akin to the DGCA here
It was quite a significant study
The first page on it reads, "Fatigue threatens aviation safety because it increases the risk of pilot error
that could lead to an accident."
Let me give you some background information regarding the second issue
If you've ever seen outside the window of your aeroplane while landing.
then you might have observed that the portion beneath the wings starts to tilt
This part is called a flap
You can control several aspects of landing by determining how open or how closed the flap is
If the flaps are open all the way, then it is called a full flap position
If they're not open all the way, there's a position in between- the flap 3 position
Using the flaps, you can control two main aspects of landing
The first is, you can control your descent angle if your speed is constant
In the full flap position, the descent angle is more steep- that is, the plane lands in this manner
In the half flap position, that is, the flap 3 position,  the plane lands in this manner
You can clearly see this in the diagram
But another very important point which happens in the commercial airlines is that
If your descent angle is constant, then you can control the speed of the aeroplane by using flaps
In the full flap position, the aeroplane would descend slowly
You would have more time and more control over the aeroplane because of the slow descent
In the half flap position/flap three position,
the speed of the aeroplane would be slightly more during the descent
-Both Flap 3 and Flap Full are recommended configurations for landing
by the operator/manufacturer, which is the Airbus
Both are safe. But the pilot needs to evaluate the conditions for both before he makes a landing
The fact of the matter is that a Flap 3 landing saves fuel
It saves fuel because you're not landing the plane at a steep angle and bringing it down gradually
and all the airlines recommend it
But there are some conditions that call for a full flap landing, for example, in case of a short runway
or if there are mountains around the runway in a hilly region
then there is not enough space for the plane to descend gradually
In such cases, a steep descent is required with full flap landings
Now, Gaurav says that Air Asia forces its pilots to ensure that 98% of their landings are flap 3 landings
if they want a bonus
So, pressure is mounted on them subconsciously to encourage them to opt for Flap 3 landings
If the pilots do not do this, they would lose out on their bonus
which is a risk for the safety of the passengers in the airports where a Flap 3 landing would not be the right choice
-We got an e-mail from the company that we should opt for Flap 3 landings 98% of the times
I had received a specific e-mail in the month of May
that in the month of March, 71% of my landings were Flap 3
which is a non-compliance of SOP
Everything in aviation runs via these Standard Operating Procedures
If any pilot deviates from this then he becomes liable for an enquiry or questioning by the company
And...
So, I first got this email in March and a follow up on 31st of May,2020
where my head of operations told me in written/in black and white that
this is a punitive policy and that I, as a pilot, am indulging in non compliance of SOP
and this SOP is approved by the DGCA
and that the company would be happy to retrain me as I was not following the SOP
and in order to make this more punitive, my bonus would be deducted as well
-Could you show proof for our viewers? Any document of Air Asia with their policy written down
which reads that one needs 98% flap landings to secure a bonus?
-So, I have an email, Dhruv, which is was sent by Head of operations- Captain Manish Uppal
It is dated 17th January, 2020
Before I show you this email, let me tell you what is a green operating procedure
Airbus provides some operating cost saving techniques
and Flap 3 landing comes under green operating procedures as well
So, this heading is- Flap 3 landing and idle reverse SOP non compliance
and it clearly states that if you do not do this, then it amounts to non compliance of SOP
..that your compliance rate for green operating procedure will improve after this email
and we won't have to apply demerits for the non compliance of SOP
What are these demerits? Everybody's points are collected at the end of the year
and the ones with more points get more bonus
and those with lesser points get lesser bonus
So if you make lesser Flap 3 landings, then fewer points would be accumulated
and you would get lesser bonus at the end of the year
So, Dhruv, I am sending you one more email which shows that the pilots have a target of 98%
The heading of this email is- Non compliance to SOP and Fuel Efficiency Procedures
I received this mail from the management on the 4th of May
"Our Key Performance Index (KPI) takes into account all scenarios" -
be it the environmental conditions or steep approach or tail wind or wet runway or pilot fatigue
The KPI has been formulated keeping all things into consideratio
".. and is on par with other AOCs in our group and other Leading world Airlines
Based on our data for the month of your compliance for reduced flap landings was 71% versus
target KPI of 98%."
-I have a question. Is this the case with only Air Asia or the other airlines as well?
As far as my experience goes, there was no number given to the pilots where I worked before
Now, I will tell you how this affects flight safety
The report of the investigation of the Air India crash in Mangalore in 2010
recommended that this could be a contributing factor
that their pilots were repeatedly counselled for hard landings
Boeing states that if the impact is lesser than 2.1G while landing, then you do not require counselling
But their pilots were counselled even if they had a landing impact of 1.9G
So, they probably felt that hard landings could invite counselling
So, in order to smoothen their landing, they were floating over the runway
and they used another 500-800 feet of extra runway
There were several other problems in the approach
But in this specific problem, they used up another very useful portion of the runway which was about 500-800 feet
So all these things keep accumulating at the back of the mind
And one day, when all the things keep going wrong, everything will align
and then that leads to an accident
-Another thing Dhruv- Ever since this issue has been raised, the pilots of some other companies..
some people develop a "macho" attitude
So, someone sent a post on social media which was very disturbing for me
Some people are saying that they would stick to the 98% even in Imphal
So, this type of an attitude which only few pilots have
has become into a "this vs this" issue
It has not been made into an ego issue which is very dangerous
Now, imagine
that pilot is committing to landing in an airport like Imphal, which has a steep glide slope
without even considering the environmental conditions on that day,
without considering anything
they're saying that no matter when they go to Imphal, they'd opt for a Flap 3 landing
Now, imagine a heavy aircraft. Imagine tail winds at Imphal.
Imagine (that) its raining and its a bad weather day and the runway is wet
The drainage conditions in Indian airport and the grooving specifications...
I will not go into too much detail about that
Imagine all the environmental conditions are against this flap 3
and still the pilot decides to do flap 3 because he has already committed that he would do so
because he wants to achieve the target of 98% and also,
if that pilot is not rested well and he is fatigued
he is operating on the 15th, because he had applied for a sick and his off day was cancelled
Imagine all these factors combined and now think where we are going
In aviation, no accident happens just because of one factor
It is never going to happen solely because of one flap 3 factor
This will be a combination of all the factors and one day, all the things will align
and a mishap will occur
We should be proactive in rectifying mistakes right where they are
It has been our habit since forever that we wait for something to happen and then find out why that happened
-The third issue that you raised is the most critical in my opinion because
basically, if the DGCA circulars on COVID19 were ignored,
then I think that the exponential rise of the COVID cases in our country today
could be because the airlines did not follow the rules
They cases that were coming in, those that could have been stopped right at the airport itself,
if there were sound rules at the airport, maybe this situation could have been avoided
Do you also feel the same way?
-Dhruv, when these talks were ongoing in March,
then there were several times when these procedures were not being followed
I always intimated the company. We also have a WhatsApp group of pilots
that is run by management pilots.  Now  calingl it official or unofficial is upto you
So, I notified this there as well
The others raised similar concerns. But it was on 23rd of March, specifically, when I saw
that a lot of procedures were not being followed and carelessness was on the rise
Then I documented it. We have a report called the "Voyage Report"
which is read by the captain/PIC of the flight
I specifically wrote there that DGCA circular number so-and-so is not being followed
And I, being the captain and the PIC of the flight, I have the full responsibility
Until I ensure the safety of the passengers sitting behind me,
I have the full authority to sign(or not sign) the document...
And whenever we sign the document stating that we accept this flight,
We take full responsibility of that aircraft
So when I know that there is such a glaring shortcoming, how do I accept it without doing anything about it?
-Did you, as a pilot, have authority to delay the flight if the rules were not being followed?
-Yes, Dhruv. The PIC has full authority to do that. And I did delay a flight on 23rd of March
and I did write down the reason that the circulars were not being followed. There were other points as well
The document that I signed required me to fill in the flight arrival and departure time (as for all the flights)
That document is extremely important and the management reviews it very carefully
If any flight gets delayed by a minute and we write down that it was delayed, then we get a call the next day
asking, "Captain, what was the reason for the delay of the flight?
Can you give us any explanation or how can we improve it?"
So...
OTP is such an important matter for us that we keep stressing on being on time
But when a captain writes it down and tells you that some rules are not being followed
which is risking the lives of the people sitting behind as well as his life
and it would be a risk to his family when he goes back home
This extremely important document that I am writing down and handing in,
I never got an email or a call regarding it yet
asking the details of what was not being followed as per his complaint
and how could it be improved in the future
I was never contacted regarding this
We always try and be on time because being on time is company's PR
Which I agree, is extremely important
And we contribute fully to make that happen
But
there's something more important than that- safety.
-Dhruv, let me explain it with an example. Say there are a 100 employees in a company
50 out of them would not be concerned with what is happening around them
40 out of them would take cognizance of the wrongs being done and would whisper amongst themselves
but they will not take this up
8 out of those would tell the boss about the wrongdoings in written
The boss says that necessary steps would be taken
Then those 8 employees would eventually take a back seat thinking this is how it happens in India
But only 1 out of those would stand up and say
that he has had it enough and has brought things to the attention of the authorities enough times
and that he has taken it up enough number of times
But yet, nothing is done about it
and he refuses to work in those conditions because that would endanger the lives of everyone
and endanger the lives of his family and him
I stand up and I refuse to work till all these things continue and till negligence reigns
So that was my attitude. I stood up and on 23rd of March, I wrote it down and refused to work on 24th
I said that a lot of negligence was taking place and that it was putting everyone's lives at risk- passengers, crew, and my family
That is why I took this step
And all these policies- regarding COVID, flap 3...
In the case of sickness, their man days are being saved if they relabel sick as an off
then they are able to get extra work done and are able to save up on man days
If you do not follow the COVID guidelines because it would incur more costs in the form of  more staffs
and extra equipment- they would have to get sanitizers installed and arrange for PPEs
Everything comes at a cost
And as you know that there is direct fuel saving in the case of Flap 3
All these policies that I stood up against are the profit making policies of the company
And the company was noticing that time and again this person was standing up and pointing fingers at policies that
hamper our profit
Even though it was safety that I stood up for
So when there was requirement for pilots, the company kept taking in complaints without saying anything
But as soon as the COVID time arrived and their operations slumped
and  they were aware that even when things opened up, they would not need so many pilots
They directly targeted me and then threw me out of the country
-I saw "boycott Air Asia" trending on Twitter
The media also took up your issue
The Minister of Aviation also responded to that tweet
But there has been no progress regarding this. What do you think is
being done by the Ministry and the Airlines in the meantime?
-I saw that this was trending on Twitter the day I put up this video but I had no idea that this would trend
and who made this trend. The people took this upon themselves to make it trend
After that, DGCI also made a public tweet that they would take this up
that somebody has raised a complaint against some airline
But I never got a specific acknowledgement from the DGCA or any communication from the aviation Minister
I have not yet received an official confirmation or communication from anywhere
Dhruv, I'd only like to point out that this is a fact based case and I would request the authorities
to conduct a fair investigation into this
I want nothing else. All I want is a fair investigation
The most important thing is that Air Asia should respond to these questions
What answer does Air Asia have to the three safety issues that have been raised
The Air Asia must say something- either accept or deny these allegations
Share this video so that it reaches more and more people and that it mounts pressure on Air Asia
to respond to the question of whether our safety is in danger or not
If you like my work, you can support me on Patreon.com/DhruvRathee
or by becoming a member on YouTube by clicking on the join button
so that I may continue to make such videos for you in the future
And you would get access to several exclusive things upon becoming a member. For example,
you can watch, unedited, full and raw interviews by becoming a member on the channel
We will meet again in the next video
Thank you