Hello, friends!
Did you hear the news?
I'm going to make a wildcard entry in Bigg Boss!
So many media houses have published this news.
India TV, India Times,
ABP News, India Today,
Zoom TV, Pinkvilla, Economic Times.
I mean, look at this headline.
"Popular YouTuber Dhruv Rathee
set to make a wildcard entry
in Bigg Boss OTT 2."
One website has confirmed this.
Dhruv Rathee Bigg Boss OTT Entry Confirmed!
So is this true?
No!
Till now no one has asked me to go on Bigg Boss this season
and neither have I told anyone that I want to go on Bigg Boss.
So first of all,
this tells you the standard of our Indian media.
They will publish anything without any hesitation.
Scroll down and see the article in Economic Times,
there is a disclaimer.
"This content is authored by a 3rd party.
Please take all steps necessary
to ascertain that any information and content provided
is correct, updated, and verified."
They do not take responsibility for the materials they post.
They shift the responsibility on you to ascertain whether the news is true or not.
And the second thing here is that
some of you would be wondering,
if I am invited to Big Boss,
will I go on Big Boss?
No!
Let me say this clearly,
even if they offer to pay me to be on the show,
hundreds of thousands, millions, any amount of money,
I will never go to such a nonsense show in my life.
In my opinion, this is a very cheap way to earn money and fame
which has a bad impact on society.
So in today's video, I would like to explain
what is problematic in the concept of this show?
Is this show scripted?
And why you should not watch such shows at all.
If you or any of your family members
waste their time watching Bigg Boss,
then this video is for you.
"Now, there's news of
famous YouTuber Dhruv Rathee's
possible wildcard entry in Big Boss."
Once, this guy Siddharth Yadav,
made a YouTube video in which
he said that there are so many jobless people in our country
who watch Salman Khan's movies
that have neither heads nor tails.
"This gives you an idea
of how many jobless people we have in our country
who enjoy watching such movies
that make no sense.
But because it is Salman Khan's movie
even if the ticket costs thousand rupees,
they need to watch Salman Khan's movies,
regardless of anything."
He was somewhat right.
We shouldn't consume any content
that doesn't have any intellectual or profound content,
that aren't productive.
It's a different matter that
he is in Bigg Boss' house now.
But it's also true that
Bigg Boss is the most apt place for this type of person.
People like him deserve to go on Bigg Boss
and, in fact, to win it.
I'm sure he can win this show.
Because there are some specific qualities
that are required for this show's concept.
Based on which this show can run.
I'll tell you about that later in the video
but first,
let's know the history of this show.
How did this show begin?
In 1949, writer George Orwell
published a legendary novel
called 1984.
This book talks about a dictator-dystopian government,
which is headed by
an unknown Big Brother.
Posters are put up everywhere,
Big Brother is watching you.
The dictatorial government
is always watching you.
In 1999,
some guys in the Netherlands
took a similar concept from this novel
and turned it into a TV show,
which they named Big Brother.
The concept of this show was that
some people would live in a house
under constant surveillance
and under the command of Big Brother.
To shape the format of this TV show,
they took inspiration from some older TV shows also.
Such as the MTV reality show
The Real World
and a 1997 Swedish TV show
Expedition Robinson.
After a while, this show became very popular
and started spreading all over the world.
Copying this concept,
America, Canada, Mexico,
Brazil, Argentina, Australia,
Indonesia, Thailand, the Philippines,
China, and Russia,
made their Big Brothers.
And when it comes to copying,
the Indian entertainment industry can't lag behind.
Big Brother was made into Big Boss in India.
It was soon launched in different languages.
After Hindi, came Marathi, Tamil, Bengali,
Telugu, Kannada, Malayalam.
Then when OTT platforms came,
they made Big Boss OTT.
Big Boss
George Orwell mentioned Big Brother as a warning in his book.
He was criticizing governments like Stalin and Hitler
and the techniques used in these dictatorships
to fool people.
How propaganda for fascism is run on the telescreen.
And there is constant surveillance,
no one is safe from it.
History is rewritten.
The people display the bandwagon effect.
Facts are presented in a completely distorted manner.
And a cult personality is created around the Supreme Leader.
The political opponents who question this dictatorial government
have to deal with conspiracy theories against them.
They are declared anti-national.
Many famous slogans were given by this book
like "Ignorance is power,
Freedom is slavery,
War is peace."
Even today this novel is very relevant
especially when the governments buy software like Pegasus
using tax money
to surveil people, to snoop.
So, this novel is a must-read.
I would definitely recommend you read it.
If you don't have time to read the novel,
you can go to ChatGPT
and ask ChatGPT for a summary.
I'll simply need to write,
"Explain the novel 1984 by George Orwell
in ten bullet points,
using simple language."
And here you can see,
I have got a very good summary
of the story in this novel.
It is about a man named Winston Smith.
If you want to expand on any point,
"Elaborate on point 4
how were historical record changed?"
Ask how history was rewritten in the novel.
It is written here that if a wrong prediction is made by the party,
people like Winston's were tasked with
changing the old news records
so that it looks like the party had made the right prediction.
With the help of AI tools like ChatGPT,
it has become so easy to understand complex ideas.
This is why I have made a 4.5-hour long course on this
so that you can master ChatGPT.
And you can get a deeper understanding of AI chatbots like this
how they work,
what are their limitations,
what is possible to do with them
and how you can use them
in your school or college life,
in your job,
in expanding your business
or in your home.
The people who have taken this course so far
found it helpful.
If you have not joined yet,
you can get the link in the description below.
The entire course is in Hindi with English subtitles
and use the coupon code BIG40
to get 40% off on this course.
This offer is available only for the first 400 people among you,
so you can quickly try it out.
Apart from the link, you can also scan this QR code
to access the course's webpage.
And after joining,
you can be a part of this Artificial Intelligence revolution.
Coming back to the topic,
what are shows like Big Brother and Big Boss doing?
Contrary to this novel,
they are providing you the cheapest form of entertainment
which has a heavy dose of two things.
Everyday sadism and voyeurism.
First, let's look at sadism.
The definition of this word is something like this
"The tendency to derive pleasure
from inflicting pain, suffering, or humiliation on others."
Enjoying hurting others and insulting them.
You may find this shocking
but if you are a part of the audience watching Big Boss,
then you are taking part in this sadistic pleasure too.
Normally, a sadistic personality is associated
with murderers or psychopaths.
Only psychopath people
who kill others or hurt others
and enjoy it as they derive pleasure in doing so.
But some psychological studies
have discovered a less extreme category of sadism
which is called Everyday Sadism.
Like this study from 2013
which was published in the reputed journal
Psychological Science.
They conducted psychological experiments on Everyday Sadism.
Let me give you some examples.
You'd remember that in the ancient Roman Empire
as you must have read in your text books
that the Colosseum in Rome
was a stadium for public entertainment.
Here, gladiators would often fight each other.
Many times when a gladiator would get badly injured
the audience in the stadium would be asked
whether to let him go or to kill him.
Many times the people would give a thumbs up
to kill him.
Often in this arena,
a hungry animal would be sent,
like a tiger or a lion,
to fight this gladiator.
This is a good example of Everyday Sadism
because the people sitting in the stadium
were looking for entertainment in the suffering of a gladiator.
Moving forward thousands of years,
today, many people enjoy watching street fights.
When two people start fighting on the road,
whatever the reason,
often a crowd gathers.
Very few people try to stop the fight.
Most people just stand around
and enjoy the fight.
Another example of this are the bullies.
People who like to bully others
in school or college.
People who enjoy humiliating others.
Or you would have seen people who
will start kicking or throwing stones at dogs
on the side of the road for no reason.
Just because they enjoy it.
A moderate example of this in an office could be
a boss who is always criticising an employee for no reason.
Not because he wants to get some work done.
Just because he enjoys
inflicting mental pain on his employees.
These are the major examples of Everyday Sadism.
Mob lynching is another example.
This year in May,
a Bihar migrant worker
was lynched in Kerala by a crowd
when accusations were raised that he was a thief.
Something similar happened in the Palghar incident
when two sadhus were lynched
because of a rumour that they were child kidnappers.
It's a different matter that later
some biased media anchors
put a Hindu-Muslim touch to this
to give it a communal angle.
You will see many examples of Everyday Sadism everywhere.
If someone on the street says that
they have caught a pickpocketer,
4 people would gather and start beating him.
They justify their actions by saying that
they beat him because he was a pickpockter.
But in reality, the reason for such things is
to derive sadistic pleasure
by beating someone.
You can see this Everyday Sadism in political binaries as well.
Like, when journalist Vinod Dua passed away.
There was a group of people who were celebrating this.
On the other hand, when news anchor Rohit Sardana passed away,
There were some people on the other side who were celebrating this.
Now, criticizing the work of these people is one thing,
but taking a sadistic pleasure in their passing away,
finding one's happiness in another's death,
is a good example of sadism.
People often have many justifications
in the name of Everyday Sadism.
Some say that this is the justice of nature,
and some say that this is karma.
But actually, all of this is sadism.
People derive sadistic pleasure
when they see someone getting insulted or trolled.
Entire YouTube channels are often made on this.
Where in each and every video, someone gets insulted,
someone gets abused or someone gets bullied.
Now, I am not criticizing the roast format here
because making roast videos can be an art.
It can be done positively
without sadism.
A good example of this would be
Slaypoint's YouTube channel
which makes roast videos.
They criticize stupid things
like being an irrational motivational guru
or some absurd food recipes.
But they poke fun on the stupidity.
They do not intend to abuse, bully, or insult someone.
A 2018 study by the University of Innsbruck showed
how everyday sadists
like to play especially violent video games.
Because that's what uplifts their mood.
That's what gives them happiness.
Often films are made to exploit this sadism.
They are called Torture Films.
Like the Saw series
or Human Centipede.
Some people liked Joker's character in the film Dark Knight
because perhaps their own sadistic personality
gets validated by that.
But on the other hand, there are some films
that I would like to state as examples
which sensitively depict sadism.
For example, the film The Platform
or Snowpiercer.
Criticizing the socio-economic system,
showing violence without glorifying it.
And finally, if we come to Bigg Boss,
TV shows like Big Brother and Bigg Boss
exploit this Everyday Sadism.
They try to appease this.
Their formula is that people like to watch this nonsense,
so they give them nonsense.
And to be honest, this Everyday Sadism in Bigg Boss
reaches the next level.
Contestants always fight with each other.
There are often physical fights.
People throw utensils at each other.
In one case, a contestant threw boiling water at another.
There's physical violence.
In one case, a contestant choke-slammed another contestant.
The contestants aren't the only ones to do this,
rather, the concept of the show encourages this.
For example, once the contestants were given a torture task
in which they had to throw chilli powder on the faces of other contestants.
The contestants are made to do such nonsensical 'tasks'
so that they can be humiliated.
People are asked to bathe in cow dung.
A man was asked to drink water from a dog bowl.
Often people leak each other's personal matters
which makes people cry.
You get to see body shaming.
A female contestant tells another female contestant
that some people were not worthy of standing with her.
Criticising their physical appearance.
"Backbiting" is a crucial component of this show.
You regularly see misogyny and homophobia.
Sometimes someone mixes soap in someone's water.
Sometimes a guy breaks the lock of the washroom
when a girl is taking a shower.
Often you see toxic relationships.
Some of these are fake relationships
which are shown just to increase the show's TRP.
Then comes the concept of Voyeurism.
This word means
taking cheap pleasure in watching other people's lives.
Enjoying closely watching what happens in other people's private lives.
Once again, you will see many examples of this in your daily life.
Like, if there is an MMS leak.
You see people searching on Google to find it.
Another example of this could be
some people like to watch daily vlogs.
There are some YouTubers whose vlogs are aimed at
when they woke up, brushed their teeth,
played with their dog, rode their bicycle,
and then they went shopping.
Why do people find these things entertaining?
Because of voyeurism.
People enjoy watching what's going on in their personal lives.
And it's a shame that some YouTubers even exploit this.
Like, their child may be crying,
but they think about getting the camera
because it will be good content.
Their child might be hurt,
but first they take the camera and film it.
If there is a fight at home,
they want to be the ones to stream it.
So that they get some content.
Many people often make a dangerous one-sided parasocial relationship
with daily vloggers.
In my opinion, children should not be allowed
to watch daily vlogs.
Since children's brains are not fully developed
so voyeurism can be very dangerous for them.
Another moderate example of this is CCTV footages.
People enjoy watching
CCTV footage of thieves being captured
or someone being murdered
or a terrorist attack or road accidents.
Media houses also often play these footages on TV.
So Everyday Voyeurism
obviously increases in a surveillance state.
So, if we talk about Bigg Boss again,
then this Everyday Voyeurism is exploited badly by Bigg Boss.
In Bigg Boss 16, 98 cameras were installed inside the house.
And now, a different level of madness is taking place regarding voyeurism.
Contestants are often recorded 24x7 with multi-cameras
and the audience is also allowed to watch them 24x7 on a live feed.
They can choose any of the three cameras
and choose what they want to watch.
And as you know, there is so much
unemployment in the country that
there are a lot of people who are free
who have no other work
so they start watching this.
By watching the live feed of these cameras
one can take some voyeuristic pleasure.
People often share their personal secrets
with their close friends and best friends.
But here, people are told
to tell their personal secrets on national television.
To generate content and TRP.
And the amazing thing is that
nothing about this 'reality' TV show is real.
Contestants know that they are being recorded for 24 hours
with so many cameras.
So will any contestant
behave in their natural state here?
Will your behaviour be the same
as it is normally?
Not at all.
Everyone will be self-conscious to some extent.
Secondly, an artificial competitive setup is created in this show
so that you will naturally have to insult others,
and backbite others,
if you want to rise above them.
In Bigg Boss' house, this is called 'performance.'
These interactions between people,
are these natural interactions
that would happen in real life?
In real life,
if so many people have to live in a house,
there will hardly be a fight between them.
Here, such setups are forced
to create arguments and fights between people.
The truth is, friends,
the world is not that stupid.
Although I have told you many examples of
Everyday Sadism and Everyday Voyeurism.
But most people are not like that.
There are many intellectual, well-behaved,
dignified, and compassionate people in the world.
Take Dr Vikas Divyakirti, for example,
He has made many educational videos on philosophical topics.
Or if we talk about actors and actresses,
take Konkana Sen, for example,
She has given so many great performances in so many films.
But in the 17 seasons of Bigg Boss,
you would not have seen a single person like
Dr Vikas Divyakirti or Konkana Sen.
Firstly, nice people will never go to such cheap shows.
But secondly,
even if a nice person goes to such shows
they are provoked
to be part of this sadism and voyeurism.
To create controversy and insult people
and if they don't, they will be thrown out.
There was a participant in Bigg Boss 8
Sushant Divgikar.
A model, singer, dancer, psychologist,
and winner of Mr Gay India 2014.
He was thrown out of Bigg Boss very quickly.
Later, he said in an interview that
he has more than 500 books at home.
he reads a lot, and has an IQ of 147.
But he said that he was sad to say that the collective IQ of the Bigg Boss 8 contestants
was less than room temperature.
All the while Sushant lived in that house,
Sushant didn't fight with anyone
he just kept busy with his songs and dance routines.
But you don't get TRP like this.
You get TRP only when
there's conflict or fights among contestants.
Bhojpuri star Khesari Lal Yadav
was a contestant in Bigg Boss 13.
He was also thrown out of the house very quickly.
And when he gave an interview to Times of India,
he said that the format of the show
doesn't suit him.
Humans become devils in this house.
And if you want to move ahead in this show,
you can do so only by insulting and humiliating others.
This was what he said.
"I was amid devils there.
There, in the form of humans,
everyone was behaving like devils.
And no one is human in there.
What can anyone do?"
Bigg Boss Season 4 contestant Rahul Bhatt said in an interview,
"I can't provide entertainment
to viewers at the cost of making a fool of myself."
Why would the channel want to keep someone on the show
if there is no controversy or romance involving them?
So on the face of it, it looks like
there is no public voting here.
Only the TRP decides who will be thrown out of the house.
Bigg Boss Season 9 contestant Aman Verma also said that
he had a pre-planned deal with the producers
that he will be in the house for only 6 weeks.
A Sunday special episode of Bigg Boss 16 was hosted by Shekhar Suman.
He had criticized some of the contestants
but the viewers criticized him
for pointing out only some of the contestants.
So he replied by saying that
he had been given a script
written by the channel
that he had to follow.
Bigg Boss 4 winner Shweta Tiwari,
Bigg Boss 6 contestant Aashka Goradia
and Bigg Boss 11 runner-up Hina Khan said
that this show is heavily edited.
The long conversations
are shown as two lines only.
It is deliberately shown
as if there are misunderstandings between the show's contestants
sheer misrepresentations.
Aashka said that she was rubbing a balm
on another female contestant's hand
after she had an allergic reaction.
But the show's editors
used editing tricks
and showed only half of the things
and made it look like
she was a lesbian.
Bigg Boss 7's contestant Shilpa Saklani says that
the show is not scripted,
but that everyone knows what to do to win.
There are prerequisites
to react and give content,
to fight with each other,
to put across their point of view,
and to be assertive.
So even if we ignore these accusations
of the show being scripted,
even if we believe that the show is not scripted,
some things are very clear in front of us.
First, there are no auditions here.
Contestants are chosen by the makers of the show.
Based on what?
Well, it seems like, based on intrigue.
Second, 24-hour footage is edited to be a 50-minute episode.
Which of those 50 minutes are shown?
Those that will attract the most viewers.
Third, the viewer's perception based on that edit,
influences the voting.
Often the rules are also bent.
Sometimes there are no eliminations on some weekends.
Sometimes the contestants who have been eliminated
are called back into the house
and sometimes, there is a wild-card entrant.
Everything is decided by the makers of the show
based on its saleability.
Fourth, the tasks given in the show
are also decided by the makers of the show
based on saleability.
And what is saleable here?
No intellectual discussion.
No social issues, philosophy, history,
sociology, spirituality,
poetry, literature, cinema, or science.
None of it is being discussed here.
People just want to watch others fighting.
People want to see their personal lives.
People want to see people backbiting others.
People want to see other people insulting each other.
A cocktail of Everyday Sadism and Voyeurism.
Whose show is it?
The show makers'.
Who's money is invested?
Who's time is being wasted?
Yours!
And whose mental state is being affected?
When Honey Singh is asked about his misogynist songs,
he replies that it's just entertainment.
That it is what the public wants.
If you ask the showmakers of Bigg Boss
about what they are showing to the public,
he will also reply similarly.
The same excuse is used
that it's just entertainment.
The public wants this,
that's why they show it.
"Entertainment. Entertainment. Entertainment."
Friends, the thing is, watching such things can affect you too.
Psychiatrist Dr Marcia Sirota claims that
just like our teeth and health are affected by junk food,
bad reality TV shows
affects our brains
and we become ruder.
When people see the reality TV shows
and how celebrities become rich and famous on it
by abusing people,
doing weird things,
and by becoming self-serving egoistics,
the audience is convinced by this perception.
The audience starts believing that if they want to earn money and fame,
then this is the best way.
Doing such cheap things.
Telecasting their personal life on national TV.
Insulting, bullying, and roasting other people.
Brian Gibson, a psychologist at Central Michigan University,
did a study and concluded that
watching such reality TV shows,
leads to an increase in aggression in the viewers.
Comparing to violent media and crime TV shows,
reality TV shows cause a higher increase than them.
An effect on the mental health of the contestants is also evident.
Many contestants have said that
after the show, they had to deal with so many mental health issues.
Many contestants who were so determined to win
that they reveal their personal secrets
later regretted doing so.
Some contestants are made into villains in the public perception,
even though they are not that bad in real life.
Then the public criticism that people have to face after coming on the show,
that causes a lot of anxiety among the contestants.
Shamita Shetty, Sana Khan, Kushal Tandon,
Nikki Tamboli, Kavita Kaushik, Shalin Bhanot,
Rahul Vaidya, Himanshi Khurana,
Apurva Agnihotri, and Shilpa Shaklani,
are the examples of those people
who faced mental health issues after going on the show
and after the show, they had to take therapy.
So I request everyone
to not treat their brain like a dustbin.
Your brain is not a dustbin
that you can keep throwing any rubbish into it.
The content you are consuming,
choose it wisely.
The type of entertainment you are consuming,
think about what effect it is having on you.
Does it have a positive impact on your life or a negative impact?
And I am not saying that you should always consume intellectual content.
Even if you want to consume non-intellectual entertainment,
think about it first.
Will it have a positive or negative impact on you?
And obviously, if you spend your time learning new things,
it will have a very positive impact.
If you want to join my ChatGPT course,
you can find the link in the description below,
or you can scan this QR code.
Remember, Homo Sapiens means 'wise man.'
If you haven't seen the evolution videos,
you can click here to watch them.
See you in the next video.
Thank you very much!