Which brand?
As good as it intoxicates it's fine.
Any brand would do for me.
Watch your drink, you've to drive.
I can control the vehicle
even if I am drunk.
Listen to his crap. He's too much.
Who's banging on the door?
Hey, just check.
Yes, coming.
Who's that? Idiot!
I want matchstick
to light my cigarette.
I don't have any. Get lost.
Please give it. Listen. Hey.
I said I don't have it. Now, just go.
Listen...
Who's banging on the door?
Just check.
Why is this constant
banging on the door today?
I told you I don't
have any matchstick.
Now, leave.
- But... hey...
- I said leave.
I just want fire,
just need a matchstick.
Listen. Hey...
Now you will get beaten up.
This is my last warning.
You idiot...
Sir, this is the
only piece of land I've.
Show some mercy.
Have mercy.
Hey, my name is Daya.
What is it? Daya.
But I'm not merciful by nature.
Nana sir has liked your land.
Now, I want it.
Come on, sign.
Sign the documents. Come on.
You?!
Kill him.
Leave me!
Leave me.
Pardon me.
Pardon me, please.
Mistakes can be forgiven.
But misdeeds deserve punishment.
No.
- Jaggu.
- Yes.
I'm tensed about Rocky.
Rocky is backed by Sultan now.
If Sultan backs up somebody
he will surely destroy his enemies.
Don't worry. He will kill
all of them and return soon.
Hope he is safe.
Both of you are cowards.
Jaggu, I am really worried about him.
- I will go and see him.
- Yes, let's go.
Don't take pain, he will come back.
- Hey!
- Come...
Rocky, these girls?
Actually, we were partying
at our friend's farmhouse.
Suddenly we felt dizzy
and started vomiting.
- Gaikwad sir.
- Yes.
Found more bodies downstairs.
- Ambulance is already here.
- Okay.
My darling, sweetheart.
Let me love you.
- To hell with this phone.
- Let it be.
Hello.
- Kale sir.
- What's it?
- What?
- Yes.
- Love me.
- Get lost, you jinxed.
Market is open for all. Give it.
- Next time I want full payment...
- Yes, sir.
...if you want the supplies.
Yes, Kale.
Ganu.
What?
Sir, call for you.
Nana sir.
Somebody killed Daya last night.
Even the stuff stored
at his site is missing.
It's a huge loss.
It has to rain to stop the wildfire.
Hey, speak up. What did you see?
Have you seen a ghost?
He's totally in shock.
Rane! Shane!
- What nonsense is going on?
- Sir.
Stop your nonsense. Madam is here.
Madam has come.
Now she will make you spill beans.
You will speak like a parrot now.
Salutation, madam!
Madam, last night
massacre happened here.
Moreover, this was a brutal murder.
It's not a murder.
It's revenge.
Revenge?!
But how?
No rocket science
needs to be applied here.
Look at him carefully.
He has been tortured first.
Isn't killed directly.
Take proper photos, I want close ups.
Yes, madam.
- Gaikwad.
- Yes, madam.
Send the body for postmortem.
Yes, ma'am.
And who's he?
The eyewitness of the massacre.
- He came to meet Daya last night.
- Take him in the custody.
- Hey, come on. Get up.
- Okay, madam.
- No one except me will meet him.
- Yes, madam.
I want proper primary report.
I don't want any carelessness.
Last time you know what had happened.
- Yes, madam...
- Back off, please.
Ma'am, who's responsible
for this massacre?
I will let you know as soon
as I get a full proof report.
And we will talk
to the media once again. Thank you.
Please give us some time.
Please. Thank you.
Ma'am one question, please.
Ma'am, what do you
think about these murders?
But madam, no body was found here.
Something is amiss, Gaikwad.
How was this Daya?
Daya always appeared
descent in the society.
But was into illegal businesses.
Builder by business.
But he used to forcefully
take possessions of lands
construct illegal buildings,
extortion.
These were his main businesses.
No one took action on him?
Nana, madam.
What do you mean?
He was Nana's right hand.
Where's this Nana?
He's in Delhi with minister sir.
Regarding election.
Delhi elections.
So he will come
here for the campaign.
Yes.
So let us start his campaign.
- Right?
- Yes, madam.
- Who's it?
- It's me. Vivek.
It's me, uncle.
I brought this for you, uncle.
How are you feeling now?
No progress.
Uncle, everything will be alright.
Wait for a few more days.
Yes.
'Famous businessman
Daya has been murdered.'
What are they showing
on TV since this morning?
About these murders?
Uncle, even I don't
know anything from this.
I just got to know.
Okay. Shall I take your leave Now?
Are you going?
Alright.
Go.
Uncle, have faith in God.
Everything will be fine. I am there.
Who?
Nana sir.
- Sir, investigation is going on.
- Shut up!
I've lost my man.
And you're still investigating?
Don't you love life?
I'm helpless, sir.
New S.P. Kalpana madam
is handling this case.
But why are you there?
- I haven't done anything, sir.
Leave me. - Come on.
Nana, he was near the murder spot.
He's from the opposition party.
Speak up. Who did you give the tip?
I don't know anything,
please leave me.
I will bury Patil tonight.
Ganu, election is coming close.
Take careful steps.
Rizvi had come at night, right?
- To see Daya?
- Yes.
Kale, where's his body?
- He's in SP Kalpana madam's custody.
- Kale.
Nana is the smartest among the lot
and gives a checkmate to his enemy
before he realizes the danger.
24 hours.
Only 24 hours.
[Sulatan Ajam Khan]
'I know you adjust a lot for me.'
'Thank God you realise it.'
"Anybody who crosses my way"
"or messes with me."
"Anybody who crosses my way
or messes with me."
"I swinge him."
"Anybody who crosses my way
or messes with me."
"I swinge him."
"I live in an entirely different
world that is full of friends."
"I'm an ordinary man."
"I've got a good physique."
"At times I'm angry man,
and at times a soft spoken person."
"I am the king of this world."
"Wow, brother."
"Wow, brother Rocky."
"Everybody needs a partner in life."
"And I'm always on demand."
"I'm always into
discussions amongst girls."
"Brother Rocky is always trending."
"Everybody needs a partner in life."
"And I'm always on demand."
"I'm always into
discussions amongst girls."
"Brother Rocky is always trending."
"I've got a good physique."
"Even the filmy
heroines are after me."
"I am the king of this world."
"Wow, Rocky."
"Wow, brother."
"Wow, brother Rocky."
What was the need
to get into the brawl?
Have we taught you this?
Rocky, remember one thing in life.
Not every time,
violence can solve problems.
Think calmly.
Mind you, this rage of
yours will ruin you one day.
Why don't you invest your caliber
on your career,
on your work, on your profession?
Show your rage over there.
Who won these medals
and certificates?
Where's that Rocky?
I want that Rocky.
Don't you want to settle in life?
Have you thought over it?
Do you really wish to settle in life?
Do you wish to get married?
Twice, brother.
What?
Two marriages.
Two marriages?
- Yes.
- Why?
Leave that. We are really hungry.
Do you have...
Vidya, will they starve now?
Coming. Piping hot fritters
are ready to serve.
I thought they will be
full after so many rebukes?
Make way.
Take this. You all are hungry, right?
Chiku, you also take it. Take it.
Listen.
Today you were very angry with Rocky.
He has grown up now.
That's why I was angry with him.
I always keep worried about him.
But we need to change
his short tempered nature.
He might land into
some trouble one day.
He should get married
and settle down at this age.
How long he will
enjoy life like this?
And how long will I feed him?
I can understand
your concern about him.
But Rocky is intelligent.
He will settle down.
Don't worry.
Rocky.
Hope brother's rebuke
hasn't hurt you today.
No.
But he's always right.
Now we must get serious
and settle down in life.
You're right, Rocky.
We do have parents in life.
But not brother like yours.
I really respect him.
Today I'm convinced with him.
Brother and sister-in-law
have done a lot for me.
Now, it's time to
return to their favours.
Brother, sister-in-law and Chiku.
I want to make them happy in life.
I will do anything for them.
You just control your anger.
And then you will see
that everything will be fine.
Sure, I will.
Hey, Rocky.
Sister-in-law had made
delicious fritters. Just awesome.
Avi, bring some more for
me if it is still in stock.
I'm very hungry.
Even the biscuits are over.
We are talking something
and you're getting it off track.
Shut up. Hungry cock.
Rocky.
No, enough is enough now.
I must seriously look for a job now.
Now, you just watch.
I will make brother
feel proud about me.
You've received many awards
and certificates in gymnastics.
- Yes.
- That's really very good.
Thank you, sir.
But you're a fresher.
Yes, sir. But if you
hire only experienced people
how will the freshers get
opportunity to show their talents?
Okay.
Hello.
Hi, Sanjana. How are you?
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Okay, listen.
Let's meet at your
favourite restaurant today.
Why?
I will tell you once we meet.
Anything special?
Yes, of course.
I will pick you sharp
at 7 pm. near your house.
Okay? Be ready.
Yes, I am always on time.
- And listen.
- What?
- I hate you.
- Rocky...
Grumpy.
Will you speak up now?
Rocky, please tell me. I've
been asking you since a long time.
What's the special occasion today?
- I've got a job.
- Wow!
- React slowly.
- Sorry.
- Rocky. It's great news.
- Yes.
I am so happy.
Waiter. One veg pizza,
one Chinese, one noodle
one veg manchow soup.
- And...
- Wait a minute.
I've got a job and not the payment.
Oh really?
Cancel all the orders
and give me a veg pizza.
Okay, madam.
I'm letting you go for now.
But not after you get your salary.
I know you adjust a lot for me.
Thank god you realized.
So then?
Rocky, I'm really very happy today.
Same here.
Now, I want to settle down in life.
I want to do a lot for brother,
sister-in-law and Chiku.
Amen.
When will you meet my dad?
I will... give me few months.
Let me settle down in job.
Then I will see him.
Because before meeting
your dad I must be independent.
- That's true.
- Exactly. Anyway.
This is for you.
Special gift.
Wow!
This is so cute!
You like it?
Very pretty. Hope our life
will also be as good as this.
Absolutely.
You were afraid of getting late.
See, you have reached.
Careful.
Now, quickly give me a
hug before somebody notices us.
What's this? What hug?
You daily come to drop me, don't you?
Rocky, I don't want to go home.
I just wish that the
time halts when you're with me.
Only both of us.
Anyway, we daily meet.
Yes, we do. I never denied.
But you don't need
to do much for that.
I've to find a new excuse every day.
Every time I deck up to come to you
mom asks me where I am off to.
And I give her excuses
of different friend's birthday.
Thrice in a year I
celebrate Akshay's birthday.
Rocky, I want to proudly
take your name and leave home.
Very freely.
When no one will question me.
When will this happen?
- Just now.
- What?
Let's go.
I will talk to your parents.
Dumbo. I just shared
my feelings with you.
And I also shared my feelings.
Rocky, I think about you only.
Sanjana.
I'm living so as to
fulfill all your dreams.
- Now go, somebody will spot you.
- Bye.
Bye.
Want me to serve you?
Dad, did you watch
the match this morning?
- Dhoni played so well.
- It was first class.
Stop discussing cricket.
Eat first.
Wait. You would always stop us.
- There she is.
- Dad.
Come, my daughter is here.
We started with the supper,
as you didn't come.
What did you bring?
Hey, who gives you such
beautiful gifts every day?
Dad, my friends.
My close friends give it.
- Close friends?
- Yes.
I must meet your close friends once.
Great idea.
Do one thing.
Invite your friends at home.
So that all of us can meet them.
- Yes, Sanjana. Invite them home.
- Yes.
Yes, sure.
I will deal with you later.
Fight later. Take your dinner first.
- Mom, I am not hungry.
- But...
She eats outside food daily.
- It's very unhygienic, you know.
- Yes.
Dad, I will be back in a moment.
- Sanjana.
- Coming.
Sanjana. Hey...
She has gone.
You should better get her
married to bring her on track.
Marriage?
She's still very young.
Leave it, dad.
Watch tomorrow's match.
Of course I will watch.
"Sometimes smiling."
"And sometimes upsetting."
"Life should be like that."
"Sometimes aloof."
"And sometimes in the crowd."
"Life should be one such poem."
"Live a little."
"It's very short."
"Although short, do taste"
"it for its sweetness."
"Sometimes smiling."
"And sometimes upsetting."
"Life should be like that."
"Sometimes her excuses."
"Kind of silly as
well as intelligent."
"Life is somewhat like her."
"Some crazy people."
"Sing in love."
"And then the life
seems to be a fairytale."
"Sometimes happiness
and sometimes pain."
"But you keep moving, O heart."
"Sometimes smiling."
"And sometimes upsetting."
"Life should be like that."
"Sometimes aloof."
"And sometimes in the crowd."
"Life should be one such poem."
I can't believe.
How can you do this?
You know what?
Dad will be left in a shock
to know about your love affair.
Rocky, I am against this marriage.
And Sanjana,
you will not meet Rocky now.
And you also will
not meet Sanjana, Rocky.
- Listen to me, brother.
- Sanjana.
Rahul! I love Sanjana.
I can't live without her.
You please tell him, Sanjana.
Rocky!
Rocky.
You forget me and our love.
Sorry. Listen, it was her plan.
Rocky, both of you are in love.
And both of you will involve
your parents in your marriage.
Then why would I object?
I'd love to make you
a part of our family.
Even my parents had
gone for love marriage.
- Really?
- Yes.
Do this,
come home day after tomorrow.
Dad will be back home by then.
Keep this a surprise for him as well.
Okay, I will take your leave.
Nana sir told me
to distribute bonus in the company.
You're lucky, Rahul.
You're working in Nana sir's company.
Rocky, you too are lucky.
Sanjana is with you.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Take care.
Bye. Reach home early
in the evening.
- Yes.
- Bye.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sanjana.
So, you were scared.
You think only you can scare me?
I am also not any less.
Yes, madam. You're great.
Correct.
You will behave like this
even after marriage, okay?
- Really?
- Yes.
Sanjana, I've got a job now.
Very soon we will get married.
Now, our dreams
are getting fulfilled.
Life seems so beautiful.
Rocky, we will live happily.
Brother, sister-in-law, you and me.
We will live together.
I like the joint families.
And how can I forget
something really important?
Our bedroom. I will decorate it.
I will paint it pink. Very beautiful.
And I will decorate the entire house.
1... 2... 3... 4... 5...
Come on. 6...
7... 8... 9... 10
Take your call.
It's ringing continuously.
- No, sir.
- Take it. Take your call.
Okay, sir. Thank you.
- Hello.
- Yes, tell me.
- What are you doing?
- Sleeping.
What? Sleeping in gym?
People work over there.
They don't sleep.
Sanjana, I am busy.
Can we talk later?
Please, talk to me for some time.
I can't.
- I am missing you, Rocky.
- So, how can I help?
Come on.
Leave it. Brother and I have
come to your favourite restaurant.
You also come for the lunch.
Sanjana, I can't come. I am busy.
Do you get it?
Why are you getting angry?
No, I am not.
Why are you shouting on me?
I am not shouting.
Rocky, why are you yelling?
I am not yelling.
I don't want to talk to you.
I won't talk to you at all.
Even if you call me up
I will not talk to you. Bye.
What's wrong, sir?
With my training your
body might look like Arnold.
But these girls are impossible.
- My body, sir?
- Yes. I will make train your body.
Yes.
What's it? Why are you
shouting on that poor fellow?
- He's on duty, right?
- Poor?
He's not poor, brother.
Besides, I enjoy troubling him.
Let's go to the office.
I've some work.
And from there we will go home.
- Home?
- Yes.
Brother, you had promised
to buy me a dress.
You had promised me.
- Do you still remember?
- Yes.
- Okay, let's go.
Sanjana, please pick up the phone.
God!
Sanjana!
Rahul. Rahul.
Rahul. What happened?
Rahul.
Hey, what are you doing? Who are you?
Mom. Mom.
- Mom.
- Sanjana.
Mom.
Yes, Mohite.
There's a problem.
- What has happened, mom?
- Please save Sanjana.
Ro... Rocky.
Sanjana.
Nothing will happen to you, Sanjana.
Na... Na...
Sanjana.
Sanjana, wake up.
Sanjana, talk to me.
I will do as you say.
Sanjana, wake up.
- Talk to me. Sanjana.
- Leave her, let's go.
Leave me. Sanjana.
I can't live without you.
Talk to me.
Sanjana.
Come on.
Sanjana. Talk to me.
How dare you rape a girl?!
And raise hand at a police officer?
Come, I will show you.
Listen to me, brother.
- Brother. Brother, hello.
- What's it? What do you want?
- Just leave.
- Just a minute.
Let me meet him once.
Who are you? Who do you want to meet?
- Rocky.
- You can't meet him.
- But why?
- Why?
Theft, murder,
rape and raising hands at police.
These are the serious
charges leveled on him.
No, sir.
Kale sir has given
clear instructions.
No one will meet him. Go.
Listen, Rocky is
not that type of a boy.
- Hey...
- Just a minute.
Kale sir is checking how he is.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir. Don't get angry.
Just two days.
Saturday and Sunday.
Kale sir will make him spill beans.
Is that clear?
Now get going.
Sign.
- Yes, brother Daya.
- Yes, Kale.
He's not ready to confess the crime.
Kale, you're useless.
You can't do anything.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Yes.
Kale, take it patiently.
Why do you do this?
Come on.
Brother Daya. Brother Daya.
- You rogue.
- Stop.
Daya.
I will break you into pieces.
Not only yours.
You've a brother, right?
A sister-in-law and a niece.
What's her name?
- Chiku.
I will slit throats.
Of all of them.
Then I will kill you.
- Sign.
- Brother Daya.
- Calm down.
- Will you not?
You calm down. I will talk to him.
Hey, he's mad. He knows everything.
Don't take the sin of
slaying those three lives.
- Sign.
- Wait.
I promise.
Nothing will happen to them.
And nothing will
happen to you as well.
Get up. Come on, sign now.
He is doing it.
- Give him a pen.
- Here.
- Yes. - No need of a pen.
Take thumb impression.
Here it is. Come on. Put it here.
- Yes.
- Very good.
This is the first time
I've seen such a case.
Boyfriend is imprisoned
for raping his girlfriend.
Kale.
Rakesh Pawar alias Rocky
is given lifetime imprisonment.
What do we do, sir?
I can't do anything now.
Your brother has confessed the crime.
How can I help?
Yes, we agree. We don't deny.
But he's innocent.
Innocent? Then go to the high court.
We are not that capable.
Why don't you understand?
Then do this.
Forgive me. Just leave now.
Take it for the sake of humanity.
Rocky can't do this.
- I did all this for humanity?
- He must have been forced to do this.
- He has confessed his crime.
- Brother Rocky.
Rocky!
Stop sir.
Let me meet him for just 2 minutes.
- Rocky.
- Dad, where's uncle going?
- My dear...
- Why isn't he coming home?
- He will...
- Where's police taking him?
Uncle. Don't go.
Uncle. Let's go home.
- Why isn't uncle coming home?
- Go inside.
I got piping hot breakfast.
Thank you very much.
- Go and serve now.
- Right away.
Rocky.
Didn't you sleep at night?
He had turned on the TV and slept.
Pakya's call?
Yes, Pakya, what's it?
What is the tip?
Color it till the top.
No part should be left.
From top to bottom
Don't do unnecessary time pass here.
I should not be able to see
any part left from top to bottom.
Understood.
The entire work should be done properly
No stain should be visible here.
We have already discussed
about the budget.
After the work finished
don't saythat you want more money.
Hey, get going.
Idiots.
What are you looking at?
He's so handsome.
Look at his muscles.
Whose? Mine?
Get lost.
Rocky, come inside.
You handle everything over there.
I will handle it here.
Are you alright?
Okay, disconnect the call.
How's everyone at home?
Brother, sister-in-law. Chiku?
They are good.
Rocky. There's a problem.
- What?
- Daya murder case is on hype now.
And those girls?
Don't worry about them.
They have reached home safe.
Once I make a commitment
I don't even listen to my mom.
But you've created a mess outside.
You murdered Daya but
left one man alive over there.
Do you remember?
Now Nana is after him.
Kale is already his ally.
He will kill him in the lock up only.
Before that Kale will be dead.
But...
Just yesterday you killed Daya.
And now Kale?
Don't you think we are hurrying up?
We have already delayed a lot.
I've been waiting from past 3 years.
Jaggu.
Kale.
Done.
"This silvery beauty."
"And curvy body."
"Eyes, as sharp as a gun."
"That kill people at a glance."
"People get crazy for
me and spend nights here."
"Intoxicated by my eyes,
they start speaking in English."
"This attitude of mine is unmatched."
"I'm little local and little English."
"Looking at my curves, hearts races."
"He replaces my figure in his heart."
"Sometimes I am spicy
and sometimes sour."
"Sometimes sweet as well."
"People come in suit and boot."
"And feel shy on seeing my smile."
"They get fever of getting me."
"And start dreaming about me."
"This attitude of mine is unmatched."
"I'm little local and little English."
Damn! Even this has finished.
- Hey...
- Yes.
Come here.
- Yes, sir.
- Go get two bottles quickly. Go.
Sir, we are closed now.
What?
Hey, idiot.
You know who I am, don't you?
- Yes.
- Go.
Idiot.
These people will never reform.
"I'm little local..."
Very good.
Wow!
How's it, sir?
- First class.
- It has to be.
- It's of the first lot.
- You bloody...
You?!
Finish him.
'Boy friend is imprisoned
for raping his girlfriend.'
Madam. Hey, madam.
What do you do here?
I work here.
What do you work at night?
Do let us know.
What are you saying?
What do you mean?
A murder took place here.
We will inquire.
We are police officers.
- We've the right to ask. Right, Rane?
- Yes.
- Rane! Shane!
- Sir.
Sir.
- What's going on?
- Sir.
What's it?
Eyewitness.
Madam, don't be afraid.
Tell the truth about what you saw.
Yes, sir.
- Take her to the police station.
- Yes, sir.
Explain the sketch artist.
Yes, sir.
Let's go home, madam.
- Rane.
- Sorry, sir.
- Sawant madam.
- Yes, sir.
- Take her with you.
- Let's go.
What?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
It was him.
- Rizvi. Do you also agree with this?
- Yes, he's the same guy.
- Joshi.
- Yes.
- Are the sketches ready?
- Yes, sir.
This is Kale's murderer.
And this is of Daya.
Exactly ma'am.
I too had the same doubt.
Ma'am, Daya works for Nana.
And Kale as well.
So, this link will take us to Nana.
- We must meet Nana.
- Yes, ma'am.
- But before that look for him.
- Sure.
Direct attack on our gang?
And loss in business.
Who could dare do this?
Nana sir.
Do something.
Ganu, I won't get scared
with the death of one or two pawns.
Nana is a king.
He checkmates his enemy
before he realizes danger.
Police has prepared Rocky's sketch.
Rocky say something, please.
- What do we do next?
- Yes.
Jaggu, get up. Tell him something.
Rocky, what's your next plan?
Ganu.
Done.
But...
- Gaikwad, is this the correct address?
- Yes, madam.
Rocky's brother and
sister-in-law live here.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- Do you have fire?
- What do you mean?
I mean matchstick.
Get going.
- Sir, tell me one thing.
- What?
Is she your new madam?
Ajay Pawar?
Yes, that's me.
Take it, sir.
- Thank you.
- Madam.
Where's Rocky?
Don't you know, sir?
Rocky is in jail
from past three years.
Are you sure you don't know anything?
No, sir. But why?
Why do you ask me this?
What happened to Rocky?
He absconded three days ago
while shifting him to the other jail.
No, sir. Trust me.
I don't know anything about this.
But where is he now?
Alright.
We are just informing you.
He has committed more murders.
- Rocky committed murders?
- Don't talk nonsense.
- Don't accuse him like this.
- Vidya.
It's impossible for Rocky
to do anything like this.
I've raised him like my son.
- He can't do anything like this.
- Vidya.
- You too are like those officers.
- They too had done the same.
- Yes, Vidya.
- They booked him under false charges.
- Vidya.
All of you've framed Rocky.
- You people have framed him.
- Vidya.
- Listen to them.
- Go inside. I will talk to them.
Sorry, madam.
I am sorry.
I can understand her emotions.
We are here to help you.
We only expect your cooperation.
Madam, I am ready to
do anything for my Rocky.
Good.
I will change his prescription.
Bring those.
We will try for speedy recovery.
I also expect the same.
Uncle, I will drop him.
And bring the medicine on way back.
Okay. Go.
Rocky.
Don't send me to your home again.
Police is keeping
watch on your house.
Is brother alright?
Yes. He's good.
Sorry. I've brought the things
you had asked for.
Check it.
Meanwhile, I will go and get fresh.
"The time is smooth and nice."
"My speechless heart is calling you."
"The desire of my heart has awakened."
"I am teasing you by my touch."
"Listen to my heart, beloved."
"All directions have become unstabel."
"You're my moon and my night."
"I feel lonely without you.
Do not refuse me."
"Why should I be afraid of the world
when my heart has chosen you."
"The breeze that blows says it
this every moment."
"Do not go away, my beloved."
"Listen to my heart, beloved."
"Wonder what intoxication is this!"
"Stop me otherwise
I would make some mistake."
"I will be restless without you.
I don't know what will happen of me."
"The desire of my heart yearns for you."
"I am adorned for you."
"I am standing ready for you."
"Listen to what my heart said."
"Listen to my heart, beloved."
Are all the documents proper?
Sir, your signatures are needed on this.
Check properly.
And tell me if my
signatures are needed.
Okay.
- Salutations, sir.
- Greetings.
Please sit.
- Sir, actually...
- Ganu.
Order a cup of strong coffee.
Kadam.
Sir, actually, you see...
Wait a minute.
And one teaspoon sugar.
One teaspoon.
Go on.
May I, sir?
- Sir, actually... two murd...
- Sorry, please take tea.
No, sir.
- Do you want?
- No, madam.
We don't want it, sir.
Sir, out of the two murders,
one was Daya.
He was a builder.
Who? Who's this Daya?
You know him well, sir.
I don't know. I don't know him.
I see. Okay, sir.
The second murder
was of inspector Kale.
One from your known circles.
I don't know, madam.
I meet countless people in a day.
I help them.
I can't remember all of them.
It's impossible.
You're right.
But these murders links end at you.
That's why I feel you should
increase police protection.
What's this, madam?
- What was that police officer's name?
- Kale.
Yes, Kale.
You couldn't protect him.
This is too much, madam.
- Tell him.
- No, sir...
I will take your leave.
Yes, Patil.
Yes, preparing for the election. Yes.
- Do you see these men?
- See you soon.
They are our protection.
Tell us if you need protection.
I will send it on discounted rates.
Will you speak to
that empty sofa now?
Just leave.
Why being so buttery? Leave.
Madam.
- Where are you?
- Here at the gate.
Okay. What about the police?
- They are on night duty, sleeping.
- Sure?
- Yes.
- How do we go?
Don't worry.
I've arranged for a scooty.
Okay, drive.
- Let's go.
What should we do now, buddy?
Go. Go inside.
What about the police
siren we heard just now?
That's not for us.
It's for the domestic
violence in the ground floor.
It's their routine now.
You don't worry about them.
- Please come.
- Come, brother.
We will go downstairs
and check. Okay?
- Come fast.
- Yes. Let's go.
You all are coward.
- Who had called up?
- I had called up.
He doubts me.
- What?
- No.
Please save me from him.
He says that I fall
in love with youngsters.
I will lock you behind bars.
You tell me, do I look like that?
No. Never.
He doubts me.
If I come close to you,
he will doubt me.
If I will hold your hand,
he will doubt.
And if I give you a kiss,
You tell me. Do I look like that?
Your wife is so cultured,
loving and good.
She's so good.
- Rane, your wife has come.
- Where?
- You're scared, right?
Scared.
If you go near her
again and touch her
I will complaint your wife.
Sir.
Hand...
Hey, don't touch her again.
Don't touch her.
- Let's go.
- Leave it.
Now, I won't doubt you.
Come on, eat all of you.
Today police visited us.
They were enquiring about you.
They have two witnesses
and they have identified you.
SP Kalpana madam.
I think she's very honest and sharp.
All of you, take care.
You can't trust her.
She might...
All of you eat. I will go, get fresh.
Brother.
Brother, I had read in
your eyes what you wanted to say.
Rocky, Vidya had
told me about Sanjana.
But it was too late by then.
I went to her house frequently
in past three years.
But I couldn't meet anyone.
The day life imprisonment
was announced on you
they just disappeared.
I tried my best to find them
but couldn't get any clue about them.
Brother.
I am tired now.
I don't understand
if I am doing right or wrong.
I tell you one thing, Rocky.
The day you see anger in my eyes
that day you will be wrong.
Brother.
I am very tired.
Brothers.
Be careful.
I am okay.
Rupesh.
Brother Ajay just visited you all.
He loves you all so much.
I am so touched.
I've only one elder brother. Sultan.
Brother Sultan.
Jaggya.
You always talk about brother Sultan.
Tell us what happened in the jail.
I will tell you.
Like the people living on rent
I was living in jail.
They used to transfer me in
different jail after every 11 months.
Fortunately, rocky and I
were transferred in the same jail.
Sir...
Sir, what are you thinking?
When I learned his matter,
I lost my temper.
I tell you. I was looking
for a chance to kill him.
Sorry.
Every time,
everywhere I used to cross his ways.
But he wasn't losing his temper.
Don't take tension.
I will handle everything.
One day I got that chance.
What's wrong with you, uncle Rahim?
Are you not alright?
I've taken insulin. I am very hungry.
- So, eat.
- No.
No one can eat until
Sultan doesn't arrive.
How can they do this?
Wait, I will bring it for you.
No, stop. Stop.
Hey, you're being too smart.
Will you take lunch before Sultan?
Are they all mad to wait here?
Leave my hand.
I won't...
Here you go.
Stop. Just stay here.
I will break your bones right here.
Stay here, you bloody idiot.
'God is great.'
Brother Sultan.
Brother Sultan. I was...
'God is great.'
Brother Sultan,
that idiot raised his hand on me.
Brother Sultan. He... he's
the one who raised hands on your men.
He raised his hand on your Jaggu.
I want his bones to be broken.
Sultan. He was taking lunch for me.
- Eat.
- Thanks, son.
Brother Sultan, jailor has called you.
His name is Rocky.
He's not as calm as he is seen.
But I can't dare tell him the truth.
Both of us have the same enemy.
But we need to make him speak.
Now, it's your call.
He has been shifted here for this.
Move aside.
Get out from here. Move.
Come on. Move. Go from here.
Jailor told me everything about you.
But I follow a principle.
I don't believe until I don't
listen to the truth from the person.
Our enemy is the same. Nana.
Tell me what had happened.
Trust me.
Sultan will never ditch you.
Oh my God, brother.
The office is so cool.
Yes. And look there.
That's my cabin.
Very nice.
Brother, washroom.
It's there.
Go upstairs and on your right.
- Okay.
- I will be in my cabin. Come there.
Yes.
Where are the files now?
Sanjana!
- What's wrong?
- Brother, you look at it. Look at it.
Come here.
Hey, check if everything is proper.
Yes, it is.
Listen, call up Ganu.
- Tell me.
And tell him to shift them from here.
Why this transport
had to strike today?
Exactly. But Ganu sir is nice.
He handles everything.
Otherwise, Daya sir and
Nana sir would have punished us.
Wonder when this
strike will get over
and wonder when we
will take them out from here?
Yes, wait. I will call up Ganu sir.
- I will tell him everything. Let's go.
- Okay.
Thank you very much
for your cooperation.
Give your address and phone
number before leaving from here.
In case, if I've to enquire more,
I need it.
- Right?
- Sure.
Yes, okay, thank you.
- Mohite.
- Name, Rahul Deshmukh.
Brother. I will just come.
It's dad's phone.
Okay. Sector 16, bungalow number 32.
Why did you go there?
You should have left from there.
What if something
had happened to you?
Mom, brother was with me.
You people will not believe me.
Come on, get ready.
Rocky is coming today, right?
Yes. I forgot.
I am thinking of
not inviting him today.
So much has happened
that I am in off mood now.
Listen, Rocky is waiting to
see your dad from past five years.
You've planned this surprise
for your dad, right?
So, go and get ready.
Listen, Sanjana. Our day is spoiled.
Let's not spoil it for him.
Let him come.
- Sanjana.
- I don't understand what to do.
But since you both
are insisting let him come.
Once Rocky comes here,
your mood will change.
Now go. Get fresh. Get ready.
I will take care of the dinner.
- Hey, sir, you?!
- Hello.
Please, come in.
- I hope I haven't disturbed you.
- Not at all. Please, come in.
Actually, I wanted some
more details that's why I came.
- Okay.
- Rahul.
- Who's he?
- Hello.
- She's my mom.
- Okay.
- He's Mr. Kale.
I told you about him some time ago.
What will you take?
Tea or coffee?
- Tea will do.
- I will get it right away.
Enough milk and less sugar.
We, the police can't do without it.
Yes.
- Come, sir.
- Yes.
Please, sit.
Wow!
Tell me, sir.
It's so nice.
My god!
Chandelier in Marathi's house?
Actually,
this is our ancestral house.
Then my dad retired.
And we renovated it
from dad's retirement fund.
What was your dad's job?
- He was a professor.
- Okay.
Okay, tell me one thing, Rahul.
- Your boss Nana sir.
- Yes.
Had he been involved in this case
then what would
have been your stand?
Even if Nana sir is involved,
I will not step back.
Correct. Very good.
Law is above all.
Exactly my opinion.
Criminal must be punished.
Yes, the criminal will be punished.
- It's true.
- Hey.
I will just come.
Will you speak against Nana?
Rahul!
Brother!
Mom.
What have you done?
Leave. Leave me.
Nana sir will have a good time.
- Leave me.
For the first time my eyes
have shed tears for others.
I will not let it get waste.
I lost my wife because of Nana.
All my men ditched me.
Nana has framed me here.
Nana is your enemy as well as mine.
You want to seek revenge, right?
Will you?
Do you have the courage?
You prepare from your end.
I will do all the
arrangements for you in jail.
- Jaggu.
- Yes, brother Sultan.
- Start making arrangements.
- Okay.
Police Gymnasium
"Let the blood boil now."
"Till when will there be darkness?"
"Get ready to win alone."
"Conquer all the odds."
"Let the blood boil now."
"Till when will there be darkness?"
"Get ready to win alone."
"Conquer all the odds."
"Do whatever you have suffered."
"Keep instigating me.
I should not get calm."
"Come and promise yourself.
I may die but will not stop."
"My eyes are thirsty for blood."
"Come on do it and win."
"Make a firm promise to yourself."
"Fight..."
"Revenge runs through my blood."
Come and play...
Brother Daya.
Sultan is training
somebody over here.
Why don't you kill them?
Are you waiting for my orders?
Okay, brother.
"Forget all your worries."
"Resolve all the knots."
"You are totally devastated."
"Why are you dreaming, dear?"
"Come and play."
Jaggu, call up Daya.
Tell him that the boy is killed.
Tell him.
Come on, speak up.
- Hello.
- Hello, brother Daya.
I've killed Sultan's man.
Also kill Sultan.
Yes, brother Daya.
It's not good for him to stay here.
Shift him.
It's time to shift him.
And then with the help of Vivek sir
Rocky and I escaped from the jail.
And out first target was Daya.
Jaggu.
You've done a lot for Rocky.
How can I repay your obligations?
No, brother?
Don't talk like this
and make me a stranger.
No, Jaggu.
You're not a stranger.
Henceforth, you are our brother.
Brother.
Brother, we incurred a huge loss.
I will become a pauper in this way.
No, this is not fair.
What do we do?
Party has paid us.
And they are angry on us.
We are tensed.
Brother, I hate tension.
Fresh stock will arrive soon.
From every corner of the country.
That's okay. But when
will we get the stock in hand?
On Ganesha festival.
How do we trust?
How do we know?
Hey. Ganu, tell him in his language.
Never ask an ocean about
the quantity of salt he can give.
Don't ask the sea,
how much salt it can give.
Hey, did you understand?
- Yes.
So leave.
[Indistinct chatter]
Nana sir.
I've taken a big
risk by promising them.
Our stock is seized.
Daya and Kale are not with us.
Opposition is already targeting us.
How do arrange for the fresh stock?
And how do we deliver them?
I am there.
No matter how big a cloud is,
it cannot move the mountains.
Ganu.
Deal must be struck
on the day of campaign.
I want money as well as power.
But this job must be done.
Get the permission. Go.
Permission?
- For what?
- For taking out rally by Nana.
Do this, sir.
Give us an application
signed by Nana.
I will give that application to madam.
Once approved by
her you can go ahead.
Who's this SP Kalpana?
- She's my senior.
- She must be your senior. Not mine.
Gaikwad.
Tell her not to cross my ways.
Because anyone trying to
mess with us will get buried.
Get up!
Hey, what worth you are?
Will you show me my worth?
You want permission?
- This will prove you costly.
- I will give you the permission.
Get up.
Will you provide us
protection in discount?
Now get slapped in discount.
Come on, give it. Fast.
Will you dare again?
Will you?
Get up. Come on.
Tell your Nana.
I won't give the permission.
Take out the rally if you have guts.
Return his napkin.
Now, who will bury whom...
And who will mess with whom...
ACP Kalpana will decide that.
Understood?
- Gaikwad.
- Yes, madam.
Throw this garbage out.
Rane! Shane!
Sir, madam doesn't
have a washing machine
that's why she
has tried hands on you.
And you know what, sir?
Stains remain after the beating.
And it's seen clearly on you.
Hope you've powder at home.
He has been beaten up so badly.
- Where to, sir?
- Let's go.
Hey, don't turn away
from your promise now. Okay?
And what money do you demand?
What money?
You will get only the
amount Nana has decided.
Is that clear?
Is that clear to you? No?
Don't mess with me.
Anyone who crosses my way,
I bury them.
You killed Daya and Kale.
Hey, hit him.
Nana. Nana.
Nana.
What's it, Ganu?
Nana, he thrash me badly.
That Satan... he's Rocky.
He has killed Daya.
He has killed Kale.
He had come to kill me today.
He will bury you alive.
You just watch.
He's the same boy.
Same boy whom we had framed.
Daya had given contract
to kill him in the jail.
He's the same guy.
Sultan had trained him.
Hit me.
All of you hit me.
Kalpana hits me.
- Rocky hits me.
- Shut up.
Who trained him?
Sultan.
Phone... phone...
Phone.
Ganu.
Hey, smarty,
you escaped death or else.
Fool, you escaped death.
You're Fool.
Don't you dare call me Fool.
- Tell me.
- Nana.
Rocky!
You might not know me.
But I know you very well.
You've ruined my life.
Now it's your turn.
I will kill each of your men.
You will yearn to see me.
But I will come before you only once.
In the form of your death.
Keep watching.
Ajay, we are reopening Rocky's case.
I saw many loopholes in this case.
I mean, first of all, Rocky's
statement is not recorded anywhere.
Professor Digamber.
Where did this man disappear
after this incidence?
No one knows.
I mean, what happened to him?
Something fishy.
Gaikwad, I will solve
this case in no time.
- Bring professor Digambar to me.
- Yes, madam.
Don't worry, Ajay.
We will try our best to make sure
Rocky gets the least punishment.
Thank you, madam.
[Indistinct chatter]
Come on. Hurry up!
Ajay is defeated.
Let's go.
Vidya.
Ajay has met with an accident.
Madam, Ajay met with an accident.
Brother Ajay is no more.
All unit stand-by.
Rocky!
Brother.
Brother...
Let's go.
Cheers.
Long live, Nana.
This is called master stroke.
One brother is up.
And one is in the lock up.
Amazing.
Good days have arrived.
The one who killed Nana's
men one after the other is Rocky.
This is Rocky who loved Sanjana.
Uncle, Rocky was supposed
to come and see you on that night.
And that was the surprise
for you from Sanjana and Rahul.
But Kale arrested
him from your house.
Coincidently he came to my jail.
Although being a brother,
being a policeman
I couldn't do
anything for my sister.
Because you stopped me.
But Rocky took the revenge, uncle.
But Rocky's brother
got killed in all this.
Please, uncle.
He needs your help now.
Ma'am, all clear.
Professor, first of all,
I want to apologize to you
for calling you here for a meeting.
But I had no other choice.
I want to hear from
you about everything
that happened on that night.
It's important for the case.
I know you will be troubled
recalling those things again.
But it's really very important.
That day I had called up Sanjana.
- Yes, dad.
- Where are you?
Dad, I am in the police station.
Police station? Why?
Nothing, there was a little problem.
But everything is fine now.
Is your brother with you?
Yes, he is with me.
- Are you alright?
- Yes, dad. I am fine.
Never mind then.
How much time you
will take to reach home?
- Maybe 2 hours or so.
- Okay, fine. Bye.
- Yes, Vivek.
- Yes, uncle.
Reach home as quickly as possible.
Sanjana said there's
nothing to worry.
I left for home.
But when I reached home and saw...
Rahul.
Just see who's here. Rahul.
Rahul, talk to me. What happened?
Rahul.
Aunt. Rahul.
Aunt. Aunt.
Aunt.
What happened, aunt?
Who had come here?
Aunt, speak up.
Tell me, who had come here?
Sanjana. Sanjana.
Sanjana. Speak up.
Look who's here?
Sanjana, talk to me.
Talk to me.
See, who's here?
Sanjana, look who's here?
Sanjana, look who's here.
Speak up, Sanjana.
Calm down.
I will not sit quiet
until they are not punished.
Now, whoever will
commit such a crime
I will punish him.
No.
Rocky!
Court has given you permission
for immersion of Ajay's ashes.
"All the worries are overcome."
"When You're there, Lord."
"There's no friend as good as You,
in this world. O Lord."
"You come on Your devotees call."
"To help your devotees."
"This strength is all by Your mercy."
"Bless me with your help today."
"I get emotional
singing in your praise."
"It's your blessings,
that safeguard me."
"The voice is heard
in the skies, Morya."
"The voice is heard in the skies."
"Glory to Lord Ganesha."
"The voice is heard
in the skies, Morya."
"The voice is heard in the skies."
You!
- Hey, spare me.
- I spare you.
Thank you.
Tell me how you framed me.
Also about Nana's businesses.
Yes, I will tell you.
Right now.
But now...
"The voice is heard in the skies."
"Glory to Lord Ganesha."
He's Rocky!
He has killed our men.
Arrest him.
Arrest Jaggu.
Madam, I am ready to take
up all the murder charges on me.
He has committed many murders.
He's a hardcore criminal.
Jaggu!
I'm doing the right thing.
I used to wander
on streets in childhood.
People used to look
at me as if I was a thief.
But no one took me
in his arms and asked me
where my parents are.
Where my family is.
I never knew what family is.
But this family needs you.
Rocky.
Will you come to see me in jail?
Rocky!
Rocky, I am sorry.
No, dad.
'I made a grave
mistake in knowing you.'
'I could not believe when saw it'
'and at the same time
a hope forced me to live.'
'But at that moment Nada came
and threatened to leave the city.'
'I got scared. I fell at his feet
and begged for her life.'
'And I calmed down Vivek'
'and with his help we left the city
and went to some far off place to hide.'
'Since past three years
someone has been waiting for you.'