hi everyone my name is alina rice and
today i'm going to raise a question to
you this is something that i have felt
and observed a lot around myself and
want to know that if this is something
that bothers you too okay so this
definitely bothers me
um okay let me just quickly come to the
point
and this is kind of ironic coming from
me because okay you'll know why i'm
saying this is ironic the point is that
indians unnecessarily speak english all
the time
you're going on the road somebody would
stop you request you to stop and ask for
direction they will ask in english then
you're supposed to reply in english okay
asking a question in english would imply
that you would
respond in english now this is slightly
difficult for people who do not know
english people who don't understand
english or who are not very fluent in it
or do not have that kind of confidence
to reply in english now it gets awkward
for those people i've seen that in my
own mother's case it is slightly
embarrassing i don't know um
not okay it may not be embarrassing for
me but it definitely is embarrassing for
her and i can see it on her face
because somehow we attach the status to
the language and
i feel that it's i okay this is just my
opinion i may not be right in your eyes
here but okay respectfully let me know
if i am not right according to you but i
feel that
it's slightly rude it's slightly rude if
you're just assuming that the other
person would know english because you
know the kind of hype we attach in our
country to this language and assuming
the other person would know english
would be like
if they don't know it then you're
embarrassing them most of the times in
our country looking at the person you
can actually see and
assume
more or less assume that the other
person would know hindi or would not
know hindi most of the times you can see
it from the way they are i think it's
easy to predict right so if it is easy
to predict that somebody would
understand hindi or not why don't you
put forward your question in hindi it
will get easier for the other person
also to handle customer care people they
always start their conversations in
english you see people ordering stuff on
the counters like mcdonald's and
everywhere it's always in english
i remember the first time i went up to a
mcdonald's counter i was a little girl i
was not very confident in english to be
honest and i remember the hesitation
that i felt walking up to that counter i
remember actually
um
[Music]
so strange i remember speaking those
words in my mind to myself okay these
are 20 words that i have to say to this
girl i was actually repeating those
words in my head okay these are the
things i have to order and then she will
ask me this and i'm this and this is the
reply that i'm gonna give her
that's how i was actually preparing my
conversation for just ordering a burger
i mean what is wrong
why can't we just simply speak in hindi
with each other why do we have to always
unnecessarily speak in english to each
other all the time i know my channel has
more than 450 i don't know 4 30 40
english videos just because this is the
genre that i've picked for myself but
otherwise i
love speaking hindi i am so confident in
hindi hindi comes to me naturally
i feel i can
express more in hindi i feel that i love
this language and
the way i can
um express my happiness my sorrow my joy
and my my excitement and everything in
hindi i can never never justify the
feeling in any other language but still
somehow we always choose to speak in
english
please don't bash me for this don't tell
me
don't tell me things that may disappoint
me later just respectfully tell me if
you agree with me or you don't i feel
that we should speak more hindi in india
that's all that i have to say because
i've actually been to some other
countries of the world like i've been to
thailand and all and i'm telling you the
value they're attached to their language
is awesome
like they're not even they they'll just
tell you on the face okay no english no
english no english and then you have to
know explaining what you have to do with
them where you have to go wherever you
where you've got to get down what you
want from that person is your problem
they will just tell you on their face no
english and then you're on your own
i hope you get the point this is not to
insult or embarrass anyone this is not
to attract any unnecessary attention to
myself i don't want to do that this is
just me speaking my mind and my heart
this is just me
talking about the kind of appreciation
and love that i have for my language and
this is just me sharing a thought with
my friends and i just want to know if
you feel if you agree with me on this or
you don't it's all right if you don't
but but i think a major section of you
would agree with me on this so thank you
very much i'll see you again soon this
is it for today
you can hear me on spotify i have my
podcast there and all these audio files
of these videos are available there so
next time you're driving and you don't
have anything to listen to you can
probably listen to me okay then thank
you very much bye