- [Jimmy] The Bermuda Triangle
is one of the most
dangerous places on earth.
Over 100 ships and
planes have gone missing
with no explanation.
Me and the boys are going to spend
24 hours straight in the Bermuda Triangle.
Wish us luck.
(upbeat intense music)
Guys, we're in the ocean.
I want you all to make a will.
I want you all to take a camera
and let us know, if something
were to happen to you,
what would you want to
happen with your money?
- It's not a will if I don't
have a feather and bloom.
- All right, I'm going to
write my will in blues.
My last will and testament.
I don't own a lot of things,
so I'll probably just
leave my dog to my fam
and everything else to my family.
But my ostrich is a free man.
- All right, so my last
will and testament,
I'm going to leave the house,
our cars, our dogs, our cats-
- To me.
- And all of our money to my wife.
- All right guys, if I die,
mom, just take the car that Jimmy gave me
and my Xbox, keep that.
- For their wills, they
wanted quills and paper,
so I got them it.
Oh Hi.
- Did you actually get a-
- Here's the paper.
- [Tareq] There you have it.
Chris is giving everything to his wife
- [Chris] And a smiley face.
- [Viking] It says, my will,
give my boat to my dad.
Shelby can have everything,
except my web history.
- We're actually, currently,
in the Bermuda Triangle.
The boys aren't really doing too well.
We're all seasick beyond belief.
Oh, this water's killing me.
Starting now.
24 hours begins.
Are you guys okay?
- Does any part of me look okay right now?
- I'm going to go tell the
captain to take us anywhere
not here.
The water's too.
- [Tareq] Bye Chan.
- [Chris] Yeah, he's dead.
I want you to stand right here
and just look at this going up and down.
We're not being babies.
It's been requested that we find
a little bit calmer waters.
- Give me 10 minutes.
It's going to be like a swimming pool.
(upbeat music)
- We came to a little bit calmer waters.
As you can see the waves aren't as big.
So, are you fine?
- I'm doing better.
- We're probably going
to go back out there.
- That's not good. I threw up 11 times.
Hey Jimmy, can I get the in the water?
- We're literally in the Bermuda Triangle.
Chris, this is the Bermuda Triangle
- [Viking] He's going in.
- [Jimmy] Hole in one.
- [Viking] Why not?
- What could possibly go wrong?
- I'm about to jump off a yacht.
I love you Jimmy. If I don't make it.
(upbeat music)
- [Tareq] We got him.
- [Jimmy] Dude, that's crazy!
(upbeat music)
- [Tareq] Marcus, you going?
- Bruh.
(laughing)
No.
- All right, Marc.
- All right Marc, go.
- How's the water feel dude?
- Feels pretty good.
(laughing)
- Are you ready to have fun dude?
(upbeat music)
(yelling)
Wait guys.
- [Tareq] Dude, where's Chandler?
- I swear he was there the whole time.
- [Tareq] Yo, he lost Chandler.
- I'm going to go find him.
- I'm out.
slowly.
- [Viking] We got him!
- [Chris] I got him by the toe!
- [Tareq] Bring Chandler over here.
- Chandler, buddy.
- [Tareq] Chandler. Are you okay?
- [Jimmy] Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- All right guys, Last one
to fall off win's $2,000.
- [Tareq] Oh!
(yelling)
(laughing)
- I'm still on!
- Last off.
- [Tareq] It's off.
- [Jimmy] Chandler won!
(cheering)
(upbeat music)
We are doing a cool trick competition,
whoever jumps off the yacht
with the coolest trick,
wins two grand.
Chandler.
Go for it.
- [All Together] Chandler!
- [Jimmy] Okay. All alright.
Front flip! All right, all right.
- [Tareq] All right Marc.
- Woo!
- [Tareq] Oh my God, that looked painful.
(upbeat music)
- [Jimmy] Another front flip!
Now that everyone is dried off,
we will crown the winners
of the trick competition.
Marcus, you just did a pencil dive.
- I deserve to win.
That was the-
(buzzer buzzing)
- You just did a cannon.
- No, I belly flopped.
- You better not. I did
the best front flip.
- And so did Chris.
- No, his was worse and I went first.
I went first!
- We all know that you never win.
- Oh?
- What was your-
- I did-
- Whoa.
(buzzer buzzing)
- [Chris] I wish I'd had pushed you in!
- We have to keep Chandler's brand alive.
We have to. It's for-
- I knew it!
(buzzer buzzing)
- I did it.
- Chandler's the winner.
(cheering)
All right. All right.
- Oh my.
(laughing)
- All right, come on,
children, let's go eat.
- [Tareq] So what happened?
- The big time lives
camera fell into the water.
So we're going to try and rescue it.
- [Tareq] Please rescue it.
- We're trying.
- [Tareq] Shine a light on
Chris, shine a light on Chris.
Do you see anything?
Don't lose Viking. Don't lose Viking.
(sad music)
- How do you liking the
Bermuda Triangle so far?
- It's pretty dangerous to cameras.
- The only thing that's
gotten hurt so far,
in the Bermuda Triangle, is
literally our $7,000 camera.
- I stubbed my toe.
- Honestly, I'm kind of enjoying it.
Maybe it's 'cause we're on a yacht
but it doesn't seem that bad.
- The reason why all those sailors
and Amelia Earhart all went missing,
'cause it's so nice here.
Why would you leave?
- Maybe the reason why
this place is so dangerous
is because they don't have trees.
Teamtrees.org or donate below the video.
We're almost at 20 million.
Now that all of you guys are fed,
it's time for the next challenge.
As you know, things in
the Bermuda Triangle
typically go missing.
So let's play hide and seek.
- You should count the 10,000,
'cause you've already done it.
- [Jimmy] I'm going to go count to 500.
You guys hide. whoever
I find last gets $2,000.
- Ooh. Okay.
- So I'm in my room and I'm
going to begin counting.
One, two, three, four.
- [Tareq] Oh my God, can you fit?
- There's no way I'm fitting.
- [Tareq] No dude. You can, you can.
- [Tareq] You have to believe in-
- Here, hold this.
I can't get out and it hurts
I know you can't see, but
I'm on the top of the boat.
He'll never see me.
- 40, 41, 42.
- Holy crap, it's hot in here.
As you can see, I'm in like a,
I'm underneath something.
- 301, 302, 303.
- [Viking] And I'm going
to try and hide over here.
(upbeat music)
They'll never notice me right here.
- 500. Let's do this.
Someone has to be here.
I hear movement.
I hope no one's hiding in the water.
We'll keep exploring.
I see you!
- [Chris] I couldn't find anywhere else.
All of my spots didn't work.
I want another try.
- Let's check the rooms.
This door's cracked and I
bet you they left it cracked,
So I wouldn't think someones in here.
Making sure I'm checking
every nook and cranny.
- Cranny!
(laughing)
The look on your face was priceless.
- I thought I had someone.
- [Chris] You said I could
not mess with other people.
You didn't say I could not sword you.
Oh, you got to be quicker.
- I think there's someone in here.
Hey.
- No!
- We know someone's in the closet.
How we mess with them?
- We need Febreze and just
start spraying Febreze.
I know where some is.
- We're going to Febreze bomb
whoever's in the bathroom.
- [Chris] Did you check in here?
- [Jimmy] Yep, we did.
- [Jimmy] Wait. I can't see anyone.
- [Chris] He's known you've been in there
from the beginning.
- Can I come out now?
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
Chandler won. We haven't found him yet.
- [Tareq] Chandler is the
only one we haven't found yet.
- I know where he is.
(upbeat music)
- Did they forget about me?
Probably.
I'm going to get the freak out of here,
I don't care anymore.
Couldn't breathe in there.
- [Jimmy] Hey, there you are.
Really, all I had to do was come up here
(cheering)
- Guys, I just heard something.
I got to find somebody who-
what the freak was that?
Hello? Jake, Jake, Jake.
What?
Marcus? Oh no.
- We're hiding from Chandler.
We woke him up and then hid.
- There's literally no one in here.
Where is everyone?
- We are now in his room.
- Guys? This isn't funny.
Yo, this is too, I'm not
ever doing this again.
Just going to go back to my room, since.
What the heck?
- [Jimmy] Surprise!
- [All Together] Surprise!
Happy birthday! Yay!
(clapping)
- [Chris] Hey buddy.
- You guys are sharing this room.
- Oh yeah, aren't you glad you found us?
- I'm very glad, yes.
'Cause I was upstairs and I saw someone
but I think it was a crew member
and I was in my underwear
(laughing)
- [Jimmy] While the seasickness,
the camera falling in the ocean
and Chandler winning
three challenges in a row,
were all bizarre occurrences,
we still weren't convinced
it was the Bermuda Triangle.
But later that night, we
managed to get some footage
of some disturbing stuff.
- Hey Chandler.
Chandler, did you hear that?
I think I heard something.
That's okay.
Got my trusty sword.
I'm going to sleep here with my sword.
- [Tareq] Conner, can you see?
- [Conner] No.
- [Tareq] Open the door,
just go after them.
- [Conner] Okay.
- [Chris] Ah, a ghost!
Why are you in here?
Call off your, whatever this is.
- [Conner] Ow dude. You're
using the sheet that doesn't-
(drumming)
- [Tareq] Do you guys want
to join in on our raid?
- [Chris] Yeah, sure. I'll raid.
It's a ghost, ah!
- Conny, that was all- oh!
- [Conner] Ooh, it's a ghost.
(laughing)
- Reveal yourself!
Oh, it was Conner.
- [Tareq] Yeah, you just tackled his head.
Hey guys, good night.
All right. Hey guys.
Marcus, good night.
Okay.
- That's not my bedroom.
- [Tareq] Oh, that's not your bedroom?
- [Viking] Excuse me. Excuse me.
This is my bed room.
- [Tareq] That's your bedroom?
- Yep. All right, well, good night.
(upbeat music)
- All right, Jake (indistinct),
it's currently 7:00 AM.
Chris, did we survive
the Bermuda Triangle?
- [Chris] I barely survived last night.
- It's 'cause you stayed up
all night playing video games.
Blade, why don't you have pants on?
- I was woken, in my awoken sleep.
- Wrapping a towel around your
waist is easier than pants?
- [Chris] It's a blanket, not a towel.
- I was told I was needed.
- Just going to go over here.
(upbeat music)
- We're heading back. It's a little wavy.
- I'm going to throw up.
- I feel like I'm going to throw up.
You want me to throw up on camera?
- [Tareq] Not again.
- We made it.
- Never going on a yacht again,
not that I can afford it.
- I got sick a lot.
- I almost threw up.
- It turns out the only thing dangerous
about the Bermuda Triangle
is motion sickness
and terrible tripods.
- [Man Singing] Mr. Beast 6,000. Oh, oh.
Mr. Beast 6,000, yeah, you know his name.
He changed it once or twice,
but I think it's here to stay.
(explosion exploding)