O God!
One Million  Subscribers
Global Collab
Hello Friends, I'm Gaurav welcoming you all
to a fresh new video of Technical Guruji
Here's just a few things from you.
All you have to do is congratulate
Thank You Congratulation is the love and support of all of you
Today we have implemented 1 Million subscribers
And I have full confidence that the same
And keep growing faster
And the tech knowledge that we share will continue to share
So let's start
How are you guys Armano Ferreira is here
Congratulations on getting 1 Million subscribers
This is a huge achievement!
Hey brother !, I heard your 1 million subscribers, many congratulations!
But do not touch me, okay!
Hello Gaurav, Best wishes for One Million subscribers
Feeling great
And this is the milestone you have
Removed early enough, your channel ran like a rocket
Good luck and pride you will take a big party
When we will meet now in Jaipur and Pune
Stay asleep
What is the friend going on? It's its ravishing zoomer,
This is a great achievement for my friend Gaurav
That to the technical guruji channel
Delivered 1 million subscribers.
I hope I am fine
But congratulations, this is a huge achievement
Hardest congratulations for one million
Keep doing the work and hard work, so the man 1 million is not 10 million away at all
Congratulations again and again!
I congratulate the success of pride in YouTube
Best wishes for further and what you do I like a lot
And all go, subscribe to him
How many subscribers?
One Million
How many?
One Million!
One Million
I am fine
Good guruji way i do not
Want a Pink Color Laptop
Tell me which one?
What's going on guys, I'm Dom
And I want to congratulate the teacher Guruji
To reach the goal of that big One Million subscriber
Keep your good work the same way
You have great content
And obviously you have earned your place in One Million Club
And if you want to meet me then you can find me at youtube.com
Very much congratulations
Hello friends, Amit, from PhoneRadar
And today I want to congratulate Gaurav, ie, Technical Guruji
Because for a very big milestone
This channel has earned ten million YouTube subscribers today
And this is a huge achievement
This is the largest YouTube channel in India
He is also above the technology for the people of Hindi language.
I give credit to not only to glory
But those ten million people, who have brought this channel to this point
And I hope that you will be connected with us through this channel
Technical Guruji Ram and Ram first and many congratulations
You have one million subscribers
The rest is our little question. We have this thumb. We are thinking, give it to you like
Eklavya gave Dronacharya and tell us this
How do we play a touch phone without a thumb?
Yes, let's tell this thing un Boxing
Un-boxed of this question
Congratulations Technical Guruji on achieving this huge achievement
I wish you all the best and many more subscribers
Whom you can give your technical knowledge
I'll give you a loving full punch
Technical Guruji To Complete A Million Subscriber Too Many Congratulations
Keep moving forward and continue to do the same.
One Million Subscriber? Gaurav This is not a small issue
I went to the most crowded city of Barcelona, ​​who had joined me
Maybe 200 people here ... or 300
But not 1 million people
Anyway from MrMobile and in the Mobile Congress
tech lover who appreciate the best tech videos
Congratulations pride and we will be waiting to reach 10 million
"stay mobile" friends
There is nothing impossible in this world
We can do everything we can think of
And it has done something like Gaurav Chaudhary i.e. your and our technical guru
No one thought
Today, what he has said in a million of YouTube's spoken language, in Hindi, 10 million YouTube subscribers have been completed.
So from the side of Mr. Sharma and on behalf of me, very much congratulating you
Best wishes and keep on moving forward
Take our Hindi language and Indians forward
From the technical knowledge that he would continue to give technical knowledge and continue to prosper
Very good luck from us
Hello friends! I'm Max Lee. From HighOnAndroid.com
I want to congratulate pride for reaching one million
Re: Great Congratulations Brother Big Thumbsup
Visit SUPERSAF on Technical Guruji
Gaurav Bhai, I am very happy to be very happy to come to your channel
And this is my prayer that soon comes up to the TWO Million Subscriber
For the Hindi audience, I will put a video,
I know we share the same audience
If someone is looking at a SUPERSAF philosophy, then he too has a big scream from me
I will meet you next time with SAF, SUPERSAF TV
♪ Congratulations
And celebrations ♪
♪ I want the world to know
I'm happy as can be
♪ Congratulations
And celebrations ♪
♪ On heading One Million Subscriber ♪
Hello friends my name is nick
Congratulations to talk about 10 Million Next Time to Touch One Million Subscriber
Keep liking videos like this
As long as I know, as long as I know, as long as I know ...
Do not forget to share videos
Till Life exists, till life exists, till life exists
Do not forget subscribing to channels
As long as I know, as long as I know, there is life
Jai Hind, Vande Mataram