- Have you ever wondered
how paper is made?
- No.
- Goldfish, the foods you eat?
- Okay, yeah.
- Perfect, 'cause we're gonna
answer all that in this video.
How water bottles are made.
- That doesn't it look
like a water bottle?
- Oh, all right.
You just squeeze it with
metal and then it inflates.
They all probably come like that,
so that way they can have different shapes
for different bottles.
And they inflate it to
the bottle they want.
So that way you can buy a ton of them,
and make different
bottles in the factories.
- Oh, really, that
actually does make sense.
- And that is all just
speculation from me,
that could be totally
false, but who cares?
This is our channel.
- How to make ice cream sandwiches.
- Do you like ice cream sandwiches?
- Literally who doesn't?
- The ice cream could be better,
if they used higher quality
ice cream in the middle,
it'd be better.
- Just buy high quality
ice cream sandwiches,
stop buying the 50 cent ones.
- I go to Walmart, okay?
They don't got high quality
ice cream sandwiches,
it's great value or nothing.
- Yo, someone make a high quality version
of ice cream sandwiches.
- Who's one of the big
ice cream companies?
- Do you think I just search
ice cream companies in my free time?
- Bro, you don't be searching
into ice cream lure bro?
- No.
- How to make the Lego mini figures.
Oh this how you get make the Lego guys
that get stuck in your
nose when you're little.
Just me?
I got one of those heads stuck in my nose,
and I had to go to the
doctor to get it taken out.
I really hope Tucker isn't like me,
'cause I was just very problematic
for a child.
- Weirdo.
How instant ramen are made.
This ramen factory runs 24 hours a day.
Oh, is that spicy ramen?
- Ooh, I love the spicy ramen.
- Bro, imagine just grabbing that,
and just being able to eat
off that conveyor belt.
- Just hot off the press.
Have you ever eat ramen uncooked?
- No.
- You haven't ever just
sprinkled the stuff on it,
and then just eat it?
- No.
- Okay, I guess...
All right, I grew up poor, okay?
- I didn't even know that was possible.
- You just sprinkle the season and on it
and then you eat it.
- It probably tastes like brick dust.
- It's kind of crunchy
but it's not that bad.
- How to build a yacht.
Jeffrey Bezos and Elon
Musk if you're watching,
here you go.
This is for the one billionaire
that watches our videos.
The rest of you that aren't
that one billionaire,
don't worry about it.
Even if I had $20,000,000
to spend on a boat
I don't think I would.
- This is why I got a Hundo.
- Nah, yachts aren't as much as you think.
- Jeffrey Bezos spent 500 million on it.
- Yeah, Jeffrey Bezos also owns the world.
He owns a couple of like oil tycoon.
- Oh, a couple of oil tycoon.
Yeah, you're right,
that's probably like a 15 million boat.
Now we're gonna react to
how play buttons are made.
- You would know you have 30 of them.
- Actually we have 35 now.
- YouTube pays this company to do this.
- Bro, YouTube makes
billions upon billions
of dollars a day,
do you think they care to make this?
- Yeah that's true.
- Do you think they care
about a couple of grand?
How to move a spaceship.
- This is over the
course of multiple hours.
- I thought you were about
to say multiple days,
I was like bro, it's
been dark the whole time.
- Oh well look at that,
now it's a course of a day
because now it's completely daytime.
Even though I didn't say
that, I was still right.
Why didn't they just build it there?
- Because there's a difference between
a manufacturing plant and a launched pad?
- What a bunch of idiots,
why didn't they just build it there
so they didn't have to move it?
- Yo honestly, don't
you want a new iPhone?
Just build it in your house.
- Look at it, it's like, "Ah."
Hey, that's going to space.
- It went to space.
- Good for it.
- All right, so this is how
they make speed limit sign.
- Nice.
- Wait, have you ever seen
a 69 speed limit sign?
- No, this is a guy who
makes them and sells them,
I've seen him on TikTok before.
- Oh that's lame.
I wanna know how the
government literally makes
millions upon millions
of sign across America.
- Jimmy, when I worked IT,
I actually had to work on the
computer that makes the sign
and it is actually just like this.
This guy just bought or has
one, but that's so cool,
he can make them say
whatever he wants Jimmy.
And they're like legit signs too.
- So I don't have to keep stealing them?
- Jimmy, don't say that, that's a felony,
I found that out the hard way.
- How Goldfish arm made.
- What the freak is that?
Oh that's cheese, oh my
god, it's so much cheese.
- Oh wait, really?
- Yeah, I forgot Goldfish
are just cheese bread.
- Oh my gosh.
Wait, those don't look like goldfish,
those look like gold catfish.
- They look like gold flats.
- They look like gold wide fish.
Wait, that's it?
You just take cheese,
and cut it, and burn it.
- I need to know more, how
deep does this hole go?
- We should start a goldfish plant,
they don't look how hard to make.
Let's just do Jimmy fish,
and it's just like Goldfish
just slightly crispier.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- How pencils are made.
- Tell you what, there wasn't enough made
in middle school when I was a kid.
And you gotta ask the girl
beside you to borrow her pencil,
and she's like, "No,
I gave you a pencil last time
and you didn't give back."
It's like I'ma need a pencil.
- I think they just didn't like you,
I'm just gonna come out and say it.
- Jennifer, you know who you are,
I failed that test.
Not because of the pencil,
because I'm not very smart.
- How to make custom rug.
- Oh, I love these on TikTok.
- I'm gonna make a Mr. Beast burger rug.
- Oh, a Mr. Beast burger rug.
- Why don't we have it
under our feet right now?
- It looks ugly right now, but the blue--
- It does look ugly.
- It doesn't.
- You're one of those people that
lie to make people feel good.
- No, I'm one of the people
that can see the diamond in the rough man.
Look how fluffy it looks.
It looks like big bird.
- You think that looks good?
- I don't think it looks good as a rug.
- See, unlike him--
- But it looks good to rub my face across.
- Unlike him I won't lie to you,
it looks ugly so far.
We'll keep going though.
- This is so much better,
but we have more to go.
- Oh, see now it looks better.
Oh wow, that's pretty cool.
And by the way, if you're
watching this and hungry
go order our beast burger.
Just literally download our app,
or go on Uber Eats, Grubhub,
or on all your favorite delivery apps.
Order one right now, it takes amazing.
How to build a wooden rollercoaster.
And if any of these guys here mess up,
you will die.
- The first thing I'm noticing
is a surprising lack of power tools,
and a lot of really old hammers
that are barely held together.
I don't know about this one man,
are you trust in your life with that?
- Oh, 100s or 1000s of
people probably did.
- I don't like wooden rollercoasters,
what's the point?
You get the crap beat out of you,
and they're so short,
and they don't even really go that high.
- Yeah, and on top of that,
this thing could light on fire so easily.
- And burn down instantly.
They're like "Yay, we have
concussions and neck trauma now.
Woo, wooden rollercoasters."
- That happens on every rollercoaster.
- No.
- Time out.
If you haven't already subscribed
hit the subscribe button right now.
We're gonna be giving
$1,000 to a random person
that subscribes in the next seven days.
So if you haven't already
hit the subscribe button
I'll love you.
And un-timeout.
- Bew.
- How to make Oreos.
Okay, this has to be good.
- You start with poo poo.
- But wait, that's brown
And Oreos are black.
- Well it's probably when
you bake 'em they turn--
- Whoa, when you bake
your poop it turns black?
- Probably.
- Here's what they should do,
they should just take
this and just break it
'cause we just want the
white stuff in the middle.
I think I speak for everyone.
Why don't they do an Oreo where
it's the white stuff is on the outside,
and then there's one
little thin black cookie--
- In the middle?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that would be good.
- What if they came out with a new Oreo,
and it's called just the white stuff.
- Can I just buy white stuff cream?
- Yeah, it's not even packaged,
it's just squirted into a Ziploc bag.
- And they need to call
it the white stuff.
- The white stuff.
- Yeah, see, no, those aren't good,
look at that.
The chocolate to the
white ratio is so off.
- Not on this one though,
this one's thick.
- Yeah, that one is fine.
But like all these other
ones I don't like my Oreos
when there's not much white stuff in them.
- This whole conversation
becomes irrelevant
when you say vanilla Oreos,
because vanilla Oreos are incredible.
- I still would rather eat a vanilla Oreo
without the top than with the top.
- We don't have to agree on everything.
- But we can agree it's
better than chocolate.
- Yes, very good.
I'm glad we discussed this,
we got to this conclusion.
- I wiped my butt with
this hand this morning.
- I also wiped my butt with this hand.
- Perfect .
- Newmans, Newman O's.
This aren't Oreos.
- Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Who the heck is Newman?
- Oreo's corporate office,
y'all need to sue Newman,
yo, he put his name on
the package, sue him.
Making of a stream room.
Is this gonna be Ninja's?
- This better not be Ninja.
- Wait, is it?
Wait, did I call it?
Oh my God, I called it.
Why does everyone think
of Ninja's stream room
when they think of one.
- Other people have stream rooms.
- Welcome to Ninja dojo.
- To the Ninja dojo.
Why doesn't Carl have a cool stream room?
- Yeah, some company should
make Karl a cool stream room.
- From basketball to hockey arena,
you pick up all the basketball court.
Love how they're just Lego blocks.
Wait, do they just lay down ice?
- Yeah, it's just like Lego blocks of ice.
I never knew that, that's so cool.
Then they also get the Zamboni out,
the Zamboni polishes it
and merges them together.
And I like saying Zamboni.
- Zamboni.
- Zambonith.
How to move an entire tree.
Oh gosh.
- Whoa.
- Wait, wait, wait,
they make machines that
can just eat trees?
- No, those are gonna scoop the dirt out,
and get all the roots
for the tree and move it.
This is so cool.
- We live in a day and age
where we can move trees.
How to make paper.
- Wait, this is wood.
- If you're a tree watching
this video close your eyes.
- Right now.
- Close your eyes.
I will say turtle when you can open them.
Now that all the trees are gone.
- You tumble wood and then it becomes
this sheet by the
tumbling power obviously.
And then you spin it
for a really long time,
and then it becomes these tubes.
Then these tubes like to
rub up against each other,
and what is going on?
- No idea.
All right.
And boom
Changed color.
- And boom, paper.
- And now it's paper.
- Giant paper, and this is what giants use
to print receipts at CVS.
- No, this is what giants
to wipe their butt.
- It looks like receipt
paper, not toilet paper.
- You're telling me that's
not giant toilet paper?
- Okay.
- Checkmate.
- Yeah, you got me there.
- Adidas making the best running shoes.
- Are they these?
Because these are pretty fun to run it.
- That looks like a sack that
back in biblical times
they used to carry coins,
and they just put some foam around it.
Does it not?
- What did I do to get
this kind of treatment man?
- You ain't even got shoes on.
- Yeah, no shoe gang.
- Get those concrete grippers outta here.
- I need an explanation.
- Your toes they be gripping concrete
'cause they look like fingers.
- I didn't know shoes were handmade.
- I figured robots did it,
I figured robots did everything.
- Yeah, I'm pretty confident
everything I see in life now
is made by a robot.
- I just assumed that
had already happened,
I don't know anymore.
- Yeah, all right, well
that's interesting,
Nike shoes are made by people.
- Those are Adidas, you idiot.
- What's the difference?
Five years from now when we're
negotiating a sponsorship,
they're gonna be like "You said
there's no difference between us."
- And you're like, to be fair
they are both literally shoes.
- How it's made, smallest car.
- Hey, this is an actual
"How It's Made" clip,
I used to watch this show at 2:00 a.m.
while I ate cheese out of the fridge.
- While you ate cheese outta the fridge?
You should have baked it,
could of had Goldfish?
- You just take one piece of craft single
and fold it in half and then eat.
It tastes better if you fold in half.
- Agreed.
- A little car.
- Yeah, I bet that's
really fuel efficient.
How to make McDonald's fries.
I'm gonna take notes for Beast Burger.
- The glossiest potatoes,
and then send them
through a freaking cannon
into a wire screen.
- Shoot them through a cannon.
- It destroys them at a
million miles per hour.
And then you drop 'em in oil
and put salt all over 'em,
and now they're taking a bath,
they're all hanging out in a pool.
You send them on a conveyor belt,
and then they put 'em in packaging
and then they throw 'em in grease again.
- Got it, Beast Burger has churros now,
now I need to go call
the Beast Burger team.
Thank you for watching.
Subscribe if you wanna win money,
- Hopefully we won't get sued, bye.