You are Sundar, the sweets maker.
You are not Shabari,
whose half-eaten berries were
eaten by Lord Ram.
And even if Lord Ram comes here,
he will not eat these 'laddus.'
Why? Have I made a mistake?
Mistake? How did you
forget to add almonds,
in the 'laddus' that are going to
be offered to Lord Ram?
She hasn't even
tasted the 'laddus' yet.
How does she know that
there are no almonds in them?
From experience.
Stop whispering to each other.
As you already know,
that my ears, nose and eyes
are sharper than your brains.
I've crossed 75 years.
But I don't have any sickness, not
even in the nail of my last toe.
I don't have any issues with BP,
Cholesterol or Sugar.
My eyesight is as sharp as an eagle
and speed as fast as a cheetah.
And my clasp is so strong that
you won't be able to free yourself.
Janki Maa, only 10 minutes are
left in offering the sweets to God.
How will I prepare a new batch
of 'laddus' in 10 minutes?
You won't be able to make them.
I will make them.
I'll call Jyoti to help...
These old bones
are still strong enough
to prepare a feast for 100 people.
Grandma, your time starts now.
[harmonium playing]
Grandma.
[song playing]
"Ram will come"
There's still one minute left.
Starting today,
we will not get sweets for
Lord Ram, from your shop.
Janki Maa, please
give me one chance.
This is the first time
I've made a mistake.
The punishment has been given
to ensure that your
first mistake is the last.
If forgiveness is given,
making mistakes becomes a habit.
'Three things in Ujjain have
not changed in all these years.'
'The cry of devotion
for Lord Mahakal.'
'Janki Maa's character.'
'And the identity of this
house with the henna plant'
'That's me, Mehendi.'
'There was a time'
'when all the relationships
were adorned with my fragrance.'
'Every day was like
the festival of spring.'
'But then, it was shadowed
by the autumn season.'
'After many years, I'm
going on a new journey.'
'From Ujjain that sits on
the banks of River Shipra'
'to Mumbai, that dwells
by the ocean side.'
'I hope to bring back
colour into the lost relationships.'
'I don't know why,
but my heart says, '
'this girl will make
my hopes come true.'
'Yes, this girl.'
'The one who adorns her
hands with the colour of her love.'
Make sure to apply it well, Neha.
This 'mehendi' has the name
of my son, Manas, written on it.
- The colour should be intense.
- Yes.
[vocalisation]
Mauli, why are you crying?
[mellow music]
You've lived in this house
since you were a child.
And you have to live here
even after you get married.
Have you not heard
about tears of happiness?
[vocalisation]
After Mom and Dad passed away,
I had become an orphan.
When I was a child, I craved
for someone,
whom I could call as Dad,
whom I could call Mom.
I wanted to have my own family.
When we don't have certain
relationships in our fate,
we look for them all our life, Neha.
Today...
Today, I'm being
blessed with everything.
[sighing deeply]
That is why I'm very happy.
Don't shed so many
tears of happiness,
that it dulls the colour
of your 'mehendi.'
[shehnai playing]
Congratulations, Dr. Manoj.
You've found the
perfect wife for Manas.
Thank you.
[mellow music]
[camera shutter clicking]
Manas. Come!
Get your pictures clicked. Everyone
should know you're getting married.
Just two minutes, Mom.
[giggling]
If you had told me this yesterday,
before I got married...
It wouldn't have
been so tough for me.
It's tough. But I have to do it.
I will make everything
right. Trust me.
[vocalisation]
Mauli, what happened?
You're looking so tense
on your wedding day.
It's not written on your
prescription or my wedding card,
that you can forget
to take your medicines
on my wedding day.
You ask patients in the hospital
every day about their medicines.
But you always forget to take
your medicines.
Here you go.
You're trying to be my
doctor, aren't you?
No. I'm exercising
my right as a daughter.
Honestly, Mauli, whatever
you have done for me till today,
even my own daughter
would not have done so much.
What, Uncle? Is this
your love and friendship?
You're making me feel
like an outsider now.
Do you consider me as your own?
Then, don't call me Uncle.
Practice calling me Dad.
Yes, Dad.
[giggling]
[vocalisation]
Even if I used a surgical light,
let alone a lamp,
I would not find a
better partner for my son.
Go on, now.
One second. This is for you.
[flute playing]
'Did you see that?
Manoj recognised it immediately.'
'It brought back long
lost memories in his mind.'
'The most important memory was
when his sister got married.'
'The entire family, '
'had a lot of fond memories
of the wedding.'
What do you mean you
want to break this marriage?
Manas, are you playing a joke on me
or making a fool of me?
I thought everything between
Ashna and I was finished.
But it's not over.
That is why I'm
taking this decision.
Manas, we were the
ones who got married.
How can you take
the decision all alone?
Because I cannot continue
this marriage with you.
Ashna is back in my life.
And I love her.
I'm going to her
for a couple of days.
Then, I will plan what to do next.
[vocalisation]
[dramatic music]
Manas!
How can you be so selfish?
She's better than
you in every aspect.
She's a doctor, which
you could never become.
She's kind-hearted.
She's beautiful.
She was ready to marry you,
just because I asked her to.
Dad, I can never be
what Mauli is to you.
You wanted me to
become a doctor. I failed.
But Mauli became a doctor.
An outsider became closer to
your heart than your own son.
Manas, decisions made
in haste are usually wrong.
Please, Mauli. It's better
if you stay out of this.
You know that I did
not want to marry you.
- Dad forced me...
- No, Manas.
You were not forced.
You were asked about it.
And you had agreed.
Yes, I agree.
But Ashna is back in my life.
I will, naturally, go back to her.
Manas.
Manas, please think
with a calm mind.
- Please.
- Mom, at least you understand.
I cannot live with Mauli and torture
myself for the rest of my life.
There ends the matter.
Then let's finish this
once and for all, Manas.
You don't want anything
to do with Mauli, right?
I also don't want
anything to do with you.
There is no place
for him in this house.
Okay, fine. You can live with
your daughter in this happy family.
I'll fend for myself.
I've made a mistake
and I'm apologising for it.
But I cannot pay the price for
my mistake for the rest of my life.
[dramatic music]
Manas. Remember this.
Once you leave the house,
then it becomes
difficult to come back.
[vocalisation]
'Manoj, once someone
leaves the house'
'then it becomes
difficult to come back.'
What have you done, Manoj?
You forced my son to
leave his own house and go.
He was apologising.
You also made the same
mistake when you were young.
Manas. Please wait.
Manas, my child. Please wait.
Manas.
'Manoj, please wait.'
'Manoj, once someone
leaves the house'
'then it becomes
difficult to come back.'
'I beg of you, Manoj,
please don't leave the house.'
'Manoj, you are the
pride of this house.'
'Don't break the relationships
this way.'
'What are you doing, Manoj?
Please don't go.'
'You're being very stubborn.'
'I'm begging you.'
- 'Please don't go.
- You are the pride...'
[falling sound]
Dad.
[vocalisation]
Please bless us, Lord Ram.
[tense music]
- Dr Gupta, once the reports come,
let's decide on the treatment. - Yes.
[tense music]
[sobbing]
[mellow music]
Dad never gives up.
He will fight and win.
You are the one who
has to be brave, Mauli.
You were eight years old.
When your parents
died in an accident.
Manoj brought you home
and gave you a family.
He brought you up like his own.
Otherwise, you would
have remained an orphan.
He gave you a good education.
He made you a doctor.
Now it's your turn to
do something for Manoj.
You got married because
Manoj asked you to, right?
You've not lost anything.
You are like how you were before.
Manas left you on
your wedding night.
He has not even touched you.
So, please...
Don't make a big issue
that Manas has left you.
Because the more
fuel you add to this fire,
the longer it will take for
Manoj to recover.
[vocalisation]
Okay, Mom. Dad will
only see me smiling from now on.
Dad's reports are here.
- Mauli. - There is
a lot of damage to his heart.
We will have to operate.
[tense music]
Please don't worry.
I will not let anything
happen to Dad.
I have to fulfil my responsibility
as a daughter
and a doctor.
[mellow music]
[sombre music]
[lights turning on]
[door opening]
[sombre music]
[steady beeping]
'Mannu'
'Mannu. How did
you get hurt, Mannu?'
'If I don't make you run
around the clock tower'
'then I'll change my
name from Janki Maa.'
'Were you standing and counting
the legs on the cockroach?'
'How did Manoj get hurt despite
being with two elder brothers?'
'Janki Maa, you're
worrying unnecessarily.'
'It's a small bruise.
It will be fine.'
'I'm his Aunt, not his mother.'
'Is that why you're saying it?'
'Whatever may be the relationship,
I have a mother's heart, right?'
'Even if the child
gets a small bruise, '
'a mother's heart
breaks into pieces.'
'Don't worry, Manoj.'
'You'll be fine very soon.'
[vocalisation]
Dr. Mauli is very unlucky.
It's sad that her husband
left her on her wedding night.
Studying to become
a doctor is one thing.
And managing your
husband is another thing.
She was an orphan.
She had dreams of
having her own family.
Neither could she save her marriage,
nor could she have a family.
[tense music]
[mellow music]
[footsteps approaching]
[flute playing]
Dad.
- How is Dr. Manoj?
- He's better.
The reports are good and
he's getting discharged today.
That's good.
There is good news for you.
Please take it.
Ajar Hospital is the
biggest hospital in Mumbai.
Many doctors dream
about joining the doctor's panel
of this hospital.
[mellow music]
You've been chosen for this job.
[jubilant music]
I know, Dr. Mauli.
I know about what
happened in your personal life.
Will you be able to do it?
Because this job needs
200% commitment.
Yes, sir.
Whatever happened to me...
I thought I had lost my identity.
But...
This job means a lot to me.
At both personal and
professional levels.
Hmm.
Dr. Mauli.
Before you sign the papers,
I want you to think it through.
It's an exclusive contract.
Once you sign this, you
cannot work anywhere else.
Nor can you get out of it.
There is no looking back.
And for some reason,
if you change your mind
or if there is a breach of contract,
then you will have to
face legal consequences.
There can be a ban on
your medical practice.
You have four days to join the job.
Sign this only if you're
fully prepared for the job.
[pensive music]
Think about it.
I've thought about it, sir.
My dream is coming true.
I will not step back.
Welcome to Ajar's.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Dad, you've performed
so many surgeries.
Have you ever seen a patient smile,
while under anaesthesia?
I have seen it.
- Who is it?
- You.
When this leaf fell on you
you opened your eyes.
I know where this came from.
Where from?
From my childhood.
From my 'house of mehendi.'
'House of mehendi?'
Everyone who passed
by on our street, in Ujjain
they would automatically
bow down in front of
the idols of Ram and Sita.
It was not just a house,
but it was a temple.
Where we four brothers,
lived like Ram, Lakshman, Bharat
and Shatrughna.
The eldest among us is Ajay.
He is a devotee of Lord Hanuman.
He would lift a
mountain with one hand.
But he is extremely emotional.
The water would flow in the tap
only after water would
begin flowing from his eyes.
'Manisha...
You will get married and go away.'
[sobbing]
Next is Vijay.
He was my friend first
and then my brother.
[laughing]
'Hey. The last sweet is for Mannu.'
'Here you go, Mannu.'
'Why? Am I not the youngest?'
- 'Huh?
- Come on.'
'If Mannu wouldn't have come before
you, then how would you come?'
'Hmm.'
As dear as my brothers
Ajay and Vijay were to me,
even their wives
were very dear to me.
Swara and Tanvi.
[camera shutter clicking]
Among all of them
was our only sister, Manisha.
Just like a magician's
soul is inside a parrot,
all our souls resided
inside Manisha.
'Oh, wow. There is
no need for make-up.'
'There is such a wonderful
glow on her face.'
'Don't make these funny faces.
You're not yet married.'
'Then your husband
will not take you with him.'
We were so happy
when she got married.
A big family with
a lot of happiness.
Do you know who was the head
of the department of our family?
My father's elder brother.
He had just Rs. 10 in his pocket
when he first came to Ujjain.
He was courageous and hard-working.
And he purchased a big shop.
'Agarwal Saree Emporium.'
He used to love everyone a lot.
But I was his favourite child.
I don't know how he must be today.
Our Mannu.
Nanhe, come and have a look.
My dad is referred to as 'Nanhe.'
He never disobeyed
anything that my Uncle said.
No.
I will not do as you say.
I don't want to see any photos.
Don't see Manoj's photos.
His son is getting married.
You can see those
photos and be happy.
Hari, when we see the photos
of our family members on the phone,
then it does not bring happiness.
It breaks our hearts.
Nanhe.
Why are you still holding on to
the bitter memories of the past?
My heart is not as
big as yours, Hari.
I won't be able to forget
how he cheated us.
He could have at least
thought about Janki Maa,
who looked after him,
after his mother passed away.
Janki Maa.
My Aunt.
There is no greater
medicine than her scolding.
She's the backbone of our house.
The entire household
runs on her shoulders.
The tea has turned into cold juice.
Please drink it. If you ask
me to heat it once again,
then I will heat it
and pour it over your phone.
[mellow music]
Dad, this letter.
Read what has been written.
'You must be worried'
'that everything was
scattered after you left.'
'But I'm happy to let you know'
'that nothing like that happened.'
'Everything worked out well.'
'The Earth, the Moon, the Sun, '
'all of these are
revolving as they were, '
'before you cheated us.'
'It did not make any difference.'
Read the rest, Mauli.
'Mini is getting married.'
'And we are having
a grand wedding.'
'I thought I should send you this
invitation on this joyous occasion.'
'Please don't think
that we are inviting you.'
'This is proof of the defeat'
'of your stubbornness
and arrogance.'
'Akshay, a stranger.'
Are you looking for something?
I sent Mini's wedding invitation
to Mumbai by courier.
Its receipt has fallen somewhere.
I'm not finding it at all.
[suspenseful music]
Oh, God. What if Janki Maa finds it?
I found it.
[dramatic music]
[metal clanking]
Nothing stays hidden
from Janki's eyes.
Akshay, Janki Maa, Dad
are all bitter because
of my mistake.
[flute playing]
You are suffering
the results of my deeds.
No, Dad. Please don't
blame yourself.
No, Mauli.
As long as I don't
rectify my mistakes,
I won't be able to
improve your life.
I must go back to my
'House of mehendi.'
I will fall at Janki Maa's feet
and ask for forgiveness.
I don't have the courage
to go alone.
Will you come along with me?
'This is not an easy
decision for Mauli to make.'
'This job is not just
helping Mauli balance her life, '
'but it is also her dream.'
'But on the other hand'
'Manoj's purpose in life
is to go to Ujjain, '
'and ask for forgiveness
from his family.'
'What will Mauli choose between her
Dad like Manoj's purpose in life'
'and her dream job?'