By swear of my kids.
Spare my life and l'll
tell you the truth.
He's from our village. Chief,
I don't believe my eyes..
..that an ordinary teacher is
provoking villagers against you.
He's provoking them
for not paying tax.
He's also abusing you.
He has abused his fate.
Now he won't remain
alive to abuse anymore.
I'll personally go to the
village to listen to his lecture.
Chief, he's that traitor
teacher who provokes villagers.
I don't provoke but awaken them.
I challenge their conscience,
and their maleness.
I tell them to wake up..
..and avenge dacoit Mangal
Singh for his tyranny.
You speak good.
But you've forgotten..
..that you're grown up eating
food grown on my land and learned.
Its government land
and not yours.
Which government
you're talking about?
I'm the government here.
Everybody knows that..
..it's my estate since
the time of British.
My ancestors were
kings. I was born a king.
And l'll always remain a king.
Ego always gets crushed,
Nlangal Singh.
Recall Ravan
(mythological character).
And don't forget that Ram
(mythological character)..
"takes birth for every Ravan.
Villagers, did you
listen to him?
Ramchandra has
born in your village.
Every year, in the festival of
Dussera, you must have seen..
..Ravan's effigy burnt
with Ram's arrow?
But today..
..you'd see one more drama.
Tie him!
Good!
Very good!
Hello, inspector!
-Inspector Surendra Pal Singh.
I'm second lieutenant Deepak.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm originally from this
village. l'm here on leave.
It's good that police once
again camped for these villagers.
That's right..
..but villagers are more scared
of police than the dacoits.
Instead of helping us they
think we're their enemies.
Inspector, poverty
has made them weak.
I beg your apology
on behalf of them.
No, it's okay.
-l'll try to convince them.
And now if the
dacoits would attack..
..we too will fight
along with you.
Thank you very much, Mr. Deepak.
Police needs co-operation
from the brave people like you.
And if you need anything else..
..you can ask for
it without hesitation.
Anything like food or water.
Mister, we could hardly
obtain water from your village.
I'll arrange for your food now.
Whatever it is, Lala.
Police's entry in this
village isn't good.
Because now the dacoits will
definitely come to the village.
Deepak, my child?!
Deepu!
-Mom!
I was waiting for
you since morning.
Mom, you can shower
your love later.
I'm very hungry.
I didn't eat since morning.
I'm starving now.
I know you can't starve
for a longer period.
C'mon, the food is ready. Come!
Mom, I want lots of food today.
I know how much you eat.
-Mom, l'm not alone.
There are many with me.
-Who else are there?
For the police officers,
on duty outside the village.
No, child. Don't commit
this mistake.
Otherwise, villagers
will go against us.
Dacoits attack on us because
of these police officers.
But, they used to
attack us even before.
Why don't you understand?
Mom, police is here to
help us. For our safety.
They're guarding our
village day and night..
..do they have any
enmity with the dacoits?
Dacoits don't rob them.
Mom, think about it. If
your son is starving..
..for saving a village
from dacoits..
..and if the villagers
won't even offer him water..
..how would you feel?
How hurt you'd be?
You're right, son.
I'll cook for them now.
Food is really nice.
Thank you very much.
Will you thank me?
You're like my Deepu.
Whenever you need anything,
remember mother's house.
Surendra, l'll call
a jury meeting today.
I hope everything would be fine.
-Okay.
Okay, aunt!
-May God give you success!
Now, l've got
mother's blessings too.
Now, if dacoit Mangal Singh
would dare attack this village..
Take the position.
Deepu!
Take this!
No, Deepu!
-Mom, don't cry, mom.
So what if l'd die? See..
there are many officers..
..who martyred for this village.
-No!
No, Deepu!
-There are nobody
to shed tears for them.
You too don't cry, mom!
Mom, don't cry. Mom..
No! Deepu!
Vijay!
Sir, how long this
will continue?
How long our officers fall
prey to their oppressiveness?
How long we'd lose our officers
for dacoit Mangal Singh?
Such a powelful department..
..won't ever be able to
finish off few dacoits?
It'll, Vijay.
But the day a brave
police officer..
..will take charge of that area..
..in a complete sensible
manner and with enthusiasm.
Sir, don't you think
l'm capable for it?
Vijay..
..your distinctive service
record speaks your capabilities.
And l'm proud..
..that you showed eagerness
for this dangerous duty.
Mr. Chowhan!
-Yes, sir.
From the head quarter get Vijay's
transfer order issued today.
Alright, sir.
Now, Mr. Vijay will be
the in-charge..
..of Fatehgarh range.
-Thank you, sir.
No mom is like mine.
No dad is like mine.
You're a darling son
of mummy and daddy.
You're an apple of their eyes.
You're a darling son
of mummy and daddy.
You're an apple of their eyes.
Munna is nice. He's so nice.
There's only one bad
thing about, daddy.
He meets only on Sundays.
He's too busy.
He can't meet us daily.
There's only one bad
thing about, daddy.
He meets only on Sundays.
He's too busy.
He can't meet us daily.
We're not far. Now,
we'll go to such a place..
..where you'll meet
your daddy daily.
Then the life would be fun.
You're a darling son
of mummy and daddy.
You're an apple of their eyes.
Munna is nice. He's so nice.
Mummy is nice and
Daddy too is nice.
May you obtain your goal!
No dreams would
remain unfulfilled!
Dreams we've seen together,
May all our dreams be
fulfilled.
May you obtain your goal!
No dreams would
remain unfulfilled!
Dreams we've seen together,
May all our dreams be fulfilled.
Now we won't separate.
We'll live and die together.
Now we'd never separate.
No mom is like mine.
-Really?
No dad is like mine.
Mummy is nice and
Daddy too is nice.
Munna is nice. He's so nice.
You're a darling son
of mummy and daddy.
You're an apple of their eyes.
Munna is nice. He's so nice.
Mummy is nice. She's so nice.
Salute, sir!
-Okay!
What's the matter, Mr. Surendra.
Village seems empty.
Sir, you know that villagers
don't co-operate us.
They think we can't
protect them from dacoits.
Why?
- Because the earlier...
place was very insecure.
I think this place in the middle
of the village would be safe.
Okay! Build the tent.
Ramsingh! Bring the material here.
-Yes, sir.
Sister-in-law, where's Munna?
-He was here.
Munna?!
Munna!
Where has he gone? Munna!
-Munna!
Inspector!
Hey! No, smartness!
-Daddy!
Have a look around
yourself, inspector.
Did you see, inspector?
A little mistake by your side..
..can kill your
officers and your family.
Let go of my child, Mangal Singh.
I'll. Come into my arms.
Mangal!
Mangal doesn't like waiting.
If you love your child..
..then send your
beautiful wife to me.
Daddy!
No, Shanti, you won't go.
I can't lose my son.
Let me go.
Let go of Munna.
Otherwise, l'll shoot.
Delicate hands can't shoot.
If you can shoot, c'mon.
Fire, Shanti.
-C'mon!
Fire!
Mummy! Mummy!
-Mangal!
Daddy!
Munna!
Lover..
Who am I and what's my name.
Why are you concern
with my name?
You can call me 'Lover'.
Who am I and what's my name.
Why are you concern
with my name?
You can call me 'Lover'.
Lover..
-Lover..
My eyes and my styles
are intoxicating.
Even I know that the
world is crazy for me.
My eyes and my styles
are intoxicating.
Even I know that the
world is crazy for me.
In the every first
meeting, people lose heart.
God, what should I do?
Who am I and what's my name.
Why are you concern
with my name?
You can call me 'Lover'.
Lover..
-Lover..
Name.. Balwant Singh!
Age, 32 years.
2 murders! Death sentenced.
He has appealed for mercy.
Oh!
Do you repent your crime?
Why did you do this crime?
-C'mon, answer him.
Enmity!
What did you obtain in return?
Death sentence.
Death sentence?
-Yes.
What will you do,
if you're freed?
One more murder.
-Whose?
Perhaps he wants to kill me.
-Oh!
Name, Sher Singh. Age, 40 years.
Crime, murder! Spent 2
years of life imprisonment.
Sher Singh, what will
you do if you're released?
I'll become an IG like you.
I see.. what will
you do being an IG?
I'll cage a lion once
again, like you do.
Name, Anand Raj. Age,
28 years. Crime, murder.
On life imprisonment.
Anand Raj, why did you
commit a murder?
I wanted to commit a
murder and I committed it.
Law wanted to punish me,
and it has.
What's bothering you?
Sir is asking it with
some special reason.
Go and ask government lawyer.
Ask the judge who punished me.
And still if you don't
believe then ask the victim..
..who died and unfortunately
she was my mother.
Name, Jung Bahadur.
Age, 30 years.
4 murders! Death sentenced.
He can't speak.
He talks in signals.
He says, he has shaved
today, as you were coming.
Take him away. Take him away.
He's habitual of
consuming poison.
Doctor gives morphine
injections twice a day.
But, Vijay.. they.. they're only five..
-Two more are there, sir.
They're in which jail?
They were in jail but are
released few days before.
But l'll search for them.
They're released and youD d..
It's very easy to
search for them.
Whenever some sad or needy
people call for them..
..they rush there.
Have mercy on these
orphan children.
Where will these kids go if you
force us to vacate the place?
We're least bothered. We
didn't give birth to these kids.
Sir wants this place vacated.
-No!
I won't let you go in.
-Will you block our ways?
Move away!
Hello!
-Hello!
Who are you?
Who're we?
You tell them.
-No, you tell them.
-You tell them.
Mister, actually we're
grown up in this orphanage.
And if you want to go in,
you'll have to cross our corpses.
I'll thrash you so hard that..
Really?
Will you thrash me?
I hope you're not lying.
I've never been beaten
by anybody in life.
It's my strong desire to
get beaten by somebody.
I want to get beaten.
Anybody stronger in you,
can beat me.
Beat me! Beat me!
then I will beat you.
- Raja
I feel he's strongest.
Yesterday, I had defeated him.
Idiot! The land was
damp and I slipped on it.
He's right. Yesterday, it rained.
But it's dry today. C'mon,
give him two punches.
C'mon, give him two punches.
l'm there in your support.
C'mon, punch him.
Tell your boss, if he
has devils like you..
..then we've gods on this
land to protect this orphanage.
They fooled us.
-Yes.
Raja! Kaka! You're like
an incarnation of God..
..for these orphan kids.
Don't say that and detach us
from our childhood, Master.
We se ourselves in every orphan.
Had you not sheltered us..
..we'd be wandering
in the streets.
You're our parents and
this orphanage is our home.
We did it for ourselves.
For the orphans like us.
Raja! Kaka!
I want your help for
few such orphans.
And l'm sure you won't refuse.
What's your name?
-Raja!
Kaka! An orphan!
Have you grown up in orphanage?
We're still in the orphanage.
This entire world
is orphanage for us..
Except this jail.
Here we get to meet
our fathers
And you're our great
grand father.
Yes! -Salute!
-Salute!
Raja!
-l'm sorry, sir.
How many times
you've been jailed?
Rampur! Siddhantpur!
Jabalpur! Nagpur!
Kolhapur!
-Yes. -Nashik!
Nashik..
Solapur!
In Solapur!
-lt's okay.
No need to calculate.
Okay, tell me something.
What's the guarantee that
you'd remain loyal to DSP?
And what's the guarantee..
That you're loyal to
your profession?
Good!
So many years of my
service and my record..
..is the proof of my loyalty.
And most importantly,
I fear God.
We don't fear God.
-Why?
What has God given us?
-No parents.
No siblings.
-We only believe conscience.
Sir, when they don't
believe in God..
..how will they listen
to DSP Vijay's orders?
They don't have manners
while talking to somebody.
They can't even stand properly.
How will they fight dacoits?
Right you're?
This is what I want to say.
They don't have manners
while talking to somebody.
They can't even stand properly.
They donD t look like
police officers..
..neither look-wise
nor by behaviour.
And I want such people
whom villagers don't doubt.
Okay.
Today itself, l'll write to
Home Minister for permission.
You start training them.
-Thank you very much, sir.
Bismillah! Is everything okay?
-Yes, sir. Everything is fine.
Bismillahi I trust
your capabilities.
That's why l've brought
few dangerous prisoners.
Sir, you don't worry.
God is above..
..and Bismillah on the earth.
Anand Raj!
Barrack is that side.
Manakya!
Why are you laughing?
Just like that.
Goto in barrack.
Jung Bahadur!
He's hanged.
I couldn't save him.
Balwant Singh!
Barrack is on that side.
I know.
-Barrack is on that side.
Barrack is on that side.
Don't touch.
Police officers are stronger
than criminals like you.
If you live with love
and a disciplined life..
..you'd get love in return.
And if you act smart..
-Then what will I get?
A kiss?
We know the ways of
your love. Got it?
Aye!
-We're born enemies of police.
Having enmity and taking it
out are two different things.
Will you take out enmity?
Take this knife.
Let's see how brave you're!
I'm already given
a death sentence.
Why do you want to lose
life? Go back to your work.
Only God has right
to kill anybody.
How will you take one?
C'mon, attack! C'mon!
Look, don't touch me.
-C'mon, attack.
I said don't touch me.
Don't touch.
-C'mon, attack.
Be aware, l'll attack.
This is formula number 44.
You people are brought
here to teach all these.
Take it easy.
After training, you too
will be strong like him.
Barrack is that side.
I know.
Bismillah! He's Raja
and he's Kaka! -Hello!
They've nothing to do
with those prisoners.
They're my men and
are here to help me.
Listen, you'll have
to stay with them.
But for my sake.
Co-operate with each other.
Nothing will happen.
Don't fight. Is that clear?
Yes, thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
Sir!
Yes.
Kaka wants to say
something to you.
I.. I.. -Now why do you stammer?
C'mon, speak up.
What's the matte?
-You tell him.
Sure?
-Yes.
Sir, actually..
-Why do you laugh now? Speak up.
Sir, you speak fluent English.
We too want to learn it.
I said that.
Sure! Why not?
Sir, get a book for us.
Bismillah, arrange for it.
You'll get it.
-Mr. Khan!
You know.. bring the book
along with the pictures.
Pictures.
-Okay, l'll get the book with pictures.
Even the small pictures would do.
-Yes, l'll bring that.
- Bye
Earrings fell in the market.
Deputy sirs stooge have come.
Speak slowly. If they'll
hear you, they'd complain.
I see. So, they can
even complain?
D O..
-G.
-E-
-G!
Dog! Meaning..
No? Eat!
Good boys don't
study while eating.
And they don't
eat while studying.
C'mon, eat now.
Let's eat and then study.
Stop it!
What's happening? Are
you eating or fighting?
Sir, tell him, I wanted water..
-Shut up!
Sit down! Take your seat!
You people are not
worth behaving softly.
All of you are indecent
and audacious.
Illiterate stupid!
Mind your language, sir.
Don't think that you're the
only literate person around here.
I know you're a DSP.
But l'm sorry to say, you don't
know how to behave yourself.
First of all, enquire
about whose mistake it is.
And then decide who should
be jailed. Understand?
I know my duty better than you..
..keep your mouth shut!
I brought you here to
give a new life.
A life in which, even
if you meet death..
..you'd take proud of it.
Nation will take pride for you.
It'll bring a new morning,
a new glory to your life.
New morning of new life.
Decision is up to you.
New life!
He'll grant us new life,
only if he'd remains alive.
You?
You want to kill me?
That one is used for
shaving. Keep it back.
Take this.
Take it.
C'mon, go to sleep. Go!
If somebody would ask
you, tell him I had called.
Okay? Go!
What'S this?
Go!
Take it little above. Fire!
If you try to aim in
the wrong direction..
We won't miss our target.
S.. N.. A.. K.. E..
Snake means serpent.
No!
Kaka!
Get up!
-What? -Get up!
See there..
Sleep!
Okay.
Hello!
In which police station you're?
Perhaps, you don't know sir.
Few days before, l'm discharged
from the police service.
Why?
On medical ground.
-Oh, l'm sorry.
I came to see IG sir.
-I too have to meet him.
I'm in a bit of hurry. Excuse me!
-Yes, sir.
All the best.
You called for me, sir?
-Yes, Vijay.
We received Home
Minister's reply.
Have we got the permission?
I was quite sure that..
What's the matter, sir?
Our request is rejected.
You must call the prisoners back.
You're mad that you got
carried away in his talks.
Police officers never
care relations..
..why will they care for you?
Great, Deputy sir.
Thank you very much for getting
us a new life and freedom.
We didn't understand
your norms, DSP.
Sometimes, you unlock us
and sometime you lock us.
You lecture us to be
a good citizen..
..and wants to send back
to that criminal cell.
Why do you play with
our emotions, DSP?
What right you've?
-I tried my best.
But l'm helpless at
High Command's orders.
Please, forgive me.
-No, sir. You won't be pardoned.
It's not justice to disappoint
somebody after giving hopes.
They were living in the darkness.
You showed them brightness.
You gave them hopes.
And now you're becoming
the obstacles of their life.
No, SP. lt's a treachery
with them. A treachery.
Yes, l'm a betrayer.
l'm selfish.
I fooled you for
my own selfish reason.
After all, l've enmity with
Mangal Singh and not you.
He shot my wife and
kid and not yours.
Yes.
It's my fault that
I brought you here.
I'm an offender. I promised
to give you freedom.
And I should be punished
for this crime.
Go! All of you can escape.
You're free..
Sir, it's against law..
-Bismillah, you won't stop them.
This is an order.
But you're committing a crime.
I'll go through it's punishment.
Why haven't they gone?
Tell them to escape.
They're free.
-No, sir.
They won't go.
-Why?
They want to punish you.
What do they want?
-Your co-operation.
We never cared for our life before.
nor do we care for it today.
Now, you're our Law, sir.
Now we'll go with you.
I didn't understand.
It's very clear, sir.
If all of us would go together.
Yes, that's true, we must
be careful from the police.
But, we must arrange for
weapons to fight the dacoits.
What are they talking about?
Sir, we can't go
out of the forest.
Anybody can see us.
And anybody can inform
police for Rs 10000.
Sir, l've a solution
to obtain weapons.
Hey, police! Police!
What?
-l'll catch you.
I'll arrest you and
take you to the police.
Will you take me to the police?
-Yes..
How many of you're there?
We're.. 1..2..3..4..5..6..7.. 8..
-8?
I'll arrest all of you.
But how will you arrest
us. We're so many.
And you're alone.
This is very powelful.
-This one?
Want to see?
-Yes. Show me.
Hold this! Hold it!
Caught you
No, it doesn't have strength!
-l've more.
Yes, drink more. We're
more, you need more strength.
Yes, slim body.
Hold it. -Yes.
-Don't leave it. -No!
Now see..
-Okay.
I've held it. -Yes, keep
hanging there. -Police!
Yes! Okay. -Police!
-Don't let him go! -Police!
Police!
Balwant, you were saying
something about the weapons.
Yes, sir. I know a blacksmith,
who makes illegal weapons.
In the Raipr Village. Kalu!
So, Nlr. Balwant, you
again escaped from jail?
Speak softly.
I keep visiting jail.
For now I want weapons.
-Really?
Tell me! What do you want?
Knife, sword or spear!
Not that, I want
pistol, guns and bullets.
We want them at any cost.
How? lt's possible!
You want bullets, right? You'll
get it. You'll definitely get it.
It's a risky job.
Possible that you'd get
so many bullets that..
..you won't need more.
And possible that you
obtain the entire delivery.
From where?
Promise me. Even if you
survive, you won't come here.
I promise I won't come. Tell me.
That delivery comes
for dacoit Mangal Singh.
From where?
-I don't know.
I only know the
place where it comes.
Where?
Chandanpur! Petrol pump!
Durjan's restaurant.
Hail Ram! Hail Ram!
Say hail Ram! Hail Ram!
I meet different people
in the form of friends.
They claim to be fans and
show me coloulful dreams.
Nobody is friend here.
Nobody loves here.
l've seen that.
I've seen that.
On my dark tresses,
intoxicated eyes..
..many are ready to die.
Thirsty hearts invite me..
..and promise, life
is noting without you.
Nobody speaks the truth. All
are liar here. l've seen it.
I've seen that.
My fans follow me
everywhere I go.
Who do I accept and
who do I reject?
Everybody want to my consent.
I don't trust them. Nobody
is loyal. l've seen it.
I've seen it.
- Wait, let me count cash.
- Wait,  Sage, stop!
Stop, sage, where are you going?
Bless us, sage.
Bless you!
-Why are you looking there?
She's my daughter.
Your daughter?
-Yes. -Then bless me!
Sage, why are you
making us sinner?
You're a biggest dance
master. Bless her.
1..2..3..
-You don't know..
..the quality, the art,
the beauty she has..
I tell you, you too
must seek her blessings.
He's not a sage, but a dacoit.
Sage, you're a biggest
dance master.
Teach her something.
I'll arrest you.
l'll arrest all of you.
Who will you arrest?
-Here too? -Yes.
-They all are dacoits.
Hey.. you too are one
of them. l'll arrest you.
I'll arrest all of them.
I caught him.
You can arrest all of them.
-I won't release him.
C'mon, sit here.
-l've caught. I won't release.
You made me sit?
-Yes.
You do one thing.
You sit here and
l'll call the police.
Don't move!
Just don't move! l'll call..
I'm moving. I understood.
You're very clever.
You'll escape if I go.
It won't do.
I'm very intelligent.
I'll sit here. You go
and call the police.
Hey.. you're very clever.
You may escape from there.
What will I do sitting here?
Both of us will sit here.
I'll arrest all of
them and you too.
Yes, wrestler! You need to
have guts to nab 8-9 people.
That's right.
And there's liquor to gain guts.
Is it?
-Yes.
It'll be fun!
Do you want me to drink more..
..and lose sense and
want to escape?
No, I won't escape.
-I won't drink liquor. No.
They're very daring people.
I too am a daring personality.
-They punch very hard.
I too punch very hard.
They'll beat you with a stick.
-lt'll break.
They'll punch you.
-I too will punch them.
They've strength!
-Keep the hand down!
I too have strength.
They'll throw liquor
bottle at you.
I too will throw bottle at them.
They'll open the
lid and throw it.
I too will open
the lid and throw.
Then they will take
a sip and throw.
I too will sip and throw.
They'll drink more and throw.
I too will drink more and throw.
Hey.. you're very smart!
-What happened?
You made me drink liquor
and want to escape?
No, I won't escape. l'm here.
-You won't escape? -No.
Hold my hand.
-Yes, l've held it.
Slowly!
Don't release it.
There comes the delivery.
I've kept the boxes.
Place it in the bullock
carts and send it to chief.
We'll check it.
You take your charge.
Sages, it's very fortunate
to meet five sages together.
Suggest me how do I serve you?
You want to serve us?
-Yes.
Then arrange for a meal for us.
Come and sit in the tent, sages.
Not in the sages. We'll eat
in the restaurant with public.
Come, sages.
Please, come. Please..
How can I serve you?
How will you serve us, child?
Just serve some food to the sages.
-Please, come.
Please, give some place, mister.
Come, sages.
- No!
This place is not pure.
We'll make our place
somewhere else.
Say hail Ram! Say hail Ram!
They're taking our boxes..
-They're sages.
They'll eat and leave.
If there's something untoward..
What will you eat, sages?
Vegetables? Curry?
Don't you have
non-vegetarian food?
Sages, you're non-vegetarian?
How's it possible?
It's because what's
possible is possible.
And what's impossible,
is impossible.
Possible could be impossible.
But impossible could
never be possible.
But, turning impossible
into possible and possible..
..into impossible is
ourjob. Did you get it?
We need third eye of
Lord Shiva to explain it.
Sage! -And God has given us
this order today.
Lord, do you permit us?
-Yes.
Miracle! Miracle!
Sage, you've direct
contact with God.
Trust me, child.
You'll be blessed.
Sit here.
-Where are you going?
I'll call the police.
I'm heavily drunk.
I drank too much.
I've a solution to sober down.
Really? -Yes. -What?
-lt's the best way.
Drink little water.
What's that?
-Water..
You never drank it?
-Never.
Water can sober down
your intoxication.
Really?
-Yes.
Where's it? -Come, l'll
take you there. Come!
Carefully! -l'm
fine. -Careful!
See.. -What's
this? -lt's a tap!
Water?
-Yes, you get water from it.
See, this is the water.
-Yes.
Isn't it nice?
Water is very nice.
It's a municipality tap.
Water, what's your colour?
Isn't it nice?
Drink it, my dear.
-lt's finished?
It's very nice. Hey..
-Yes.
Where's municipality office?
-Why?
I'll buy a tap.
How will you arrange for money?
I'll get you arrested and
get the reward of Rsloooo.
And l'll buy a tap from it.
-Okay. You can buy it.
You can buy.
Police! -Hang
here. -Police!
Salute, sir!
-Okay!
Whose truck it is?
-Mine.
From where have you come?
-Jabalpur!
How many people were there?
-Three.
Who are these people?
They're villagers
having their meals.
Listen! -6 to 7 prisoners
have escaped. -Okay.
If they come here or if you
get any information about them..
..then inform us.
-Okay, sir.
Great! Sages and
non-vegetarian food?
Good! -Inspector!
lt's possible but impossible.
Possible has made
it impossible and..
"impossible has made
it possible.
Both have confused each other.
-I know it very well.
What's there in these boxes?
They were lying there? We
took it for our comfort.
Hail Ram!
Sage, please pick up your plate.
Constable!
-Yes, sir.
Open this box!
Don't you dare.
Sages, now you too
escape from here.
As your order, child.
Idiot, let me serve
him water at least.
Bismillah!
-Sir!
Call up at the police station!
-Yes, sir.
Hello! Police station?
I'm calling from the
service station here.
Your officer Bahadur Singh
is lying injured here.
Please take him away
as early as possible.
I'm a human being.
Sir, hurry up, sir.
Before police force
reach here, I must go.
But, sir.
-I know what you're thinking.
And you must not
even forget your duty.
But you must understand
that I too love my duty.
I too am serving police
and law. Even today.
The only difference is
that l'm using my ways.
Sir!
Will you stop me?
If I could, l'd have
definitely stop you.
C'mon!
Sir, nobody will recognize
us with these drama company.
Yes, we've got the guns.
Now let's see when
we meet Nlangal Singh.
Tomorrow Mangal Singh's men will
come to Fatehgarh to collect tax.
What are you waiting for?
Pay your tax.
I've nothing that
I can give you.
Don't you know
about the punishment..
..of not paying
tax to Nlangal Singh?
I mean it. l've
no food to eat.
Tie him! We'II
punish him, later.
Somebody go bring
the liquor bottle.
C'mon, move forward.
Hello!
-Pay your tax first!
Shall I tell you something,
if you don't mind?
What nonsense?
I'm here to take this
away and not to pay you.
Hey, old man! Have you gone mad?
If you touch it,
you'll get killed.
If he'II get killed,
you too won't be spared.
Now repeat after me.
-Yes.
Let him take it away.
-I knew it.
Keep your pistol.
It's very little.
But never mind.
Now tell your men to let
the villagers take away..
..money and food grains.
-But..
Listen! Look into your left.
Above!
Now look down.
Now Look into your right.
Oh! l'm sorry.
Did you saw?
He's saluting you! Reply him!
Reply him!
Now speak up.
We..
-What?
I've decided to
return the villagers..
..their money and food grains.
Baldy! Brother,
return their grains.
Villagers, you can
take away your grains.
Great!
Now? -Now tell your men to
place their guns on the bed.
Place your guns on the bed.
-Yes, to take some rest.
Take rest! Take rest!
Now? -Now, tell your men
to stand facing each other.
All of you stand
facing each other.
In a queue!
Now tell them to slap each other.
-No.
This won't be good.
It'd be very good. You don't
understand. C'mon, say it.
C'mon.
-Now slap each other.
No, I didn't enjoy it.
-No?
No, tell them to punch harder.
Speak up loudly!
-Punch harder.
Okay, now tell that man
to hit on the baldy's head.
No, he's a dangerous man.
-He's less dangerous than me.
Tell him to hit on baldy's head.
And don't call him brother.
Hit on the baldy's head.
Hey..
What nonsense is this?
Don't you love life?
That's why l'm
saying this nonsense.
You too would have said that
had you been in my place.
Listen to me.
lt's your chief's order.
Chief! Chief!
It's not happening for
good. l'm telling you.
But I like it.
Shall I smoke?
-Yes.
You want?
-No, I don't smoke.
I don't understand why
do you do this business?
Taking away their grains,
why you do all this?
I'm helpless.
You kept..
-With respect.
You placed gun here. And
I followed your order.
Mangal Singh places gun
here so I follow his orders.
What should I do?
You go away from here.
Yes. -And live a respectful
life. Okay? Go!
And listen!
My friends..
-Yes..
Who?
-He..
My God! He..
And him..
Be careful from them.
Villagers don't fight.
Just save yourself
from them and escape.
Okay, I'll.
-C'mon, run! -l'll..
I hope you won't
shoot from behind.
See this!
It's empty?!
It's empty!
-Yes.
It's empty?
It's empty? Kill me! Kill me,
l'm not fit for being a dacoit.
Kill me. Kill me.
No! l'll go.. l'll go away.
I'll go somewhere far.
Tell your chief to personally
come and collect the tax.
Go!
-Get lost!
Well done! Well done!
You've done a miracle.
Who are you?
Your friends and dacoit's enemy.
Now dacoit Mangal Singh can't
raid any village till we're there.
If you trust us.
Why not? We completely
trust you. Right, brothers?
Yes! Yes!
-Well said!
Did you see how
they ran away, Kaka?
Child, will you stay with me?
In my house?
I'll cook food for you.
What are you thinking, child?
Don't you think
l'm like your mother?
Come, child! Come!
-Yes.
Consider it your own house.
-Okay.
Come, child.
Hey, why have you stopped?
Come inside.
-Yes.
You didn't like
your mother's house?
No! -Yes! -Yes!
What's this? Why are
you giving short answers?
Can't you call me mother?
Mother!
Mother?!
Only mother? Nothing else?
Had there been my Deepu..
I'm very hungry. I didn't
eat anything since morning.
I'm starving.
Come! Come, child. Come inside.
Come!
Sit down!
Child, l'll bring milk for you.
You don't even demand
anything to your mother.
Have you seen anybody
keeping distance from mother?
Had there been my Deepu,
he'd have drank all the milk.
And have asked for more.
Again you got up? Sit down!
I've brought milk.
Don't touch it.
I'll make you drink it.
What's the matter,
child? Why are you crying?
You speak up.
Mother!
Actually, till date, nobody
talked lovingly with us.
Nobody offered us food to eat.
And.. even if we're offered..
..it was thrown to us
like how you feed animals.
Yes, mother.
We had to eat that
to satisfy our hunger.
That's why we learnt
to snatch away things.
Mother,
we don't have a mother.
We're orphans!
No, my child. you're not
orphans. l'm your mother.
Mother!
-l'm your mother.
Child, have one more chapatti.
No, mother! l'm tired
of eating. lt's enough.
It's from mother's share.
Take it.
You too take it, my child.
Mother, if you'll
serve us everything..
..you'll remain starving.
There's enough food.
l'll eat later.
No! Not later. Now
we'll feed you morsels.
Child..
-Hey..
No, mother.. let me feed you..
Child, l'm fasting today.
So l'll cook it later and eat.
Okay, mother.
Henceforth, we too will
fast along with you.
And we'll eat
only when you'd eat.
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison
to a mother.
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison
to a mother.
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison
to a mother.
O mother..
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison
to a mother.
You're my temple
and my worship.
You're a boon to me.
You're my world.
Both the world lies
at your feet.
You're my temple
and my worship.
You're a boon to me.
You're my world.
Both the world lies
at your feet.
You're the other
image of Lord.
I see Lord in you.
Mother, your love
flows uninterruptedly.
Your shadow is like a heaven.
Nobody can love us like you.
Mother, your love
flows uninterruptedly.
Your shadow is like a heaven.
Nobody can love us like you.
Motherless children know
your real value, mother.
Mother is a mother..
Apple of your eyes passed away.
And your dreams shattered.
We'll share your grief
and wipe your tears.
Apple of your eyes passed away.
And your dreams shattered.
We'll share your grief
and wipe your tears.
You're not alone.
You're not helpless.
Now we're your
support, mother.
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison
to a mother.
O mother..
Friends..
What's the punishment we give
to he who escape? -Death!
Death!
-Okay.
But I don't want to reduce
my strength by killing my men.
He had gone to collect
ration for us.
But he returned empty handed
and that too running away.
And while running away,
..he must have
used up his energy..
So feed him something.
-Yes. Take this.
No!
-Eat an egg.
Give him cock.
-Yes.. -No. -Eat it.
I'll make you eat more
and make you powelful..
..so that you'd never return
empty handed in future.
Chief, order me.
I can bring them alive.
Bring them. -Then he too
will accompany you.
No! I won't go.
-You won't go? -No..
I won't go.
You won't go?
-No, I won't.
-Yes, l'll.
What happened? -Don't go inside.
They're the one
who met me before.
They're terrible.
-Are we any less?
We too have a gun.
Break open the door
and bring them out.
Listen to me.
This time we'll return
and tell chief..
..that they were
not at home. -Look,
l'll kill you now.
-You too talk like him.
Gun! Gun! l'm going.
Should I go?
Hey, it was open!
It was already open.
You?
-Yes, it's me.
I mean it's me.
Look! Just listen to me.
Please, come out.
-Why?
Look, l'm already
thrashed enough at my den.
My accomplices
are waiting outside.
Please come out.
Try to understand.
Who will go first? You or I?
-Anybody..
No, you'll go first.
-With respect.
Yes, you please go first.
-Okay..
Slowly!
Slowly! Walk slowly!
Welcome!
Friends, have you seen a
camel under the mountain?
And if not, then see them.
Your men hasn't seen a mountain..
..how will they see camel?
Are you imitating me?
Who's interested
in imitating you?
I speak like this
since childhood.
Yes, you're carrying gun. So
your childhood is still not over.
If you don't trust me,
ask your man.
Tell him.
-C'mon, tell me.
Yes, he speaks like this.
You speak like this. He too
speaks like that and I too.
I wish the entire world
to speak like that.
Like that.. -Enough now.
I understand everything.
Now get ready to die,
guys! Okay?
Look, if you want to
kill, kill me first.
I'm younger. -No, l'm elder
to him. First you kill me.
No, Raja, l'll die
first. -No! -Kill me.
Here it is.
I told you.. I told
you not to come here.
I see, so its you?
Don't you have any other work?
You neither sleep nor
do you let others sleep.
Never mind. -We'll massage them
properly.. -And make them sleep.
Let's go.
C'mon!
-Move!
What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
What should I do?
lt's my destiny.
I told you, it's not
your cup of tea.
Then why did you come here?
I'm helpless!
Chief kept me on gun point
and I came to the village.
You..
- With respect.
You kept me on gunpoint
and I returned.
Again chief kept me
on gunpoint..
Listen,
l'm giving you last chance.
-Okay.
If I see you again
in this dress..
..or if you try to
become a dacoit again..
..l'll brutally kill you.
-No. Don't kill me. -Go.
I'm going.
-Get lost! -Yes..
Earrings fell in
the market place..
What's happening, Sher Singh?
Nothing. I was just passing by.
This way?
Yes, I was going on the
farm. But, on the way..
A tree came in.
-Yes. a tree came in.
But it's fruitless, Sher Singh.
You're right. -Go back
to your work. -Okay.
Earrings fell in
the market place..
Ever since he's here
in this village..
..he keeps drinking liquor.
I understand his pain.
He hasn't obtained
a motherly love.
His mother left him
when he was too young.
He hates a word 'mother'.
And when he grew up,
he killed his mother.
Now, he's always drunk.
Bismillah, I hope I have
not committed a mistake..
What are you saying, sir?
Look at Raja and Kaka.
They're so happy.
Sir, look there.
Sir, look there too.
They've so very well
mixed in the village.
You don't worry, sir.
By God's grace,
everything will be fine.
What's your opinion
about me, sir?
You and here?
You were sick, right?
Yes, sir.
L'm suffering from cancer.
-Cancer?
Oh my God!
Then why are you here?
You should be in some hospital.
-No, sir.
I'm an officer.
Instead of dying
on the hospital bed..
..l want to meet
death while on fight.
H.. h.. -She's saying
hello to you, sir.
Are there any outsiders
entered in the village?
No, sir.
If you see strangers whom
you don't know inform police.
She's asking you.. why?
They're the absconding
prisoners.
She keeps doing that, sir.
We'll inform you as soon as we
see a stranger in the village.
Okay!
-Bye!
Bye! Bye!
Very nicely you fooled
the police officers.
Mister, we're
from drama company.
It's very easy for us.
I hope you're not
playing drama with me.
With you?
No! Tell me something, mister.
Do you love me?
-Oh yes, we'll get married.
There's no life without
wife. You didn't get it?
We'll get married.
What's more worrying is that..
"Villagers are fearless
about king Mangal Singh.
Entire Village is
helping Vijay and his men.
That's why police
can't nab them.
When we heard this,
we couldn't believe it.
People of Fatehgarh
were scared of you.
But how could they
dare raise head at you?
We're proud of our
respective areas..
"because of your
power and name.
When we raid a place, people
think it's Mangal Singh.
That's why nobody used
to argue or challenge us.
We served your father, Chief.
My brother Rajan and
I will die for you.
Order us, Mangal Singh.
We'll make them bent at you.
Aye! We'll crush those heads.
They'll be found dead
by tomorrow evening.
Lala!
-Yes, Chief.
You inform the villagers
that few people are coming..
..with a marriage
proposal for your daughter.
This way, we'll
enter the village.
And you'll cordon the
village with your men.
If they'd try to escape..
..they'll have enemies
in front as well as back.
Mangal Singh was born a
king and will remain a king.
Hello, Lala.
I'm expecting few
people from Chamangarh..
..with my daughter's
marriage proposal.
You people are also invited.
Fine, l'll take your leave.
l've to invite many others.
Why are you sad, my child?
I'll get you married this year.
-Papa..
Boy is really nice.
Sage!
-Don't you dare take his name!
I want to marry you
with Laxman from Rampur.
He's a famous confectioner.
You'll get to eat many
varieties of sweets.
Papa, I don't want to
eat sweets. -Shut up!
You must marry
a man of my choice.
Go back to the tent.
You go and get married. I won't.
She doesn't listen
to her father.
My sweetheart.
Today, you've a chance.
Take the advantage.
Rupa! Why are you
crying, darling?
What's your concern?
I'm concern that's why l'm here.
Let go off my hand.
-lt's a strong grip.
Son of a..
Let me see how strong
grip you can have.
Get away! -Don't you dare
held her hand again.
Is that clear?
Why? Is she your sister?
Yes, she's my sister.
You too make her.
I'll catch her wrist.
Are you fond of catching wrist?
-Yes.
Hold this.
-C'mon.
Not like this. Like this.
If anybody dare
act smart, we'd shoot.
Hey..
Won't you welcome the groom with
a procession in your village?
Everybody take off your belts.
Villagers, now watch
the drama l'd show you.
I'll put belt in your neck,
you government servant.
Get up!
Your men are so loyal, inspector.
They're feeling your pain.
If I wish I can crush
you to death now.
But I don't have
any enmity with you.
This inspector is my enemy.
He's my enemy and yours too.
You know what?
He provoked you and brought
you face to face to your death.
In short, Mangal
Singh's gun at one side..
..and gallows on the other.
I know you're brave. But
you're still a prisoner.
And I appreciate brave people
and want to see them free.
I can free you, if
you come into my camp.
Accept me as your chief.
Whoever from you wants to
free, can come to my camp.
Mangal Singh, I accept
you as my chief.
You're the only one
intelligent in them. C'mon.
But on one condition.
I'll take away your sister.
-You cheap! You lowly!
Let go of me.
Nice girl! -Mangal Singh,
there's one more thing.
Bring it.
-Take care of her.
Let go of!
Sir, what are you
doing? She's my daughter.
Why do you lie, Lala?
How could you have such
a beautiful daughter?
Sir, she's my daughter.
Kill me but save my daughter.
Don't insult me. -Lala,
she'll remain your daughter.
But l'll make her my queen.
Take her away.
Oh! God!
I'll count till 10. Anybody
who's interested, can come.
1..
2..
3..
Chief! l'm with you.
Very good! One more intelligent.
Come in!
Hail Lord!
Child! Child!
Child, I hope you're
not injured.
Child! Child!
Mother!
I've removed the bullet
but pulses are going down.
She lost much blood.
If blood isn't supplied on
time, it could risk her life.
Now don't waste time and take him
to the city as early as possible.
To some hospital.
C'mon, Bismillah,
let's arrange for a car.
Wait! You people don't go out.
Mangal Singh's men have
cordoned the village.
How do you know? -l'm the
traitor in this village.
I used to give all information
about this village to Mangal.
But today his evil eyes
fell on my daughter..
..which opened my eyes.
Dacoits are never friends.
They're only dacoits.
Now you can punish me anything.
But you please don't go out.
He'll kill each of you.
Lala, for the first time,
we've got a mother in life.
We don't mind losing
life for her.
We'll definitely
take away mother.
C'mon, Bismillah!
You've given this life,
We'll die for you.
There's nothing
in life without you.
lt's useless living here.
If anything happens
to you, mother.
We'll set the world on fire.
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison
to a mother.
Don't worry, sir.
-Chase them.
They shouldn't escape.
-Come with me.
Buggy shouldn't pass.
Explode it.
Every dog has a day!
Your game is over!
Throw your weapons!
Sher Singh!
I had heard..
That vulture flies to the
city when it's death is closer.
But why did they
come here to die?
Anyway, when they've
come, do something.
Tell me what's their
name and profession?
So that I can decide
their death accordingly.
Mangal Singh, you've enmity
with us and not with our mother.
Mother will die if she isn't
reached to the hospital on time.
We promise you, Mangal Singh.
We'll come back after dropping
mother to the hospital.
But sons have to
serve their mother.
So you'd pull the buggy and
l'll become the coachman.
But it'll pass from the village.
Okay? Shera! Inform the
villagers that l'm coming. Go!
Leave him, Raja!
He's my prey!
Vijay! Stop, Vijay! Don't shoot!
Sir! Nobody can stop me today.
But it's against law!
Sir, he ruined my family.
I won't spare him alive.
By swear of the law you've
served all your life.
Hand over that man to me.
Drop your weapons.
Drop your weapons!
She's absolutely fine
now. You can take her away.
No..
You?!
-No, not me.
Stop!
You.. -Nothing, government
telegram came in the office.
Your punishment is cancelled.
Mother is a mother..
There's no comparison to a mother.