[OPENING MUSIC PLAYING]
TECHNICAL GURUJI: Hello, guys.
Its Technical Guruji coming
to you all the way from Dubai.
And I'm really excited to
be in front of you all.
In fact, excitement
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
I will be a part of the first
ever 100% virtual YouTube
FanFest 2020.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
But at the same
time, right now I
think it's very
essential for all of us
to stay home and keep
our communities safe.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
But you know what?
This extended lockdown in
India has altered the lives
of millions, especially the
millennials who are not able
to go out as before
and socialize,
and date and
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]..
And you know what?
This stay-at-home
situation has given
birth to a new series
of content based
on virtual dating etiquette,
managing heartbreaks,
break-ups, relationships,
and all those things.
So let's see some
of this content,
and get entertained together.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
[CLOSING MUSIC PLAYING]