Tamiga & 2Bad - Baby, C'est La Vie
Your love babe get me high
It makes me lose my mind
Day dreaming bout you
You make me feel alive
Baby I'm yours for life
In all my dreams you're with me
The sun is
washing down over your big blue eyes
By them baby I'm simply hipnotized
Let's run together and live by the sea
You next to me
Baby c'est la vie
Runaway with me
Let's go to the ocean
And make memories
Baby c'est la vie
Tell me you love me
Kiss me oh so softly
Alway be with me
Baby c'est la vie
You're the only baby
Your love can set me free
I feel safe in your arms
I want your love badly
Without it I'm empty
Stay close to me
The sun is
washing down over your big blue eyes
By them baby
I'm simply hipnotized
Let's run together and live by the sea
You next to me
Baby c'est la vie
Runaway with me
Let's go to the ocean
And make memories
Baby c'est la vie
Tell me you love me
Kiss me oh so softly
Alway be with me
Baby c'est la vie
Runaway with me
Let's go to the ocean
And make memories
Baby c'est la vie
Tell me you love me
Kiss me oh so softly
Alway be with me
Baby c'est la vie