Gauri!
What happened?
What happened to Gauri?
Garv, Gauri and Siddhi
were offering milk to Lord Sheshnag.
The milk was hot and when Gauri tried to
move the cup, she got bitten.
[Sanskrit chants]
O' Lord Sheshnag
you bit Lord Shiva's profound devotee.
That too because
she didn't want to hurt You.
You bit her
and upset us all
and let Lord Shiva down.
If You don't want God to be miffed,
spare Gauri's life.
Save my Gauri.
[Sanskrit chants]
Garv!
Glory be to Lord Shiva.
[Sanskrit chants]
Thank You, Lord Sheshnag.
Thank You.
Gauri!
Are you all right?
When did you get here?
God, thank You for saving Gauri.
Forgive me if I have sinned.
You spared Gauri's life
and restored my happiness.
Gauri!
You got blessings from Lord Sheshnag.
Amazing!
You took away
all of your husband's troubles.
You succeeded.
[Sanskrit chants]
'Siddhi, make something special tonight.'
'I am expecting some guests.'
Vinayak's message.
But, Vinayak is here. Then this message...
It's time for the prayers.
All devotees come forth.
Sage, I have an offering to make.
Give it.
Well, I'm making a huge offering
so I should get the honour
of offering prayers.
To perform the prayers,
Sumitradevi Bhardwaj is here
from Ayodhya.
[Devotional song]
You've come at the right time.
The prayers are about to begin.
- Let's start.
- Wait a minute.
I am making a huge donation.
Yet she gets to do the prayers?
This is our ancient temple in Banaras.
She's from Ayodhya
yet she gets to offer prayers first?
Who is she? What is her status?
'I fear Shaku might come to know'
'that these are fake notes.'
I hail from Ayodhya
and my name is Sumitradevi Bharadwaj.
Hello, Ms. Sumitra.
If you want to offer prayers first
you may go ahead.
Devotion is beyond competition.
I don't seek your charity.
I am making a huge donation.
Hence, I deserve to offer prayers first.
Ms. Shakuntala,
God doesn't care about money.
God belongs to both,
the rich and the poor.
Shakuntaladevi,
if you don't mind,
shall we pray together?
God will be pleased with our unison.
Sister,
join us.
Yes, Ms. Sumitra.
Garv, how's Gauri?
Is she all right?
Yes, she's better.
Actually, I wanted to confirm
if Gauri really saw Vinayak.
I got his message
saying he's in Agra.
Gauri is right, Siddhi.
I also saw Maya and Vinayak
in this temple.
When I questioned Vinayak...
You should be performing this ritual
with your wife.
Why are you here
with your sister-in-law, Maya?
Actually, he consumed hemp.
He came here intoxicated.
He was adamant on
performing the ritual.
So, I complied.
No!
My sister can't do that.
Siddhi,
never trust anyone blindly.
The deepest of wounds
comes from your loved ones.
Garv, I want to meet Gauri once.
Come.
Gauri...
Gauri!
Where is she? She was right here.
Gauri...
Gauri!
- Gauri!
[Devotional song]
Gauri!
Garv, she isn't that way.
Where could she go?
[Sanskrit chants]
Help!
No!
Somebody help!
Garv...
Help!
You made me suffer immensely, Gauri.
You shall suffer way more than that.
If you wish
you can be spared of this agony.
For that, you have to
- spend a night with me.
- No!
Garv!
Get me out of here.
Who could have done this?
It has to be the snake charmer.
He tried to kill Gauri earlier as well.
That means Gauri has an enemy here.
Siddhi,
we have to find Gauri at any cost.
[Devotional song]
'Gauri, you shall leave this temple dead.'
[Sanskrit chants]
No!
Let me out!
Somebody help!
[Sanskrit chants]
In return for sparing your precious life,
I'm asking for a petty price
not great wealth.
Just one night.
Spend one night with me.
Then you'll be free.
[Sanskrit chants]
God,
please help us find Gauri.
"With an innocent face"
"but a strong character"
"here comes Nandini, true to her roots."
Gauri!
- I'm sorry.
- Siddhi!
- Garv, did you find Gauri?
- No, did you?
Are you looking for someone?
Yes, my friend Gauri.
Was it some snake charmer?
I'm sure the snake charmer
went this way.
He seemed strange.
He was carrying something heavy
on his shoulder.
He forgot his flute behind.
How can a snake charmer forget his flute?
This means, he carried Gauri
on his shoulder!
- Can you tell me where he went?
- Why not?
I'm a farmer from Madhupur, Ayodhya.
Helping people is in my nature.
I'll surely help you guys.
Come with me.
This way.
I saw him come here.
He couldn't have taken Gauri
too far from here.
Thank you very much.
We wouldn't make it here
without your help.
Thank Lord Shiva, not me.
I just came to offer prayers
at the Lord Sheshnag temple.
A new story is about to begin.
Hence, I came to seek blessings.
I will ask God
to help you find your wife.
May your new journey be a great one.
May you and your crops, both bloom!
Thank you and let me know
if I can be of help.
I will join you 8:30 onwards.
- Glory be to Lord Ram.
I am sure
Lord Ram will guide you.
See you. Glory be to Lord Ram.
[Devotional song]
[Sanskrit chants]
I think Lord Sheshnag is guiding us.
Yes, let's go.
Are you ready?
Somebody help!
I think Gauri is in there.
Don't you dare come in!
If you do, I'll kill Gauri.
Nachiket!
Garv, go in and save Gauri.
I'll go thank Lord Sheshnag.
Gauri!
Take one more step
and I'll fill this capsule
with poisonous gas.
If anything happens to Gauri,
you'll be dead.
I will surely remain alive all right.
You better think of
a way to keep Gauri alive.
The closer you get
the quicker the gas will fill this.
Nachiket, release her or I'll kill you.
Gauri!
Nachiket!
As long as I have this remote,
you're helpless.
Gauri!
'Save me from this devil.'
'Help me.'
[Devotional song]
Move this away or else...
[Sanskrit chants]
Gauri...
This is broken.
Hang in there, I will save you.
Garv, how will you get her out?
Gauri,
move back.
Shut your eyes and sit down.
Glory be to Lord Mahadev.
[Sanskrit chants]
Gauri!
Are you all right?
- Stop!
- Garv!
Lord Sheshnag has punished Nachiket.
[Sanskrit chants]
Gauri, I better leave now.
I have to go to Agra.
I saw Vinayak.
Something is not right.
Take care of yourself.
Find out what's cooking.
You too take care.
See you.
[Sanskrit chants]
Hail Lord Shiva.
Glory be to Lord Mahadev.
You are Ms. Sumitra, right?
- Yes.
- Greetings.
- I've heard a lot about you.
Glad to have you in Banaras.
It was great meeting you, dear.
When can I meet you again?
Don't worry, dear.
We'll meet often.
I'll take your leave now, dear.
Yes.
Gauri, finish the prayers.
Wait.
How can Gauri do the prayers?
Her fast was broken.
The priest fed her milk
and wood apple juice.
You're mistaken, Ms. Shakuntala.
For the first time in 100 years,
Lord Sheshnag appeared for this girl.
She has God's blessings.
Don't even think
about impeding her prayers.
Or else, you'll face the consequences.
Shaku,
the priest is right.
Gauri will offer the prayers today.
Gauri,
go on.
Yes, Choti Mai.
Come.
Stay quiet now. Garv is fuming.
What if he insults you!
Gauri!
What happened, Garv?
I will never leave you alone hereafter.
If anyone tries to attack you,
I will kill that person.
Your enemies will have to fight me first,
even if it's my own family.
Yes, Inspector.
I am willing to testify.
Just arrest him. Please. Yeah.
Who asked you to call the Inspector?
I don't understand one thing, Mom.
Why do you care about Nachiket?
Why won't you let me complain against him?
Shaku, I wonder if
you're in cahoots
with Nachiket to harm Gauri!
Mom, if I come to know
that you were behind this,
Gauri and I will leave this house.
I've come from the medical lab.
Come in.
Here's the DNA report.
What's happening, Mom?
I told you not to get a DNA test done.
They why?
So that I could expose these sisters.
[Sanskrit chants]
And here's the evidence.
You trust them blindly.
Take a look at this.
[Sanskrit chants]
These reports say that
Ganga's baby
is sired by Yug.