[Music]
give me those sweet mango mango do it
this is one small fill we'll take
everything no thank you
I'm not trusting you on that look at it
I'm not
[Music]
hello the four men who emit or fully
looking Nvidia Marcus quality or Marisa
play Luis or technical guru ji Howlin
kqg EA USA - let's make this video in
English so let's get started in this
video we are gonna do a different kind
of unboxing we're in Luis would be
showing us I mean actual unboxing one of
the most famous I would say biscuits
from India this is called as parle G
parlor genius genius genius Bemidji and
if their genius is that I'm not sure she
might be an old lady nobody able to get
from it is so this is yours and we want
to know your feedback your quick review
on ya and about this biscuit so we have
an unboxing like oh wow that's a serious
serious knife as well I don't think I
need it I don't think I need maybe I did
it that's okay oh there we go
you've tasted this before right oh
really
now this is a snack like you would have
this so you would just so you would just
eat this watching TV like Netflix in
parlor G what do you no idea what's next
but yeah let me just wait on you oh
there we go I got one
so what's your review about it what they
obtained so far the unboxing experience
not great well the first one busted here
okay and took me a while to get in there
but Oh hmm okay yeah pick delicious is
it yeah yeah flavor fight
[Music]
okay okay okay chill everybody a shot
you want one yeah yeah you might as well
sure but now let's go for the next one
which is also a famous man again none of
these bands have been your sponsoring
this video just alive that's a lie
this family's dead no every single one
is paid promotion what do you think
about this hmm what do you think would
be the taste yeah this is gonna be like
salty cheesy maybe no crispy waste at
home well that was right all right I
know how to read okay um these look good
this kind of reminds me of a practice
called rest get everything rich it looks
exactly like this thing so I assume in
the US have yeah um yeah this would be a
cracker
[Music]
so far so fiery smooth complete cracker
here delicious it almost it is identical
to a risk cracker
okay okay so if anybody is in North
America you know you try to read that's
what this tastes like
I think this is getting boring because
you know these guys are just eating
whatever it's been shown to them so
let's go for its challenge rather than
just giving an unboxing so how about you
some interesting stuffs like you never
heard of what is here from India you
know about aloe vera most of the guys
I've got a totally there's something
German brush which is an anti immunity
kind of not recovered
you will die for drinking
perfect thank you mm II so we have two
spoons here I look at this family dead
no this family is died already
yeah her face it says back here derived
from 2500 year old formula 2500 years Oh
purple challenge we're in I'll be giving
you equal amount of food at the same
time and both of you have to I thought
he was supposed to get more because he's
local
oh I'm the outsider okay that's know
that appeal how much do you think he
should have no you know what no that's a
good I know I can eat masala all right
[Music]
pick up a glass and put some of them in
and let's see who would win this
challenge
you know I need two glasses to glasses
so this is a fun video not if you really
want to see a professional video head
over to unbox therapy I hope that's the
right so here I think
yes stop it here I'll be giving you
three pieces of slidden
sweet biscuits oh we just change the
dished so that you be ready for the next
challenge
okay so nowadays we have the chocolate
most of you guys right so both of them
have to eat the mango good so this is
the most of our time boxing
[Music]
that's mango easier than the candy that
actually manager than the candy to India
again we watch that nobody wants that
[Music]
come on nobody wants that what is in the
middle of that I want to know what is
that you don't fix a few bets eject yeah
you'll hate me you hate me after that no
but I think it sort of chewing will just
keep it in your mouth and we dissolve
won't be shown should be yeah yes have a
spoon of this thing
a little whole spoon that's cheating
come on Lou if after what you just did
to me you won't trust me this is the
aloe vera test
that bad no no you need to oh man I'm
gonna go quick easier than the candy but
this is good $40 juice and it's a
dietary supplement
you know what that one's not that bad
this is like oh man what are you doing
no way no no no I'm not trusting you on
that I'm not trusting you on that look
at it I'm not what does that look like
show the audience was you didn't to
pronounce this thing okay
this is gold yeah yeah good luck Shinhwa
shower brush join the Shaolin brush