What's this?
Is this a joke?
One day, I'll buy the whole of Dubai.
Hello, everybody.
I am Saiman Says,
and I am the most underrated
youtuber of India.
Today, I am with some overrated youtubers.
Subscribe to Saiman Says.
Make him reach 1 million subs.
In Dubai...
...want this as a background.
- Done?
- Yeah.
Let me see.
These are really good pictures.
- Thank you, sir.
- Here's a little gift from me.
- [laughs] Thank you, sir.
- What?
- No, I insist. This is for you.
- Okay, thank you.
- Good.
[unintelligible]
Oh, he's sandwiched with you.
How do you feel?
I feel good, very good.
♪ It's all about the game and how you play it.
All about- ♪
- Right now, we're taking a ride in this Ferrari,
uh, with my manager Pranav.
It's his Ferrari,
and it's completely normal,
you know, this is how we roll.
Every night, we ride around Dubai in this Ferrari.
Right?
- Left. Left and right, we roam everywhere.
Underrated talent with an underrated manager.
- Yes.
Oh my God!
- Flush!
- Wow!
- Hello, everybody.
Welcome to Simon Says.
This is a try not to laugh challenge.
I'm going to make Saiman laugh.
Today, I'll be reviewing my subreddit
because it is also low-effort content.
- Hi, I'm Aksh Baghla.
What's your name?
- Everybody knows my name, okay?
I don't have to introduce myself.
- Right! I'm sorry, sir!
- Yes.
- My bad.
- Good for you.
- Yes.
- Listen, lemme tell you a joke.
Have you heard the new song on TikTok?
- Which one?
Touch it, touch it, touch it, touch it,
Shwetabh and Gangwar.
It was funny. Laugh.
According to data, I'm a pervert.
♪ Shut up, and bend over ♪
Shwetabh and Gangwar
You're a real dumbass king of YouTube.
There is a reason why I'm visiting
this aquarium in Atlantis today.
I can relate to these fishes because
these fishes live in a tank,
and us youtubers live in a bubble.
So today, we're going to desert safari to
celebrate MythPat's 1 million subscribers.
Ten. Ten million.
Ten million.
- Ten million?
Ten million?
- Ten million.
100 lacs, 1 crore.
10 million subscribers.
How does it feel, Saiman,
when there are 3 overrated youtubers and
1 underrated youtuber in one car?
- How can you call yourself overrated?
- He's saying it because he is.
- 3 RATED youtubers and 1 underrated youtuber.
Cut this, please.
No, I'm not gonna cut it.
I'm going to edit this myself, with love.
Alright, last day in Dubai. I'm at
JBR beach right now, enjoying the sunset.
What now? I don't know what to say?
I forgot how to vlog. Okay?
Uh, if you liked the vlog,
good for you, otherwise...
see you in the next video.
When in doubt...
take a time lapse.
- Let's do it, brother.
What do you do for a living?
- I'm a youtuber.
- Alright.
- Yeah, I make videos.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, you can subscribe to
my channel, Saiman Says.
- Brother, let me ask you one thing.
Did you know the guy from India?
I think his name is AJ.
By the way, my name is AJ.
- AJ?
- AJ, yeah.
- What do you think about him, brother?
Like...I've watched a lot of his videos.
Is that really real, my brother, like,
whatever he does? Like whatever he's doing?
- [sigh] Yes, whatever he does
is 100% real, you know...
- Alright.
- ...it's a very authentic prank, what he does.
- He pranks his audience, not the girls,  you know?
- He calls the girls like "madam".
What madam, you know?
Uh, excuse me, ma'am.
- Like, whatever he did.
- Yeah.
- He tried to make fool of us. Yeah?
- He thinks we're stupid.
- We're fucking idiots,
but we'not fucking dickhead, my brother.
- Yeah, he thinks we are...
- We're fucking dickhead, but in reality
we're not fucking dickhead, my bro, you know?
He can think about himself. He's crazy
or he dickhead, or he's whatever, you know?
- Yeah.
- But not us, my brother.
- We're people, yeah?
Like, whatever he did...
I don't think he's doing that good. No?
- Yeah.
- I absolutely agree with you.
- Yes, you're my brother.
- People are people, my bro, yeah?