Good morning, sir.
I'm your new assistant..
Is the boss not here?
No matter what it is
my boss doesn't let others
take control of him.
Good morning, sir.
I never knew he could smile.
He does smile.
But the thing is..
He only smiles for his siblings
Sonu and Karthik.
Oh!
'Brother, please decide
a lehenga for me!'
'Okay. - Which one do you
like among these?'
'Or this..'
'Oh, my God!
Look at this one.'
'This?'
'Brother,
they're so beautiful.'
'There are too many of them.'
'Brother, please!'
'You have no idea about'
'how sentimental girls
are about the lehengas.'
'That's true.'
'That is always mentioned
in a girl's CV.'
'They can wear it
like professionals.'
'Why are you jealous?'
'You should buy
this simple one.'
'Brother, I'm buying a lehenga
for my engagement'
'and not to take my dog
on a walk.'
'Select again.'
'You could've bought
a new house for that money.'
'Yes, but I can't wear
a house, right?'
'Guys!'
'I have a meeting now.'
'I'll come home
and choose one.'
'Brother, that will too late.'
'I can't select anything
without selecting the lehenga.'
'Neither the earrings
nor the necklace.'
Excuse me, sir.
You have a meeting
with Mr. Mehta
in the cafe in 15 minutes.
What the heck!
Hi!
I have to deal
with a big problem.
Can you please give me
a lift?
Please help me.
I'm saying the truth.
You can see it on my face.
Look at me.
Look closer.
Hurry up!
Get in the car.
He has agreed.
Get in!
The driver.
Drive towards CP.
What are you looking at?
Let's go.
People don't get
their desired username
but you got your desired spouse
because of me!
Couldn't you have put
in a little effort?
Why were running
in the same place?
Thank God we found this guy.
'This guy..'
Your families would've
caught you otherwise!
Were families after you?
Joint families!
Two of them!
Aunts, brothers-in-law,
grandmothers, children..
Kids.. One of them followed
us on a tricycle.
Why were they following you?
I got them eloped and married.
And..
What..
What's up with him?
Out.
I said, get out!
Why, though?
I can't have a girl who gets
people eloped
and married
and hurts their families.
All right!
It's fine if you put me out.
Drop these two..
- They have to get out as well.
Why won't you listen to me..
You two, out.
Those people will come soon!
You don't understand..
- Shut up!
And you two..
What's wrong with you guys?
Family is everything!
But youngsters these days
don't understand family values.
Do you have any idea how bad
your families must be feeling
because of what you've done?
What's the girl's age?
Is she legally adult?
Oh, God!
Show me your face.
She doesn't look
it but she's legally adult.
Don't.
- I'm sorry
but it's an emergency.
What's up with him?
It's my effect.
I don't mess with hearts
but directly with minds.
Sir..
Your car?
It was stolen.
It's not a problem, sir!
We can do this!
We can get into this car..
And go..
Feed sweets to each other.
Ishki, thank you.
You took such a huge
risk for our sake..
Sir
you have to take risks for love.
Such a huge one..
You stole a man's car.
There's a limit to risks.
That's the point!
There are no limits
when love is concerned!
Love is the most valuable
thing in this world.
Even if life is lost
in its pursuit, it can be
considered a good bargain.
You've lucky
to have love.
Don't lose it.
Also
just because someone
will fast for your long life
doesn't mean you can neglect
taking medicines.
I've heard a lot about you.
The great Veer Malhotra.
I'd heard that
you're very punctual.
You're whole five minutes late.
You don't know
the value of time.
I'm sorry, sir.
Increase the price.
That's because the rate
has jumped
to Rs. 5 crores. - But we'd
a deal for Rs. 4 crores.
Verbal commitments
can always change.
Darn!
Excuse me, sir.
Why did you two come here?
Why?
Brother, it's high time
you finalise her dress.
Guys, I'm in a meeting!
- I'm sorry, Brother.
I can't shop till my dress
is finalised. Please pick one!
Look.
Hurry up!
This one.
- Thank you, Brother!
You're the best!
Why did you close your ears?
- This dress is loud.
Stop criticising!
- I can't help it.
Guys!
I'm extremely sorry, sir.
Actually, my sister
is getting engaged tomorrow.
And family is everything
to me.
What did you decide?
It is Rs. 5 crores
or consider the deal cancelled.
Not with you
I'm talking to your dad.
- He has gone old.
So, talk to me.
Either it is 5 crores
or get out of here.
Sir, family runs on two things.
Love and discipline.
When youngsters doesn't respect
their elders, problem arises.
This cheque is worth
Rs. 6 crores.
Twice, your son spoke
rudely with you in front of me.
Punish him like a father..
And this cheque is yours.
You..
Hey!
Stop provoking my haggard dad.
Stop picking up
topics on family.
Everybody knows
about your family.
Your mom ran away..
And you teach us
about family values.
The way your mom ran away,
your sister will follow suite.
I'm not able to do it.
You help me.
Not like that!
Give me the cotton.
Since childhood,
we'd to bear the embarrassment.
We'd to put up to taunts.
Why did mom take
that step, Brother?
No mother leaves
their children in the lurch.
How long will we have
to bear this insults?
Forever.
A mother leaves behind memories
for her children.
But our mother left
only shame and embarrassment.
No wonder when I hear her name..
I'm sorry.
I lost control.
I'm your elder brother.
My duty is to protect our family
and its values.
Not to create a scene.
I'm really sorry.
'I won't let any harm
come to my family.'
I need to return the car, too.
How do I find the address?
'Ahaan Veer Malhotra'..
The name doesn't suit him
at all.
Sonu, is it true that
your in-laws don't wear shorts?
Why? - Because they live
in a penthouse.
Brother, don't laugh
and encourage his jokes.
I've got such strange brothers.
One can even die for me
and the other won't even
pass me the TV remote.
W-Why can't you be like brother?
It's so tough for even him
to be himself.
Then how can I?
But I can be like you.
And talk all the time
about marriage! - So what?
Everyone has a dream.
So do I!
To marry a nice man
and settle down.
Don't steal my dream!
Do you want to marry
a nice man, too?
Very funny!
- I know.
I want to marry a working woman
and settle down.
When we have kids
we'll share responsibilities.
It's responsibilities.
Not some property
to share so excitedly!
I want no responsibilities
at all.
After marriage
there'll be no restrictions!
Full freedom!
Everyone here always tells me
'do it after marriage'.
Finally I'm getting married!
Oh, my!
Happily ever after!
Brother's life is good, too.
Even his dreams are decent
like U certified films.
Where his wife appears
and only cooks for him.
Very funny!
You're laughing because
you think..
Cooking food, home making..
- Is a petty thing.
But not for me.
It's important to me.
So I want a good homemaker.
- Why not a working woman?
I've no problems,
but I need a housewife.
Things are fine
when people are a couple
but when they form a family
the dynamics change.
And three things are needed
to run that family.
Money, love and morals.
Oh, no!
Not the morals again! - Yes.
Earning money is
the husband's duty.
Love is that of both
and morals, that of the wife.
Brother, I really wish
you were my laptop.
At least I could upgrade you!
Brother, it's 2021,
not 1921!
Everything has changed!
- Nothing has changed.
Things have changed on surface,
it's still the same inside.
Family, family values..
Husband handles worldly matters
and the wife, home.
And your opinion
won't change anything.
This is the grammar
of relationships.
My plan is simple.
I just want a girl
providing for whom
will be my priority
and my family and their respect
will be hers.
Hail the preacher!
- Hail the preacher!
I must warn you.
Both your expectations
about a working wife
and a homemaker
can be ruined by one thing.
What?
- Love!
Oh!
It sounds so comforting!
The 'v' sound in the end!
'Love'..
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Tell me something.
What if you both
fall in love with a girl
of a different type?
- No way.
I just need a good homemaker.
- And me, a working woman.
We won't fall for anyone else.
Right, Brother?
- Really!
I think you guys have not heard.
There's no control over love.
- Control.
That's what I said.
There's no control over love.
Did you see that?
I made you say it.
Did you hear that?
- Oh, nice!
Kids, where are you?
I knew that the three of you
would be here itself.
Is the beer cold?
People consider beer
as 'shikhanji' these days.
They open the bottle
the moment summer sets in.
It's very hot today, right?
Aunt.
No, I'm not in a mood.
- Okay.
I'll have it if you are
forcing me so much.
Kids.
Did your aunt come here?
Oh!
You guys are drinking beer.
God knows that I stay away
from all this.
I drank only once
on the day of my 'roka'.
It is Sonu's 'roka' tomorrow.
She'll be heartbroken
if I don't drink.
Come on, open one bottle.
Wait.
Give it to me.
Kids, where are you?
You guys are sitting here.
I..
Oh, wow!
Beer?
Come on, open one bottle for me.
It is Sonu's 'roka'.
I should drink one bottle.
Oh, wow!
Chilled beer.
It's fun to drink with the kids.
What's happening in this house?
Nobody will hide anywhere now.
What do you mean?
Who else is hiding?
It is our Sonu's 'roka'
tomorrow.
Let's celebrate together.
Come on, all of you say cheers.
Cheers!
The house will become empty
after Sonu leaves.
Oh, please, Aunt!
The IQ level of this house
will increase after she leaves.
The level of noise will reduce.
We'll get an extra room too.
I will be so happy
that I'll start crying
as I'm laughing.
I'll start crying.
You look ugly when you cry.
Yuck!
He doesn't look like Tom Cruise
when smiling either.
Let's save our tears
for the farewell ceremony.
We'll only celebrate today.
What?
- A girl wants to meet you.
Huh?
What girl?
One who's very special to you.
What nonsense!
She brought a letter.
She must be special.
I ever served her sweets.
Did she bring the letter
for Aahan?
Yes.
I wonder what's in the letter.
Grandma, it probably
says
'My sweet Aahan'
'I have no ambitions'.
'The idea of a job
makes me dizzy'.
'Making cauliflower parathas
for you in my dream'.
I'm absolutely sure
that the letter won't have
a single hug or a kiss.
Sonu!
Brother is too cultured.
Those come in the letters after
the marriage. - Guys, shut up!
Who is this girl?
You're that car thief!