Is this Bhabhi's conspiracy?
Does Bhabhi wants him to leave the channel?
Was Bhabhi always plotting?
Was this Bhabhi's plan?
Was this her conscious plan?
Yesterday, Gaurav Taneja aka Flying
Beast was arrested, by the Noida Police.
He was arrested on the basis of these
two sections visible on your screen.
Will discuss whether this
arrest was right or wrong.
What this tells us,
we'll talk about it and decode
whether the arrest was fine or not.
But before that, let's understand
a few things. What is Vlogging?
Show our life by holding camera?
Why does one do vlogging?
If something interesting
is happening in your life,
then you give a chance to
the people in your life to peek.
You must have seen that we are more
interested in the life of others than our own.
When we give this glimpse to others,
then it is a source of entertainment for them,
and for those bloggers, there is a
chance to get fame and create an influence.
a chance to create an influence.
Nowadays it also becomes
a huge career option.
Many times we also create such influence
which benefits socially, also do great things.
I will also talk about
those great things,
must watch this
video till the end.
Before this video, I asked all
of you in a community post that
what do you get to learn from vloggers?
Got interesting reactions.
I would highly recommend commenting
through this post and read the comments.
If you have any interesting
observation then you must also comment.
I would love to react
to this on my Instagram.
Earn money by telling the
personal matter outside.
How to show off your big house?
Tell me, I am poor.
Teach to speak 'Guys' loudly.
How to auction the privacy
of the house in public?
To go to jail.
Flying the dog by tying it to a balloon.
They teach that the car can be rented.
'Ghanta'.
Is it wrong to earn money by
vlogging like this from YouTube?
I don't think this is wrong.
So many people who are in various positions
they earn so much money
through corruption, through cheating,
earn a lot of money
through manipulation,
then a person by working hard,
Means that when you are a small
vlogger, you don't have a team
you edit yourself and big
vloggers also edit themselves.
So I don't think there is any mistake if you
are entertaining someone by working so hard.
The mistake is when you set the wrong
example in your vlog due to wrong influence
encouraging people
to do wrong actions.
It is wrong to show fake
lifestyle in the name of content.
Making people feel zealousy, and
being absolutely fake and overly sweet
showing so many good things
that I think it's not possible.
Sometimes people go
fake, I think he is wrong.
And making mistakes one after the other and
not learning anything from that mistake,
not acknowledging and admitting mistake
and not telling audience that I've made a
mistake, and making many mistakes in a row.
What's not wrong?
It is not wrong when your mistake
has happened for the first time,
or the situation becomes
such that that thing looks wrong.
It is not wrong when you do a lot of such
things which are not discussed in the media,
but when you make a mistake
or someone misguides you
and there are thousands of
discussions about that thing.
When you are socially aware, channel your
influence towards social initiatives too,
that is not wrong.
Teach people something
with your content.
Something similar
happened with Flying Beast.
Such an incident
has happened to him,
which must have happened for
the first time in his vlogging career.
So Ritu Bhabhi thought that I will
make Flying Beast's birthday in the metro.
She gave invitation to all 7 million
people to come to Sector 51 Noida.
Tomorrow is Gaurav's birthday.
And I have planned
such a wonderful surprise.
I have booked the entire metro for him.
Will make his birthday
there with all of you.
This is a surprise and don't
put any story by tagging him.
You all come and we'll have a lot of fun.
Tomorrow1:30 pm, Sector 51 Noida.
I'm sure all these 7 million
people are not only from Noida
but also from Delhi, Gurgaon, Ghaziabad,
Faridabad and may be from some other state also.
How will these people let such an
opportunity pass, that too on Saturday?
A crowd gathered there.
There the traffic stopped,
whether it was an ambulance, whether someone
had an emergency, going to office or school
whether someone was going for
any emergency, they all stopped there.
were restrained, which was
not intentional, unintentional.
but they were restrained and
that's why this section is applicable.
You must be aware about the Covid situation
for which this section is applicable,
but it has also been violeted.
Whether it happened
intentionally or unintentionally,
here Flying Beast is wrong, Ritu
Rathi is wrong or not, let's discuss.
Let's talk first, why
would she have done this?
The first reason that might
have come to your mind as well.
Is this Bhabhi's conspiracy?
-No!
Does Bhabhi wants him to leave the channel?
Was Bhabhi always plotting?
-No!
Was this Bhabhi's plan?
Was this her conscious plan?
No, if it was Ekta Kapoor's
serial then it would have happened
but obviously there's nothing like that.
I think Ritu Bhabhi did this because she
genuinely wanted to give back something.
or may be wanted to make
his 36th birthday memorable.
so she did that, out of pure
genuinity and innocent emotion.
But what I expect from Ritu
is being more mature because
obviously she's captain, she's educated,
she know's about law.
I hope she know. So, this is tricky!
And I'll judge this thing on
5 grounds in a little while.
But before that let's talk about what other
reasons can be that Ritu Bhabhi did this.
First, obviously she wanted
to make his birthday special.
I think she was misguided!
Obviously Ritu bhabhi
would have reached out,
to people, agencies, management
agencies that how we can do this.
May be that idea was a misguidance!
She must have been misguided
that this can be managed.
There should be something different.
You know, Gaurav and Ritu
never did any kind of controversies.
There are many vloggers who
get views by doing controversy.
I react to controversy
because it is my content.
because I want to give perspective,
what is right what is wrong,
who is manipulating
you and who is not.
But this is not the content
of Ritu and Gaurav.
There are many people whose content
is not like this, yet those people do.
But Gaurav never did that.
He has make this vlogging
channel purely on the basis of merit.
I don't think it was a publicity stunt.
The psychology of vloggers
is to do something different,
and to make it different, it happened!
And whoever has this misguidance,
we should pay attention to it.
I will talk about that too but the third
reason, that why she would have done this.
I don't think it was a publicity stunt.
Psychology of vloggers is to do something
different and make it big, it may be.
As a vlogger, psychology challenges you,
stuck on this particular number
of what to do something different,
stuck on this subscriber base
and now how to go ahead,
how to do something big and something new.
How should we return the
love back to the audience.
I think all this problem has
happened because of it.
Now let's talk whether he
should have been arrested or not.
I would like to discuss
this thing on five grounds.
First - Awareness.
Did they know about these sections?
Section 144, Covid situation.
I believe so.
Gaurav is IIT graduated
and both are captains.
Now Gaurav is also studying
Law, so I should believe.
There was awareness.
Now coming to the context.
Get carried away by emotions
She got carried away in emotions.
I'm making tea, after
that I'm going to get ready.
See you at 1:30. Bye!
Third - Intent!
Was it her intention that
people should suffer?
Was it their intention that we don't care
about law and order, as some people are saying.
I don't think so.
But, yes there intent was to do something big.
I'm 100% sure about it. Atleast,
from whatever perspective.
But to do something
big, that was their intent.
Fourth - Pattern.
Is it their pattern to do all this? No!
As we discussed, there was no pattern.
But there is one thing, even though
Gaurav and Ritu did not have a pattern,
but all our political parties do.
Whatever the situation was, they did it.
They've done it in much bigger numbers.
But if someone else does all
this and they are not punished,
then does it make you
right? I don't think so.
If someone else is making a mistake,
do you get a license to make a mistake?
I don't think so!
I don't think so.
So even on this basis I
wouldn't give them any point.
Even if their pattern is not
there, but there is a mistake.
Last but not he least is Responsibilty.
Was this a responsible act? No!
This was not a responsible act at
all.  Because if we talk about health,
talk about covid, talk about
safety, talk about law and order,
then it was absolutely
wrong and irresponsible act.
Hello!
Because with great powers,
comes great responsibility.
If this is the first mistake,
then it can be forgiven.
But this mistake has to be
acknowledged, has to be discussed,
so that other mistakes don't happen.
Because as part of my
content, I always talk about
where creator gone wrong, in our
'Where creator gone wrong series'.
So, thisb  time this creator has
gone wrong, specially Bhabhi.
Specially when you talk
about 241, Wrongful Restraint!
How many ambulances would be there,
how many people would be in emergency,
when those people are
upset then there is a mistake.
I think there were many such risks in
this case which should have been forsee.
Anyone who is misguiding,
Shouldn't have been agreed to him so soon.
But, whether Ritu Bhabhi and Flying
Beast should have been arrested or not,
then they were arrested, it was right,
but they got bail, that was also right.
But my question is how many more people
who should have been arrested in this.
This is the whole process of approval,
when Bhabhi booked a metro coach,
under whom does the metro come?
The approval which is given is given on
whose basis, whose approval is involved,
what is its escalation
process, when approval is given
then who interprets its repurcations.
Should the police be notified or not and by whom?
Should the agency be arrested?
Should any government official be
fined, on the one who gave the approval?
Is this the result of inefficiency?
Is this the result
of negligence?
Is this matter only the result of the negligence of
Ritu and Gaurav or of many other administrations?
Is our administration useless?
These are many questions
that need to be asked.
And it also has to be asked that what
happens when these political rallies happen?
But at the same point of time, I
don't want to give creators excuse
If it happens, we can
do it too. No, you can't.
If a person is doing wrong
things then you cannot.
If someone else is selling tobacco,
then it's fine, their
principles are different.
But it doesn't give you the
liense to do the same mistake.
And what is happening, it is
not necessary that it is right.
And accepting what has been happening, because
it is happening like this, is also wrong.
So, that's why we shouldn't accept
and just take this as an excuse.
The reason is simple, guys
There is collective irresponsibilty.
There should be a collective penalty,
on all those departments which are involved
in this, everyone should be punished.
Media shouldn't just focus on one person,
it should focus on entire process
and the chain of events  linked to that.
That would be my submission, guys!
If you want to support my work, then you can
buy this tshirt by visiting the given link
and become a brand ambassador of 'Ab Kuch
Nahi Chuppega'.
You can become a change agent. You can join this change community by visiting this link.
One more amazing
contest for all of you guys
I want to give this tshirt to
10 people with heavy discount,
our team will reach out the
first ten people who comment.
They've to update their
email ids on their channels.
So, that's an offer which
is valid only for today!
So, comment fast!
Let's see who will comment first.
If you like my work
then please support,
like, share this video
and give your feedback.
I will keep bringing such videos
because nothing will be hidden now.