Dear Brothers and Sisters click on Subscribe
Hello Friends.My name is Prash,
You are watching Angry Guruji
So, lets begin
*music*
So today we are going to talk about two great phones
Whose name are Hoppo and Viko Vajradanti
Good thing about these phones are there is no need to make separate video for both
Because they just have different names but do the same work
To F*ck us politely!
And they do this job with true earnest
U know what these two phones are of same company
BBK Electronics
They think we have written C on our head
In these phones u will get so many Features
First these phones have a selfi option
*applaud*
Secondly these phones have a front camera
Which takes pictures of you
*applaud*
Third, you yourself can take pictures of yours
That is a mind-blowing a*shole invention!
And their Selfi is just not your ordinary selfi
NO.......NO......NO......!!!!
Their Selfi's are Moonlight Selfi's
That means they have hired moon for giving light at salary of Rs.3000 p.m.
Do u know these phones have one more great Feature
These phones are Selfi Experts!! Ya Expert!
That means they have three experts sitting for us in the camera
Whenever you click on a expert advice option
Then these Experts will take your Picture
Have you seen this Feature in any phone?
And do u know who r these Experts?
Deepika,Ranbir and Alia Bhatt.
If u see their real life
U wont find Hoppo and Viko in their pockets,home or not even in their toilets
They just know to make people fools on TV
*indian badword*
*music*
Do u know in these phones u will get 4 GB RAM
Do u know how much is 4 GB?
Ur Phone will run  very very fast
As if u will keep the phone on the floor It could easily defeat Milkha Singh in running
In these phones u will also get Gorilla Glass
Do u know what is Gorilla Glass?
I will tell u.
Gorilla Glass is an ordinary glass,
On which Gorilla is asked to shit on that glass
And after washing that glass becomes Gorilla Glass
Do u know the speciality of this glass?
No Scratches will be found on these glass
In fact there will be a big crack which will again cost u 4-5 thousand rupees
Look, there r so many great features in this phone
Who would not like to buy?
U go to India's any corner or any shop,
For instance u will not get a Apple,Nokia or Samsung phone
But u will definately get Hoppo and Viko
Beacuse r Indian Government have announced these phones as National Phones!!
And I have also heard If any guy doesn't use Hoppo or Viko phone
His hair will be shaved of from above and below!!
*laughs*
And If u don't want this to happen buy a Hoppo or Viko phone
*indian phrase*
If you like this Review Hit Like
If ur new get subscribed
And If you r interested in watching such Reviews in future leave a Comment.
*outro music*