When Governor Scott visited Adilabad last time...
...he brought back a little girl with him.
That girl belongs to the Gond tribe, sir.
So what?
Do they have horns on their head?
Mother
They have a protector.
To capture the tiger,
We need a hunter.
There’s only one man who can do it, sir.
Your friendship is more valuable than this life, brother.
I’ll die with pride.
Don’t leave me here, brother.
I keep remembering mother.
For the crimes you’ve committed against the British Government.
I’m arresting you.
We shouldn’t be scared anymore.
We should surge forward!
Whoever comes in our way needs to be eliminated.
It’s very dangerous.
You’ll lose your life.
I’ll give it away happily.
The weapons will come on their own in search of their war.
Bheem,
How long do we fight these jackals?
Let’s hunt down the lion!