Hey friends today I have an awesome video
So today I have,whoo
Jio phone so today let's unbox it
let's see what are the box contents
How is this phone,How can you use it
and with this phone whatever you can do
if you buy this phone for 1500 for this JIO Phone
So hey guys,my name is Gaurav Chaudhary ,You are watching Technical Guruji
so let's get started
So guys this is the colorful box of the JIO Phone
and here you have peshwa bajirao
which tells you that you can enjoy movies
and TV on this phone
And here you get info about the Jio Cable
with which you can connect jio phone to your Television
here you have some technical specifications
Here you have highlights about jio services in this phone
You can see movies,TV get music in this little phone
when you open the box you can see the black jio phone
let us put it aside,you get some more accesories
you have some guides,you have a charger
with micro usb connector
with an output rate  of 5v and 700 mili amperes
we also have a big 2000 mAH battery
It is big because it gives your phone a lot of capacity
and you only have this much,what else can you expect from a 1500rs phone
getting a phone is a great thing
so lets boot the phone
first we have to insert the sim card
and then we will insert the battery
and along with the sim you can also insert a memory card upto 128 GB
So we will talk about the phone's physical overview while the phone is booting
you get a 2.4 inch QVGS screen
there is not gorilla glass but,
by the weight you can say that the durability
can also be compared with an Iphone
down you get a 1234567890 keypad
on the upper side of the phone you get a torchlight
on the back side you have a 2 megapixel camera along with a loud speaker
on the front side you have a 0.3 megapixel camera
below you get a micro usb connector
with a 3.5 mm audio jack
as I told you you can remove the back of the phone too
and that's it for the physical overview
when you boot the phone
it is written "powered by Kai OS"
it is a different type of OS based on
here you will get a feeling
of android at some heights
if you go to settings and all
because even if this phone is cheap as 1500
you get very good options
first of all you get many apps
[Jio apps] Jio TV,Jio cinema,Jio music,my Jio etc.
and you get the basic apps
which all the other phones have
EG. Calculator
wireless radio and unit converter
obviously calls and messaging
you also get some shortcuts
if you try pressing the D-pad
left,right,up and down
you can get into different apps
in setting you also get support for
wi-fi,bluetooth,NFC and GPS
only thing that is not there is wifi hotspot
we hope we'll get it in the next updates
you also get Jio money in this phone
you can also make video calls through this phone
you also get option for S.O.S
if you hold the no.5 button for a while
you can give a message to your favorite contacts
in fact you can also send your jio location
there are many things in this phone
there are many apps too
In fact
you can also browse websites
but it would be better if I don't talk much in this video
it would be much better if you use this phone yourself and
you explore your jio phone
my opinions:
we all know that no one provides these features at this value
and these 1500rs.
will get back to you when you
return the phone to Jio after 3 years
but the main problem is
about the availability because the demand is very much
so if you haven't booked it yet then book it right now
I think that this phone can turn the people of India
on your side of Internet
who played the snake game in Nokia 1100
but because of jio phone's live tv, movies
the can connect
to internet
so this is an awesome option
but no use for me
because there is no Jio network in Dubai
so one of you viewers is gonna get
you just have to comment what did you like about this phone
you also have to like and shower your love
and also share this video
and subscribe the channel if you want to show your love and also press the bell
if you wont no problem but if you will then I'll feel good
that's all for the video
I hope you liked the video
if you have any questions or suggestions about the jio phone
if you havent liked or shared then also like and share
and dont forget to subscribe the channel because
I bring videos like this EVERYDAY!!!!!
JAI HIND ,VANDE MAATRAM