Have food.
Bunty, stop!
Bunty, where are you going? Stop!
Bunty, don't run!
Who's that?
Don't you know
this jungle is dangerous?
Man-eater tiger wanders in this forest.
Who are you?
I haven't seen you here before.
I'm coming from far away,
I want to meet Maheshwar.
I see.
Did the tiger enter your village too?
A man-eater.
It took away all I had.
The tiger ate everything away.
Only Maheshwar can do something.
Come. This is my granddaughter.
Offer him water.
My child,
don't walk around here.
Get inside.
Two years ago, this child's parents
were mauled to death by a tiger.
Before the crack of dawn,
Maheshwar killed the tiger with his spear.
I have heard a lot
about wild hunter Maheshwar.
If whatever I heard is true,
then only Maheshwar can help me out.
Maheshwar will kill all the tigers.
Lord Krishnan killed Kans,
Lord Rama killed Ravana.
Maheshwar took incarnation
to destroy these man-eaters.
He was barely 9 years old
when he killed tiger for the first time.
Maheshwar.
Take.
Uncle, I have this with me.
Maheshwar's weapon is not a catapult,
but a spear.
Mom, look what uncle gave me.
Lord Maheshwar's spear.
- Alright.
Come on, have food.
You need to take food for father also.
My darling son.
Mom!
Father!
Mother...
Come on.
- Come on.
Hurry up.
Stop.
Eat, son. Don't cry.
Mahesh, stay with him.
You're stealing wood from the forest?
Hey!
Stop!
- Run!
Don't stop!
Hey, stop!
- Stop!
Stop! Else you will die!
- Don't look back.
I say stop!
He must've gone there. Come on.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Maheshwar...
Run.
Run away.
Save your little brother's life.
Run!
No!
Mahesh...
Eat something.
I will kill it.
I will kill the tiger.
"He is a fighter.
Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
Fasten it tightly.
What's going on?
What's the kid up to?
The tiger killed his father,
he wants revenge,
so, he has set up a trap.
The tiger that turns into a man-eater
never gets trapped.
If you want to kill it,
go to its den and drag it here,
that is the law of the forest.
Uncle!
Mahesh...
Mahesh, fast!
"He's a fighter."
"Everyone knows he's a fighter."
Ever since then,
he has not spared a single
man-eater tiger.
But Maheshwar is not here anymore.
The whole village is waiting for him.
But where did he go?
It's a big story.
A few days back,
Maheshwar's younger brother
Mani's friends had come to the village
to meet their uncle Balram.
How many more miles to go?
About 20-30 miles.
It's a wild elephant.
- Wild elephant?
Their menace will be there
for another 7-8 miles.
After that, we'll be free of elephants.
Then on, there are only tigers.
Man-eaters.
But if tiger comes in front,
there's no need to get scared at all.
- Why?
For it will kill us for sure.
Then why get scared?
Shut up and drive.
Don't scare the hell out of me.
It's too cold today.
This is your room.
Did you have dinner?
Or you need something to eat?
What's available?
- Dried fish chutney and rice.
You want to have?
Where is the bathroom?
- That one, there.
He is naming the dishes.
- There's lot of dust in the room.
Nobody comes here.
Dust the bedspread before you sleep,
you'll get rid of snakes and scorpions.
- Over here?
Yes.
Oh, my God! Ghost! Save me!
What's wrong?
- Shiva, there's ghost in the bathroom.
Come on.
- Don't go there.
It looks scary, I saw it myself.
That may be Sashi.
- Does Sashi lives with the ghost?
It's not ghost,
it's Sashi, he lives in this village.
He's a peeping tom.
Don't be scared.
Don't talk nonsense.
I am not attracted to men.
Are there no ladies?
- No.
Very waste of time.
Well, don't repeat this.
Let's go.
Let's introduce ourselves to each other.
I'm Sashi, I'm a hunter.
You wouldn't have heard about me.
The animals in the forest
are scared of me.
Come, we shall sit and discuss.
Don't be frightened.
I don't fire at humans.
Let me know if you need something.
We have brought everything.
- Very good. Then get it.
Security, get three tumblers and water.
Did you see?
The villagers respect me a lot.
Oh, God! Liquor!
Everyone wants to drink for free.
Sashi, do you know Balram?
So, you're here to buy firecrackers
to drive the wild boars?
He is very close to me.
Balram's crackers are really good.
If you set fire to 10,
at least one will burst for sure.
Will I be able to meet him now?
- No. No point seeing him today.
He will be drunk now,
meet him in the morning.
This is an international hotel
of our great village.
Tigers don't visit this place,
hence people come here to eat food.
Hey, get going.
You're here again
to have food for free.
Don't be scared.
Mr. Ramu, three cups of tea.
One bit strong, like me.
Sashi, who are they?
My friends from the town.
- I see.
Ramkali, I have an advice for you.
If you've quarreled with your husband,
you can have me.
- Shut up!
Rascal!
- I just hate Indians.
He is just disgusting.
Sashi.
- Yes.
I think you'll be beaten up
by the women of the village someday.
The women are scared
to also take a shower because of him.
He is such a shameless man.
- Just ignore him.
Why is the village head
coming here with the villagers?
What's wrong, sir?
What brings you here?
Tiger entered our shanty last night.
Then?
- It took away Chinu's daughter Chameli.
We want to see Maheshwar.
Sir, it's not Maheshwar's duty.
The one who has to do this job
is eating free breakfast inside.
We can't do anything unless
we receive orders from the government.
As if you will turn down the mountains
if you receive orders.
I cannot do anything alone, Sashi.
I can't fight with the man-eaters
with a mere baton.
I have three daughters,
and I am retiring in six months.
I don't wish to die.
And everyone knows that Maheshwar has
more experience than the forest officials.
Only Maheshwar can trap the tiger.
Lord, everything lies in Your hands now.
Help us get rid of the man-eater.
What will God do?
It's the job of the government.
The government will do nothing.
Only Maheshwar can save us.
Only he'll be able to do something.
He had rescued us
from the tiger earlier too.
Only Maheshwar can rescue us
from the man-eaters.
Who is Maheshwar?
Do you want to know who Maheshwar is?
Yes.
- He is the celebrity of the jungle.
He's the nephew of Balram.
If the tiger enters the village,
it becomes Maheshwar's prey.
This is Balram's work shop.
These four boys are his sons.
It's a happy family.
My child, where is your father?
He must be in the toddy shop,
go check there.
Let's go. They are able children.
Balram's mother-in-law Bhavani
owns this work shop.
Balram used to buy
raw materials from Bhavani,
the loan amount was so much that
she got her daughter married to Balram.
and compensated those debts for dowry.
Ms. Bhavani.
She has great concerns for me.
- Shut up!
To heck with you.
Where is your son-in-law?
He must be in the work shop.
- Only your grandsons are there.
He's not in the work shop?
- No.
Oh, my God!
Then, he must be at home.
I got to rush to his house.
Step aside.
He won't stop begetting children.
Why did she run screaming?
- I told you it's a happy family.
Balram begot children
just like hen lays eggs.
Geeta, have you lost your mind?
Quickly open the door!
I know he's inside.
Nobody would come out if you scream.
Let me peep in and
see what's happening inside.
There is a hole on the window
in the back side.
Shut up!
Don't you hear me?
I've been calling out!
She's at it all the time.
- I will... Call him out.
Why do you pay attention to her?
Listen, one of the legs
of the cot is broken,
get it fixed by the carpenter.
Make it quick, I can't wait. Understand?
- Shut up!
Oh, my God!
Perhaps I've to look after one more baby.
What's the problem in that?
What else you have to do?
- I said shut up! Idiot!
It is so much fun to see
the old woman get annoyed.
It's a daily routine.
Aren't you satisfied seeing it?
Sashi, who are they?
My friends from town,
they're here to meet you.
Actually, we are Mani's friends.
Really? Please come.
- Come.
My name is Badrinath,
people call me Badri.
And I'm Shiva.
We need a favour.
Anything important?
Mani has gone
to a faraway place to study,
but I've never even
stepped out of this village.
Balram, it's Mani.
Mani.
- Uncle.
How are you?
- What's going on? Give my phone.
Wait a minute, please.
- Mani,
your friends are here.
I only sent them there.
The guy with dark complexion
is my classmate.
The guy with dark complexion?
Why have you sent him to me?
They need a favour.
Only you can help them, Uncle.
How can I help them?
There is an herbal medicine factory
called Giriraj Pharmacy.
And Shiva's Father,
Dada Giriraj is the owner of the factory.
Dada Giriraj, it's a strange name.
With the help of a scientist,
they've discovered medicine
to prevent cancer.
Oh.
The medicine is good and effective,
but to mix the ingredients together
they need marijuana.
Marijuana?
- Uncle, talk softly.
If this medicine works out,
it will be sold everywhere.
I will also get a good job
in that factory.
Dada Giriraj also promised me.
I can do anything for Mani's happiness.
And let me tell you something.
Mani's happiness
is Mahesh's happiness.
And Mahesh's happiness
is my happiness.
The village head often tells me that
the treasure of medicines
lies in this forest.
But it's amazing that marijuana
is used for prevention of cancer.
Watch out, it's slippery.
Watch out. Come.
We walked for 2 hours
in this dense forest,
but we still haven't reached.
How much long will it take?
- Still a long way to go.
Keep walking.
What a pleasant surprise!
Who are they?
- They are my friends.
I want to buy stuff from Rambo.
You know he doesn't
deal with strangers.
I know,
but I told you they are my friends.
Alright, I will talk to him,
and that's because they are your friends.
I will talk to him right away.
Normally I won't have
any dealings with India.
It's risky.
Most of my business is from Singapore,
then to Europe.
My assistant requested me,
so I'm talking to you,
but the stuff will be delivered
to you only for once.
Okay.
- And it will take two weeks.
Two weeks?
- Plants are in the harvesting stage,
they only need to be cut and dried.
The stuff will be delivered
to you in the village.
Then, it's your risk.
Walk fast, we need to move
out of this forest before dusk.
It will take the same amount of time
to get back to the village.
What's wrong?
It's flooded here.
We will have to take the other route.
- Is it?
Come quickly.
Come on.
- Come on.
Why do you look worried?
A man-eater has been wandering
in the route we've taken.
It has killed four people till now.
By saying this,
I didn't want to scare you.
Walk fast.
Mahesh is not to be seen
past couple of days.
Had he accompanied us,
things would've been different.
By the way, there will be
many tigers in the forest.
How'd Maheshwar know
as to which tiger needs to be killed?
You don't have much knowledge
about the forest.
Every tiger has its own territory.
And a tiger will not enter
into another tiger's territory.
Come on.
- Give me your hand.
Quick.
It's not going to be easy.
There is no other way
to get to the village.
We'll have to get out
of the forest before dusk.
Understand?
- Come on.
Come on.
Balram.
- Move back.
Run!
- Balram!
My God!
It's coming after us!
- Run!
Stop!
- Badri!
Oh, my God!
You don't have to fear anymore,
Maheshwar is here.
"He is a fighter.
Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
"He is a fighter.
Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
What's wrong?
Why do you look upset?
I got news from the village.
You killed a tiger.
You promised me, didn't you?
What rubbish are you talking?
- I am not talking rubbish.
You killed the tiger, didn't you?
tiger? Which tiger?
Stop pretending.
The punishment for killing tiger
is imprisonment.
Nothing of that sort. Come on.
Let go. Don't coax me.
Where were you for the last two days?
I was in the fields. I told you, didn't I?
- Father!
Yes.
Chakki!
I know where you had been.
If the forest officials interrogate you,
you will see my true colour.
I know what your true colour is.
Show me your true colour for once,
Chakki will get a company.
You're so shameless.
Dad, is mother really like a lioness?
- Yes.
I really so scared of your mother.
Behalf yourself.
- My father is as brave as a lion.
Go inside.
Come, sir.
Chakki, Babita is here.
Go play with her.
What brings you here?
Villagers are having sleepless nights.
The tiger has killed
four people till now.
You must come for our protection.
We have nobody else.
Don't worry.
The tiger will never
enter our village hereafter,
it won't kill anyone.
It's my promise.
Even if the tiger comes,
only you can rescue us.
You're our belief.
God has made you our messiah.
Come on, sir. You go.
When I am here,
no tiger will enter our village.
Be rest assured.
Did you tell him you won't
let the tiger enter the village?
That's right.
I was just giving him hope.
I know what you will do. Enough is enough.
Come on, Chakki.
Your father doesn't care about us.
Let go.
- Maina, I am hungry, stop quarreling.
Have you ever thought about us?
You're only concerned about the villagers.
You will even sacrifice your life for them.
Have you ever realized
what'd happen to us if you die? - Maina...
Darn it.
Shiva, look there.
It looks like a city car.
You're right.
It's Mr. Sharma's car.
Come on.
- You recognize the car.
Hey.
She's Mr. Sharma's wife. Hide.
She belongs to our hometown.
She's Julie,
the only daughter of the landlord.
She married a person in our hometown.
She lives nearby. - Is it?
Then, let me warn you.
I once ogled at her accidentally,
her father battered me to pulp.
Just for ogling?
- Yes, I saw her bathing.
Oh, my God.
- Turn around.
Driver, pull over.
Driver, can't you hear?
Pull over.
- Okay, sir.
Take.
Chakki.
- Yes.
I have brought chocolate for you.
Sir, tell me something.
Why does ma'am meet that little girl?
Who is she?
I've no idea.
- Ma'am is your wife.
Being her husband,
why don't you ask her?
I could never muster courage
to ask her.
Just ignore it.
Where is your father?
He has gone out,
he'll be back only at night.
Tell your father I was here.
- Who are you talking to, Chakki?
Brother!
- Mani!
How was your exam?
- Have I ever failed in exams?
And you will never fail.
Come. You must be hungry.
- I was famished, I had eggs.
How many eggs did you have?
- Two eggs.
Only two eggs?
Let's have lunch together. Hop on.
Oh. Brother, you still serve the villagers.
Mani, they are not just villagers,
they are our family.
If tiger enters the village,
they need you,
they need you for everything.
Amid this, do you find time
for your personal affairs?
Mother passed away
soon after she birthed you.
Father also died
trying to rescue us from the tiger.
Do you know because of whom
you and I are successful?
It's because of the villagers.
My service to them is no match
to what they did for us.
Okay.
Tell me something, Mani.
Your friends are staying
in the guesthouse here.
They don't appear to be good.
They are really good, Brother.
They are Dada Giriraj's boys.
Dada Giriraj is a bigwig in Mangalpur.
His company is conducting
an experiment in medical.
If the experiment is successful,
I will also prosper.
He has promised to give me job.
Is that so?
- Yes.
In that case, I will help him too.
Let's go meet them.
Who's that?
It's my nephew, Maheshwar.
Oh, my God! tiger!
Sir,
you appear like a tiger to me.
You're absolutely right.
That's Shiva.
- Mani told me about you.
Maheshwar, sit.
- I am fine.
Hi.
- Mani?
When did you come?
- Just now.
Come, nephew.
- Uncle!
How are you?
Get tumbler for Maheshwar quickly.
- Wait.
That's imported liquor.
I don't like imported liquor.
I have mine in the lorry.
I will go get it.
- Come on, Mahesh.
I liked his style very much.
What do you think, Shiva?
Mahesh is still childish.
He can also sacrifice
his life for a friend,
but he doesn't
spare those who betray him.
Never.
Mahesh, you will never change.
You prefer to drink only toddy.
Have a drink.
- No.
No one would find out.
Come on.
- What is that?
He was...
What's going on?
I was telling Mani to have a drink.
- I will kill you.
He is still so young.
Mani won't drink liquor.
He won't smoke cigarette too.
He will drink only tea.
Mani, take the lorry and go.
Deliver the stuffs to the people.
- Okay.
And stay out of my
mother-in-law's sight.
What will you tell my wife about me?
- I don't know.
Tell her you didn't meet me
nor did I drink liquor.
Other than Mahesh,
only one person can drive his lorry
and that's Mani.
Uncle, you know I was very young
when I purchased the lorry.
Mani and the lorry are my children.
They are like my life.
You know something?
Mani has been offered a job.
- Yes, he told me.
Uncle, I never thought our village
would contribute in fighting
a dangerous disease like cancer.
When the product
is launched in the market,
all the credit will go to Mani.
He will be the marketing manager
of Giriraj Pharmacy.
Thank you very much.
I'm living only for him.
Without him, my life is meaningless.
What are you saying.
We just need your support.
Sure.
- I present you deer meat.
What? What did you say?
It's mutton.
Deer meat?
- No, it's kid meat.
What?
- Kid meat.
Did you kill deer?
- How's it possible?
It's a crime. It's mixed mutton,
just like mixed vegetables.
He thinks I am a fool.
I know the difference between
deer meat and mutton.
It took me lot of effort
to catch the deer,
taste the meat, please.
Get going.
- Get going.
The doll starts dancing
when you press this button.
What's wrong, Sister-in-law?
Why are you silent?
Nothing!
Brother neither went to guest house,
nor touched drinks!
Even you're lying to me.
Your brother instructed you, right?
Let he return,
I won't let him inside the house.
Careful. I can't assure you
that you can stay in my house.
Still, there's nothing wrong to try.
It's possible Maina might agree.
Mani, had dinner?
- Yes. - Good boy!
Where is Maina?
- She's inside.
You sleep.
Uncle, you also sleep.
Where is Chakki?
I already finished my dinner!
Didn't you have?
Maina.
Maina,
why are you silent?
Vow of silence?
You're so drunk that you're swaying,
what should I talk?
I am standing straight.
Watch there! It is uncle
who is walking on four legs!
Look at him.
- It's done.
It is so mischievous.
It came this side. I'll roll it again.
Come on. Get straight.
Are you missing me?
Wait.
Now it is okay.
Where are you going? Come on.
Where are you going?
- I will thrash you.
Dad, I want to give you chocolates.
- My child.
Give all those chocolates
to your father.
Which chocolate?
Lovely chocolates!
Who gave this? Your Uncle?
No, ma'am gave this.
Which ma'am?
- The lady who came in a car.
What?
Why are you pretending to
spit it before me?
You meet her stealthily.
You still have a chance
to go stay with her.
We both will live our life.
I didn't even speak to her.
Why are you saying so?
Oh, do you wish to talk to her?
Then, go and talk to her.
She must be anxiously
waiting for you.
Julie ma'am asked me to inform
you that she'll come to meet you.
You're my darling daughter, right?
Please don't add fuel to fire.
She could go in the car,
what was the need for her
to take a walk from here?
She will pass by our house.
I know that
she wants to meet you.
What are you saying?
I am not blind.
I was mad to marry you.
What is going on here? What is
the problem? - Julie ma'am.
Julie ma'am?
Why are you interfering?
Dare you mention her name.
Go to bed.
Why are you still awake?
Who is Julie?
- What do I tell you?
She's a nuisance.
It happened 7-8 years ago.
You were pursuing your studies
in the city that time.
During that time,
I had fallen in love with her.
'How are you?'
'Why are you teasing her?'
'If you love her so much
why don't you ask her
for marriage? Don't you have guts?'
'I do have courage.'
'I become feeble on seeing her!
- Shut up.'
'Stop the lorry.'
'Get down. Get down I say.
- What, Uncle?'
'Go and propose to her.'
'What do I ask her?'
'Ask her if she'll marry you.'
'I will ask her tomorrow.'
'No! Ask right away.'
'What's the hurry.
- Shall I kick you? Go.'
'Uncle...
- You came back?'
'I might goof up in haste.'
'I'll ask her after 2-3 days.
- I will thrash you. Go.'
'What is it?
- Nothing.'
'Then, move from the way.'
'He blocked the way.'
'Go.'
'Listen, Maina.'
'Don't be alone.
- What?'
'It will be better if you get married.'
'Marry whom?
- Anyone.'
'Oh.'
'You quit driver job and took
over marriage broker job?'
'No!
- Move aside! You coward.'
'What did you tell him?
- Go and ask him.'
'What happened?
Did she agree? - Yes.'
'Did you ask her?
- Yes.'
'What did she say?'
'She said I was a coward.'
'What? Arrogant woman.'
'Hey, my nephew.'
'You're not a coward.
- Uncle.'
Hold it properly.
Come on, put it here.
Pull it.
Enough.
- Pull it.
Hey.
- Pull it!
Come on, put force.
Yes, it's coming.
Let it go.
Where are you lost?
Forgive me.
Come on, pull it.
Very good.
- Listen, Nephew.
I think something is fishy.
What happened?
Did you have a flat tyre?
Yes, there's a flat tyre.
- Where?
Someone's heart has gone flat.
- What do you mean?
Look there..
- Where?
Look there.
Did you see?
Is she watching me?
- Yes.
She's been staring at you constantly.
You don't get such opportunities.
She's boss's only daughter.
Utilize this opportunity.
You'll hit jackpot.
You know the rest.
Why are you showing attitude?
Uncle, I like that slim girl.
Who?
- The one who's coming from there.
She?
Get me some water.
Can I get some water?
Stand straight.
You can never become rich.
You could get her easily,
but you want this girl.
Uncle.
- What is it?
She's getting water for me.
Take bath.
Maina, give it to me.
I will give to him.
Fatso interrupted.
- You still stand a chance.
You'll become the owner
of this estate.
You're the hero and messiah
of the villagers, right?
Nothing as such.
He's not thirsty for water,
but something else.
I want to talk to you in person.
Can you meet me in the evening?
Nephew, she is crazy about you?
Did you meet Julie?
Mani, are you mad?
- Brother...
Hey!
What happened?
I thought you were coming to hit me.
I was asleep.
- My Kanchan.
Let that old woman leave,
I will come later.
He's lamenting in sleep.
Are you still angry?
It's because of Julie
I lose my cool.
I don't have anyone
other than you in the world.
The tiger is here!
Where is the tiger?
That was not tiger, but Maina!
Uncle, you go back to sleep.
There's still time. Sleep.
Maina.
Don't touch me. Go to your Julie.
- Why?
What happened?
Why are you crying?
My doll broke.
You shouldn't cry for
such petty matter.
Come, Nephew. - Uncle, we've been
booked for two weeks now.
You must also come.
We have to go far.
- We'll go.
Greetings.
- How are you?
The stuff will reach in 2 days.
Stuff?
- Yes, our medicine.
Marijuana for preparing medicine.
Yes.
Only you can help
to take it out of the forest.
I am going out for two weeks.
We won't be able to
leave from here without you.
It'll be very helpful for Mani.
Please don't go.
- Maheshwar,
I went home looking for you.
There is an issue!
Forest officials recovered dead
tiger in Dhanakpur.
When investigated,
they found out that
humans have killed it.
That is not the issue now.
New ranger has taken up charge
for the continuance enquiry.
Our RK.
He says he's sure that
you'd have killed the tiger.
Mahesh, he will arrest you.
Go and hide in the forest.
Ranger must have
not forgotten the past.
If he takes this as a chance,
then things will go haywire. Go.
Who will do our work?
Are you mad?
Why are you still standing here?
Leave.
Come on.
Come, I say.
If Mahesh gets into the forest,
even God can't find him out.
- Who is RK?
What problem does
Mahesh have from him?
That happened 7-8 years ago.
During that time, a tiger entered
in the neighboring village
and it had taken away
4-5 people and 2-3 children.
Mahesh entered the forest
to kill the tiger.
Even the government had passed
orders to kill the tiger.
At that time, the ranger came there.
If someone tastes
wild meat and forest women,
then he will never leave the forest.
Sir, please forget that Maina.
She is an orphan poor girl.
She is not your daughter, is she?
Even otherwise, it wouldn't
have made any difference.
I don't compromise in such things.
She has been slipping away
from my hands since a year.
Today, I will fulfill my desire.
What happened? Where is Maina?
We chased her for a long distance.
I don't know where she disappeared.
Where did she go?
- She would've gone inside the forest.
We tried to find her,
but couldn't get her.
Stop!
Where are you running?
Why did you jump in the water?
I have something important to tell you.
- Here in the forest?
Even if you slap me here, nobody
will see. - What do you want to say?
I wish to marry you.
In this forest?
No, not in this forest,
but in a temple.
But I need your acceptance here.
Don't you have any other business?
First, get me out of this place,
I'll think about it later.
You give your consent for marriage.
That will not happen.
- We'll stay here then.
Until you don't agree,
we won't leave the forest.
Oh, God, I've heard
that there are big crocodiles
in the river. What if they eat us up?
It's better to get eaten up by a
crocodile rather marrying you?
No.
Stop talking and get me out from here.
Give me your consent for marriage.
You'll find many girls,
then why are you after me?
What?
- Don't pretend.
All the girls in the village
chant your name.
What? I didn't get you.
- Really?
If you have to marry me, you won't
ogle at any girl or I'll kill you.
Will you marry me?
Shall I carry you?
It's too slippery here.
What if you fall? - I'm walking on
these rocks since childhood.
Fine, go.
Sir, she is my would be wife, Maina.
I'm going to marry her.
If you dare to
ogle at her again,
I won't spare you.
I'll pierce your chest
with my spear.
Ranger got transferred after few days.
We thought all problems had gone.
Now, he is back again...
Maina... Wild Maina!
Where is your husband?
I don't know.
He is not here.
If you say so,
will I believe you?
Do you think I am a fool?
It's not possible that a wife doesn't
know about husband's whereabouts.
Sir, please leave her.
- Uncle.
Ask me what you want to know.
I will ask her.
You do your work.
Move away!
Uncle.
I want to interrogate you.
- Sir, let her go.
Talk to me.
Although a mother of one,
you still look young.
Mother!
Sir, no.
Sister-in-law!
Where will you run to?
"He is a fighter."
"Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
Hey!
Maheshwar is a tiger.
He does not hide!
He just attacks!
"He is a fighter."
"Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
"He is a fighter."
"Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
This is the final warning for you.
If you step into this side
of the bridge,
I will sever those legs.
Get away!
"He is a fighter."
"Everyone knows it."
Only the head of the village can treat
those thrashed by Maheshwar.
Or he will never walk again.
Shut up.
You're lucky to be alive.
Maheshwar doesn't spare
the one who lays
his hands on his wife alive.
Will you shut up?
My wife is inside, she will hear you.
Oh, my God. Dear.
What happened, Vandana?
Someone is peeping into the bathroom.
That must be Sashi.
Don't watch! Go and catch him!
Don't catch me, sir.
I couldn't see anything,
she started screaming unnecessarily.
- Stop!
Stop!
Are you blind?
- I was here to clean their bathroom.
I slipped,
I am going to take a shower.
Hey...
- Catch him!
Hey, stop!
I am I.P. Zechariah ACP.
I got the information.
Thought I'd meet you in the morning.
I heard you had an accident,
hence I am here in person.
It doesn't look like a minor accident.
It's an attack of a tiger.
Don't worry. I know everything.
I also here to hunt a tiger.
And you will help me hunt it.
What is your name?
- Diwakar Sharma.
Then, you leave and take him along.
I got something personal
to discuss with Ranger.
Okay?
Don't take this lightly, Maheshwar.
Tell me something.
Has any police officer came here
looking for you?
You will land in trouble.
- But what wrong did Maheshwar do?
You've no idea
how serious the issue is.
It's a big crime to kill a tiger.
It is a non-bailable case.
Any evidences against me
for killing the tiger?
Maheshwar, don't be so innocent.
It's RK who is writing the FIR.
He doesn't need evidence nor witness.
He will produce the FIR in the court
and become the self-witness.
This will be sufficient for the court.
You are in deep trouble now.
Diwakar sir is right, Mahesh.
It's better to move away from here.
What for?
I never kill the tiger
after it enters the forest.
Everyone knows that.
I have killed the tigers
that troubled the villagers.
They had become man-eaters.
No police case
if tiger kills the people,
but if I kill the tiger,
then it is a case?
I can even be hanged to death?
Why should my family and I
move to the city fearing like ranger?
Never.
Quick. Place them properly.
Also cover them well.
Why are you loading the stuff?
- What do you mean?
Brother is not totally unaware of it.
We were unaware of it too.
We didn't find time to inform.
- And your brother promised to help us.
I thought it'll be done.
- I agree, brother said he will help,
but now, the situation is different.
Brother won't go anywhere
leaving his family.
I will talk to him.
He will arrange you another vehicle.
Okay. But let the stuff
remain in this vehicle.
It's also your responsibility.
We're doing this for you.
Don't forget that.
What is it?
- Come with me.
Tell me.
- Rambo's aide Gopi has been arrested.
Rambo escaped,
but Gopi was aware of our stuff.
What shall we do now?
- Move the stuff from this area quickly.
Only Maheshwar can do it.
Forest officials and policemen
will reach here anytime.
I'm also going to escape
into the jungle.
I'd to pass on the information,
do something.
How's it possible? Mani said his brother
won't go anywhere leaving his family.
I've no idea about that.
But now, only Maheshwar
will be able to help you.
We enquired well.
Ranger got admitted in the hospital.
Attempt to murder case
has been filed against you.
And another case too,
for killing the tiger.
We can get out of here,
but we don't want to go
leaving you in this state.
We can't do that.
If the police arrests you,
you can never be bailed out.
You and your family come with us.
Once you get out of this place,
you'll be safe from the police.
You just need to get out of here.
Nobody would be able to
lay hands on you, it's a promise.
Think about it. If police arrests you,
we will be ruined.
Mahesh, there's no much time,
get going.
I will handle things here.
Take your family and leave at once.
Sir, quick.
Police will reach here any moment.
- It's impossible.
I won't let anyone cross the bridge.
Mahesh, leave at once.
Come on, leave.
I have never left my place
fearing the police or anybody.
But if you people feel this is right,
I will go.
Come fast.
Come. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Balram, save me.
What happened?
- Police is coming to nab me.
What for? - They are offended,
because I saw the ranger's wife bathe.
Come on.
Get to Mahesh's lorry fast.
Mahesh...
I'm also coming.
- Quick.
You're quite punctual.
Stop.
It's them, right?
- Yes, sir.
They are trying to escape
through the jungle.
I know the other route,
if we take that, we can nab them.
Then, come on. Don't waste the time.
Hurry up. - Yes, sir.
There's the lorry.
- Yes, sir.
Faster...
Maheshwar...
Speed up, don't let them get to us.
Speed up.
- Yes, sir.
They are after us
and there's marijuana in the lorry.
We must cross this forest, somehow.
There will be no danger,
we will reach my father's territory.
No one can dare touch you there.
It's my promise to you.
Be careful. Stop.
Follow them. Come on. Hurry up.
- Quick.
Stop. Take reverse.
Take reverse. Quick.
Take reverse, quick.
- Quick.
Since then, Maheshwar and
his family has been staying
in the protection of
Dada Giriraj in Mangalpur.
And Dada Giriraj told Maheshwar
that he would handle all his cases.
Since it's a promise,
he must've kept up his word.
You may go now.
We will try to help you.
- Okay.
Listen. I forgot to ask.
What is your name?
Dada...
Dada Giriraj.
We've come so far
and not a single policeman
dared to chase us.
I couldn't have thought of
the idea by sir even in my dream.
You're amazing, sir.
You're intelligent too.
I hope Sashi is safe
at the back of the lorry.
It's a sunny day,
at least get me cold drink.
This is too much.
- Actually...
Manager, you should've
told him in detail.
You've borrowed money from me,
so you must repay it.
I waited because you were
in financial crunch.
But now, you have got money
and the entire city is aware of it.
If Mr. Kader has asked
for his money back, what's wrong in it?
Mr. Jumman, you broke the partnership
and you also want back the money.
The business has certain principles.
Dada will repay the money
only when he wants.
You need to wait.
In that case,
then let me tell you something.
You'll pay a huge price
if you betray Mr. Kader.
You know the fate of those
who betray him.
I hate those who talk loudly.
I was the king and
will be one forever.
Tell Kader to recover the money from me
if he has the guts.
Mr. Jumman, get going.
Please come.
Daddy, this is Maheshwar.
Where's the stuff?
- It's in the lorry.
He has some problems in his hometown.
Hence he moved here with his family.
Dad...
Please don't mind.
That's daddy's nature.
Manager, they will stay in the outhouse,
please do the needful.
Did you hear that?
Listen, unlock the house
and do the needful.
This is your new house,
you will be staying here.
This?
- Yes.
This house?
No, I don't want this.
A small room will do.
Come on, sir.
As you've come from a small place,
you feel so.
You'll get used to it soon.
Untie me.
Are you still alive?
- A little bit of delay, I would've died.
Come on, get down.
This is really a deceit.
It's your punishment.
- But why?
This is what I do to those who get
on my lorry without my permission.
I need to pee. Where is the toilet?
What can I do?
- Where can I pee?
Inside the house.
Inside the house?
- There's toilet inside the house.
I'm used to pee only in the forest.
- Hey...
In the city,
rain also pours inside the houses.
Must be the shower.
I don't know.
- People in the city are strange.
Forget that.
Make a drink for me quickly.
Mani, already your brother
has begun to jabber.
Don't give him anymore.
- You're right.
Your wife is absolutely right.
Too much alcohol
is not good for health.
Give me some.
- Don't touch.
Or else I will chop your hands.
Mani, I don't know how to cook in gas.
Arrange some firewood outside,
I want cook food.
There's no firewood here,
I shall light the stove for you.
That's alright.
- Father...
Come here.
What's it?
- I will tell you, come here.
Your daughter is calling you, go.
I'll kill you.
- I will only smell it.
I don't mind getting thrashed by him.
What is it, Chakki?
Dad look, the mattress is so soft.
Wow!
Maina...
- Mom...
I guess you're too drunk.
Why are you screaming?
- Come on.
Come to me.
You will never reform.
- Hey...
Let go.
- Come.
Get away.
I didn't do anything.
- Come.
- Come. Leave her.
Let go.
- Why are you getting angry?
Go away.
- Dad...
Come fast.
- Excuse me.
Even I want to sleep.
What?
- I'm tired, I want to sleep.
You're going to sleep beside
your wife on mat. - What did you say?
Believe me, even my ancestors
wouldn't have slept
on such soft mattress.
Their souls will rest in peace
if I sleep on it once
and my upcoming generations
will be blessed.
I will slap you.
I will sleep here, go away from here.
My ancestors will bless you.
- Out!
What are you doing?
- Your brother is so mean.
Drive him away.
I won't spare you if you came back.
Brother...
- Yes.
If you drive him away,
he will expose us before the police.
Oh! I didn't realize that.
Don't go. Wait. You...
Allow me to stay until morning,
I'll go away in a couple of days.
Alright, I will go away
the day after tomorrow.
Will you behave well?
- I'm from an educated family.
In that case, you can stay here.
But if you don't behave well,
I won't spare you.
I will...
Hereafter, I will behave well.
I'm not a peeping tom anymore,
I won't pee or take a shower...
Mr. Maheshwar...
- What?
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
The marijuana has to be moved
to the pharmacy tonight.
Where is the pharmacy?
It's about 3-4 drive from here.
Let's start immediately.
I am sorry,
I won't be able to drive the lorry.
But why?
- I am too drunk.
My lorry gets angry
if I drive it in a drunken state.
I have experienced it.
Let's start in the morning.
Sir, we will have to do it tonight,
there will be checking in the morning.
- Then, how's it possible?
Then, give me the keys,
I will drive the lorry.
- No.
No, that's not possible.
Sir, I will bring
the lorry back by morning.
There's no other option.
Please, sir.
Be careful about my truck.
The lorry is dear to me.
Sure.
- Be careful.
Thanks.
- Listen...
Nothing will happen, don't worry.
He is taking my lorry away,
I feel pained.
Let's drink more.
I drank the remaining liquor.
What are you saying?
"Clean India. Good India."
"Every leaf is flying."
Don't you take a shower in the morning?
I take a shower before I come to work.
Call me when you take a shower,
I will help you.
I will beat you with the broomstick.
- She seems to be dangerous.
Is your name Jaanu?
- No, Sumati.
What is it to you?
Actually, the name Jaanu
suits you well.
I will beat you with broomstick.
Hey...
What's going on?
- It's social service.
I offered her help,
she said she'll lose her job
and you know my nature.
You know how much I respect women.
Let me help her.
Why hasn't he brought
my lorry back as yet?
Is it?
Then, it would've met in an accident
or fallen into valley for sure.
Shut up. I will cut off your tongue.
Come on, I was just joking.
Clean India...
- Sashi...
I am coming.
It has not arrived yet.
- What?
My lorry is not back yet.
Don't worry, it will come back.
23...
- He's having a tough time getting up.
He has so many men around,
but no one is helping him.
Shall we help him?
He is exercising.
- Good manners.
27... Come on.
How are you, Maheshwar?
How about competing with me?
Sir, you will be defeated.
No one can defeat him
in such challenges.
He is like a lion...
- Keep quiet.
I am be glad if you
assign me some work.
I am not used to being idle.
- He's right.
But I love to remain idle.
Shall I wash the cars?
Sir, whatever you say...
- Okay.
Keep quiet.
Okay, no problem.
I will show you how to wash them.
- Go fetch water.
Hey...
What happened?
Are you okay?
- I am fine.
Dada, we have a situation.
Men arrived in jeeps
and seized the lorry.
They took away the lorry and Shiva too.
I don't know who they are.
It was Kader's man,
he demands 10 crores.
Both, the lorry and Shiva
are in his custody.
Let's not worsen the matter.
I suggest you give him the money.
Don't take risk.
What's wrong?
It's an old issue,
but I guess it will be resolved.
Dada could've given a befitting reply.
Seeing Dada calm,
don't think he will forgive Kader.
He has dealt will many such men.
Dada has taught them a good lesson.
Take the money, go give it to him.
He has wronged.
We will deal with him later.
Go, get my son released
from his custody.
What about my lorry?
Don't worry,
you will get your lorry back.
Raju, let's go, quick.
Wait, I will come along.
I want my lorry.
- Come on. Get in.
Wait. Stop.
They took away all the vehicles.
Should I take a shower with this water?
What are you doing? What's wrong?
Jumman, you said Dada
won't give me money.
No one can make away with my money.
Manager, tell Dada Giriraj that
those who have messed with me
have lost their lives.
Well, he knows that.
After all, we were old friends.
Jumman, take the money.
- Okay.
Basheer, bring him.
Bring him.
Untie him, let him go.
Go on.
We would've offered him tea,
but the goat didn't give milk.
There are no keys in the lorry.
You're right.
That's because they are in my pocket.
Handover the keys to me.
- No, I won't.
His father had kicked Jumman,
I'm deeply pained about it.
So, I decided to
have the lorry as compensation.
What are you saying?
It's my lorry.
Kick me, I don't mind,
but give me the keys.
- Won't you leave without the lorry?
No, I won't. I want my lorry.
How dare you?
Do you see them?
These both dogs are very ferocious.
They will run when I signal
and will tear you to pieces.
If you have understood then get going.
I won't go without my lorry.
Jumman, give the dogs a chance
to feed upon human flesh.
Basheer, get him.
"He is a fighter."
"He is a fighter.
Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
The keys.
Take them out from the pocket yourself.
Did you find them?
"He's a fighter."
"Everyone knows he's a fighter."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
You're amazing, Maheshwar.
You have impressed me today.
You're like a tiger.
When Dada is impressed with someone,
that person will do good in life.
We need to wait and watch.
By the way, does the bathrooms
in the mansion have ventilators?
What do you want?
Ask for anything.
Assume God is asking you what you want.
Go on, ask.
If I got a chance,
I would takeover
all the bathrooms in the city.
I mean, I would turn them
into public toilets.
Go on, ask.
Can I for anything?
- Yes, go on.
Anything?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
Go on.
Give my brother Mani a job.
What's wrong?
Tell him to join our pharmacy
from tomorrow.
Really?
- Monthly salary will be Rs. 40,000.
I hope it's not less?
What are you saying? Not at all.
You're more than God to us.
Mani got a job,
monthly salary will be Rs. 40,000.
My dreams are becoming reality.
May God keep His mercy on us.
I don't know why,
but I feel something fishy.
Silly, I agree he's strange,
but he's good man.
Don't worry.
He has an amazing name,
Dada Giriraj.
How can someone name
himself as a leader?
He is very generous towards you.
I suggest you be careful.
Don't talk rubbish. Go to sleep.
You spent your life in forest,
you won't understand.
As if you were born in city.
Don't talk to me. - You too.
Get away.
Coward.
You're a coward.
I got to know
the intentions of everyone.
Look at him,
he's sleeping peacefully.
I shouldn't have trusted this man.
I am tired of him.
He brought me to the city
by manipulating me. Get up.
Oh, my God!
- I know you well.
What happened?
Oh, my God!
You must've had a tough time
bringing us here and
finding this house for us, isn't it?
- Yes.
No. What are you saying?
'What are you saying?'
It's even futile to talk to you.
What happened, Dad?
Why is mom yelling?
I don't know.
I guess she has lost his mind.
Come,  my child.
Let's find out what's wrong with her.
He manipulates me
with his talks all the time.
Take it.
- What's wrong? Tell me.
Come.
- Tea for me as well.
You won't get tea.
What's wrong? Tell me.
I've been living in pain all my life.
You don't know of it.
You don't care.
Be precise.
- I will tell you.
The problem lies at the neighborhood.
The light of the bathroom
at the neighborhood was on,
Seeing the lights turned on at midnight
I thought it is waste of electricity.
And you know my nature,
how mannered I am.
I peeped in to find out
who is wasting electricity,
I was surprised.
Do you know who was there? - Who?
It's suspense.
Tell me.
You know that person since long time.
- What do you mean?
You know that person well,
you'll be so excited to see her.
- Who's that?
When I show you, you will kiss me.
Take my word. Come with me.
Come, Maina.
- Darn it.
You will also find out
why your wife is upset.
Look over there.
Ju...
Not Ju, it's Julie.
What?
Later.
- When?
Oh, my God!
Why did you come here?
What were you telling her?
- I was just...
We came here, because she stays here.
- I had no idea about it.
You know nothing.
You have fooled me.
Hey...
- I will deal with you.
I won't let you in. - Was she unaware
about your affair with Julie?
You're very angry.
Why aren't you ready?
You got to go to work, go.
Why are you venting
your anger on me?
I am a victim. I am going.
Sir, Shiva is inside.
Come, sir.
I think you need to check.
Just check it once.
Yeah.
- Okay, sir.
Okay? Carry on.
Welcome, manager.
- Hi.
Sir, he's Mr. Mani,
our new marketing manager.
And his brother Mr. Maheshwar.
- Hello.
And he's Dr. Subramaniam,
the scientist.
What's that?
He's a scientist.
Oh. He's a scientist.
I had heard about scientists,
I got a chance to meet one today.
He is the scientist who manufactures
medicine for cancer with marijuana...
Talk softly.
None is aware of the secret formula.
Do scientists look like him?
He is quite intelligent.
That's why his hair has turned grey.
Mani, your cabin is over there.
Joe.
- Yes, sir.
Please take him. Go.
- Please come with me.
Come, sir.
- This way.
Come, Brother.
Mani, you will sit over there?
- Yes, Brother.
It's says 'Mani', right?
No, it's says 'Marketing Manager'.
Thank God it's just the two of us here.
Mani, sit on that rolling chair,
I want to see.
Bless me.
- Hey...
What are you doing?
It's all because of you, Brother.
You're no less than God to me.
Sit over there.
I should be going from here.
Dada had sent for me.
- Yes, come.
Come, Maheshwar. Sit.
I am fine.
Manager, make a drink for Maheshwar.
No, thanks.
You don't drink?
I do.
- He's drinks a lot.
He's feeling shy.
Even if he drinks more than you,
he still remains steady. Mahesh.
The liquor is expensive
and also for free.
Only in one break.
Maheshwar, do you know him?
You must've heard of him for sure,
he is Rambo.
Rambo? Please hold this.
I've never seen Veerappan,
you look like his maternal cousin.
I am so fortunate. Kiss me.
I've heard a lot about your bravery.
Mahesh, do you why Rambo
has come this far to meet dad?
No, I don't.
- Rambo needs your help.
He says only you can help him.
Raghuveer, the ranger of Rampur Jungle
he never content no matter
how much money we give him.
He has seized my stuff worth 4 crores.
What stuff?
Sandalwood.
He has taken my stuff into his custody.
He has deployed
forest officers to watch it.
He has ordered to shoot me at sight.
I am unable to get my stuff.
But I know it's possible only by you.
You will have to pay for it.
Hereafter, you will have to deliver
marijuana at my doorstep.
Do you agree?
It's a child's play for Mahesh.
Isn't it?
- No, it's not.
I've never done anything as such.
But I can't say no to you, I will try.
I'd need my uncle's help.
Be prepared.
Uncle!
It's worth 4 crores in the market.
Pay me only 2 crores.
Why are you hesitating so much?
I will get the stuff cleared
from the check post.
Hello.
Pratap.
- What happened, sir?
The sandalwood have been stolen.
I know it's Rambo's handiwork.
Search everywhere.
- Sir.
Search the entire jungle,
alert every check post. - Sir.
The stuff shouldn't be taken out
of the jungle. Do you get it?
Sir, the checking has been tightened.
The officer is very upset.
His men are deployed
in the entire forest.
You need to think of a foolproof plan
to get the stuff out of the check post.
Lord Shiva is the superior.
Lord Jesus is the superior.
Is it a festival today?
- Yes, it's Good Friday today.
They take out procession.
Then there's no need to be afraid,
Lord will show us the way.
"You're the giver, you're the God."
"The universe exists because of You."
Sir, did the members of our group
pass this way?
They are not sure of the route.
I hope...
- They just passed this way.
Sir, donate some money,
God will bless you.
You will be warded off
by evil spell, if any.
We don't force you for donation.
Here you go.
Rs. 500?
You're quite generous.
Open the gate, let them go.
"You're the only faithful."
Wonderful!
They fooled the police officer.
They made crosses with the sandalwood,
changed the colour
by applying tar on them
and used incense sticks
to get rid of the sandalwood odor.
You're amazing, Maheshwar.
Dada, he's a gem of a man.
Keep him close to your heart.
He's one in a million.
Stop kidding me.
Maheshwar, our stuff is lying
in the state border,
I want you to fetch it.
The task is risky.
But I know you will do it. Won't you?
Maina...
Don't scream or else she'll get angry.
- Good night.
Good night.
Maina...
Is Maina inside?
What?
- Is my wife Maina inside?
I am Maina.
What's the matter with you?
Seeing your attire,
I thought Julie is here as a witch.
Shut up.
She looks more beautiful than Julie.
- Maina...
Maina...
- Dad.
Who bought new dress and toy for you?
Ms. Julie bought them.
Shut up.
- Uncle bought them.
It's uncle Mani.
- Brother...
Mani...
- I received my first salary today.
I bought clothes for you.
Uncle.
- Yes.
Mani bought new clothes for me.
Maina...
You...
Mani has grown up.
- Uncle, shirt fabric for you.
I didn't a shirt of your size.
There are dresses for your wife
and children too. - Excuse me.
Didn't you buy anything for me?
- Of course, I have.
I have bought this for you.
- How sweet of you.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
It's body spray.
A new brand?
You need to spray it on your body.
Then when will I drink it?
Let me try it on him.
What are you doing?
- You haven't bathed for days.
Uncle...
- What are you saying?
Come.
Uncle, look at her.
Don't we look like newly wedded couple?
Let go.
- How does the shirt look?
It's Julie's favorite colour.
Shut up. - You look good
in traditional dress, not in this.
What's wrong, Uncle?
Mahesh, I want to go back to village.
What's the hurry, Uncle?
Are you missing your mother-in-law?
Nothing of that sort.
I want to see my children.
Do you really want to see them or
you're planning to have more children?
Don't you wish to go back to village?
Of course, I do.
We belong to our village.
But the case needs to be closed.
By the way, Dada has promised
to have the cases closed.
Pull over.
Mani, carry on, you got to get to work.
Okay.
- I will go from here.
Hey, get him.
- Who are you?
Get him.
- Let go of me.
Let go of me.
- Come on.
What have I done?
- Move.
What happened to Mr. Diwakar?
The tiger killed him.
Who else other than Maheshwar
will protect us?
Mr. Diwakar also
got killed by the tiger.
He went with the
newly appointed forest Ranger.
Sir, we should've come here
during Maheshwar's presence.
You're Maheshwar's stooge,
don't talk rubbish.
The government has appointed me
to catch the tiger.
Find it.
Come on. This way. Quick.
Let go.
Diwakar...
- Let go.
Stay put, the tiger is right behind.
Don't move.
Diwakar...
We're praying for Maheshwar's return.
Balram, where is he?
He must brought back.
I've no idea.
There's no news about him.
He will definitely come.
He has to come to drive away
his people's sorrow.
Maheshwar.
- Yes.
I know you're worried.
I want to tell you something.
I am in a fix myself.
But I promise you,
I will bring your brother back.
I guess the forest officer
is trying to avenge you.
Because your brother
was kidnapped from the village.
Dad, I received information from
our informer that Mani has been confined
in a workshop at Mumlapur.
That means, it's Kader's handiwork.
Kader has avenged Maheshwar,
because he had hit him.
That's why he kidnapped his brother.
Manager, summon your men,
I have to bring his brother at any cost.
No,
I will go there alone.
I am their enemy,
so I will go there alone.
Hey...
Come, Maheshwar.
I kidnapped your brother
because I wanted to meet you.
Release my brother.
Talk to me.
Alright.
I heard you're going great guns.
You're managing to make away
with marijuana stealthily
from the forest.
Sit.
Maheshwar, I know you did it
for your brother.
Then, how could I spare him.
Water?
- Mani has not wronged, he's innocent.
I agree he is innocent.
And you?
You've become
Dada Giriraj's right hand.
Tell me what you know about him.
I've been chasing him
past fourteen months.
A local goon from Mangalpur
has become a gangster.
And he's running illegal businesses
in the name of Giriraj Pharmacy.
Are you aware of it?
He sells marijuana in the pretext
of Ayurvedic medicines.
He makes Hash of high quality.
He supplies marijuana
to foreign countries in huge quantity
in the pretext of Ayurvedic medicines.
Giriraj Pharmacy has started
huge international markets.
And your brother is the
marketing manager of the company.
I am unaware of it, sir.
They told me they were
making medicine for cancer.
Medicine for cancer?
Really?
The managed to bring even your brother
who's MBA graduate, under their influence.
They must've told you I've been
posted at the village to arrest you.
They lied to you so that you come
under their influence and work for them.
In fact, I was there to arrest Rambo,
the drug peddler.
If I file this case,
both you and brother won't get bail.
I can save you.
But you must help me.
I have no proof
to the illegal business running
in Dada Giriraj's Ayurveda factory.
I will let you go if you get me proof.
His men will get arrested too.
Your brother can do the job easily.
If you do it, I promise, your names
won't be mentioned in the case.
We received wrong information.
It was police who kidnapped Mani,
not Kader.
Maheshwar has taught
a good lesson to the police,
he will bringing his brother back.
The information is accurate, Dada.
I found out myself,
two policemen have been hospitalized.
What about Maheshwar?
- I guess he's back.
Maheshwar, what happened?
When I got there,
I found several policemen.
They were torturing him,
he was being interrogated.
They said we don't manufacture medicine
with marijuana in the factory...
What did he say?
- Hash.
I told them we do use marijuana,
but we use it to manufacture medicine.
I thrashed them and brought him.
Will there be a problem?
No. Go, I will handle everything.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Dad, the matter is quite serious.
The police had nabbed Mani,
they can get to the factory any moment.
It's not so easy,
the police will never
be able to get there.
Even if we feel
Mani has exposed us,
he won't be able to get away.
It's risky to keep the stuff
in the factory,
it's better to shift it.
I spoke to the agents in Europe,
they will be here tomorrow.
Before that, we must
move the stuff to Mangalpur.
They will take the deliver
directly from there.
Get the stuff loaded
in Maheshwar's lorry.
Don't go with him.
Because I smell something fishy.
Make sure Maheshwar doesn't find out.
I ask you for the last time.
To whom did you send the video?
Sir. - Where's the manager?
- He's upstairs.
Who is he? Tell me.
Mani...
- Hit him.
Shiva, what's going on?
Why are you beating him?
Betrayal.
I can never forgive the one
who betrays me.
What are you talking about?
He is our friend.
Then ask your friend
to whom he sent the video.
I will never tell you.
You...
- Shiva, let go.
I will kill him.
Mani, tell him.
Don't beat him.
What are you doing?
Mani...
I will extract the truth from him.
- Don't do that, Shiva.
It was I who brought him here.
Maheshwar, sit.
I have parked the lorry down.
Good. The Ayurvedic boxes
that will loaded in your lorry,
you will take it to Mangalpur.
Our men are over there.
Here's the details of the product.
Here's the rest of the documents.
Produce them at the check post.
- Okay.
Where is Shiva?
Shiva is handling a cheating case.
He won't be able to accompany you,
you leave.
Kill him!
No!
Brother...
Don't let him go!
What are you waiting for?
Brother...
Shiva...
Surround them! Hurry up!
Nobody should escape.
Drop your gun, now.
Fire!
Darn it! Follow him!
Come on, hurry up.
Maheshwar...
- Sir...
I didn't...
- I will handle everything.
Go to your village soon.
Any news?
Maheshwar
is not here.
I've no idea where he is.
We must lay a trap to get him.
And then deal with him.
Mahesh.
- Yes.
Did you see the consequences
of sending me away from the village?
You thought I will be safe in the city.
But you must've realized
that human beings
are more dangerous
than the animals in the forest.
We can sense the danger from an animal,
we can fight it.
How can you be alert
from a human being
who first creates a bond,
win our trust
and then break it?
He betrays us.
Least did we know
something like this would happen.
I didn't tell anything to Maina.
She thinks Mani met
with a major accident.
Maheshwar, where have
you been for so long?
The tiger entered the village again.
It took away seven people in a month.
We were desperately waiting for you.
But there was no trace of you.
Maheshwar, my only granddaughter Babita,
my only support,
the tiger took her away last night.
Had I told you, you would fret.
Moreover, you were already in a fix.
What are you thinking?
Are you again planning to kill the tiger?
Look, Chakki and I have nobody
other than you.
Pay heed to me.
How could you even say that?
Have you lost your mind?
She was a little girl like Chakki.
Had Chakki suffered the same fate,
would we keep quiet?
Would we still do nothing?
No, I won't let you go.
Maheshwar, Sashi was
taken away by the tiger,
we rescue him with great difficulty.
Maheshwar...
I have realized that
the gun alone is not enough
to catch the tiger.
You're right.
The gun won't help.
To kill the tiger,
one has to get hold
of its throat straight.
One has to sense its moves.
Not everyone can kill a tiger,
except Maheshwar.
Maheshwar, I've realized
why the villagers have
so much faith in you.
I have received the permission
to kill the man-eater.
Look, it's the order
from the forest department.
Only you can save their lives.
Who did it?
Dada... Dada Giriraj.
He said your life is at stake
and took me to the jungle by deceit.
If Mahesh goes to the jungle,
he informs us.
I happened to meet him in the jungle,
he asked me to bring you.
Balram...
Hey... Sashi...
Balram, save me.
Balram...
Maheshwar's right hand.
Just as close as
Lord Krishna and Balram.
But unfortunately,
it's all going to be over,
because you're going to die.
And the good news should be
passed on to Maheshwar.
He will inform Maheshwar
about your death.
Balram...
No...
The village head was right.
Whether the enemy
is the tiger or human being,
he should be
killed in his territory.
It's the rule of the jungle.
He will learn the lesson of his life.
He calls himself tiger.
And I am the hunter.
I will deal with him.
"He is a fighter."
"He is a fighter.
Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
Darn it.
I won't spare him.
"He is a fighter."
"He is a fighter.
Everyone knows it."
"He doesn't miss his aim.
He is a real fighter."
Shocked, aren't you?
Balram will have to pay a price
for Shiva's death.
If you have the guts, save him.
I didn't kill your son.
He was killed accidentally.
But I lost my son.
Even you should feel the pain
of losing the loved ones.
Won't you rescue him?
Uncle...
Hey...