"We are proud of our country"
"We are proud!"
"We will live in victory
and die in victory"
"Die in victory"
"O Country, we will decorate
your character"
"Come, we will guard you
against evil"
"Every drop of my blood
is for guarding you"
"We are proud of our country"
"We are proud!'
"We will live in victory
and die in victory"
"Die in victory"
Arjun Ranawat is a killer!
- He is a murderer!
Hang Arjun!
- Hang him! Hang him!
Arjun Ranawat is a killer!
- He is a murderer!
(Brakes squeal)
Hang Arjun!
- Hang him! Hang him!
Arjun Ranawat is a killer!
- He is a murderer!
Hang Arjun!
- Hang him! Hang him!
Your Honor.
This is ACP Arjun Ranawat.
He barged into the prime
minister's farm house..
..on the night of 1st November..
..and brutally killed the
deputy prime minister..
..Badrinath Trivedi,
his son, Munna Trivedi..
..the police commissioner
Yeshwant's son..
..Chandrakant Deshpande..
..police inspector Avasthi,
advocate Kulkarni..
..the six MLAs of the reigning
political party..
..and counting some government
and police officers..
..all in all, 18 people.
Your Honor.
He isn't the guardian of
the law, but its abuser.
With this cold blooded massacre..
..not only has he maligned..
..the government and police,
but even humanity.
These are some of the photographs..
..taken from the crime scene,
Your Honor.
The police requests the accused..
..to be kept in remand for
fifteen days to investigate..
..this brutal massacre
and the reason for it.
Arjun Ranawat, do you want to say
anything about these accusations?
No.
Do you have a lawyer?
- No.
Would you wish the court
to appoint a lawyer for you?
No.
The government has accused you
of killing 18 innocent civilians.
It has asked for a remand of
15 days for investigation.
Do you want anything
during this time?
Do you have the need for anything?
Yes, I do.
- What is it?
Death.
The accused, Arjun Ranawat,
is placed into police custody..
..for 15 days in remand.
'While claiming that
he was perfectly sane..'
'..Ranawat said that he has committed
this massacre in sound mind.'
'When the judge asked him
whether he needed anything..'
'..he answered what he
had said before. Death.'
'Vandana Sajnani, Aaj Tak, Mumbai.'
Yeshwant Deshpande.
Is this the charge
sheet you've prepared?
Is this it? Just a murderer?
He isn't a murderer! He is a demon!
Come. Look at this! Look at this!
He snatched away my son, my brother
and my son-in-law from me!
He wiped off the vermilion
from the foreheads..
..of my daughter-in-law
and my daughter.
He even got your son, didn't he?
Aren't you sad about that?
He didn't leave anyone to
light our funeral pyres.
He vanquished our bloodline!
Our dynasty!
Listen to me, Tyagi.
Bad character.
Corruption.
Bad thoughts.
Betrayal of the country. Even to
the extent of calling him a traitor.
Accuse him of every crime
written in your law book..
..and label him a lawless character.
Slap all the sections
of your law on him!
Release his chains.
Sign these documents.
Arjun Ranawat.
You have killed my only son.
Until the court punishes you..
..I will give you a new death
every day in this prison.
Deshpande, he hasn't signed
these documents.
He has placed his life
into death's hands.
Please come.
Son.
Why did you put down your
weapons in the court today?
Why don't you tell the world
why you massacred them?
Why are you asking for
death for yourself, son?
Why are you doing it?
Because I have performed my last rites.
I wish freedom from my body
and this birth.
Mother.
From today, both you and Rakhi..
..please don't come
to meet me here.
Because in the Hindu religion..
..mothers and sisters don't attend
funerals and enter cemeteries.
I'll leave now, Mother.
We were to be together for
just this long in this birth.
Don't cry when I die.
I'll be back again.
Ask your God to make me
your son next time too.
Respected Mr. Samar Singh.
My final salute to you
and your principles.
I've walked away
from your principles..
..this uniform and
this police force.
I have a final request of you, sir.
Please don't say 'Truth always triumphs'
ever again.
Because the truth is that in
this eunuch-like society..
..lies..
..unlawfulness..
..and injustice are always victorious.
I want to tell you, sir.
We soldiers are not
mere government machinery.
Outside the police station,
even we have a life.
We don't know where we lost it
while walking on your given path.
So, you're here still.
You haven't gone to the temple.
Didn't I tell you, son?
Mother. What will I do
going to the temple?
You've worshipped your
body for too long now.
Come and worship God too, son.
(Sighs)
You want me to go to the
temple and pray to God?
Yes. I'll be very grateful to you.
Where are you taking me?
- Come here. Sit down.
Okay.
'Hail the Goddess Jagdambe,
Hail Goddess Durga"
'Hail Goddess Kali,
Hail Goddess Saraswati"
You crazy boy, what are you doing?
Don't you see, mother?
I am praying to my God.
It's been truly said.
God can't be everywhere
at one time.
That's why he created mother.
Mother, you are my
temple and every deity.
Are you crazy?
A mortal man is never compared
to God, son.
Is it so?
Do you remember
the '1984 riots, Mother?
When a child was crying
over his dead parents?
God hadn't come at that time.
You had, Mother.
My real mother had
just given birth to me.
You've given me my life though.
My existence is because of you.
Only because of you, Mother.
I gave birth to Rakhi.
But you're a piece of my heart.
I didn't ask for anything
after getting you.
Why are you lying, Mother?
You pray for brother's wellbeing
from morning to evening..
..and yet you say that you
don't ask God for anything?
Rakhi, keep quiet.
You're just jealous.
Because mother loves me more.
What? I'm jealous of you?
My foot!
Oh, God!
She's in the mood to fight.
I haven't come to fight.
I have come to tell you
that I'm going to college..
..and I've taken Rs.1000
from your wallet.
Did you see that, Mother?
Robbery in a policeman's house.
I didn't rob anyone. I've just
taken what is mine by right.
By the way,
I have served breakfast.
When you both mother and son
complete your tearful reunion..
..please have it. I'll be very grateful.
I'll leave now.
Bye. Bye, Mom.
Did you see that, mother?
Rakhi has grown up.
Yes, son. When the daughter grows up..
..a mother worries even more.
What are you talking about, mother?
Does a cow ever feel that
her horns are heavy?
You worry about Rakhi's marriage,
don't you?
Yes.
- Don't worry.
Your son will get his sister married
with such pomp and splendor..
..that the whole world will be stunned.
(Police siren wails)
(Brakes squeal)
Greetings, Lukkha brother!
Did you see, sir? Even a hero's not
as famous as Hakim Lukkha is! (Laughs)
Come on!
What is the hurry, sir?
I am human too.
Why are you dragging me
like a beast?
Sir, will I get a smoke?
Shut up and walk, you wretch.
Let the judge get you
in police custody once..
..I'll give you good cigarettes
in the lock up after that.
That will be decided
with the judge's verdict.
Your Honor.
When these police
men were accusing..
..Hakim Lukkha of cutting off the..
..prostitutes nose
and ears, he wasn't..
..in Mumbai city forget
about Grant Road.
He had gone to Lucknow.
For the party's work.
Your Honor.
This is the proof of the
police's wretchedness.
This is the air ticket to Lucknow.
This is the register of
the guesthouse in Lucknow..
And Your Honor, this is the manager
of that guesthouse in Lucknow.
Your Honor.
This lawyer is lying!
Hakim Lukkha is a pimp.
This scoundrel whores innocent girls.
Did you hear that?
Did you hear that, your honor?
This is the respected police
of our Mumbai city.
They abuse people
right here in court.
ACP Arjun Ranawat.
If you use any abusive and vulgar
language in this court the next time..
..you will be suspended.
This time, I'm letting you go
with just a warning.
Please don't waste the court's time
by bringing such matters here.
The accused is released honorably.
I've told you a thousand times.
Be respectful in the court.
They are ripping our shirts apart.
And you're saying that
we should respect them?
Didn't I show you your place
in court, Mr. Arjun?
I had said it.
I had announced it, Lawyer.
That this time too,
Hakim Lukkha will be released.
Why? What did you do?
Actually, sir.
Messing with me is
dangerous for you.
And dangerous for your sister, too.
I've heard that your sister
is very beautiful, sir.
No, Arjun!
Wait, Arjun! I say, stop it.
(Glass shatters)
I say, leave him, Arjun.
I said leave him alone.
Compose yourself! Are you crazy?
Get up, Brother Lukkha. Get up.
Hey, Kulkarni. Take this pimp away!
Hey, explain it to your hero!
These wrestling antics of his
will prove very expensive to him!
I'll have his uniform snatched!
You will have my uniform snatched?
Come on.
Arjun.
(Snaps finger)
Hey, take him away.
- I am going.
But explain to this hero.
Enmity with a lawyer
will prove very costly.
Come on, Brother Lukkha. Let's go.
Enough, Arjun. It is enough.
What enough? You always stop me.
That wretched Hakim Lukkha..
..spat on our faces and
we couldn't do anything.
And you tell me to stop?
See this. Do you see this?
The government has hung
a gun around our waist.
But we can't use it.
And those scoundrels shoot
in the middle of the street.
And what do we do? What do we do?
We just take those pimps
into the magistrate's presence.
And then Kulkarni
comes and releases them.
And what do we do?
We hold this in our hands and stand.
Get up.That pimp is not wworth
irritating your brains.
Let's go!
- You go. I'll be here a while.
Yes, why will you come?
It's time for your angel to come.
You've started it all over again?
- You scoundrel.
Why are you shy of speaking
what's in your heart since a long time?
She has expressed her love
to you a thousand times over.
And you..
Haider, please go.
I'll go.
It's bad to suggest
anything to anyone nowadays.
And listen, don't drink
a lot. You'll be driving.
Jannat, did your lover give
you a flying kiss today too?
Thank you for your sympathy.
Jannat, all rich people
are at your feet.
And you are dying for a policeman?
What does he have?
You won't understand, my dear.
Rich and generous people
are found in this bar.
But l can see only lust and hunger..
..in the eyes of every man here.
But Arjun.
l see respect and conscience
in Arjun''s eyes.
You crazy girl, till wwhen wwill
you wait for him like this?
For my whole life.
And if that is less, l will
give my next life to him too.
This ring that l wwear in my neck.
Only Arjun will make me wwear this.
She wwon't understand.
(Brakes squeal)
(Engine not starting)
(Tires squealing)
Did you recognize me?
Lukkha. Hakim Lukkha.
(Laughs)
What are you staring at, sir?
You'll just have to speak
to me with respect, okay?
Respectable people are
spoken to with respect.
(Bottle shatters)
Who do you call a pimp?
(Snaps finger)
See this street.
It is deserted.
Neither a man,
nor any sign of humans.
Look here too. Look.
You can't see anyone till afar.
If I kill you here right now..
..nobody will get any
proof or any witness..
..about who killed
ACP Arjun Ranawat.
There will only be your photo
in the newspaper tomorrow.
And your sister will be
in my jeep from tomorrow.
I'll leave now.
(Snaps finger)
Think about what I told you.
Work for me. Or else,
an unknown death may occur. (Laughs)
'He is correct.
A lonely street, unknown death.'
'What if I kill him here?'
Hey, Lukkha.
Yes, tell me.
What do you want to tell me?
Thanks for the suggestion.
Suggestion?
(Groans)
Hey!
(Gunshot)
(Screaming in pain)
Look here. Empty street.
Look here.
No man, nor any sign of humans.
(Screaming in pain)
And the papers tomorrow will carry
your photograph, not mine.
Unknown death.
No!
(Gunshot)
Arjun Ranawat,
your activities last night..
..have shaken the entire city of Mumbai
and the government.
Your murdering spree has slandered
the police force's reputation.
Look at this. Look at this
and look at this.
While some are calling
us uniformed hooligans..
..others are calling us
uniformed devils.
You will have to bear
its punishment.
Write on that paper..
..that you lost your anger
and sanity and murdered them.
I didn't massacre them
in anger or insanity.
I did it in self-defense.
It was an act of self-defense.
Act of self-defense? My foot!
Don't think me to be a fool.
One doesn't break 17 bones
in someone's body in self-defense.
He doesn't make him
lay on his back..
..and empty the entire magazine
of his gun.
This is the autopsy report.
Have you not read
the procedure code?
You must warn a criminal first.
Then bullets are shot in the air
and later on the legs.
And then, you could inform
the control room too.
You are right, sir.
I committed a huge mistake.
When his revolver was below my ear..
..and he was about to
press the trigger..
..I should have called up
the control room.
Then I should have fired
in the air once.
After that, I should have
fired at his legs.
You are right, sir.
I committed such a huge mistake.
Sir, that wretch was
talking about killing me..
..and making my sister
a courtesan.
At that time, I should have told him,
"Brother, please wait".
"It is a crime to kill a police officer
and make his sister a courtesan."
I'm sorry, sir.
But if I had walked on your path..
..my name wouldn't be written here..
..but outside the police station..
..on the list of personnel dead
in the line of fire.
And you wouldn't be shouting here.
You would be shedding tears
over my bullet-ridden body..
..wrapping it in the Indian tricolor flag
and playing the bugle.
Shut up.
There is a limit to insolence
and shamelessness.
Did you see that, sir?
I say, we should declare him a killer
and set an example for others.
Why not, sir?
If you want to clean up the
good-for-nothing and useless image..
..of the police force with the
blood of an upright police officer..
..you are most welcome.
Nobody has any proof
that I did these killings.
Neither you, nor you were
present at the murder site.
You can only declare me a killer,
but you can't prove it.
And I won't say this.
My lawyer will say this in court.
And nobody will have
any answer to this.
Sir..
This Hakim Lukkha had
38 cases against him.
He had started thinking of the
police station as his house..
..his house as a brothel..
..and police officers
like me as his pimp.
What had we done to him?
Sir..
In 12 years of this police service..
..I've died a thousand
deaths at their hands.
I had just two ways out.
Either I would live on Lukkha's scraps
and barter the law..
..or I'd put down this uniform..
..and tolerate everything like a eunuch.
No, sir.
I refused to be a pimp or eunuch.
Sir, if these criminals
can be released by court..
..and allowed to move around
like innocent civilians..
..then why can't I,
Arjun Ranawat, kill them..
..and move around like
an innocent civilian?
Why?
Do you want to say anything else?
No, sir.
You may go.
He is speaking the truth, sir.
But sadly, what can be done?
That's what we will
have to think of, Jadhav..
..what we'll have to do
in such a situation.
No, sir. Punishing Arjun
is not a solution to this problem.
What is the solution
to this problem?
Encounter!
Encounter?
Yes, we won't catch
them in a clash.
We'll kill them.
We'll encounter them.
When the criminals see this
terror hovering around them..
..they will see only two
ways out for themselves.
Give up or die.
Surrender or death.
And only then will the dream of
a crime-free country come true.
Are you ready for this?
You ready the Crime Control
Squad, Mr. Samar Singh.
My government is with you.
Hands up!
Police? run.
This is too much, brother.
The police that would shiver in fear
when they'd hear of you..
..the same police has now killed 27
of our men in only 13 days.
Yes, brother.
This Mumbai Police has shaken up
this same Mumbai city in 25 days..
..which we ruled for 25 years.
The police has become
synonymous with death today.
They don't arrest or
ask for surrender.
That commissioner tells them
to kill directly.
Brother, that CM has backed the police.
Therefore, the lowliest of the officers..
..laugh at Zafar Supari's face.
I'll tell you, brother.
Just say the word.
I'll go and blow up that
commissioner's head right away.
I'll show the Mumbai police that
one must not touch a live snake.
Majid.
Call that opposition leader
Kashi Trivedi.
Tell him to create a hullabaloo..
..by branding the police as the
murderers of the Dalits(low-caste sect)..
..minorities and the innocent
in the parliament.
Through the accusations of
fake encounters in the press..
..make life difficult for the
policemen and the government.
Shake up that CM.
I will show the CM
and the commissioner..
..that the government with whose
backing they prance about proudly..
..is run by Zafar Supari
sitting in a foreign country.
Down with the killer police!
Down with the heartless government.
Down with the uniformed hooligans!
Down with the killer police!
Mr. Trivedi, if you want to
create a ruckus here too..
..just like at the parliament..
..what is the meaning
of this meeting?
What is your problem after all?
I don't have a problem.
I have a question.
Till when will your police..
..carry out bloodshed on the
streets of the city of Mumbai?
Until the last one of this
city's gangsters isn't dead.
Until we don't achieve the
objective of a crime-free state.
Until then.
- Mr. Chief Minister..
..please make your crazy
commissioner understand..
..that he needs to stop shedding the
blood of Dalits and minority groups.
Kashi Trivedi,
politicians like you shed blood.
Not the police.
Who created fights in the country
regarding temples and mosques?
You did.
The Brahmins against
Yadavs in Bihar..
..the Thakurs against
Dalits in UP..
..and the Muslims against Hindus
in Gujarat. Who did all this?
You did.
Just for a few votes, you get a
brother to kill his own brother.
Then you warm yourselves
with their funeral pyres.
That's what politicians
like you do, not the police.
Human rights violator!
You are accusing me? Me!
I'll topple Satyanarayan Joshi's
government in a snap. (Snaps finger)
I'll topple your chair, understood?
I'll bring you down to a
constable from a commissioner.
(Laughs)
Kashi Trivedi.
Whose human rights
are you speaking about?
Those hooligans, who don't
consider humans as humans?
Those who shoot
at innocent people?
Who widow their wives
and orphan their children?
Kashi Trivedi, are you
praising their human rights?
They aren't humans.
How can we have a human
consideration for them?
They are inhuman.
They just understand one language.
This one.
Shut up! You mere police inspector!
You're flying high on
their strength, aren't you?
This chief minister's
days are on thin ice now.
I'll transfer this
commissioner as soon as..
..I become the chief minister.
And as for you..
..if I don't make you
salute me everyday..
..my name won't be Kashi Trivedi!
Then listen to what I say too,
Kashi Trivedi.
The day I get some proof
against you..
..you won't be sitting on
the chief minister's chair..
..but on your funeral pyre.
And I promise you, Kashi Trivedi.
You won't even get one man
to shoulder your funeral.
Mr. Encounter Specialist.
You have turned this
city into Gestapo.
You have colored the streets of
this city red with blood..
..in the last 30 days.
What do you have to say about this?
Is this not the death of democracy?
How long will you kill
in the name of humanity?
What is the difference between
the police and the hooligans?
Is this encounter your
helplessness or greed?
Encounter is murder of democracy.
It's dictatorship.
What is the need of murdering
under the pretext of encounters?
It is necessary.
There is a necessity.
What do you think?
When we go to arrest them..
..do the criminals
wait with garlands for us?
They welcome us with a spray of
bullets and dangerous weapons.
It is our moral right to shoot
in self-defense at that time.
It is our democratic right.
Do only criminals and
terrorists have human rights?
Doesn't a soldier
have any human rights?
Are we soldiers not human?
Mr. Encounter Specialist.
Zafar Supari has
threatened to kill..
..every person in the encounter squad.
He has made a hit list of
the entire encounter squad.
What hit list will that pimp make?
We have made a hit list.
Look at this.
Do you see these red marks?
These are with God today.
Soon, the rest will be too.
Take this hit list. Print it
in your newspaper tomorrow.
The next time Zafar Supari
gives you a telephonic interview..
..tell him that we have
started striking off his name..
..from the ration cards.
(Brakes squeal)
Bye!
Hello! Hey.
I've come to drop you till
your home. Won't you call me in?
l mean, tea or something?
Oh, tea!
Yes, l am your lover, l love you.
l have that much right at least.
Okay. So come in, Mr.Vivek
Acharya. Please come in.
You will be made to drink
tea and with that..
..you wwill be introduced
to my brother too.
What! Brother is at home..
l mean, is he home?
He is a policeman.
When he''s at home..
..when he is in the station,
when he..
..goes to do someone''s encounter..
..even the almighty
doesn't know that.
Okay, Miss Rekha, l mean,
Miss Rakhi, l will leave.
Why? Don't you want
any tea or something?
Tea? l won't even be able
to drink water now.
Why? Aren't you scared of brother?
Scared? The whole city is
afraid of your brother.
He speaks less with his mouth
and more with his gun.
You fool!
lf you don't meet brother, how
will you ask me for your hand?
Madam!That is your responsibility.
Mr.Vivek Acharya, son
of Justice Acharya.
l will talk to my brother.
But when will you talk to your dad?
Leave him to me. Once that
our marriage case..
..reaches in his court, his
decision will be in our side.
Okay.
Love you. Take care. Okay.
Bye.
- Bye.
Brother.. there is a boy.
He studies in your college.
BSc. Final Year.
His name is Vivek Acharya,
Justice Acharya's son.
The two of you love each other.
How do you know that, Brother?
I am a policeman, not a milkman.
I keep an eye on the entire city.
Won't I know whom my sister meets,
and where and when?
Do you take me for a fool?
Do you love him?
- No.
What?
- Yes.
Look at me.
Good choice.
Really, Brother?
Yes. Yahoo!
I'll talk to his father.
It is a matter of pride
to make your sister..
..my daughter-in-law.
But..
..remember that we're
from the boy's side.
We have some conditions.
They'll get engaged tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
But we need some time
for the arrangements.
No, nothing doing.
The engagement should take
place tomorrow. It is an order.
But sir..
You're not in a hurry.
I'm in a hurry though.
If your sister changes her mind..
..my son won't get
such a good wife..
..and I won't get such a good
daughter-in-law anywhere else.
(Laughs)
Therefore, the engagement ceremony
will be held here tomorrow.
(Music)
"She is so beautiful,
she seems to be my heart"
"If she just opens her eyes
the heart sputters"
"The lips say that she
seems to be my life!"
"She seems to be my life!"
"She is so beautiful,
she seems to be my heart"
"If she just opens her eyes
the heart sputters"
"The lips say that she
seems to be my life!"
"She seems to be my life!"
(Music)
''The eyes.''
''Your eyes.''
''Bindiya..''
''Your bindiya..''
''Bangles.."
''lt decorates so well!'' ''Earrings!''
''Your earrings!''
''Even the moon will shy away
looking at your face.'
''The star''s hearts will break.''
"She is so beautiful,
she seems to be my heart"
"If she just opens her eyes
the heart sputters"
"She seems to be my.."
"The lips say that she
seems to be my life!"
"Dreams!"
"Your dreams"
"Keep it"
"Keep it well"
"O dear!"
"Your beloved looks so cute!"
"You got the procession,
I will go in the procession"
"I will go from the house
but not from the heart"
"She is so beautiful,
she seems to be my heart"
"If she just opens her
eyes the heart sputters"
"The lips say that she
seems to be my life!"
"She seems to be my life!"
"He is so handsome"
"He is so handsome, he
seems to be my heart"
"If he just opens his
eyes the heart sputters"
"The lips say that he
seems to be my life!"
"He seems to be my life!"
"If he just opens his
eyes the heart sputters"
"The lips say that he
seems to be my life!"
"He seems to be my life!"
(Music)
Sir, your informer no.
555 wants to meet you.
Send him in. - Right, sir.
Salutations, sir.
Come in.
Yes, tell me. What
news have you brought?
Sir, I have definite news.
Zafar Supari..
..he has given (clicks tongue)...
a contract to kill the commissioner.
And Zafar Supari's main
hitman is Pappu Kalia.
He has a master plan, sir.
And to succeed in his
contract, he's going to meet..
..four to five shooters at the
'Can Can' nightclub tonight.
Okay, you can go.
Goodbye sir.
(Music)
"Oh darling! Oh darling!"
"The beauty is wearing
a blouse of flames"
"And yet love has
not aroused yet"
"You have robbed me, my beloved"
"I've drowned in
the sea of love"
"I won't regret even if I die"
"I'll be reborn just for you"
"My heart is restless,
it only wishes for you"
"I don't know what may happen"
"Oh darling! Oh darling!"
(Music)
"My heart burns and
its smoke rises"
"When will you know
that, my love?"
"If the pain rises
or I loose my sense"
"Even then I gave my
heart only to you"
"I consumed the poison,
I swallowed the pain"
"Even then I didn't
take your name"
"I have decided that I'll do
what I have never done yet"
"Oh darling! Oh darling!"
"I consumed the poison,
I swallowed the pain"
"Even then I didn't
take your name"
"I have decided that I'll do
what I have never done yet"
"My life belongs to my love,
but my love is not aware of it"
"I don't know what may happen"
"Oh darling! Oh darling!"
(Music)
"I have no other wish
in my heart except you"
"Your lover is yearning while
you have fun and frolic"
"You are the God of my love
and I'm thirsty for your love"
"I see the divine in your eyes"
"You are the God of my love
and I'm thirsty for your love"
"I see the divine in your eyes"
"You are my pride,
you are my dignity"
"I don't know what may happen"
"Oh darling! Oh darling!"
Pappu Kalia.
You're under arrest.
(Gunshot)
Arjun, drop your weapon!
Or else I'll kill this girl.
I'm telling you to
drop your weapon.
Or else, this girl
will lose her life.
I'm telling you for the last time, Arjun.
Drop your weapon!
I'm telling you to
drop your weapon.
Drop it!
(Laughs)
(Grunts)
(Gunshot)
Kashi Trivedi! I made you
a minister from a milkman.
I made you an MLA (Member
of Legislative Assembly)..
..and a leader of
the opposition.
For what? For this day?
So you can give milk
sitting in the parliament?
Hey, Kashi! Pappu Kalia is dead.
One by one, all my lead
men have been killed..
..by that police
commissioner of yours.
My reign of 25
years over Mumbai..
..has been destroyed
by your Mumbai police.
And there, you have ruined
my name in front of the ISI.
Do something, Minister.
Think of a solution to this.
Relieve us off this problem.
I have a solution
for this, Don Zafar.
But it will cost
you a hefty price.
I was just wondering when you
would bark for more money.
Okay, then. Tell me how much.
Then listen to me
carefully, Supari.
The government of Chief
Minister Satyanarayan Joshi..
..is supported by only
11 independent MLAs.
And from those 11, nine
are ready to be bribed.
The cost is Rs. 600 millions.
That means with Rs. 600 millions
you can become the Chief Minister.
Okay, Kashi. Overrule
the government.
You'll get Rs.600
millions by tomorrow.
Then consider yourself..
..the prime minister
of Mumbai, Don Zafar.
Everyone in the government
will consist of our people.
The government will be ours
and the rule will be yours.
(Laughs)
Hey, Munna! Hey, Badri!
Didn't I tell you?
I'll fix. I'll break.
I'll fight and make
others fight too.
I'll make the parties
and break them too.
But one day, I'll definitely
sit on this chair.
(Laughs)
That day has arrived, Munna.
Now, I'm the king of this state.
And the rest all are subjects.
(Laughs)
Listen, Brothers. All
you ministers, MLAs..
..and officers. Honesty,
that is ho..nes..ty..
..is a thing of the past with your
past Chief Minister. Understood?
Now, whatever I say will
be considered an order.
Whatever I decide
will be the law.
Sir..
Tell me, Bhonsle..
..have you brought my transfer orders
from the Home Minister's office?
How did you know, sir?
I knew.. as soon as the
new government is in rule..
..the ministers have an old
habit of transferring officers.
Bhonsle, explain
to these ministers.
Only areas can be
changed by transfers..
..not determination.
Tanaji, you take care of yourself
and keep writing letters to me.
So, you have also received
the news of my transfer.
What's there to worry about?
These sort of things do happen.
But sir, people who changed
the government in 13 hours..
..and transferred
you in three hours..
..how can soldiers like
us who are only paid..
..Rs.10000-12000
fight against them?
Avasthi, by putting a
price tag on this uniform..
..don't insult all our
country's honest officers.
Avasthi, terrorists fight for money.
But a soldier does not.
Soldiers only fight for the dignity
and safety of their country.
Sorry, sir.
Son, they can put
someone else in my place.
But they can't change our
thoughts and our rights.
Sir, from now onwards, your
thoughts will be our duty.
The fire in your heart is now
burning within our hearts.
Sir, the dream you had
of a crime-free state..
..we'll fulfill that dream now.
This will be our
gift to our mentor.
I have spent Rs.600 millions to
break and make the government.
And for that, not just
60, not just 600..
..but I'll torture 3600
million citizens of Mumbai..
..to repay that amount.
From builders to actors..
..and from doctors to
producers, don't spare anyone.
Tell them. If they want to live,
they need to pay protection money.
If they want their
families to be safe..
..then they should
send money to Zafar.
If anyone wants to do
business in Mumbai..
..even if someone wants to
breathe freely in Mumbai..
..then send Don Zafar
his salutation money.
Yeda!
The police thrashed my
men in their own homes.
Threaten their homes too.
Their mothers,
sisters, wife and kids.
If anyone disagrees,
chop them up.
Tell the police force to be
afraid of this father of theirs.
Of Zafar Supari.
(Brakes squeal)
Bye.
You take care. - You too.
Bye. - Bye.
Mom.
Mom, where are you?
(Laughs)
(Screams)
Brother. Brother!
Brother! Leave me.
Leave me!
Don't worry.
I'm not here to kill
you but to warn you.
You know Zafar
Supari, don't you?
He lives out of country..
..but rules over all of Mumbai.
Inspectors like your brother
fall at Zafar Supari's feet.
Explain to your brother..
..that he must respect
Zafar like a father..
..and Yeda like
an elder brother.
He must salute and
fear Zafar every day.
Next time I won't come
here to explain anything.
I'll chop your mother into
pieces and kidnap you, too.
And anyway, a pretty girl
does not belong here..
..but in Don Zafar's
harem and with me.
(Brakes squeal)
Who was here?
Rakhi.
Who was here, Rakhi?
Tell me. Please.
Yes, tell me. - Yeda!
One of Zafar Supari's men.
(Bullet clinks)
So tell me, Chopra. How would
you like to have a bullet?
With whiskey?
With soda?
With water?
No, Don. - Or..
..direct!
- No, Don Yeda. Forgive me.
Forgive you?
Under that commissioner's approval,
you all were flying very high.
No, Don Yeda. I.. I.. I..
Come on. I want Rs.30
millions in cash..
..the overseas rights
of your new film..
..and the contract for
its home video and music.
Come on, go.
I'll get it. I'll get
it right now, Don.
What did you say?
You'll chop our mothers into pieces?
Kidnap our sisters?
No, Hyder.
So, Zafar Supari's pimp.
Come on. Now spread
your terror in the city.
Now threaten the police force.
No, Arjun.
So Yeda, now tell me..
..how would you like
to have a bullet?
With water?
(Coughs and splutter)
With soda?
With whiskey? Speak!
(Coughs and splutter)
Or..
No. - Direct?
No.
(Gunshot)
(Phone rings)
Chote, it's Yeda's call.
- (Phone rings)
Yes, Yeda. Tell me.
- Don, they've killed Yeda.
What?
(Over phone) What rubbish?
It's not rubbish. It's
the truth, Zafar Supari.
Who are you? - MPS..
MPS? - Yes.
Maharashtra Police Service.
Zafar Supari, here's
a word of advice.
Don't send a band of eunuchs
to take on real men again.
Remember Zafar, for
goons like you..
..there's no competition in
this world, but the police.
Zafar Supari, your
final warning.
For you, there will
be no charge sheet..
..only D-final, which
means only death final.
Jai Hind!
Brother.
Hey, Rakhi.
Both of you at the
police station together?
Tell me, who's here to
complain about whom?
First of all, you write
down my complaint, sir.
This sister of yours keeps
threatening me all the time.
If you don't do this,
I'll get you arrested.
If you don't do that,
I'll get you handcuffed.
She's doing nothing wrong.
(Laughs)
Look, Brother..
..the government is
granting him a scholarship..
..for higher studies abroad..
..and this gentleman
here refuses to leave.
Brother, it's not even been three
weeks since our engagement..
..and she wants to exile me
to Canada for three years.
No, Brother. I don't want to go.
If I were in your
place, I would've left..
..the very next day after the engagement.
- Brother.
It's a lifetime opportunity.
Don't miss it.
You've already got her.
Now don't leave that.
And as far as your
fiance is concerned..
..I'm Arjun Ranawat.
Don't worry.
(Laughs) - (Phone rings)
Hello. - (Over
phone) You traitor.
(Over phone) Under your reign,
that inspector, Arjun Ranawat..
(Over phone) ..tortured Yeda
and my men to death, like dogs..
(Over phone) ..while you're
laying eggs on your CM's chair.
(Over phone) Warming
the seat, is that all?
No, Don. The thing is..
- Don't interrupt me.
If you don't take care
of those policemen soon..
..then I'll take care
of your entire family.
But Don, I was..
You wretch.
If I can make a government
with Rs.600 millions..
..I can even blow your head
off with a bullet worth Rs.60..
..and wipe out you and
your entire family.
What's the matter, Mr. Kashi?
Who was it?
It was my boss.
Zafar Supari.
You idiot, Yashwant Deshpande..
..I brought you all
the way from Pune..
..and made you the
police commissioner here.
For what? To dance in
your father's procession?
You didn't do me a favor.
I paid you Rs.25 millions for the post
of the Police Commissioner of Mumbai.
There. Did you hear
that, Kulkarni?
He's crying for his
25 millions rupees.
Explain to your father.
Those encounter specialists
killed Zafar's men.
Were you sleeping?
Now go and dismiss
this Encounter Squad.
I don't want to see this Encounter
Squad again. Do you understand?
That's not in my
power, Mr. Kashi.
Then what's in your power?
The sage's bell?
Am I the Home Minister
of this country?
I told you that it's
not in my power.
Even the DG(Director General) and the
Central Home Ministry are involved in this.
We'll gain nothing
out of anxiety.
Whatever we do, we must
be careful with it.
Mr. Kashi, first decide what
to do with Arjun Ranawat..
..and even before that, decide
what to do with Hyder Ali.
Hyder is Arjun's eyes and ears.
He handles his
entire spy network.
If you eliminate Hyder..
..you can be sure you've
broken Arjun's backbone.
You are right.
Mr. Kashi, I'll
take care of Hyder.
I'll make an issue
of his religion..
..and try for his transfer.
I don't want mere effort.
Make sure he's transferred
and make it quick.
(Music)
Thank you.
Mr. Arjun.
Wait a minute. - Yes.
I know that you are the
strong and silent sort..
..who don't express
their feelings.
But what will you
do with your eyes?
What are you saying?
I mean to say that I
can clearly make out..
..from your eyes that
you love me a lot.
Anything else?
Okay, then tell me.
Should the ring be worn..
..on the finger or
around the neck?
On the nose.
Stop joking. Please tell me.
On the finger.
Then hold my hand and put
this ring on my finger..
..and make me your companion.
Companion? - Yes.
First don't make me suffer so much.
- What?
I'll put the ring on later,
but first put this on.
Jannat, beauty is adored
when it's covered up.
(Music)
"The heart which falls in love"
"That heart becomes
a non believer"
"Then may God be angry with
you or the world leaves you"
"Or even if the
life deserts you"
"In the spirit of love"
"When the magic of
love takes over"
"Then everything seems
to be unfamiliar"
"When the magic of
love takes over"
"Then everything seems
to be unfamiliar"
"Lovers are already crazy, but
even the world seems crazy"
"The intoxication
takes over your eyes"
"The fun of life begins"
"My heart just feels
to be restless"
"In the spirit of love"
(Music)
"There's a sea of
love in my heart"
"You come and sail on it"
"My heart seems to be drowning"
"You come and save it"
"My heart is going
out of control"
"My heart just won't
slow down thumping"
"My heart just feels
to be restless"
"In the spirit of love"
(Music)
"Love is such a thing"
"It's dearer than life"
"It would trade your life"
"It is such a nuisance"
"In the spirit of love"
Hyder Ali, here are
your transfer orders.
You are being transferred from
the job because of your caste.
Hand over your charge
to ACP Arjun Ranawat.
But why, sir?
The special investigation
team is on..
..an operation to investigate
the Mumbai underworld's links..
..with the ISI and are exposing
some of the ISI agents here.
It is their opinion that..
..in this operation,
some of our officers..
..may be gentle to the
alleged ISI agents.
Why don't you say
it clearly, sir?
That I'm being transferred..
..because I'm a Muslim..
..and hence could be helping
the Muslim criminals?
Look at this. Can you
see these bullet marks?
These are marks from bullets
fired by Muslim terrorists.
The bullets coming
out of my gun..
..don't ask a criminal
his caste or religion.
Whether he is a
Hindu or a Muslim.
Through this report,
you want to convey..
..that my caste, my
religion is a proof..
..of me being a traitor.
- Hyder.
No, Arjun.
Even if I cut off my head
and give it to them..
..even then this department..
..would not believe that
Hyder is an honest..
..and patriotic police officer.
No, I don't care. - No.
Hyder don't do it.
Ali don't do it.
I don't want to do
this job, Arjun.
Commissioner, Hyder
Ali is such a Muslim..
..who can sacrifice his
life for his country..
..and his land even
without this uniform.
This is a mistake
on your part, sir.
The traitors have no
caste or religion.
They are neither
Hindu nor Muslim.
The mere fact that I'm a Rajput,
or that you're a Brahmin..
..is not proof of
us being patriots.
Such a cheap criminal thought takes
several youths like Hyder Ali..
..to wrong directions,
distancing them from our country.
Why don't you understand? These
decisions are not taken here.
They are taken in the offices
of the Home Ministry and..
..DGP (Director
General of Police).
If you have the guts..
..go there and tell them
what you just told me.
(Brakes squeal)
Shut up.
You mean that he, who
took his belt off..
..and walked out abusing the police
department in front of a commissioner..
..that ill-mannered junior
of yours is correct?
That we are all non-secular?
Communal?
Is that what you want to say?
If your seniors call you and
tell you that you are a Sikh..
..and that you'd be aiding
the Khalistani terrorists..
..and are therefore being
transferred from Punjab..
..then you'd have
not liked it either.
Sir, if you were not stopped
from fighting Sikh terrorists..
..why is Hyder Ali Khan
being stopped from fighting..
..Muslim terrorists
and ISI agents?
Without any proof or witness..
..just on the
grounds of religion..
..to suspect somebody
is unconstitutional.
Sir..
..our constitution gives prominence
to duty. Best man for the job.
It does not give
prominence to religion.
Sir..
..Hyder Ali Khan
is such a soldier..
..who would like his uniform
to be adorned a million times..
..but would never let it
be tarnished even once.
They have proven me a traitor.
Now, they'll knock me off
in an encounter any day.
What is this? My arrest warrant?
Or is it a search warrant
against a traitor?
No. These are orders
to have two more pegs.
But have it with joy.
- What do you mean?
Read it and you'll know.
Your transfer order
has been cancelled.
You did this for me?
No, for myself.
Because the police department
needs officers like you..
..and I need a friend like you.
- Is that so?
Then you must also
do something for me.
Just ask. - Then listen.
A daughter-in-law like
Jannat for mother..
..a sister-in-law like
Jannat for me and Rakhi..
..and Jannat as your
wife is what we all need.
Cheers. - Cheers.
(Music)
"I'll hide you in my
eyes in such a way"
"However you try to escape,
I'll steal you away"
"In your love my dear"
"In your love my dear,
I'll forget the world"
"However you try to escape,
I'll steal you away"
(Music)
"The vermillion on
my forehead tells it"
"The bangles on
my hands tell it"
"The anklets on my feet tell it.
Listen to it my dearest"
"Listen to it my dearest"
"I'll adorn you
forehead with stars.."
"..I'll fill your
heart with happiness"
"I'll make you my bride.
Listen to it my dearest"
"Listen to it my dearest"
"I've found out my life"
"I've found my happiness"
"I've found my love"
"I'll make heart.."
"I'll make heart as
the mirror of love"
"However you try to escape,
'I'll steal you away"
"I'll hide you in my
eyes in such a way"
"However you try to escape,
I'll steal you away"
"In your love my dear,
I'll forget the world"
"However you try to escape,
I'll steal you away"
(Music)
..on the day of
celebration of our Goddess.
My fortunes have opened up.
May you live long.
Dear, this is a special gift.
Rakhi had it made, so as to
give it to her sister-in-law..
..when she first
enters this house.
Hold this, dear.
May you live long, dear.
May your hands always be around
to protect and bless me, Mother.
Hold this, Mother. Let me show
you the house, Sister-in-law.
Go along, dear.
She is good. You sit down.
I'll arrange for some food.
(Laughs)
Hey, Deshpande..
..you're as nervous as a 16
year old on his first date.
Listen, I'm the
Deputy Chief Minister.
And when the elder
brother is the CM..
..what damage can the report..
..being prepared by ACP
Arjun Ranawat do to us?
Don't you read the newspapers?
If not, start reading them.
Because of the leak in
the Jaiswal report..
..a DGP, a commissioner and..
..a dozen officers are
rotting in custody.
Their bells have been
rung, understood?
Listen, Mr. Kashi.
Arjun is digging into our
nexus with the underworld.
If he succeeds in
establishing that nexus..
..it would dig a grave
for us and the underworld.
Try and get that report
at any cost, Mr. Kashi.
If that report goes to Delhi..
..all of us will be behind bars.
And if.. - (Shushing)
Badri. - Yes!
Those forged documents that are
being printed in our press..
..should be given to me tomorrow.
- Yes, Brother.
And yes..
..regarding that report
by Arjun Ranawat..
..that report will
be on the table of..
..Chief Minister Kashinath
Trivedi tomorrow morning.
(Laughs)
Did you remember something,
ACP Arjun Ranawat?
I told you that one day,
I'll occupy this chair.
(Laughs)
And that you'll salute me.
Do you remember?
You're mistaken, Kashi Trivedi.
I've saluted this
constitutional position..
..and not you.
Those who sit on this chair
keep coming and going.
Stay within your limit.
From today, I'm your master
and you're my servant.
I'm a public servant
and not yours.
I'm a public servant.
And so are you.
Tell me. What did
you call me for?
Then listen.
I've kept the home
ministry with myself.
That's why I gave this order.
The data bank on the Mumbai
mafia that you have compiled..
..give it to me.
I knew it..
..that you'd want the
information on those..
..who helped you reach here.
Take it. Keep it safe.
(Laughs)
Confidential..
So, this is the real deal.
You must have worked very
hard to compile this.
But..
(Laughs)
Saw how I burnt it
to ashes in a moment?
You must be feeling
heartbroken, right?
No. Yours will hurt.
Maybe, you'll even
have a heart attack.
Because one copy of
this has been sent..
..to the Central Home Ministry..
..the second to the
President's office..
..and the third to the
Prime Minister's office.
Your mafia friends
can't escape now.
You're a scalper
for Zafar Supari.
What did you say? You
called me a scalper?
Me.
You called Kashi a scalper?
You called the CM a scalper?
You small-time police
officer, what's your status?
What do you think you are?
Kashi Trivedi, when the
bones break at this age..
..they're set back
with great difficulty.
Take your hands off me.
Now I'll show you your status.
You beat up the CM!
You beat the CM!
No, a patriotic and
honest public servant..
..has beaten up a treacherous
and dishonest public servant.
Kashi Trivedi, my
name is Arjun Ranawat.
To me, death is like a pillow
and a coffin is like a bed.
Jai Hind!
Yes, 555. What is the news?
Who? Arjun sir?
No, I'm Hyder speaking. Tell me.
Sir, the minor girls brought
in for prostitution..
..from different
parts of the country..
..have been hidden in the
old Jassai railway yard.
And they'll be sent to different
brothels in Mumbai tonight.
Please save them, sir.
Don't worry. We'll go
there and save them all.
Please don't kill me, sir.
Leave me.
(Gunshot)
(Brakes squeal)
(Gun cocks)
There's nobody here.
Was the news given by 555 false?
Sir, could this be a trap?
- Yes.
This is a trap.
A trap for all of you to die.
Zafar Supari, you?
Yes, it's me. I'm in India.
Look around you.
Encounter Specialist, I'll
do the encounters today.
Yours, your friend
Arjun Ranawat's..
..and of all of Mumbai.
See, I've brought
500 tonnes of RDX.
Turn around and see.
It's good that
you have brought..
..your own funeral pyre
materials to burn yourself.
Instead of you burning
the city of Mumbai..
..I, Hyder Ali
Khan, will burn you.
(Gunshot)
(Rapid gunfire)
We're trapped, sir. Five
of our colleagues are dead.
We have no option,
but to retreat.
This is not the time
to retreat, friends.
This is the time to pay back our
debt to this uniform we wear.
Today, all of us will
pay back that debt.
How much ammunition
are we left with?
Last magazine, sir.
Friends, our prime target
is destruction of..
..the RDX brought
by Zafar Supari.
I'm moving towards
that direction.
You both will cover me.
Any doubts? - No, sir.
(Gunshot)
(Empty gun clicks)
No!
Oh, God.
(Explosion)
Hyder!
Zafar Supari, you'd set out
to burn all of Mumbai, right?
Look. Hyder Ali Khan
will burn you up..
..in the same burning RDX
pile you brought here.
(Gun cocks)
(Gunshot)
Avasthi? You?
Traitor! - Yes.
Hyder Ali!
(Gunshot)
(Empty gun clicks)
(Phone rings)
Hello.
- Yes, MPS. Maharashtra Police Services.
Go to old Jassai railway yard..
..where the corpses of
your brother, Haider..
..and other colleagues of
yours are waiting for you.
(Cellphone beeps)
(Explosion)
Ashok.
Hyder.
Deepak.
Yashwant Rao.
Hyder.
"The uniform is our pride."
"The uniform is our faith."
"The uniform is our identity."
"The uniform is our God."
Hyder.
"I've sacrificed this
life for my country."
"We are proud of our country"
I'm very sorry to
inform the press that..
..Hyder Ali Khan, the bravest
officer of the Crime Control Squad..
..was a secret agent operating..
..for the underworld and
Pakistan Secret Service, ISI.
Pakistan and the
underworld together..
..had planned for another
serial bomb explosion in Mumbai.
Inspector Hyder Ali
was helping them..
..bring 500 tonnes
of RDX into Mumbai.
Yesterday, Inspector
Avasthi reached the spot..
..and destroyed the
dangerous mission.
Not only did Avasthi destroy
the RDX, but also killed..
..the traitor Hyder Ali
Khan and his accomplices.
During our raids at
Hyder Ali's residence..
..we found some floppies,
foreign bank accounts..
..forged passports and visas..
..and some ISI identity cards.
- (Camera clicks)
These are proof of his having
been a Pakistani agent.
(Phone rings)
Zafar Supari.
'What am I doing?'
'I had vowed not to discuss
that incident with anybody.'
'But today, I've broken my vow.'
'No.'
Tyagi. What is this man saying?
Samar Singh has resigned
from his police job..
..and is going to
fight Ranawat's case?
He has filed a lawsuit in court.
(Chuckles) What is so
alarming in that, Mr. Kashi?
Everybody knows that Samar
Singh is also a lawyer.
But he is also an
emotional lawyer.
But I am a professional lawyer..
..experienced in proving true
as false and false as true.
Let it be. - But we should be..
Mr. Kashi. The false
evidence that we have and..
..the charge sheet I've prepared
is so strong and foolproof..
..that let alone Samar Singh..
..even God can't save Arjun
Ranawat from death penalty.
The game is over.
Your Honor, I would like
to present the officers..
..who have been working with Arjun
Ranawat for the past 15 years.
These witnesses will tell us..
..who Arjun Ranawat is and
what his character is like..
..and what the truth is.
Permission granted.
Your Honor, this is
that Arjun Ranawat..
..who is considered
the lion of Mumbai.
The mafia gangs would shiver in
their boots on hearing his name.
Sir, he's that Arjun
Ranawat because of whom..
..the underworld was
not only forced..
..to leave the city,
but the country too.
Your Honor..
..if the police force..
..didn't have officers
like Arjun and Hyder Ali..
..then these mafias would have
made the police their pimps..
..and Mumbai their brothel.
But this is the misfortune
of this country..
..that one was killed by humiliation
while performing his duties..
..and the other..
..is standing in
this witness box.
I would like to call
Arjun Ranawat's mother..
..Shakuntla Devi
to the witness box.
Permission granted.
Mrs. Shakuntla
Devi, when court..
..will declare your son to be a
traitor and sentence him to death..
..won't you be ashamed
of being his mother?
Won't you regret it?
Regret?
I'll regret that
I didn't bear him.
I'll regret that every
mother of this country..
..didn't give birth
to a son like Arjun.
Not regret, but I'll be
proud of Arjun's death.
The same pride which 'Bhagat
Singh's' (Indian freedom fighter)..
..mother felt on the day of
Bhagat Singh's execution.
Every countryman
would have felt it.
Your Honor, not just in this
life, but in every life..
..I would like to live
and die as Arjun's mother.
(Clapping)
Wow! What a speech!
Astonishing! Incredible!
But I would like to
remind the court..
..that this case is
a mass murder case.
And the criminal has
already admitted his crime.
And Your Honor, I also
want my friend to know..
..that cases are fought with
evidence and witnesses..
..not with speeches
and dramatics.
Also, Your Honor..
..when his mother has already
compared him to Bhagat Singh..
..then to spare that
great martyr's name..
..I'm left with no other
choice, but to unveil a truth..
..after which every
mother and sister..
..of this world would
like to die in shame.
And this mother..
(Chuckles)
..she'll be left
utterly speechless.
Okay, Mrs. Shakuntla Devi.
Tell the court..
..on the night of
1st of November..
..where was your
daughter Rakhi Dixit?
Answer me, Shakuntla Devi.
Where was your daughter
and his so-called sister..
..on the night of
the mass murder?
Answer me. Where was she?
You tell me, Arjun Ranawat..
..on the night of
the 1st of November..
..where was your so-called
sister, Rakhi Dixit?
Answer me, Arjun Ranawat.
Why are you so quiet?
You can't answer this question
and nor can your mother.
I'll answer this question.
Your Honor, on the night
of the 1st of November..
..his sister, a girl
of loose character..
..an aimless and uncultured woman..
- I object, Your Honor.
..was at the chief
minister's farmhouse..
..making merry with the
Deputy CM, Munna Trivedi..
..police commissioner's son and
many other people, Your Honor.
I object, Your Honor.
She was a high society
call girl, Your Honor.
She didn't just have illegitimate
relations with many men..
..but also with her so-called
brother, Arjun Ranawat.
She was his sister during the
day and his mistress at night.
His mistress.
Tyagi!
Arjun! Don't Arjun!
(Groans)
What's this? He's
started with hooliganism.
Somebody stop him.
Guards, security. Catch him.
Guards! Catch him. Hold him.
Arjun! No, son. No, son.
Arjun!
Arjun! I say, no. Leave him.
Swear by me.
(Groans)
(Coughs)
Did you see that, Your Honor?
He doesn't know of any other
way to stifle the truth.
He can't tolerate
any other man..
..in a relationship with Rakhi.
(Coughs)
On the night of 1st November..
..when he found his 'mistress-sister'
with not one, but three men in bed..
..he lost control
in just this way.
And that's why, he
committed that mass murder.
Tyagi!
(Gavel Bangs) Order! Order!
I say, stop it!
Samar Singh, one more inappropriate
action like this from your client..
..will force me to stop
this proceeding right here..
..and come to a conclusion.
Sorry, Your Honor.
Today's proceeding
is stopped here.
Tomorrow's proceeding will
be held in the presence..
..of paramilitary forces..
..and only the people who
are concerned with this case.
Shameless. Rotten scoundrel.
If I wasn't bound by the
boundaries of the law today..
..I would have shot that Tyagi.
By presenting Rakhi
in court tomorrow..
..I'll clear all the lies
Tyagi has been spewing.
But Rakhi cannot come to court.
Why? Why can't she come?
She'll have to come
to court tomorrow.
But sir, she is in deep shock
due to Arjun's killings.
Since she's got the news, she
just won't react to anyone.
She is being treated at the St.
Mary's sanitarium in Khandala.
'There is definitely some secret
that Arjun is hiding from me.'
Don't sit like a rock.
Tell me, Rakhi.
What was the reason behind
that mass slaughter?
One of your brothers, Hyder Ali,
has died a humiliating death.
And the other one is
charged with treason.
Will you be able to bear that..
..your brother Arjun
is sentenced to death?
No.
Will you able to live
after hearing that..
..your brother is a despicable
and disgraceful person?
You stone-hearted woman..
..will you be able to
bear people saying that..
..you had an indecent
relationship with your brother?
Will you be able to listen to the
taunt that you are Arjun's mistress?
No! (Screams)
(Thunder crashing)
Tell me clearly, dear,
what the truth is.
Perhaps, I'll be able
to save Arjun's life.
Tell me what the truth is.
I'll tell you, Uncle.
I'll tell you the truth.
(Crying)
Your Honor, these
are some documents..
..that I'm going
to give to the..
..Chief Minister and
Police Commissioner.
Please watch carefully.
So Chief Minister, what
do you have in your hand?
They are the pamphlets of
my election propaganda.
And this is my newspaper,
'Mera Bharat Mahan.'
Can you tell us where
they are printed?
At my own printing press in Nagpur.
- Good.
So, Police Commissioner. What
do you have in your hand?
This? They are the documents
from Pakistan which mention..
..that Hyder and Arjun
Ranawat are ISI agents.
Pakistan's government's
documents.
According to the reports
given by laboratory experts..
..the ink used in printing
these documents from Pakistan..
..is the same as the ink used
in Chief Minister's newspaper..
..'Mera Bharat Mahan.'
Now, there can only be
two things, Your Honor.
Either Chief Minister's
newspaper 'Mera Bharat Mahan'..
..is printed in Pakistan.
Or documents from Pakistan..
..are printed in his
own printing press..
..which is in
Maharashtra, India.
Your Honor, these
two great people..
..forgot this small point.
And to prove Arjun and
Hyder to be traitors..
..they printed these fake
documents of Pakistan..
..in their own printing press.
Arrest them.
Your Honor, he's
misleading the court.
Because this case isn't a case
of forgery, but of murder.
And no one can change
the truth that..
..the accused has
killed 18 people.
Does his lawyer
have any evidence..
..which will prove that
this murder wasn't a crime?
I have that
evidence, Your Honor.
Then present that evidence
and prove Arjun innocent.
Why are you so silent?
Show us the evidence.
I have the evidence, but I
can't present it in court.
Do you know that this
statement may also..
..result in the guilty
being awarded death penalty?
Yes, sir.
Sentence Arjun to death.
I'm asking you for
the last time..
..what was the reason
for the murder?
Answer me, Mr. Samar Singh.
Sentence him to death.
I can't tell the reason.
Your Honor.
Your Honor, I'll
tell you the reason.
No, Rakhi! You go back.
I'm telling you. Go back, Rakhi.
Swear on me, Rakhi. Go back.
For mother's sake, Rakhi,
back off from this hell.
No, Brother.
Neither any promise, nor
God can stop me today..
..from telling the truth
about our relationship.
Don't get emotional, Rakhi.
You'll be ruined.
Let me be ruined.
Today, I'll tell
what the truth is.
Your Honor, on the night
of the 1st of November..
..the brother of this CM,
Deputy CM Badrinath Trivedi..
..underworld don Zafar
Supari, Inspector Avasthi..
..this commissioner's
son and his men..
..kidnapped me and took
me to their farmhouse.
Your Honor, to rape me.
To gang rape me.
No, please. Brother!
- Come here.
Leave me. Brother!
- Come on, Inspector.
Brother! - Good.
- Save me, Brother. Leave me. No!
No! Brother!
Come on. Come. - No. Save me.
No! - Save me, Brother.
Brother!
No! No!
(Laughs)
(Phone rings)
Encounter Specialist,
Arjun Ranawat.
I'm Zafar Supari.
If you have the guts..
..then come to the
CM's farmhouse..
..and stop your sister
from being raped.
Zafar Supari.
(Tires squealing)
(Gunshot)
(Glass shatters)
(Grunts)
(Screams)
(Rakhi crying)
Brother!
Arjun!
(Sobbing)
This is the truth of that night.
Now does anyone want to know why
my brother has kept his silence..
..and wished for
a death penalty?
Just wait, Your Honor.
Your Honor, I'm a soldier.
I don't want a life of mercy.
My only wish is either
victory or martyrdom.
Give me death penalty.
Because I'll come back again.
And to save the
pride of my country..
..I'll pick up weapons again.
Because Arjun had always taken
up weapons on the battleground..
..in the past, the
present and the future.
This court hereby orders
a case to be filed..
..against the Chief
Minister, Kashinath Trivedi..
..and Commissioner Deshpande
on counts of treason.
And with that, the one who took up
arms for the safety of the society..
..Arjun Ranawat is declared..
..free from all charges
leveled against him.
Long live Arjun Ranawat!
"In the holy book of
Gita Lord Krishna said.."
"..to kill evil is not a sin."
"In the holy book of
Gita Lord Krishna said.."
"..to kill evil is not a sin."
"Death destroys the body."
"The soul is immortal."
"Always fight for justice."
"Every drop of my blood
is for guarding you"
"We are proud of our country"
"We are proud!'
"We will live in victory
and die in victory"
"Die in victory"
"Uniform is our pride."
"Uniform is our belief."
"Uniform is our identity."
"Uniform God is our."
"Gave birth to the country."
"Every drop of my blood
is for guarding you"
"We are proud of our country"