Today I went to Tech Burner's studio.
Bro, the studio is so big that
we had to use hoverboard here,
to go from one side to another.
Then on the way I saw Tech
Burner's 5 lakh rupees dog.
It had a camera in its nose.
It had too many
sensors in the mouth.
And brother, it was showing
it by doing different tricks.
And this is the first dog in my life
whom I slapped and it
did not bite me, poor dog.
Then I saw this red camera
which is usually used in movies.
To lift it, first I had to make
body with dumbbells,
because it was too heavy.
Even its price was equally heavy.
Rs.6.5 lakh.
And this 100TB server was to
keep the big footage of this.
Then I did the first collab of my life,
with Tech Burner.
Overall I learned a lot,
and had a lot of fun.
One more thing is too fun,
that's the subscribe button of "mosttechy".