Param, you are behaving as if
it's Dussehra, on the day of Holi.
Are you high?
The hemp can slow done,
but I am permanently high.
If you stare so much,
you will come down from the
category of a lover to a goon.
Hey, look.
Oh, God. I died.
Sister-in-law.
Param, the next festival
after the monsoon,
is the festival of Raksha Bandhan.
Shut up.
- Think about it.
Be positive.
But Gurpreet you are right.
Maybe I will keep staring
at the girls
during the festivals
and keep shying away
and finally I will be ashamed
in my life.
Do one thing,
- What?
Get me married.
You can’t even love
and you want to marry.
I am not talking of my wedding
but of someone else’s.
You are aware in Punjab, love
happens during other’s weddings.
And in your own wedding,
others are scheming.
The girl is Jasmeet’s friend.
So the guy is ours.
So find out, who will sacrifice.
Find out.
No worries, I have a scheme.
Who will stop Gurpreet Singh
from sacrificing
in this whole village? Tell me?
Correct.
No aunt, don’t,
I have already eaten 12 ice-creams.
If I eat any more I will be frozen.
How is that,
you are young and hot blooded,
if you eat even the ice will melt.
This is only ice-cream.
No, I don’t want, my stomach is full.
You have eaten 12 ice-creams?
And I have not even had one.
We had called 15 people
from his house.
He has come alone.
He deserves to eat the ice-creams.
Aunt, feed her.
Assume I have eaten it.
No, that’s not done.
She isn’t your wife.
That if she eats
and it will enter your body.
Okay, then feed his wife.
Stop.
I am not married.
Engaged?
- No, I myself have stopped.
You must have had an affair.
- No.
But I had fallen in love,
last Dussehra.
With the one,
whom you keep staring
at all the festivals?
The loafers stare,
the lovers, gaze.
It is not ringing in your dreams.
It’s coming from there.
Listen.
- Yes.
I am making an excuse
and going to bring ice-creams.
It’s an excuse of returning late.
So that you both can sit together
and converse.
No aunt, what are you saying?
Your heart must be happy.
If you are not interested,
go and eat ice-cream
with your friends.
I am leaving my stole here and going.
Hear it is.
Ice-cream.
Thank you, aunt.
But, Param is playing with fire.
Jasmeet’s grandfather
is a very orthodox man.
If he comes to know,
he will get the girl
married elsewhere.
Greeting, blessings.
- Bless you.
It was very nice meeting you.
Any progress?
Half. 50%
Means?
From my side.
75%.
It has to be 100%.
Father is coming in 2 hours.
By then set it up.
Is this a movie?
Go down and guard the gate.
Jasmeet.
Should we inaugurate our love?
Yes.
But I have a condition.
- Condition?
I want to work after the wedding.
I am a Jewelry designer,
and want to keep doing it.
But grandfather and brother
will never allow this.
There is only one reason
for me to live
that my husband
will be understanding
and will let me do
what my heart wants.
I have no right to make a decision.
But if I have the right
then the decision
will be in your favor.
The girl can predict,
whether the boy has
passed or failed,
by the way the boy holds her hand.
What is my result?
You have ranked. First class first.
Param, the danger of you
both getting caught is increasing.
Is it?
- Yes.
Then start thinking of new excuses
from tomorrow.
Done.
Hello.
Bless me grandfather,
I am Mitti speaking.
Bless you, dear.
The boy is coming to see me,
if you could send Jasmeet,
then my life would be easier.
Why not? Definitely.
Grandfather if Jasmeet
could help me in History...
Yes, dear.
Grandfather,
if Jasmeet could teach me
how to cook desert...
- Sure, dear.
Grandfather,
the boy is coming to see me.
Again?
Sure, dear.
Greetings, grandfather.
If Jasmeet could...
If Jasmeet could,
if she could teach me to stitch.
Yes, why not, dear.
Grandfather, bless me.
Send Jasmeet,
the boy is coming to see me.
Why don’t you try fasting?
Or else this is go on forever.
Yes, I will try that too.
Don’t you have any other excuse?
There are not so many boys in Punjab,
the number of times
you have used this excuse.
Aren’t you ashamed?
Who will find
new excuses every day?
If it can be used, let it be.
Hurry up.
Sit down.
The gate is locked,
now nobody can come in.
Brother has to do for his brother.
Starters are not ready.
Get two cottage cheese pancakes.
- Sure.
Wow, my favorite.
Is it the sweet one?
Last time there was lot of salt.
Drink.
You are sad.
What happened?
So my lover has reached that stage
where he can x-ray me with his eyes.
What kind of lover is he,
if he can’t know her heart?
Come on, tell me.
After seeing my designs,
a jewelry designer from Amritsar
has called me.
For the job of a consultant.
That’s amazing.
They are paying me well too.
Then why are you sad?
You should be happy.
I can’t understand girls.
You can’t understand girls
because girls are not supposed
to be understood.
It’s thrice in a week.
Grandfather and brother
have blankly refused.
Because I am a girl.
That’s why I am barred.
Sorry.
Grandfather and brother
are doing wrong by stopping me.
Then I too will cheat with them.
Will you drop me to Amritsar,
thrice a week?
It’s a matter of three days,
so will have three excuses to drop
and pick you from Amritsar.
Done.
Don’t hug me like this, girl.
You don’t know,
what all thoughts, run in my heart.
Param, statue.
Such expensive, glares?
You spent your whole salary
on this or what?
It’s my salary,
I can spend on whoever I want.
Now, what is this?
New clothes for you. Wear it.
Have you started taking loans?
No, this is from my bonus.
Hey, buddy.
Yes, father.
- Son.
You have been wearing this
since a week.
Take it out.
Or the municipality guys
will throw you out.
Greetings, grandfather.
Send Jasmeet,
the boy is coming for alliance.
Do boys come every day to see you?
Not every day, thrice a week.
Has your father fixed this,
or is it written outside
your house,
see the girl on this day only.
Monday, Wednesday, Friday, is good.
Have I ever called you on Saturday
or Sunday or Tuesday or Thursday?
That is true.
All right. Best of luck.
Keep the phone away sometimes,
everyone has equal share on it.
Greetings, grandfather.
Its baby shower.
Congratulations.
Greetings, grandfather.
The other girls are having
their baby showers.
You are still stuck
with the boys alliances.
What’s the matter?
Lala.
- Yes.
What happened?
- What happened?
What about Mitti?
What happened to Mitti?
Did Mitti’s alliance work out?
What was supposed
to happen to Mitti?
Since 6 months, every week,
she is meeting boys thrice,
so at least 72 boys have seen her.
Then what happened?
- Listen,
you may be big built.
But I too have grown up
watching wrestlers.
Don’t talk nonsense.
I was just enquiring,
you have seen so many boys,
and then do you like any of them?
What are you talking?
Mitti’s wedding
has been fixed a year ago.
With Amarnath’s son, Kapil.
Who told you all this?
You are working behind our backs?
You are travelling
to Amritsar alone.
What is so wrong in working,
grandfather?
It is wrong to go against
our wishes.
Why is there so much disparity
between brother and me?
It’s a man’s duty to feed a woman.
And a woman’s duty is
to give birth to his children,
and take care of them.
That is the difference.
Find a groom for her.
Jasmeet, everything will be fine.
The iron is hot now, strike it.
Even if the house changes,
the fate of the girls
doesn’t change.
Chill. Once you come to my house.
Then how does his rule
and regulations matter?
Please, eat.
What was the need
of writing a letter?
You could have just told.
For the first time, I am talking
about the marriage proposal,
so was hesitant.
I won’t do it next time.
What nonsense I am talking.
If I meet Jasmeet’s grandfather
for you marriage proposal then...
What will I get?
You will have to spend now,
after 5 years a granddaughter
or son.
I am not asking for any investment
scheme, but grandchildren.
Five years?
Gave 3.
- No, 4.
Done deal at 3 and half.
Done.
- Done.
Congratulations.
Jasmeet, come.
Jasmeet is going to become
the daughter-in-law of your family.
But I have one condition.
Food, and clothes,
will be according to your wishes.
But you have to promise one thing.
But after the wedding,
Jasmeet will not go out to work.
The world is changing.
Then it's Jasmeet’s wish.
There is no limit
for wishes and desires.
But it’s about our society.
The world is changing,
then why hasn’t
the society changed.
I am elder than you.
Then too I am folding my hands
and requesting you.
Sir, you are elder,
don’t do this.
Then promise.
Promise.
Sorry, girl.
I know how much you wanted to work.
It’s not about working,
or doing a job.
It’s about having the independence
of making your own decision.
Which I never had, nor ever will.
Forget it, everything will be fine.
Nothing will ever be fine.
You are a man,
you will not understand.
I don’t understand your desire
to live independently?
Father respected your grandfather
and promised him.
If you want,
I can still break this relation.
I dream,
but I am not mad.
I had two dreams,
one to live my life
on my own terms.
And other to marry you.
The first one will not be fulfilled.
- Hey.
Let me complete the second wish.
Okay, so where will you take me
for our honeymoon?
Honeymoon will begin here.
Because you know,
when you hug me like this,
then what all kinds
of thoughts run in my heart.
Param.
- Jasmeet.
Greetings.
God bless, son.
Everything is alright.
Welcome.
You have become a stranger
after getting married.
We don’t get to see you.
She wants to go to Switzerland
for honeymoon.
Switzerland.
- Honeymoon.
Means setting is final.
Wow. Congratulations.
Hey, get a beer.
Sure.
No, beer.
- Why?
It’s not finalized.
Where is the visa?
All the property, papers, income,
is in father’s name.
Then I can’t get the visa.
How will I go?
Why are you tensed,
when Gurpreet is around?
It’s a shame then.
Listen, you give all the documents.
I will gift you the honeymoon visa
on your wedding.
When will father help?
You don’t worry.
You have a beer. Bring the beer.
Make a large one for me.
Did you make a large peg?
It is so diluted.
Are you in your senses?
I have never touched it,
and you sprayed it on me.
The enlightened one,
impart your knowledge elsewhere.
It only fell on  your clothes,
not down your throat.
Fell on my clothes. Rubbish.
Param.
Apologize.
It's okay. He has no manners.
He is your friend, he is our guest.
Let it be.
I will forgive the guest.
But how can I forgive my friend.
- Param.
He has to apologize. Shut up.
He has to make it right.
Apologize.
- Param, leave me.
Say sorry.
- Param.
Param, let me go.
Param let it be.
- Param, let me go.
Param, let me go.
Param, you have insulted me
in front of everyone.
It’s okay.
You have exploited me a lot
in friendship.
Now you will come to know about
the losses due to enmity with me.
You are in a mood of going to
Switzerland for your honeymoon.
I will not allow your visa
to be passed.
And if you get your visa,
deal with me.
Get lost.
I will not get your visa done.
Watch now.
Thank you.
Your lunch. My lunch, check.
Phone, check.
Glares, check.
Okay, I am leaving. Bye.
Keys, check.
You can drive without the keys?
Why do I have the feeling that
I am not going to get
this key back for free?
Because the Jat,
has a bad character.
And he will not give anything
for free.
Now, I am getting very late.
Come.
Take it.
Leave me. Leave.
Leave me.
Leave.
Girl.
- Yes.
Return back from abroad.
Gurpreet Singh has cancelled
so many times that,
I have no other option
to go abroad, except in my dreams.
But you have a good scheme
to go abroad.
Cheap, pretty and long lasting.
I get depressed every morning.
Today don’t get depressed,
but impressed.
Have to meet grandfather today,
have to go to your house.
Yes, that it is.
So we have another chance
to talk about the job.
Lovely, my life is made.
No, life is yet to be set.
You know, my character is bad.
Nothing is free.
Get started. Please start.
Leave.
- Don’t be shy.
You haven’t even brushed.
After one year of the wedding
you are talking of brushing.
After 3 years
you will talk of bathing.
You talk a lot.
Then seal my lips.
Why do you make
your lover chase you?
If you don’t make
your guy chase you,
then he will chase someone else.
You can make me run here or there,
this lover will always be behind you.
Today, convince grandfather
for my job.
Such a petty request,
I can kill for this.
Murder.
Son, it’s been a year
since you are married.
I want my grandchildren voice
to echo in this house now.
Unlike the working women.
Who for years are
after their career?
Then keep visiting various doctors
and ask for help.
Do you understand?
Hello.
- Param.
Have to take Bhavri
for an injection.
Okay, dad.
Make her also sit behind.
It’s good if she walks a bit,
she has put on a lot of weight,
bull will divorce her.
Jasmeet.
Harpreet.
Who is she?
Harpreet, she was studying with me
in high school.
She failed in 8th grade
so she never came back to school.
She had never travelled
outside Amritsar.
She is married in London.
Hi, Jas.
We are very, very sweet, yo.
You are so cute, totally.
How are you?
When did you come from London?
How is Sukhwinder?
Busy, busy, busy. You know.
He doesn’t get a leave.
He is at a high post,
so has severe headaches too.
But I told him, hello, excuse me.
It’s been 5 years. I am going
to India, at times I miss a lot.
I get so nostalgic sometimes, Jas.
- I know.
Oh, so it’s only been 5 years,
since you have shifted to London?
- Yes.
After listening
to your fluent English
I thought you were born there.
This is my husband. Param.
Hi.
- Hello.
He jokes a lot.
I am not a jockey, I am a farmer.
I have done M.Sc.,
in agriculture sciences.
I meant you are very humorous.
Funny.
That’s why I cracked this joke.
So what does your husband do
at London?
At London’s Heathrow airport.
He has the responsibility
of keeping the airport,
eco-friendly on his strong shoulders.
Wow.
Come home along with me,
we will catch up over a cold drink.
Okay, you go.
Catch up over a cold drink.
I will get her injected.
Injection? Is everything alright?
Yes, everything is good.
You, see this buffalo,
she is preggers,
so I am just going to take her
for a shot. Nothing else.
Wow, you speak English so well.
You should be in London.
You are wasting your talent
by giving shots to the buffaloes.
Frankly I am telling you.
Okay, let’s go.
It was good meeting you.
- Same here.
I was sweating in this heat.
If you are healthier than me,
but to go out here,
have to wear 8 meter cloth.
You know what I mean.
Really, in London,
I can just go like this,
and whoever I meet, Indian
or others, hello, hi, greetings
and will leave.
But here if I leave,
then there will be my MMS made
called, fun sister-in-law.
Do you remember Chutki?
How had a faint moustache?
Yes, moustache suits her.
She is the hero of the house.
After having two kids,
she went to college
and now she is a lawyer for women.
You too has
reached heights, Harpreet.
Yes, look at me.
I am no longer a village belle,
I mean I have worked on myself.
I went to a night school,
did a course of a beautician.
I taught myself English.
Means, bank account, kids,
I can manage all kinds of work.
It’s great.
But you tell me,
first class first.
You had showed us the dream
to prove ourselves.
We are conquering forts
and you have become a housewife and
giving injection to the buffaloes.
What do you think?
Did I not see the dream
of doing something?
But you are also aware,
here girls don’t have
any freedom to do anything.
Yes, I know.
That’s why girls like me marry
and run away from here.
Dreams like ours can
only be fulfilled by going there.
My dream will never be fulfilled.
The reason is Gurpreet Singh Karon.
He was rude to my father
during the wedding.
Param raised his hands on him.
Param did the right thing,
but Gurpreet is very influential.
After a lot of effort also,
Param is unable to get the visa.
I have a solution to your problem.
Gurnaam Singh Visa.
But will your hero,
take the illegal path?
Look.
Where do I see?
Should I write the property
in your name on this paper?
Please see carefully. Get up.
I have seen you very carefully.
Look, for a minute.
Harpreet has given,
the number of Gurnaam Singh.
This can help us in settling
in England.
So today’s idea of the
wedding night was of Harpreet’s.
You keeps doing this
to your innocent husband.
Idea was of Harpreet,
but it was my wish.
You have looted me by emotions,
come, my girl.
Please, not now. Listen to me.
I am sure after seeing Harpreet.
After going to London
all out troubles will end.
Okay.
But have to talk to father.
I will not go anywhere
without his permission.
Yes.
Carefully.
Father.
Yes.
I wanted to talk to you.
Speak.
Father, I...
Father, I mean...
Father, Param is unable
to tell you that,
he wants to settle down in London.
Half of Punjab is settled there.
You also go there.
Father, you are happy
with my decision?
Look,
when I had a heart attack.
Then you were into the fields
like the bulls.
After studying so much at Amritsar.
You never wished to stay
in the city.
You have given 5 years
to the family.
That is...
Now it’s the time for your family.
I will call you
as soon as I get settled.
You have to teach my children too.
I will come and teach that,
like my son is,
they too have to be like that.
Be like him.
Yes, father.
Take this.
Look after, I will be back.
Where?
- Over there.
"Dance with joy."
"Come, talk to me."
"You have good mannerism."
"I've given my heart to you."
"Dance with joy."
Enough.
Enough of it, dear.
You are a big star.
When you will sing
and the world will hear,
then they will forget
Wadali brothers.
Wadali brothers are two,
he is alone.
If he calls himself as both,
then he will be called a star.
Darling, what are you seeing,
bring snacks and drinks,
for the star.
And listen.
Don’t put ice in the butter milk.
Star’s voice is a gold mine.
If he will ice there will a flood.
Yes.
Okay darling, go to the next room,
fill up the form.
Have you got money from father?
Deposit it.
Don’t go without
drinking the butter milk.
Good morning.
Don’t worry, darling,
not only visa, I will send you
to America without passport too.
Okay, don’t want to say,
then hang up the phone.
Look darling,
he is being tensed, even after
being a client of Gurnaam Singh.
Is it the first time that
I am sending anyone overseas,
without the passport.
He isn’t tensed about going,
but returning back
after being caught.
Darling, some people do get caught.
But so does an aircraft crashes
every year.
Does that mean that
people get scared and stop sitting
in the plane.
Sir, you give very good examples.
You give good examples,
or give visa too.
Who are you?
Who is he?
Do you have an appointment
or disappointment?
I will be disappointed if you
don’t get the England done for me.
Harpreet said, you will surely
make me reach England.
Param Singh,
who never gets his visa?
Listen,
for young Punjabis to get visa
is as difficult as terrorist
getting heaven.
But darling, you don’t worry.
I will make you reach your heaven.
Can’t I go alive, with a visa.
Darling Gurpreet Singh Karon,
is not giving you the visa.
And I will not let you stay
in India.
Father will not let me go by,
trafficking.
Darling, you are grown up,
and still you are still scared
of your father.
I was never scared of him,
even in my childhood.
But I respect him from childhood.
You have won my heart.
And along with it visa too.
So much respect for parents.
Look.
Oh, your parents.
No, darling.
This is Yashpal Singh
in front of the rickshaw.
Same to same Yashpal
is standing next to BMW.
And to make him stand next to a BMW
is London’s lady Maya.
She had mercy on him,
got married to him
and took him to London
and went away.
Darling, this is the only way.
Darling, go to London and laugh.
You have started
laughing here, itself.
Gurnaam, you have done it
without the visa.
I just can’t stop laughing.
I was going to bash him.
Then I remembered,
already Gurpreet has taken away
all our visas.
If I hit him,
I will not even be able to go
to Bangladesh in my life.
But what did he say?
I can’t even repeat it. Let it be.
If you were there and heard it,
you would have murdered him,
Jasmeet.
But what did he say?
He said, darling...
No need to be romantic.
He said 'darling'.
- Oh.
He calls everyone darling.
He said you marry a girl
from London.
She will get you a visa and
take you along with her,
you will get residency
after a few days, then divorce her.
Then come back here and
get married to Jasmeet again
and then go back to London.
He said this.
Jasmeet there is
no use of getting angry.
Listen to me, leave it.
Please.
Leave it. Please.
Mr. Gurnaam.
Param Singh has come with his wife.
Should I increase your security?
My security is in my head.
Let them come.
Sister-in-law. Greetings.
I know you are very upset with me.
Anyone will flare up,
since when I have constrained her.
Sister-in-law, your husband
is very handsome.
And handsome men are very foolish.
I want to explain to you.
This is only...
That this will only be acting.
I understand.
You are not at all handsome.
So I thought
you will be intelligent.
And if you are smart,
then I could not understand
why you were unable
to make him understand.
I was so stupid, I was not
able to understand your reaction.
Sister-in-law, I did not know,
that before explaining to you,
I have to explain him.
Or else I would have
explained earlier.
Happy, sister-in-law is looking.
Bring sweet on this joyous occasion.
Sweets for what?
No need of any sweet.
Sit. Sit down.
Why are you sitting?
- Please be seated.
Hey, Jasmeet.
Darling, you must be watching movies.
I do, so.
So when Shahrukh acts like
the husband of Deepika.
Then he doesn’t cry or blabber
in front of the director.
Director sir, I am married to Gauri.
How can I marry someone else?
I cannot do acting of love
and marriage. I can’t do.
But who will be the director there?
There will only be the lady and me.
And Gauri too never
gets suspicious of Shahrukh.
Because she knows, that Shahrukh
is just acting for her and kids.
Sister-in-law, you explain
much better than me.
You get it,
you have to become Shahrukh.
But Shahrukh is acting,
not going to a government office and
marrying in the morning with Deepika,
then divorcing her and night
and marrying Gauri again.
What are you saying?
Your role is lengthier and
better than Shahrukh, darling.
This is a moment of happiness.
Darling, get inspired by Shahrukh.
Don’t focus on the time
but on acting.
What if I get more inspired.
What if the naughty man inside me
gets instigated?
What if the lady
starts over acting?
Darling, I will manage the lady.
But sister-in-law, if the actor
doesn’t have faith on his acting.
Then what can I do?
What rubbish.
I am saying with right means,
neither can you go to London
nor to Tata.
Don’t scare me.
If you want to get angry on me,
then do it.
You taunted me? I will slap you.
Have you gone mad?
Have you lost it?
What nonsense
were you saying there?
I will get married to another woman
and go away
and it won’t affect you?
It is not a real wedding.
It’s just a compromise.
After compromising so much in life,
it has stopped effecting me.
After all this, once we go there,
all compromises
will come to an end.
Please, understand.
You want to play such a gamble
for your independence in life.
Not only me, but any girl
who is living my life will agree.
They don’t even have a chance
to live their life.
I have, and the reason is you.
Param, I trust you more than
my own self.
I can make a mistake,
but you will not.
Jasmeet it does not matter
where we stay.
With whom we stay
and how much they love me.
That makes the difference.
Give me my independence here,
I will not go.
Is it so wrong to dream?
There is no harm in dreaming.
To fulfill it in the wrong way is.
By doing this,
you are gambling your marriage.
But I cannot do this.
Param, come.
Today you thought of me
after your wedding?
Come, dear.
- Gurpreet,
I have come to apologize.
If you want I will apologize
in front of the whole village.
No need to say sorry.
You are my friend. I forgive you.
Thank you.
But...
on whose legs you had made me fall,
let him bow down to my legs.
Then it is equal.
Sister-in-law.
I was tensed searching for you.
What are you thinking? Come, sit.
I will drop you to London.
Sister-in-law, I will send you
to London on a work visa.
Come.
Param.
The trouble has come.
- Param.
What happened?
You will not believe what happened.
I will, tell me.
I got a job in London.
And you will go?
Leaving me.
Alone.
But we had spoken about this.
We had decided.
But you had promised,
that she will not do a job.
Grandfather,
she is just going on a work visa.
She will stay at my friends place
and enjoy her holiday.
Gurpreet should hear this.
Then he will say that,
he is making his wife overseas.
He will spoil
my reputation much more.
He will forget.
But what will happen by then.
My friend will somehow
get a residency for Jasmeet.
Once I get the visa for residency.
No law can separate a couple.
Jaspreet will call me there
and Gurpreet cannot do anything.
It’s a plan.
This is not the place, girl.
You know,
when you hug me like this,
then so many naughty thoughts
run in my heart.
This is the departure lounge.
We may be separated, but
we should get a room at least.
Don’t try to make me laugh,
I will cry.
Don’t stop me
from talking nonsense.
Or else I will cry.
I have...
I have hidden something from you.
Jasmeet, let’s go.
I am marrying Samar
and going on a marriage visa.
I am sorry.
I have done all this for us.
Trust me. Forgive me.
Take care of yourself.
I have to go.
Grandfather.
Jasmeet.
Bless me, grandfather.
- Live long, dear.
Samar would have sweet talked
a lot to you.
But he is a number one rogue,
government official.
Whether anyone understand or not,
you surely will,
that’s why I dared to do this.
Sam.
Hey, guys.
How's it going?
Alright, thank you so much.
The literacy levels of UK
are going to fall.
Sam has imported such a villager.
Hey Sam.
- Hello, darling, how have you been?
Happily and married.
How did all this happen?
Wait, let me guess.
Lust at first sight.
But without a wedding,
a Punjabi girl would
not have agreed.
No, it will be in your case.
Lust at first sight but,
the rest you had agreed
without the wedding.
So I was right,
she dint agree so you married her
and got her.
Excuse me.
And by the way, like this...
Jasmeet, this is Alisha.
Alisha, this is Jasmeet.
Hi.
- Hello.
You know what,
he is my childhood friend.
And a very big idiot.
If he troubles you,
just let me know.
I want to set him right.
Isn’t it, Sam?
Excuse me.
Hello.
It’s me Jasmeet.
Not so many days have passed
that you have to tell your name.
You are upset with me?
You hate me?
I am trying my best.
Even after 8 beers,
I still miss you
and not feel anger.
Why are you so nice?
Scold me.
Abuse me.
Why did I do? How did I do?
At least ask me that much.
You had written,
whether anybody else understands
or not, I will understand.
So then I have understood,
what is there to ask.
'Sister-in-law,
you watch pictures,
I will tell you story.'
'The pictures are of the heroes.'
'Samar Singh Sandu, alias, Sam.'
'He has lot of wealth.'
'But he just has a relative
a grandfather.'
'Who is unwell
and is 90 years old.'
'And on top of that he has cancer.'
'I have many girlfriends
in London.'
'I have a rocking social life.'
'But my grandfather feels that
if I don’t marry an Indian girl.'
'Then my life style
will destroy my life.'
'So for his happiness,'
'Sam is marrying a beautiful,
Punjabi girl.'
'But fake.'
'There will be no relation
between us.'
'You will not even touch me.'
'You are doing it
for your grandfather,
and I am doing
for citizenship of UK.'
'For both these things,
till we require to remain married,
we will.'
'Sister-in-law, don’t let Sam know
that you are already married.'
'Or else the deal will break.'
It’s okay
if the world says I am wrong.
Will you forgive me?
Then I don’t care about the world.
I had forgiven you at the airport.
Or else you would
not have boarded the flight.
And I would not be at home,
but at the jail.
Because you are so good,
I take advantage of you.
Getting married again
despite of being married,
and you call it taking advantage?
Param, this is not a marriage.
And our wedding?
Does that remain a marriage?
Remains, absolutely.
Even if you would have to London
then also it would have remained.
I have come here,
then also it will remain.
And will remain forever.
You just wait for me to come
and fetch you here.
Whether you are here or there,
you are good at waiting.
Not I.
I want to go to London.
Legal, illegal. Everything is fine.
Darling, before Gurpreet
comes to know,
you go along with my men,
you cross Bengal
and enter Bangladesh.
From Dhaka, you take a small boat,
and in the middle of the ocean,
you will be transferred
to a bigger boat.
From where you will reach Brussels.
What happened? Are you mad?
There are more than 50 people here,
and I thought that only my girl
is crazy after England.
Jasmeet.
We need to take some
new clothes for you. Let’s go.
New clothes? I have clothes.
You can’t wear
these kinds of clothes in my circle,
to look like my wife.
You need a makeover.
Jasmeet, hold on.
I am going to pay for it.
No, I have money.
We will only do that much
for each other,
what we had promised.
Thank you.
Awesome.
Girl, bless you dear.
You have brought me back
to my roots.
Without the tickets.
Even my accent has changed.
I am saying,
tic kas instead of tickets.
My dear, now I can
attain salvation definitely.
That too without effort.
Move aside.
Give me some more.
It’s less for me.
Here you will only get this much.
Old man. Move.
What to do,
have to bear this much.
Have left Punjab in search
of a job to get food.
Grandfather, you can get food
at a Gurudwara too.
You can get however much you want,
that too free.
We go overseas for luxuries,
like bungalows and cars.
Not because of food.
From Brussels you will go
to Paris via train.
Because when once you enter Europe,
then they don’t check
your passport.
The biggest danger
of the whole journey is
at Clive check post.
The check using carbon dioxide,
if anyone is hidden
inside the truck.
You have to cover your head
with a plastic bag.
And whatever happens,
even if you lose your life,
the bag should not be taken out.
Remember it.
London girl.
If I wasn’t married,
I would have surely married you.
What have you become?
Where are you staying?
Don’t worry about me,
I have planned everything.
I had told you in Punjab,
I had no problem, of you having
a fake wedding and coming here.
Then why do you have a problem?
I had also said there,
that I don’t have a problem,
in you coming here.
Problem is of lies,
with this drama.
I am doing this drama
for both of us.
For us to settle down here.
Till we get a visa to stay.
I will do whatever possible.
I will have to lie to Samar.
I will lie.
I have taken such a big risk,
lowered myself in everyone’s eyes.
And I have come here.
Param, now I will not go back.
Whatever happens?
Your grandfather, your whole family
did wrong with you.
For that you can’t take revenge
from the whole world.
The war is only fought,
where it belongs to.
I...
Hello.
- Hey it’s me.
Listen we have to go
for the inauguration of Zaika.
Zaika?
It’s an Indian restaurant.
You reach home,
we should be leaving soon.
Okay, I coming.
I have to go for the inauguration
of an Indian restaurant.
I have to go.
You are just tasting this place
or have started working too?
For which, you had come here.
The job that I want to do,
I cannot do,
till I get my residency.
It’s not possible legally.
But I have prepared everything.
Spoken to the Jewelers,
my designs are ready too.
Everything is ready.
Once I get my residency.
Nobody can stop me.
Jasmeet I thought it was
your childishness.
But this city has become
your obsession.
First time...
I am witnessing a woman’s affair
not with a man, but with a city.
Since I have come already,
let me see after all
what this city is about.
But Girl, remember.
I am a true lover.
I will only be in peace
after removing
this obsession from you.
Finally after reaching London,
you will meet a man,
whose name is Iqbal Khan,
from Rawalpindi, Pakistan.
Darling, he will help you onwards.
Param.
- Yes.
So you are an army man.
I am a farmer. Doing M.SC.
A fresher from Punjab.
Here illegal guys
are called army men.
Oh, that’s respect.
In our country, an army man
expels the illegal guys.
You are a jolly guy.
You come along me
to Buckingham Palace. Come on.
This is your Buckingham Palace.
Only the queens don’t live here,
only the kings.
This is Shyam.
And he is Murlidharan.
And that’s mine.
Illegal Asian tiger’s versus
legal home department of England.
Since 10 years the trophy
belongs to us.
I will teach you the trick
of roaming freely as the army men.
My bed?
We won’t let you sleep
in the drawing room.
This is your lavish bed room.
This is the bathroom.
From morning 6 to night 10.
After that,
it turns into a bedroom.
But you have to sleep
after 10 o clock.
Come, I will show you more.
Keep the empty boxes.
She is my wife and,
she my daughter.
When I left home, she was still
in her mother’s womb.
I saw her on video call.
But I could never pull her cheeks.
Could never play with her
on my lap.
This is the biggest problem
of the Punjabis.
Whenever we meet the other Punjabi
the flood of tears start flowing.
Oh, my kids, my wife.
If we loved them so much,
then why did we leave our land?
And come to London to earn pounds.
But I have an answer for it.
Even if I am not there,
their lives are sorted.
Life is set.
This answer of yours is wrong.
You are here, she is there.
How is their life sorted?
I started off, on the first day.
You enjoy. I will get beer.
Then will cry, I mean will talk.
Let’s go.
Iqbal.
- Yes.
Show me an address?
Rest of the beer
I will drink there.
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Cheers.
This is for you.
What is this?
For what you have done
for grandfather.
This is nothing
in comparison of that.
A girl can make so much
of a difference in someone’s life.
I learnt, after meeting you.
Thank you for the lesson.
Trust me, it’s a gift.
Please, no gifts.
I don’t want to divorce you.
Because I really like you.
You are a fantastic person.
You are attractive,
and we are formally married too.
Jasmeet Malhotra.
Finally you reached London.
Wow,
that’s what I called a Desi Hunk.
Oh God, one more Indian.
UK, government
should ban these Indians.
You speak another word about him.
And I am going to kill you.
Do you guys know each other?
Know each other?
We both marry...
Wedding.
We both used to go
to the village weddings
and whack ice-creams
and sweets and deserts.
That’s why our bodies
are like this.
You should have told.
- By the way, I am Sam.
Nice to meet you, man.
Actually Jasmeet will give
a better introduction of mine.
Introduce me, Jasmeet.
He is Param Singh. My...
He is my...
- Neighbor.
You took so long to say neighbor.
Your Hindi has become poor,
in London.
But don’t worry,
I will improve your Hindi.
Sam we are neighbors.
- Okay.
Hey gorgeous lovely people.
Ladies and gentleman,
we know that you.
All like to do a bit of Bhangra.
So girls and boys, get ready,
let’s get some dancing.
Jasmeet, you were amazing.
You have hidden
a lot about yourself.
This is just the beginning. Sam.
She is a stock of surprises.
She has surprises in Kilos.
Look she doesn’t get angry.
But when she rolls her eyes
that means it time to shut up.
Param, can I drop you somewhere?
I always get dropped by girls.
You too drop me.
Come, my car is right there,
see you guys.
Bye.
- Bye.
It was nice meeting you, Sam.
- You too, Param.
I will see you soon.
- Yes, surely.
Jasmeet, I will be there,
waiting for you. - Yeah.
It was very nice
meeting you too, Jasmeet.
We will dance again,
I mean will meet again.
Yes, we have to meet.
Don’t trouble Alisha much.
And don’t let her trouble you also.
I can take my guarantee, not hers.
Alisha, where have you got me?
This seems like a hill station
in London.
How does it matter?
Don’t bite, it will help me
in wearing spectacles in old age.
What’s wrong, Param?
You don’t find me attractive?
Attractive?
If in Punjabi
we have a girl like you,
then we call it Diwali Bumper.
Then why are you acting funny?
I hope you have a reason
to act like this?
Wedding.
I am married man.
Param,
I like experienced men.
I am married to Jasmeet.
And I have come to London for her.
Punjabi girl was looking so...
Sam, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Helping you to decide.
Sam, please.
You know what,
I am not used to hearing a no.
We both had promised something
to one another.
I am abiding my promise.
You too abide.
What if I break my promise?
What if I don’t divorce you?
Do you know,
if today I tell Jasmeet,
that live in London without me?
Or come back to India with me.
She will come quietly come back
with me.
She loves me so much, mad girl.
But I don’t want her to be helpless
and take this decision.
I want her to take the decision
with her heart.
If there were more boys like you.
Then I too would have been married.
So, I will help you to stay.
Thank you.
But what is the point
of just staying.
I don’t think, Jasmeet will go back
to India again.
In today’s world, marriage, love,
has no importance.
Has no value.
Even today there is
only one thing left.
On which the whole world
is dependent.
Love.
My Jasmeet will surely come back,
and I know how.
You get married to me.
Fake.
If she finds me making a mistake.
Maybe she herself
will realize her mistake.
Mad girl will understand.
To first hurt someone and then
search for happiness is stupidity.
It’s stupid.
It’s very profound.
And it sounds like fun. I must say.
Okay, I am ready.
But here is the deal.
Till the exact time of the wedding,
if Jasmeet realizes her mistake,
and she is ready to go
to India with you.
Then it’s fine.
But if it doesn’t happen.
Then there will
surely be a wedding.
Not a drama but for real.
Means.
You will not marry me otherwise,
this is my single chance
to marry you.
So are you ready for this bet.
I am serious, Param.
I know you are serious.
Done.
I trust my Jasmeet completely.
And I believe this world.
Let see who wins.
The game starts tomorrow.
What happened, guys?
Why aren’t you all sleeping?
His daughter is unwell.
What happened?
Got a call from the hospital.
She is admitted there.
Have faith.
Everything will be fine.
I trust him only.
Otherwise, I have done
what my heart desired.
Alisha.
You look lovely.
Thank you. How are you?
- Very nice.
Hi, Jasmeet.
- Ht.
You look beautiful.
So, yesterday night’s dance,
and today’s surprise party?
Is there really a surprise or...?
What will be the surprise
if I tell you?
I had told you, we will meet again.
I had told you, we had to meet.
But here, like this,
I had not imagined.
Oh brother is here too,
what a surprise.
What is surprising in this,
Jasmeet’s husband
will be with Jasmeet.
Not necessary,
now a day’s many husbands
are not with their wives.
Isn’t it, Jasmeet?
Anyways you guys carry on.
I will see you around.
You guys discuss your stories,
I will be back.
Param, will you look
after your friend.
If she allows me,
then I surely will.
Why has he come here?
I like him.
Yuck, Alisha.
Chill out, enjoy your party.
Hi guys, see you.
What is all this?
Why were you not picking up my phone?
I was sleeping.
Where?
How does it matter?
Why are you asking this question?
Did she do something with you?
Till day I have not suspected Sam.
Then why are you suspecting Alisha.
Very bad.
Don’t procrastinate, answer me.
You are asking questions
like wives do.
I am your wife.
Oh, you remember. Congratulations.
I thought you must have forgotten.
Couldn’t you find anyone else,
to be friendly.
She is that type of a girl.
What are you saying?
She is a very good girl.
I can’t find a girl like her
in Punjab.
Do you know, even while staying
in London, she is a vegetarian.
So what if she doesn’t eat meat.
She eats men.
She has slept with half
the people present in this party.
You remember,
Babli from my high school.
She is like that.
If someone tells her to sit,
she will lie down.
If people know that
she is a naughty girl,
why do they tell her to sit?
When she is back, I will tell her,
Alisha don’t sit, not at all.
Whoever says anything don’t sit.
- Param,
I don’t like you getting friendly
with her.
Whether you do something or not.
What If I say the same thing?
You have no answer.
Jasmeet you enjoy the party.
And let me also.
Where is the bar?
How are you? Are you enjoying?
Yes I was going to. You halted me.
Party with London’s high society.
Everyone will enjoy.
Especially if he comes
from such a place,
where there is nothing
except dust and dirt.
By the face, you look
as if you are made of the same mud.
No, I am British.
I was born here.
I have never gone to India,
And I don’t like
to be called an Indian.
Mr. Trishanku,
you don’t like being
called an Indian.
You are dying
to be called a British.
But if a British man finds you
even a kilometer away,
he will say,
look an Indian is coming.
Excuse me.
What did you say?
So you hate being called an Indian.
Because we litter all around.
Spit betel leaves.
Break traffic signals.
We don’t like to stand in queues.
We take bribe and also give bribe.
There are more pot holes
than roads.
More scams than the ministers.
Though we are like this,
we are different too.
We have been independent
since 70 years.
Take any young country around us.
There is still a question
on their identity?
But we make everything ourselves,
from a needle to a rocket.
After attempting 20 times,
larger countries send satellite
to mars.
But we in the first attempt,
at the cost of a Rickshaw,
have sent satellite
after satellite to mars.
Because we are very influential.
We were not like this from before.
We were the golden birds.
The Kohinoor diamond which is in
the crown, at the tower of London.
It is not made in Bartaniya
like you.
But made in India.
But we have not stopped
in our old glory.
We are progressing.
We are changing.
If we develop at this speed, and
keep fighting against corruption.
Then, in the next 50 years,
India will develop so much that,
Americans and British’s will say.
We too want to be known as Indian.
Then don’t change your side,
Mr. Trishanku.
Be happy with what you are.
Don’t find mistakes of the country.
Not your identity.
She sat down.
Param Singh. Will you marry me?
What?
- What?
Will you marry me?
I know it looks a bit odd. But...
Not bit, very odd.
Alisha, you don’t even know Param.
I don’t care.
I just know the girl
who will marry Param,
will be luckiest girl in the world.
Alisha, please get up.
Your knees must be paining.
He is anyway going to refuse.
Yes, I am going back to India.
I am okay.
I will go along with you.
But you will not be
able to settle there.
You will feel suffocated.
You will be entangled
in cooking chores.
You will feel like
going for shopping,
and you will have
to inject a buffalo.
You will not at all be
able to take up a job.
Param Singh, for you,
I will take the bull or buffalo,
to get injected.
- Really?
Alisha. You get up.
He cannot marry you?
Why can’t he?
- Why can’t he?
Because...
- Because?
He is already married.
You are already married?
I was once upon a time but,
as I told you earlier,
husbands don’t live
with their wives now a days.
So, now a days I am single
and ready to mingle.
I do.
You were going to follow me,
here, there all around the world.
Which path did you take now?
Was I upset at the airport?
Then why are you? Relax.
I...
Ice-cream.
I have not married him in real.
Sam was not begging on his knees.
Sam was acting.
Now the drama is over.
Why isn’t he giving you
the divorce?
The long haired guy
has started liking his role.
He is not going
to give you divorce,
it is written clearly on his face.
Do you know why?
Because he has fallen
in love with you.
Or you know that
he has fallen for you.
But you are hiding from me.
But I don’t love him.
So that means he does.
Irrespective of whether
he does or not, I don’t, Param.
But I also don’t
love Alisha, Jasmeet.
Then why are you marrying her.
- The way you did.
I know Sam
is not going to divorce you.
I will marry Alisha.
We will get residency here.
I will divorce her
after a few days.
We will register
our marriage again.
You will be a resident here.
In between, Alisha may fall
in love with me and get emotional.
Her heart might break,
she may be destroyed.
How does it matter to us?
Right or wrong does not matter.
We just have
to get settled in London.
Enjoy the ice-cream.
Where are you going?
I am getting married after 4 days
on the 14th.
I have to do lot of preparations.
Bye.
Param.
- Leave me.
Harpreet. Harp.
Oh, my God. Param.
Oh, bloody Aaru, Greetings.
- Greetings.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
You are in London.
You did not inform me.
It was worth keeping it a secret.
- What?
I mean,
everything happened quickly.
You smell of Punjab.
Still? I have also have
had a bath after coming.
He is such a funny guy.
We really want to chat a lot,
but I have to drop him to work.
So, give me your number?
Oh, very good,
we too will come along.
We will chat, will gossip,
Let’s see, let’s go, Heathrow.
If you don’t mind,
can I tell you something?
I agree no work, is big or small.
But you have a land in the village.
Then also you are doing this.
If an uneducated man comes here,
then these people won’t make him
the president directly.
So, have to do whatever job I get.
Means everyone who comes to London
doesn’t have a story like this.
Yes, maybe better than this too.
Or worse than this too.
But the bad story
does not reach our country.
Or people like Gurnaam
don’t let them reach.
Hello.
Jasmeet, let’s go.
My daughter died. My daughter died.
I am doing things for them,
for them whom I have
never seen them alive.
Are you worried about yourself?
If you are waiting for
one more bad news from home.
No.
Iqbal,
coming to London, working hard,
earning money.
There is nothing wrong in that.
This city respects people
who work hard.
But someone who has come illegally,
there is no respect anywhere.
Nowhere.
Iqbal brother, don’t look behind.
A real man is the one
who after everything
still has the courage
to walk ahead.
It's home coming not a farewell.
What is the use of the tears?
Param. Hi.
You both are so happy to meet me
that you forgot
to invite me inside.
Sorry, come in.
Wow, what a house?
Sam, after seeing your house,
I can understand why,
people are desperate to come
to London.
I thought you will be busy
preparing for your wedding.
I will have to come to you
for the wedding.
Don’t tell me,
she is the number one
wedding planner of your village.
No, she played a very
important role in my first wedding.
So, it must be for the second too.
I want my second wedding should be
as challenging as the first one.
What?
Can I sit?
You too sit, it’s your own house.
You forgot?
Jasmeet.
Yes, Jasmeet sit.
Jasmeet, you remember my wedding.
The most beautiful day of my life.
The girl whom I loved 100%,
I was going to marry her.
I remember,
she was looking so beautiful.
Hold on, let me get this right.
You want, your second marriage,
to remind you
of your first wedding?
My tomorrow is also a part of me.
Wherever I am today,
is because of tomorrow.
And I never want to forget that.
I want Alisha to look exactly
like my first bride.
Make her wear the same clothes.
The same ambience,
the same atmosphere.
The same invitation card.
The same feast.
Everything same to same.
You must have
remembered everything.
Sam, won’t you offer
a drink to Param.
Yes, of course. What will you have?
Bring anything,
you have good taste.
If it’s a drama,
then why all these preparations?
If it's drama, then why so much pain
in arranging all this.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Cheers.
- Cheers to a happy married life
and this one being the last.
Okay, I am leaving.
Jasmeet, I will see you tomorrow.
Done.
Take care.
- Take care. See you, man.
Do you know Alisha, I did not wear
a suit on my first wedding.
God has fulfilled that desire.
Jasmeet, we will take black suit.
If she sees him in a suit then
will not divorce him for 7 years.
Silver, let’s buy a silver one.
I want to like a groom
not a pomfret fish.
If you don’t approve of my choice,
then why did you call me?
But I want my groom in black.
Oh.
You have got your groom in black.
This connection is called black.
Isn’t it, Jasmeet?
It’s your wedding you should know.
You must have had the experience.
I am buying a silver suit.
Don’t waste my time by chatting.
Should I buy black shoes or
wear golden and become a mermaid.
Mermaid?
Mermaid baby.
You are so sweet.
- That I am.
You have to give me
a discount please.
It’s already discounted.
She is asking for a discount
on her husband’s wedding suit.
She is looking nice.
But not like you.
No. 8 on 10.
Is she your friend?
That you are rating her.
8 out of 10.
She is your rival.
What are you laughing for?
If you were a real Punjabi,
you would have jumped
on her by now.
Fighting with her,
pulling her hair.
Tore her clothes. You are laughing?
- What happened?
Am I looking stupid?
No, not at all,
he keeps making me laugh
all the time.
She has gone in flash back.
Alisha, you look very pretty.
If my first wife was here
she would have given you 8 on 10.
Baby.
- Come, baby.
Thank you.
Actually not 8 out of 10,
you should get 10 on 10.
No, she isn’t laughing.
But she isn’t wrestling also.
This is good.
The card should be simple
at the second wedding.
Jasmeet, it’s my first marriage.
Yes.
The card should be exactly the way
it was on our first wedding.
I mean my first wedding.
You had made me write an oath
on that card, Jasmeet.
Do you remember the oath?
My husband,
my groom lives immortally.
Never ending.
Never dying.
Beautiful.
What does that mean Jasmeet?
She just remembers the words.
She has forgotten
the meaning long ago.
My husband,
my groom lives immortally.
Never ending. Never dying.
The one who never abandons me.
Jasmeet.
- Sam.
I can understand everything
that you are trying to do.
You think I am a simpleton
from some village
whom you will not give residency
and I will keep tolerating quietly.
And finally I will have
to obey you.
You will get residency tomorrow.
There is an interview
at the home department.
After that you can stay here
as long as you want.
Alone.
Can I give you the flowers
and open champagne,
or you still want to scold me?
No, I want to make a call.
'Oh, west minister abbey.'
'Should I tell you something?'
'Whenever I see this place,'
'I feel like going to London
and seeing this place with you.'
'The place where 2 real lovers
walk hand in hand.'
And now may I kiss the bride.
Param, stop this wedding.
I am getting
the residency tomorrow.
Now there is no need of this drama.
Whether others understand or not,
I thought you would understand.
Why I am marrying, Jasmeet.
Param, the destination is very near.
Please, wait till tomorrow.
To harm each other today, thinking
that tomorrow will be better.
There can’t be anything more stupid
in than this in the world, Jasmeet.
It can’t be.
- "The heart is stubborn."
I am married.
Param and me.
I knew it.
Because if you weren't married,
then you could not have resisted
my charm.
Go, go to him.
Excuse me. Where is the wedding?
My wedding.
Did you really think,
Param would do something like this?
I know he is your husband.
He told me the day I met him.
Param can be duped,
but he can’t dupe.
'I will fulfill my promise Alisha.'
'I will just do the ceremony
but not the vows.'
'I will not be able to say them.'
'Because my heart and life
is somewhere else.'
'Who will take second hand love
from such a loving person?'
'Go, you are hers for 7 lives.'
'Then it’s my chance. Promise.'
'And I will not let you break it
this time.'
'Thank you.'
'I never thought that one day
the city will win and I will lose.'
'But I was wrong.'
'I made one more mistake.'
'To come here illegally.'
'I am going to rectify
that Jasmeet.'
'I am going to Indian Embassy
and getting myself deported.'
Param.
Param, you haven’t lost.
You never lost.
The minute I saw you, I realized
that I have made such a big mistake
of coming to London like this.
To cover up that mistake
I kept making more mistakes.
I felt when everything
will become alright,
we will forget all this.
But...
But I was cracking from inside.
I cannot forget that
I am doing so wrong with you.
I was doing so wrong
to Sam and Alisha.
The country whose praises
I was happy to hear.
I was doing so wrong with it.
Param, I have realized.
London is very nice.
But now London has
no meaning for me.
I want my, Param.
I have understood
which city we live,
it makes no difference.
With whom we live,
and how much he loves us.
Only that matters.
What was the need to go so long.
You could have just hugged me
and said sorry.
You know that.
When you hug me,
so many naughty, naughty thoughts
run in my mind, girl.
Come into my arms.
'Girl, get ready.'
'We have a bigger war
to fight in Punjab.'
'We will fulfill your first dream.'
'I promise you,
I will surely convince grandfather.'