Hi guys and welcome to French Guy Cooking.
Today : an explosion of indian tangy flavors
trapped in the most reassuring english Tradition,
Plus !
I'll bring you the most undisputable proof
that you have the power to work miracles.
Let's make the unexpected but stunning Palak
Paneer Hinglish Pie...
You are about to make your own cheese.
How you feel about it ?
The Paneer cheese is insanely fast and dead
simple to make.
Paneer is a fresh cheese quite common in India.
It is made by curdling heated milk with an
acidic liquid.
It tastes quite soft, but it is milky and
nutty.
In a big pan over medium high heat, pour 2
liters of whole milk and 1 cup of cream
Stir it from time to time.
When there is serious foam forming
Remove the milk form the heat, and add half
a cup of apple cider vinegar.
This is where things get exciting !
The reaction just takes a few minutes.
The milk will separate into curds and whey.
Now get yourself a piece of cloth.
This can be called a cheesecloth or a muslin.
Just take whatever cloth you find.
Place the cloth in a strainer over the sink.
Pour the liquid in.
Carefully Make a knot.
Now put weight on it.
It will squeeze the excess of water out.
The Paneer Cheese will be ready when we need
it.
A good pie is all about a good filling.
For this one, we 'll use Fish and Spinach.
What ?
Do you remember we are trying to gain subscribers
?
Well I do, and thrust me
you won't find any watery spinach or bland
fish in this recipe.
Instead, think of outstanding explosive flavors
like mint, ginger, garlic, lemon !
First things first.
Let's marinate the fish.
Cut 4 fillets of trout into big chunks.
Season well with salt and pepper, then place
them in a bowl.
Add a Drizzle of oil
A drizzle of honey
A crush of garlic
A gratted thumb of ginger
The juice of half a lemon
And all the zest you can get from it
A sprinkle of chopped mint leaves can't do
any harm.
Let it rest while we prepare the greens...
From now on, we will use an oven-proof frying
pan.
You can also use a skillet.
Or a frying pan and a pie dish.
Over medium high heat, a big knob of Butter
Add a thumb of gratted ginger
2 crushed cloves of Garlic
Chop 3 onions,
2, 3 minutes should do it.
Add loads of fresh spinach and let them fall
down in the frying pan.
Spinach will litteraly vanish in the pan.
So When I say loads, I mean tremendous amounts
of spinach.
Like : "fuck i shouldn't put that much".
A good big pinch of Salt, pinch of pepper.
When almost all the water has evaporated,
we can move on to the next step.
Let's build the pie up.
Two rolls of puff pastries on the board.
Parchment paper under it.
Heavy Sprinkling with an indian spices mix.
Coriander seeds
Cumin seeds
Nutmeg
Salt
Pepper corn
A bit of cinnamon
Fat is always a good carrier of taste, because
many flavors do not dissolve in water.
In this case we use the fat of the puff pastries
to retain the indian spices.
Thoroughly rub to the puff pastries.
On one roll, sprinkle breadcrumbs.
They will suck out the excess of moisture
during baking.
Spread the onions and the spinach.
Carefully slide it in the same pan we used
earlier.
We are baking it in the frying pan for two
reasons :
One, It is convinient.
Second, it's unexpected.
People are gonna get curious about it and
even more when they'll discover what's inside.
Next add the drained chunks of fish.
Time to use the paneer cheese.
Unwrap it, slice it and place it on top.
Fold the edges towards the center.
Place the second roll on top, spiced side
down.
Here comes a cool part.
We are forming the pie, not by sealing it,
but by folding it like a bed sheet.
why ?
How many pies have you sealed in your life
?
And how many beds sheets have you folded ?
Gently Push the edges back in the pan, under
the first layer.
Prick the pastry so that steam can escape.
And finally, brush the pie with milk.
BOOM !
In a preheated oven until you achieve a nice
golden brown finish.
There we have it : The unexpected Palak Paneer
Hinglish Pie !
Outside, the shiny crust is crispy as hell
and encrusted with bold indian flavors.
Inside, it's all about freshness and moisture.
Tell a story : It's no boring pie !
it's journey made of warm blankets and dream
countries.
Thank you guys for watching, always a pleasure
to have your comments, your likes and your
good energy !
And don't forget to subscribe for the next
video.
Bye Bye !