- I'm not that happy, you know.
Like, well, actually I've joined
you because, you know, like,
you are the host.
You have the power.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[CROWD YELLING]
- And you are the ones
who can get me a box.
- Yeah but we don't
have a small box.
We only have a big box.
Is that fine?
- It's fine.
Big is better.
- What, like how big?
Like that big?
- Bigger.
- Like that big?
- Bigger than that?
- It's that big!
[CROWD GRUMBLING]
- It is kind of big.
It's huge!
- When you see it, you'll
know how big it is.
- Wait for it.
And--
- Really?
- That's a big box.
- Yeah.
That's the one.
- It's a big box.
- Oh my god.
Have you ever seen [INAUDIBLE]
unbox anything this big?
- The largest unboxing ever!
- By the way, by the way, by
the way, by the way, by the way.
Unboxing [NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[CROWD OOHING]
- [NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[CROWD GRUMBLING]
- Do your thing.
- Just go [NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[CROWD CHEERING]
- [NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[CHEERING]
- Guys, guys, guys--
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[MUSIC PLAYING]