WE'VE ALL VISITED WEBSITES
THAT OFFER SPECIAL DEALS IN
EXCHANGE FOR YOUR EMAIL
ADDRESS, THAT'S NOT ALWAYS
SOMETHING YOU WANT TO DO.
WE'RE ALL GETTING MORE EMAIL
THAN WE CAN HANDLE. OUR
CONSUMER TECHNOLOGY REPORTER
JAMEY TUCKER HAS FOUND A
SOLUTION THAT HELPS PROTECT
YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS.
((--JAMEY TUCKER REPORTING--))
It's important to protect your
primary email address. Bad
guys can, and do, use email
addresses to bombard people
with malware and even steal
identies. You've heard of
burner phones, those phones
used, often by people who want
to hide their tracks. If you
don't like giving away your
email address...you'll love
burner email. You're visiting
a website that offers a
special deal in exchange for
your information, specifically
your email address. Sometimes
you're okay with that, but a
lot of times you don't want to
be bothered, AFTER you get the
special deal. Burner email is
an extension for both the
Chrome and Firefox browser
that creates a secret email
address. Here's how it works:
Install the burner email
extension, you'll find it in
the Chrome Store or as a
Firefox plugin. Now, when
you're asked to sign up for
something, look for the flames
in the signup box...get it,
burner? Click on it and the
extension will create an email
address for that specific
newsletter or site. When the
company sends you one of their
emails, it goes to burner
email first, and gets
forwarded on to you. The
company or website never gets
your primary email address.
You'll get the newsletters for
as long as you want them.
Getting too many, you can turn
it off, or if you're done with
them, delete or burn it the
secret email address. Using a
burner or disposable email
address will protect the one
you use for important things.
That's What the Tech? I'm
Jamey Tucker
(--DARRELL--)
TOBIN IS NEXT WITH SPORTS.