(dramatic music)
- [Jimmy] The last team
to leave this rollercoaster wins $20,000.
Chris and Chandler are team captains.
Chris is the blue team, and
Chandler is the white team.
(bell dings)
Chandler's team is sitting
in the front.
(bell dings)
Chris's team is sitting
in the back.
Chandler, are you guys gonna win?
- Go team.
- [Jimmy] Gotcha.
Are you gonna win?
- Yes.
- Of course.
- Yep, yes.
- Yes.
- [Jimmy] You sure, Chris?
- 100%.
- [Jimmy] Let's see it.
All right, fire up the rollercoaster.
Send them off.
- [Contestant] Yeah!
- Here we go.
(hands clapping)
- [Jimmy] All right, guys.
(contestants cheering)
$20,000 on the line.
(cash register rings)
Chris, 20 grand, think
of what you could buy.
- [Tareq] This is never gonna end.
- No.
Whoa!
- Oh.
- Okay.
- I feel it.
That's crazy.
(rollercoaster rumbling)
- Yeah.
Great jerk up.
(Chandler laughing)
(hands clapping)
(Jake laughing)
- [Jimmy] All right, guys,
your first lap just finished.
How did it feel?
(hands clapping)
- Fantastic.
- Great.
- Awesome.
- I don't like rollercoasters.
(Chandler laughing)
I get sick, so.
- [Jimmy] So, are you gonna
do two more laps, Chandler?
- I don't know, we'll see.
I might do like 10.
- [Jimmy] How was it, boys?
- It was really good.
We've figured out some
strategies how to win.
- [Jimmy] All right,
let's do lap number two.
Round two, boys, round two.
(hands clapping)
(rollercoaster whooshing)
(Ty imitating engine revving)
- I peed myself.
- My eyelash is coming out.
What's going on?
- I'm already sweating profusively.
- I decided to become the
cameraman for team blue.
How's it going, blue?
- It's going great.
We figured it out.
We're good.
(rollercoaster whirring)
(playful music)
- Ah, we stopped.
- Guys, this looks kind of similar.
(rollercoaster rattling)
- Hey, how you doing?
- Is it just me, or did it feel faster?
(contestants exclaiming)
- Chris, I agree, that felt
extremely faster than normal.
- It did, it feels way faster.
- [Jimmy] Ma'am, did
you speed that one up?
(sad music)
- [Tareq] One more time?
One more time?
- Stretch, stretch, stretch,
stretch, stretch-
- Again, again.
- Woo-hoo, we're going again.
(triumphant music)
(rollercoaster whooshing)
(rollercoaster rattling)
- All right, we're gonna go straight.
Go, go, go.
Lean left.
(contestants screaming)
That hurt, bro.
That hurt.
- Woo-hoo!
- Look, I'm gonna be the first
person to not have any joy
on a rollercoaster.
(triumphant music)
That was my joyless rollercoaster ride.
- [Jimmy] They're about
to go into lap number 10.
Jake, stop that.
How do you guys feel?
- I feel bad.
My butt cheek is hurting.
- [Jimmy] Which butt cheek?
- My left one.
- [Jimmy] That's fine.
You still have the right one.
- Mine too.
- [Jimmy] All right, we're
going into lap number 10.
(Marcus speaking faintly)
- [Jake] If I have
to crawl back there.
- [Jimmy] Are you guys good?
Yeah, please crawl back here.
- Yeah, come on back here, man.
- Please, please, come on.
- Come on.
- Come on, get out.
- [Jimmy] All right.
Ma'am, just start lap number 10
before they're all no longer friends.
(rollercoaster whooshes)
(tense rock music)
(Chris exclaiming)
(relaxing music)
- Carlos, you're doing great.
(tense rock music)
(Chris exclaiming)
(relaxing music)
- Ah, so bright.
(Dustin humming)
(tense rock music)
(Chris exclaiming)
- Whoo!
- Do you guys want a little break?
- [All] Yeah.
- Too bad.
Start it up.
- Wait, you said break.
You said break.
- [Jimmy] Sorry, have fun.
- [All] No!
(tense rock music)
- [Jimmy] Hey, welcome back, boys.
I hope you enjoy your two second stay.
Start it back up.
- [Contestant] Aw, man, come on.
- [Jimmy] All right.
- I'm gonna do my longest
yeah, boy, on a roller coaster.
- [Tareq] All right, go ahead.
- Yeah, boy.
- Boy.
(voices trilling)
(rollercoaster rumbling)
- (inhales deeply) Oh.
- [Jimmy] How many
challenges have you won?
- Technically, it's like three
or four 'cause I won two teams
and then two individuals.
- [Jimmy] How many have you won?
- Two.
- One.
- [Jimmy] Wait,
which one did you win?
- Treadmill.
- [Jimmy] You did.
You haven't won one yet.
- No.
- [Jimmy] But this is a team of winners.
Even the cameraman here
didn't win anything.
- [Audience] Aw.
- [Jimmy] Sorry.
- The last one-
- [Jimmy] The Tesla still hurts.
Jake, how many challenges have you won?
- Two.
- [Jimmy] Bailey won the house.
Egg one was purely random.
You've won one.
Oh, you've won one, that's right.
So, you guys, two.
Have you won one?
- I haven't won anything.
- [Jimmy] Have you won one?
- [Jimmy] They've won six challenges.
You guys have won two, and
one of the two was by chance.
I don't know, guys.
- Two of the people back there
have been able to compete
in more challenges though.
That's all I'm saying.
- [Jimmy] Oh, oh.
They said your win/loss is worse though.
- But we have more experience-
- [Jimmy] Okay.
(tense rock music)
(rollercoaster rumbling)
(body thwacking)
(contestants exclaiming)
(sad music)
- All right, I'm going, boys.
- No.
- Please.
- I can't.
- Chan-Chan looks sick up there.
(Chandler exhales sharply)
- [Jimmy] Wait, so what's wrong?
What's wrong?
- Just a bit dizzy.
You know I get motion
sick, and I'm done for now.
- [Jimmy] You're leaving the team?
Chandler, if you step out, you're out.
(contestants cheering)
(buzzer buzzes)
All right.
He's out.
Chandler is out.
That now leaves three
left for the white team.
- [Chandler] My butt fell asleep.
- [Jimmy] Chandler, you got out first.
- Yeah.
- [Jimmy] Do you feel bad
taking $5,000 if your team wins
for you?
- No, I told them I would only take three.
- [Jimmy] Oh, well, in that case.
In that case, you're a nice guy.
- Yeah.
They get like six.
That's a fair deal.
I picked the squad, you know?
I'm the coach.
- [Jimmy] And you're gonna
be there cheerleader, right?
- Yeah.
- [Jimmy] Okay.
So, how do you feel now
that Chandler left you?
- I'm great.
I got more room.
- [Jimmy] Chandler,
apparently there's kids
out there chanting you suck.
Let's go address it.
- Everyone was chanting Chandler sucks.
- Why would you-
- [Jimmy] Well, now he's right here.
Tell it to him to his face.
- It was her.
It was her idea.
- What?
- Chandler doesn't suck.
- I was-
- [Jimmy] Hey, you guys, keep riding, go.
(playful upbeat music)
So, I just noticed, not only
are you guys riding the rides,
but also your cameraman.
So if you guys win, your
cameraman gets $3,000 as well.
- [All] Hey!
(hands clapping)
- Hey!
- [Jimmy] Tareq, bless the team.
- Thank you.
Guys, they gave me a blue shirt.
I'm part of the blue team now.
So, we're definitely gonna win.
- Hey, guys, guess what?
Chandler's already out.
- Chandler lost.
(tense rock music)
- Whoo.
- Ah.
- Ah, ah.
- Oh.
Whoa.
- Yeah.
- [Tareq] Is that a fan?
- You want some misty?
- Yes, please.
Oh, right in my face.
- [Tareq] Can I get one too?
Oh.
- Oh, sorry.
(sad dramatic music)
- Wow.
(tense rock music)
We are going to try and hold our breath
from start to finish
once we exit the tunnel.
Now.
- [Tareq] All right,
he's holding his breath.
You can breathe if you want to.
(rollercoaster rattling)
Oh, we lost Chris, guys.
(Chris breathes deeply)
- I made it.
- [Jimmy] Who here wants a pillow?
- Me, pillow.
- [Jimmy] Okay, I-
(Marcus coughing)
Are you dying?
- We just held our breath-
- We just held our breath the entire time.
- We held our breath the whole time.
- [Jimmy] Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- [Jimmy] All right,
we're gonna have a contest
for the pillow.
All right, Garrett, pick a
number between one and 100.
- 76.
- [Jimmy] No.
- 17.
- 12.
- 6.
- 63.
- 54.
- 32.
- [Jimmy] All right, screw it,
just give everyone pillows.
(contestants cheering)
(gentle relaxing music)
- Ride it with your eyes closed.
It's so much fun.
(Luke laughing)
Oh, my God!
- No, it's not.
- I can't handle it.
- It's way worse with your eyes closed.
- I decided to ride
one time with the boys.
- Hey, boys.
- Oh, and Chandler came with me.
Blue team's in the back
doing blue team things.
I think I'm just gonna start
my own team, team yellow.
Ah.
Blue team has numbers,
but white team has heart.
Chris is also sleeping.
(contestant screaming)
We'll see how it goes.
- [Tareq] All right, looks
like Jimmy's out guys.
- I am.
Yellow team lost.
I quit.
(Tareq laughing)
(gentle music)
- [Contestant] Check his pulse.
- Are you alive?
You alive?
- What's up?
- Oh, he's alive.
- What?
- You good now?
(Chris groans)
- All right.
I'm just gonna assume that he's asleep.
Yeah, he's asleep.
- They're not talking trash.
They're talking nice.
Hey.
You all have really nice smiles.
- Thank you.
It was a gift from my wife, yeah.
- You look good in blue.
- Thank you, you also look good in white.
(Luke laughing)
- [Dustin] Your Gucci slides are fly.
- Thank you.
You could deserve anybody.
- [Dustin] You smell like roses.
- I think they've gone crazy.
(upbeat music)
(Tareq laughs)
- I've been through a lot.
Hair tie?
- Oh!
- I'm a pirate.
(rollercoaster roaring)
- Wow, That was so loud.
- The speed limit's 30.
- We all here.
(hands clapping)
They only got three.
- [Jimmy] All right.
It's been another hour and 1/2.
I want to do more negotiating.
Who do you guys want to give up?
Dustin.
Who would you guys trade for Dustin?
Garrett?
Chris?
Marcus?
(relaxing music)
What would you guys trade for Jake?
- I think I got some pocket lint.
(Tareq laughing)
(Garrett laughing)
- [Jimmy] All right.
- Dustin, what are the
odds you get out right now?
- [Jimmy] This is your best
odds to even out the players.
You gotta make big boy plays
if you want the 20 grand.
- One out of 10.
- [Jimmy] One out of 10.
- I got to stand up for this.
- [Jimmy] On the count of three,
you're gonna pick a number
between one and 10.
Same with you.
If you guys say the
same number, you're out.
If you say different numbers, you stay in,
and we do the same for Ty.
If they say the same number, Ty gets out.
One, two, three.
- [Ty] Two.
- [Dustin] Two.
(contestants screaming)
- Let's go!
(dramatic music)
- Want to do it me and you?
One time.
- [Jimmy] All right, first one's for Luke.
Remember, boys, it's one through five.
This time, it's for Chris.
One, two, three.
- Two.
You haven't said anything.
- I held up my hand.
- [Jimmy] All right,
well, it's written down.
- [Garrett] It's one.
- [Luke] Hold on.
- [Jimmy] This is what
he wrote down beforehand.
- That's fine.
- [Jimmy] We're gonna
keep rollercoaster going.
All right, Ty, you got out.
How do you feel?
- I feel pretty confident
we're still gonna win.
I got faith in my boys.
- [Jimmy] Can you still dance?
- Oh, I can definitely still dance.
- [Jimmy] Let me see.
(upbeat music)
- [Ty] That impressive, Connor?
(Jimmy laughing)
(bouncy upbeat music)
- [Jimmy] $1,000 for the
next person to step out.
I don't care who.
None of you guys want $1,000?
Dustin, you could have
a grand and be done.
- That's fine 'cause last time I checked,
five is more than a one.
- [Jimmy] Go ahead and send them off,
but let this thought
marinate in your head.
- All right.
- [Jimmy] $1,000, boys.
Final offer, $2,000 if anyone steps out.
(Dustin groaning)
Here's the deal though,
if one of you left,
you would have more leg room,
and you actually might
be able to last longer,
instead of being scrunched up.
- I like it.
- [Dustin] All right, I'm doing it.
- [Jake] Are you going?
Are you doing it?
He's doing it.
Doing it.
- [Luke] He's doing it.
- [Jimmy] $2,000 step out right now.
You getting out?
- [Chandler] Welcome.
- [Jimmy] All right.
(hands clapping)
Dusty just won $2,000.
Congrats.
- Oh, my God, leg room.
- [Jimmy] So, how do you feel?
- Mentally, I'm drained.
I couldn't go any longer-
- [Jimmy] So, fans want to
know, do you have eyeballs?
- Yes.
- [Jimmy] Nice, gotcha.
And three people remain on blue.
You guys have lost two teammates,
but you've gained a lot of leg room.
Let's see how it does you.
- [Fan] Chris, you want some gum?
- Oh, yeah, hold up,
when we come back around.
This kid's gonna throw me gum.
You got to catch it.
I got it.
Yeah!
He threw me gum.
- Thanks for the gum, boys.
Hey, they love us.
Hey, let me get another piece.
- That gum's really good.
Oh, whoa.
Whoa.
- Yeah!
- He gave the boys gum.
- [Tareq] Hey, we got
a whole pack this time.
- Hey, Jimmy, some kid gave me gum.
- I wish I had some playing cards
or like a board game or something.
- Do you want your gum back?
- [Fan] Nah, do you
want beef jerky though?
- Yeah.
(Chris laughing)
(hands clapping)
Yes.
We put in an order.
This time he's getting us jerky.
- [Tareq] Y'all, Chris made a
friend on this rollercoaster.
- [Man] Holy.
He got a jerky.
- [Garrett] No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- [Chris] No, no, no.
- [Fan] Hey, will you sign this?
(fans yelling)
- [Fan] Bye!
- We started a problem.
Now, every kid wants to throw us stuff.
- [Tareq] That's not a good idea.
Especially being on a rollercoaster.
- No.
What if we came back
with a Xbox this time.
(Tareq laughing)
Just, we got an Xbox now.
(upbeat music)
- [Jimmy] So, I heard
you guys have a deal.
- We want to trade Marcus for Jake.
Marcus gets out, Jake gets out.
- [Jimmy] I'll let him
know your negotiation.
They offered Marcus for Jake.
- No.
- [Jimmy] Jake said no.
He said, screw your offer.
Keep going.
- I look like Gangster
Mike from "The Office."
Oh, Scranton, where you at?
- [Tareq] Garrett, you
are Dwight happening.
- [Garrett] I'm not Dwight.
- You are Dwight.
(upbeat music)
Whoa, Chris, what are you doing?
- I'm getting out.
- Chris, no.
- [Contestant] Not this time.
- I'm getting out.
- [Tareq] Chris, what's going on?
- I entrust everything
in Marcus and Garrett.
They can do it.
- [Jimmy] If you get out, your
boys might not carry through
with the 20 grand.
- [Chris] Boom.
- [Jimmy] He's out.
It is now a two V two.
- Game over.
- [Jimmy] Game over?
- [Garrett] We will win this for you.
- I get really motion sick,
and that roller coaster
was just tearing me down,
tearing me down.
I knew I had two solid teammates.
I'm gonna just get out,
and you guys got it,
and I believe in them they can do it.
Blue team.
- And then there were four.
- [Employee] All clear.
- All clear.
- [Tareq] How does it
feel to have more space?
- It feels like I got a lot of space.
- [Tareq] Aye.
(hands clapping)
- Mom, if you want to know
why I haven't messaged you
at all today, I've been here.
- Whee.
- [Tareq] Oh, put your legs in the cart.
- We have lost Garrett to the
madness of the rollercoaster.
(upbeat music)
- [Jimmy] Let's Rock Paper Scissors.
- We're talking it out.
We're just talking out
the thought process.
- [Jimmy] All or nothing,
Rock Paper Scissors.
- Yes.
- All or nothing.
- Okay.
- [Jimmy] White team
wants to settle it all
for nothing, Rock Paper Scissors.
- Ah, let's get it, come on.
- All right, let's just game it.
- [Tareq] Why is it-
- 20,000 on the line between you guys.
The reason we're doing
this is 'cause the park
actually closes in under an hour,
and they're gonna go all day.
So, we literally have no
other way to settle this.
Do it.
Rock Paper Scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- [Jimmy] Turn around.
- [Jake] Let's go.
- [Luke] Hey!
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- Hey, let's go.
- [Jimmy] It is now tied.
It's tied.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- [Jake] Let's get it.
- [Luke] Yes!
- [Jimmy] Oh.
All right.
White is up two to one.
If you lose this next one,
that's 20 grand, boys.
- Chris, don't screw up there, bro.
- Chris is good, we got this, we got this.
- [Jimmy] You guys are currently
up 20 grand on the line.
- There's more adrenaline
right now than the entire day.
- Chandler, look they're cheering.
(fans cheering)
- [Jimmy] Chandler never wins.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
(contestants screaming)
(bouncy upbeat music)
- Let's go!
Get over here.
(contestants cheering)
Let's go!
- [Jimmy] Well, I'm sorry, boys.
(sad dramatic music)
Okay, hey, here you go.
Split it up, Chandler.
Don't forget about Dustin.
- Hey, (indistinct) come here.
- [Dustin] Thank you.
- [Jimmy] The bottom of
it is 100s, share it.
- [Fans] Chandler, Chandler!
- [Jake] White team.
- [Jimmy] Right.
They're cheering on you.
- [Fans] Chandler, Chandler!
- [Chandler] What do you guys want?
- [Jimmy] So, what are you guys gonna do
with all the money you won?
- We're gonna go bowling.
- [Both] Bowling.
- Yeah.
(all cheering)
- Okay.
- [Jimmy] Hey, wait, wait.
Can you guys at least pay
for the other team's bowling?
- Yeah, yeah, we'll do that.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, all right.
- [Jimmy] That's the least, all right.
- Okay.
- You want to ride more rides?
- No.
- Yeah.
- [Jimmy] All right, Chandler,
that's your second W.
- In a row.
- [Jimmy] Wait, really?
(hands clapping)
- [Jimmy] Whoa.
Is this the new Chandler?
- Whoa.
- Yeah. (shrieks)
(explosion booms)
♪ Mr. Beast, oh ♪