today i'm gonna be reacting to videos i
couldn't upload to this channel like one
time we rammed a car going 100 miles per
hour into a wall
another video that never got uploaded
was a video where we built a city out of
bouncy castles it was insane we also
tried to lay the world's longest domino
chain we visited the seven wonders of
the world and much more me and the boys
are gonna react to them and just you
know tell you what went wrong which
video do you want to react to first
chandler 100 mile an hour car versus
wall that's a good one there's no story
in this at all we just duct taped a
bowling ball into a car and then just
slammed into trying
wait wait chris you want to see your
strike in slow-mo i do why you're so
happy
and in case you're wondering yes this
was filmed on a closed course with
professional supervision obviously don't
try this at home this was fun
what look how far it goes i don't even
remember filming them
oh yeah because we could edit the green
screen we thought it'd be funny to hit a
green screen oh wow we hit a shark oh no
we're getting eaten by a shark oh no we
get more who puts that there oh wait i
already know chris is gonna freak out
chris loves this one so chris what
happened here you got a bread on this
card you got a bread on this car they
hit boom sandwich
look at that it actually worked kind of
that counts sort of worked instead of
having your parents make you sandwiches
just grab two cars and ram them together
and that's how you can make it use your
parents cars and also take their credit
card now after all that chaos it finally
came to the time when we rammed this car
100 miles an hour into a wall you threw
a brick on the gas pedal and there she
goes no one's in the car
she's going she's climbing
and there you go the build-up of the
entire video to a blurry camera shot and
right when i saw that camera shot that's
when i went we're just gonna delete that
and that's 100 mile an hour car versus
wall but not all videos get scrapped
because they're story lines some videos
they just fall apart literally here's
security camera footage of our warehouse
that right there is a giant pit of glue
and we were gonna do last leave glue
wins a bunch of money but the glue pick
couldn't hold it and it literally just
bust open which is kind of ironic
because you would think thousands of
pounds of glue would stick together that
literally took weeks to clean up it
wasn't fun the next video that didn't
get uploaded is visiting the seven
wonders of the world what i did is i
surprised all my friends with vacations
to a random wonder of the world you went
to the pyramids of egypt yeah and you
went to stonehenge
yeah that was terrible garrett went to
machu picchu and we're here why i don't
know jamie
marcus went to the grand canyon
and so on oh wow whoa
we gotta get a comparison yeah this is
the guy your girlfriend tells you not to
worry about this is you yeah yeah so
let's start off with you chandler this
is you yes at the great pyramid we are
at the great pyramids this is our tour
guide with the umbrella hat how were the
pyramids they were
big yeah here's your on the floor this
guy took me on a hit right here oh my
gosh yeah we were doing wheelies it was
so fun here's ty at niagara falls i
think he was trying to act like a news
reporter it's been a while since i
looked at this footage
all right where's chris if you're
wondering where chris is it's because he
went to stonehenge and there's nothing
to do there look there's rocks behind us
literally just rocks and it's a wonder
of the world and it's a wonder i wonder
why it's a woman that's why it's a
wonder the world wonder i went to was
the roman coliseum but when i was flying
there i accidentally left my camera on
the plane and i could not find a camera
store in freaking italy i'm gonna hit
you guys with the sigh
this video cost around 90 000 between
all the plane tickets the hotels the
food all that stuff 90 grand and because
i left my camera on a plane and i called
the airlines they couldn't find it i
didn't have my footage and we couldn't
upload it and the next video we scrapped
is dominoes we tried to film this domino
video four times and all four times it
didn't work let me run you through it
the first time we filmed this video i
got all the boys in a room and i told
them whoever made the coolest domino
contraption won money but the problem is
they all suck at laying dominoes and it
wasn't that cool so i gave them three
days to build stuff and all they could
build was the eyes of a creeper whatever
that was seven thousand dominoes that
took a long time yeah you guys had three
days what is this so then the next week
we tried to lay the world's longest
domino chain this is us laying dominoes
and we were dead set on trying to lay
the longest domino chain ever the wind
kept knocking it down so we ended up
laying them on their sides it sounds
good on paper breaking the world's
longest domino chain but what we quickly
realized is it's boring as crap to watch
people lay dominoes for 15 minutes all
these scrap videos are from months ago
obviously none of these are recent what
is this video i don't know here's a shot
of the line after a very long day this
is all the dominoes look at that that's
a big boy we were dedicated and chandler
did keep knocking it over but you know
we kept going every time and by chandler
i mean me huh i wonder why this video
didn't get uploaded we're getting bored
watching it yeah i know for some reason
we thought we'd be able to lay a domino
chain on the side of a road and break
the world record that way but no once we
realized that we just decided to knock
them all over because why not and uh
yeah this is the the chain that
didn't work
now it doesn't
this is the chain this is not as hype as
i thought it was gonna be this is not a
slope this is so boring i mean you can
clearly see why we scrapped this video
the domino chain might have seemed a
little lame but we had a cool surprise
at the end we literally laid all this
domino artwork at the end as like a
finale of the video look at that youtube
button that isn't good forever
that's very satisfying that's really
satisfying oh
none of what we laid work we have to
constantly go in and knock more dominoes
over it was a disaster okay we're not
good at laying dominoes you know how
much those dominoes cost how much i
think like 70 grand good thing i didn't
pay for it
social distancing the next video i
scrapped is a video where i wanted to
give a couple dogs the best month of
their life what i did was i got a barn
and i renovated it to look like a doggy
wonderland i even built a giant fence
out back i got the dogs unlimited food
unlimited toys literally anything they
could ever want but the problem is in
america when you're housing a bunch of
dogs there's a ton of laws and
apparently you just can't do it so yeah
i spent like 60 70 000 on this barn and
all this other stuff and then um when it
came to filming i realized oh i'm not
allowed to do this i'm not allowed to
just get a bunch of dogs and treat him
like king apparently you have to have
licenses and stuff to house a bunch of
dogs so we had to get it up next is a
video where we tried to break a bunch of
world records
the gist of it was me and the boys were
gonna try to break like 100 world
records and shocker it's a lot harder
than we thought so these are some of the
ones we did and we even called on cam
newton he's a nfl quarterback to help us
break some football world records
with 31 yards you are officially amazing
thank you dad
that was the longest throw through a
tire 31 yards yeah no like road through
a tire that's amazing gotta
three on you on youtube
chandler broke the world record for the
longest blindfolded catch believe it or
not this is actually a legit world
record like guinness was there and that
is the longest blindfolded catch ever
another
guinness world record title you all are
still officially amazing thank you hey
you and cam newton broke a world record
yes we did and i want to say thank you
to cam for giving me this record
didn't you break another one with them
oh yes this one right here was held by
a lot of nfl players the most one-handed
catches in a minute was 30. and then you
and cam did 32. 51. wow
oh
with 51 catches
i would not have been able to do it
put my quarterback man
and the final world record we try to
beat is the highest football catch ever
i got in a helicopter 600 feet in the
air and i was dropping footballs as you
see here it was hitting the stadium and
we kept missing and we actually ended up
running out of time so we didn't get
that world record but that one would
have been sick yeah and the next one we
scrapped was i built a city out of
bouncy castles for whatever reason we
thought it'd be a good idea to rent
dozens of bouncy castles and then bring
all these people in and have a city this
drone shot you're looking at right now
we literally built this city out of
bouncy castles okay so here's how the
video started we pull up to the city
right here out of bounty castle
everything here is bouncing related and
our citizens are very bounce happy
brother bobby boulevard that's a call
back right there look at this tree with
the tags
this is the most embarrassing video
we've ever filmed in our life but who
put that there the cringe hasn't even
started yet area each one is complete
with a p.o box and all of our lawnmowers
blow bubbles
all of our lawnmowers blow bubbles this
guy was apparently the town fruit dealer
and he was charging us a hundred dollars
for plastic 100 quality so how much is
that a hundred dollars that's how you
know it's right
how is it
dude the middle of that thing hurt it
was solid i thought that was dude i got
like five concussions in this video oh
that's where i get great i also told him
the technique
taylor the entire video is going to
people and saying tackle chris he was
the good part for some reason we had a
three-way banana duel it was a standoff
yes
we were like what's going on this is
just a fraction of the city we built
it's a fraction of the cringe yes better
way to phrase it all right now bounce
city had a bounce obstacle course
i did great look at this look look at
this
kill look at marcus
and at this part chris had a pair of
scissors which this is a city made out
of inflatable bouncy castles right you
pop it they're done for it so then he
started popping things and then so then
we started running away and everyone
chased us because we had scissors don't
worry i threw the scissors before i
started running
we got chase out of the town because we
had a pair of scissors and that's
against the rules and that's i built the
city out of bouncy castles that was a an
emotional roller coaster to say the
least i was hoping that would never see
the light of day but it just did you're
welcome this is my corner of pain and
the final video i'm going to show you
guys today is this dinosaur video
basically me and the boys rated a mall
with dinosaurs and you guys liked it so
we did it again with even more dinosaurs
and you guys like that so my logic was
let's just do it again with even more
dinosaurs so we bought 1 000 dinosaur
costumes and got hundreds of people to
gather on a day again this was months
ago before all this stuff currently
going on and we gave them all dinosaur
costumes and began to raid places the
reason this didn't work out is i ended
up getting sick and i had to leave
halfway through i hate when i get sick
sick jimmy not good jimmy but regardless
of that the video is still really
freaking funny wow look at all these
dinosaurs i still can't believe we had
all these people come out shout out to
everyone who uh put on the dinosaur
costume i love you guys it was also very
hot that day and of course after playing
around in the field the first place we
had to raid was a gym but not just any
gym a trampoline
all those dinosaurs
oh
wipeouts the idea for this video was if
we just had hundreds of people in
dinosaur costumes we could just go into
stores and it'd be hilarious the gym was
cool but my favorite part is when we
raided the movie theater so here you go
we took hundreds of people in dinosaur
costume to a movie theater we bought
every ticket to every seat in this room
so we could get this shot wasn't that
pretty expensive it was and here it is
that's so funny
wait do we forget to buy two tickets are
they on a date in there then people are
having a date in the middle of our
what
this is a asteroid hitting the earth and
obviously this is going to anger the
dinos that would make me angry it's
giving them flashbacks and they all went
crazy we thought this would be so funny
out of anger we then raided them all
because
we were forced to watch the earth be
destroyed again everybody was loving it
though at the mall it made everybody's
day at least yeah except for probably
the mall owner was like what in
tarnation that's what he said actually i
heard it when i felt better i wanted to
redo it and i was like so how many
costumes do we have and when they were
like oh they're all gone everyone just
took them home and i was like
boy and you get the gist of this video
we scrapped tons of videos in the past
if you add them all up these videos that
i never uploaded probably cost over 400
000 film but i care about you guys and i
don't want to upload garbage and if the
video isn't good i don't upload it and
money aside these videos actually took
forever to make like this bouncy castle
video we spent weeks on the seven
wonders of the world we spent over six
days flying the domino's video we tried
to film four times the 100 mile an hour
car video we spent almost a week
prepping for in a few days filming like
this is like a month's worth of work too
that just never saw the light of day
like when i say i only want to upload
good videos like i genuinely mean it i
don't care if we spend a month on a
video if we spent over a hundred
thousand dollars like if it's not
entertaining and i don't think you guys
will like it i will put it in this png
of a dumpster i will make ice age baby
eat it i don't know why these are on my
wall so do me a favor and subscribe
because i promise whatever's in your sub
box will be at least kinda sorta good
love you guys see you later
you