Subscribe to the Technical Guruji channel
And press the bell icon to get latest technology videos everyday.
Friends, all of you often talk about
your laptops, computers , mobile phones about the type of processor, display , battery.
how much storage and RAM it has.
and think that increasing RAM and storage will make it great.
But, here comes the question that we are going to discuss today in this video.
that whether increasing the size of RAM has any real practical benefit or should we also take a look at the speed of the RAM
Hello friends, my name is Gaurav. You are watching Technical Guruji. Lets begin.
Friends, RAM is something which we are able to discuss very easily with our friends.
because it is easy to understand like 1GB, 2GB , 5GB.
but if it is a complex term, which a common man can't understand then maybe people won't talk about it so much.
For example, people don't generally talk about the Cache memory because
a common person doesn't know the role of a Cache memory
Now whether it is 2MB Cache or 4MB Cache, he doesn't really care.
Yes. But people understand RAM. 1GB, 2GB, 3GB, the more the better.
and on the basis of this thinking we keep deciding about the devices
I remember my first android phone , which was Samsung Galaxy S2, it only had 1 GB RAM
There were many phones available in the market below this as well at the time
And now we have 2,3,4,5,6 and now we even hear the rumors that upcoming phone will be 8GB RAM, 16GB RAM
And all we are focusing on is to increase this number further. But have you ever thought,
whether we practically need this much RAM or not?
Suppose today if you want to build a PC at home to play games, 8 GB RAM is all you need. All the games work smoothly on that
But as we are always looking for the best, so despite it costing more
we will go for 32 GB RAM, 64 GB RAM.
does the RAM whether 8GB or 32 GB play any role in the performance of the game?
Not really.
So guys, there is a thing called RAM capacity.
Suppose I am the processor and the table is the RAM and whatever I am working on, I have already called it here.
Everything else is stored in the cupboard which is actually the Hard Drive.
Now suppose if this table was very large, still my hands can reach this space only.
so only this RAM is of my use.
Or if suppose the jobs at my hand are small enough to fit this space, then I don't really need a table that big.
So, after a limit, the remaining RAM is a waste and you are not really able to use that resource.
but if suppose, this table starts throwing object that I need in the job towards me, so that I am able to work with more speed
that is in simple language, the RAM has become fast
the data transfer between the RAM and Processor is taking place faster
so this will be beneficial to you instead of just increasing the size of the table again and again
4,6,8,15,25 , people keep on increasing RAM and then think that their device is faster.
So here we need to think a bit practically. I understand that the table/ RAM is sufficient for you today
but it might not be enough in 2 years time with improvement in the softwares.
I understand that after sometime you need to upgrade your phone or PC whatever it is , but we need to see where we are getting the best value currently.
You need to see the specifications of the RAM. How many Mega Hertz is its speed, whether DDR3 stick is used or DDR4 stick is used.
Whether your phone has DDR3 RAM or DDR4 RAM or what does your processor supports best, where you will get the best optimization
We sometimes ignore these things and just keep running behind MORE.
Bro! I am using 64 GB RAM.
For what purpose? Games.
You could have played the same game on 8GB RAM as well
These are few things that we need to keep in mind.
You can tell me in the comment section below about your views on this blind race
I mean, we don't even know the finish point of this race. We don't even know why are we in this race. But we are just running behind the numbers
The same thing goes with the storage
People say , I have a hard drive of 2TB
Now if same person is told that I have a Solid State Drive (SSD) of 256 GB
capacity is less than Hard Drive but performance is many times better, then he might not be able to understand it
so, here we need to have these things in mind, that not only we choose the best possible technology for ourselves but also understand why are we choosing it
Friends, you can tell me about any such experiences you have had faced with any friend or with some relative
where they were fighting over the numbers.
I hope you liked this video
Don't forget to comment any suggestions that you have
If you haven't liked and shared this video yet then please like it and share it
and don't forget to subscribe the channel
As I keep bringing such videos to you daily
Jai Hind. Vande Mataram