Atreya!
Atreya! Open the door.
Atreya, call for you.
Hello.
- Hello.
Yes, uncle.
- Sheenu.
What do you want to say?
You've to come home at the earliest.
In four hours a bus will
leave from Bhopal for Tirupati.
Get down at Nellore.
Be brave. Take care.
What has happened, uncle?
How did this happen, uncle?
When did it happen, uncle?
This is the most important
scene in this film.
Can you see that man sitting on the chair?
He's Kayzer Soze.
He's the mastermind behind all the crimes.
No way. Is it true?
Yes! I was also shocked
when I watched it the first time.
When I watched the film for the second
time I knew that he was the criminal.
Look. Look at his innocent face.
The character who appears
to be innocent and..
..incapable of committing any
crime should be the first crime suspect.
Watch it.
He's cooking up stories after
seeing the objects in the room.
Stop! Stop!
He was in which building?
- 344.
In which building was he supposed to go?
314.
How does he know?
This proves that DiCaprio is the police.
No way. Is this true?
- Yes.
Don't act melodramatic all the time.
Once is enough.
Even if the plan is perfect
the criminal panics and makes a mistake.
We need to notice it.
Play it.
DiCaprio.
Do you like DiCaprio?
He's my favourite, sir.
- Really?
Would you like to marry him?
Of course, if I get the chance.
No. You got bowled out by my googly.
Detectives don't have a personal life.
When you're investigating a case,
your concentration should be on it.
Okay?
- Hmm..
Sorry, sir.
Tell me something..
Do you like DiCaprio?
- He's disgusting.
That's good.
Did Tom Hanks come?
- Yes.
Did he meet DiCaprio?
Did he go to the hotel?
- Yes.
Did he give the wallet?
What do you think is in the wallet?
It has only a blank paper inside.
Even an experienced detective
like Tom Hanks was fooled.
Wait.
Agent Atreya.
Shirish, tell me.
Okay. Okay. Right.
Yes! Yes!
What happened, sir? Any good news?
A dead body has been found
near Gandhiji's statue in Nellore.
Somebody is dead.
- Huh?
I mean.. we've got the case.
It's not yet clear if
it's a suicide or murder.
Oh!
I've to go there.
Did you see how detectives are?
You've to become like them.
An ordinary life is boring.
But, a detective's life
should be unique and interesting.
Whatever we do should be done in style.
What if your styling
efforts bite the dust?
Look there.
If that happens make
sure that nobody is watching.
Oh!
Let's go.
To solve a crime..
Hold on.
What are you doing?
- Sir, light, fan, TV..
No. We need to leave
immediately when we get a case.
Keep the TV on, the fan will keep moving..
..the light will be on,
and the shutter will be kept open.
While visiting the crime scene it's
important to carry a coffee mug in hand.
Keep sipping the coffee.
C'mon, let's go.
Onions for 20 rupees per kilo.
Good quality onions. Buy it.
Oh God! They've spoilt my look.
Ignore this insult.
It's not yet over for us.
Tell me something.
Why did you suddenly
want to become a detective?
It was not a rash decision.
We were taught..
..'The Hound of the Bhaskarvilles'
in our English class in school.
It's not 'Bhaskar' it's 'Basker',
Hound of Bhaskarvilles.
That's our car.
Go and open the door quickly.
Hey tomato seller.
Get lost from here.
You're disturbing me doing business hours.
Have you been squashed?
I told you to open the door.
Sorry, sir.
- Take some fresh tomatoes.
Hey! Good joke.
I told you to open this door.
Sorry, sir.
- Get in.
Where's the driver?
Has he gone out to have a cup of tea?
Call him.
Who'll drive if the driver doesn't come?
Shall we go now, sir?
- Yes, start.
Sneha..
- Yes, sir.
I'll prescribe the
dose for the next ten days.
You must watch 'The Shawshank
Redemption' daily in empty stomach.
In breakfast you must watch
'The Silence of the Lambs'.
And half an hour before lunch watch 'L.A.
Confidential'.
And 'Shutter Island' after dinner.
Follow this diet for ten days.
When we'll watch thriller
and suspense movies next month..
..you'll have to guess the murderer
within first ten minutes of the film..
This is your homework.
- Hmm.
Good.
- Okay, sir.
Where are we going?
I heard somebody died.
Sshh.. don't discuss crime inside the ar.
We'll discuss it after
we get out of the car.
Have casual conversation inside the car.
- Okay.
We'll start discussing the
crime as soon as we get out of the car.
Stay casual now.
Very good. Good.
What's up?
Look around.
Did you have breakfast?
I had idli and medu vada
for breakfast today.
Medu vada is my favourite.
I travel long distances
to eat delicious food.
A street food vendor sets up his stall
outside Murli Hotel near Gandhiji's statue.
He makes delicious medu vadas. Fantastic!
I also know this place.
- Really?
My friends and I would spend our
entire day there when we were in college.
The vendor came everyday at
4 pm and I was his first customer.
Do you know what happened once?
Once my friends and I bunked
class and went to have medu vada.
But, I met my uncle there.
What happened after that?
Your uncle thrashed you?
The girl's name is Sanjana.
It's believed that she
committed suicide at night.
I told you that we'll have
a casual conversation inside the car.
But, the moment we step out
of the car we'll discuss the case.
Let's go.
Brother, what are you doing here?
- FBI.
FBI?
- FBI?
It's a well-planned murder.
How can you be sure, sir?
Look at the suicide note on the table.
It's kept on the left.
While other books and
notes are kept on the right.
The pen is on the left
side of the notebook.
The table lamp is on the right
and the food items, phone, cold drink.
Chocolates are on the left.
She was left handed.
Then why did she hold
the gun in the right hand?
The girl done all her
work with the left hand.
Then why did she shoot
herself with her right hand?
Point number two.
She may have shot herself
with her right hand.
Why didn't the gun fall
down from her hand when she fell?
She might have held the gun
tightly as she was in a state of shock.
In that case the finger
should be on the trigger.
The pistol has been placed on her hand.
Point number three.
Smokers have the habit of throwing
away the butt only after finishing it.
Especially the depressed people.
But this girl shot herself
after finishing half the cigarette.
She may have shot herself after
smoking only half the cigarette..
..but in that case the cigarette
would've got burnt by now.
But, it didn't.
She still has a cigarette in her hand.
This means somebody else was smoking and..
..it was placed on her
hand after she was killed.
The most interesting point
is that she is not a smoker.
This is the only cigarette in the house.
There isn't a single cigarette
anywhere in the house.
Check the dustbin,
there are no cigarette butts, no ash tray.
There's no smell of cigarette.
Every room is clean except this room.
Point number four.
The ills for depression kept on the table.
The medicines have expired a year ago.
If a middle class girl
wanted to commit suicide then..
..why didn't she hang herself by the fan?
Why did she buy a pistol?
The pistol, anti-depressant pills,
cigarette, this dirty room.
The suicide note,
all these have been kept here..
..to make everybody believe
that she was depressed and..
..she committed suicide.
This is not a suicide.
It is a cold blooded murder.
Sir, you're a genius.
Hello, sir.
Who are you?
Sir, this looks like a suicide
but it's actually a murder.
Come, I'll explain.
Don't act smart.
We also know that this is a murder case.
Her friend has confessed
that he killed her for money.
You must've thrashed the
suspect and made him confess.
But, I guessed everything
by inspecting the crime scene.
Tell me something.
How did you come inside?
We didn't invite anybody for inauguration.
But, you cut the ribbon and came inside.
Look at your hat, overcoat and clothes.
It seems as if you've
come here for interrogation.
Who are you?
- FBI.
FBI? But, that's in America.
They copied the name from me.
Fatima Bureau of Investigation.
Fatima was my first girlfriend.
I named my bureau Fatima
Bureau of Investigation after her.
It was a long name
so I like to call it FBI.
It sounds very impressive.
When you go to America and
hear about FBI you can say that..
..there's FBI in Nellore.
I give discount to policemen.
Where shall I put in my card?
Forget it.
Let's go.
We solved the case together.
This calls for a selfie.
Nice #MurderSolved,
feeling excited.
Sir, are you on social media?
Shall I tag you?
I would've fallen down.
Do you still need to fall down after this?
You've already fallen down.
- Okay.
Do you want coffee?
I didn't fall down, I was about to fall.
Did they thrash you badly, sir?
When we were eating
medu vada uncle caught us.
Oh! Okay. So, uncle caught you that day.
- Yes.
What happened after that?
- What else?
He tied me to a tree
and thrashed me badly.
So, you're used to getting thrashed.
Focus on the road.
Hey! Watch out, blind fellow.
Look.. look at them.
They fooled a detective like Tom Hanks.
These things are common
in a detective's life.
They get betrayed and also thrashed.
The way you were thrashed today.
What did you say?
Got it, sir.
- What?
Whatever you were explaining.
Don't act smart.
It's my job to act smart. Got it?
What kind of clothes are these?
Why are you wearing these specs?
I don't want you to dress
like this from tomorrow.
I told you that detective
should be stylish.
Hat, coat,
band aid on the forehead are necessary.
Do you've an account in social media?
- Yes.
Do something.
Login and find my page FBI Nellore.
Like the page.
Sir, only two people have liked your page.
One is you and other
one is Sherlock Holmes.
Yes!
I made a fake account in Sherlock
Holmes' name and liked the page.
He's God for us.
Our reputation will improve
if he likes our page.
Oh!
Do you've a passport size photo?
Yes sir.
- Bring it tomorrow.
I'll make FBI ID card for you.
You'll join work from tomorrow.
- Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Sir.. sir.. I want to ask you something.
What do you want to know?
Can we put a tube-light here?
The place will look brighter and nice.
No, a dark place suits our profession.
We should not only work hard
but maintain the office environment.
Oh! What a logic!
Remember one more thing.
- What is it, sir?
Don't irritate me by
calling me sir all the time.
Then how shall I address you, sir?
'This shutter, my house, my abode.'
Agent.
- Yes.
I've brought home made snacks for you.
Keep it there.
I'll have it after I finish work.
- You can work later.
What's our plan today?
Plan?
- Yes.
We're a new company.
We aren't going to get cases every day.
We didn't have a case even yesterday.
We barged inside the crime scene.
What did you say?
- Nothing, sir.
We'll soon get a big case.
Let's solve some ordinary cases till then.
We'll have regular income.
What do you mean by ordinary cases?
We've got one.
Pass the box quickly.
Shut up! I'll thrash you.
Sir, I'm speaking the truth.
Hello, sir.
Agent, what's up?
- Everything is fine by your grace.
Take a seat. What's the case?
A theft has taken place in
the temple in the neighbourhood.
The priest saw these two
fellows roaming around the temple.
He's blaming him and vice versa.
I want to know who the real thief is.
Don't worry, sir. It's simple case.
Who stole from the temple?
Sir, I didn't steal. He is the thief.
Sir, he's the thief.
- Okay.
Take this. Don't open this now.
Do something.
Choose one finger.
One finger is for the thief
and the other one for the innocent.
The one who chooses the
finger of the thief is the thief.
You're in great hurry.
You've chosen the finger of the thief.
Why did you steal?
Sir, I didn't steal.
Sir, he's the thief.
- No sir, I didn't steal.
He's in hurry because he's nervous.
He thought that he would hold
the finger first as it would give him..
..the chance to escape.
So, he chose the finger quickly.
The innocent doesn't
know what he should choose.
The story is really impressive.
I went to the temple
last night to offer prayers.
But, you announced that I'm the
thief just because I hold your finger.
You're right.
I don't know why I feel
that you're speaking the truth.
You don't look like a thief.
I think I saw you outside
Leela Mahal theatre.
Did you go there last night?
- Yes, sir.
Did you go there to watch a film?
You booked a balcony seat. Right?
- Yes, sir.
You parked the vehicle in
the basement and went up. Right?
Yes, sir.
I told you that I didn't steal.
Sir, he's the thief.
- Sir..
Leela Mahal theatre has been
shut down for weeks for renovation.
What were you doing there?
- Sir.. well..
Did you go there to watch a
film on the cell phones of the workers?
Yes, sir.
These shameless people
steal inside a temple.
Sir, arrest him. He's the thief.
You can go.
- Sir..
I'll teach you a good lesson.
Come with me.
- Sir, I've solved the case.
Let's take a selfie.
This calls for a selfie.
You also join us.
Why are you smiling?
Make a face like that of a thief,
shameless fellow.
Okay, sir.
- Yes.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Sir, payment?
- How much?
The theft took place in
the temple so give me 1100 rupees.
But, he stole 500 rupees.
Take 11 rupees.
It's considered a lucky number.
Come on.
- Sir..
Get some important cases for me.
You always bring trivial cases.
I got this case after much difficulty.
Sir, leave me. I will give you money.
- How much?
I gave you a chit of paper. Right?
- Hmm..
Open it.
How?
I knew it.
A criminal maybe confident but
he's always scared of getting caught.
The fear reflects in
the eyes of the criminal.
Not everybody can hide it,
he also couldn't.
Can't the criminals hide it?
Do you think criminals
are very smart and intelligent?
Most of them are stupid.
You just need to read their thoughts.
How was the crime committed?
What are they afraid of?
If you can find the answers to
these questions you can solve any case.
Agent!
Hey Shirish!
- Sir.
How are you?
- Superb!
I haven't met you for years.
The crime reporter's job is so stressful.
I'm always busy writing articles.
When I get some time..
Do you remember my Guru at the NGO?
I go there.
- Oh!
Today the NGO is closed
so I came to meet you.
Lucky me.
Shall we go out for a coffee.
- Let's go.
Anna, serve me coffee in this.
How's life?
- The same routine life. Busy life.
What are you doing these days?
Any interesting case?
It's also the usual life for me.
Hey Shirish! I met you after a long time.
What are you doing these days?
I am a bit busy.
What are you doing in my locality?
I came here to meet my friend.
Agent Sai Srinivas Atreya.
- Hello, sir.
Agent? Are you a LIC agent?
I've heard about a
good life insurance policy.
What do you suggest? Should I opt for it?
He's not a LIC agent,
he's a detective agent.
He's a detective?
- Yes, a detective.
What do you exactly mean?
- Well..
I'll explain.
Sir, has the construction
work in your house over or not?
What do you mean?
- Don't say that, sir.
Sir, don't you park your
green scooter AP262473 here?
You buy a newspaper and take
the 10:30 bus from that stop..
..and go to office.
You're going to office at 11 am
which means you're a government employee.
There's only one government
office in this bus route. PWD.
You've a pen in your pocket
along with a calculator.
Are you accounts supervisor at PWD?
You get a salary of 15000
but you own two cell phones and..
..one of them is an iPhone which
you've hidden in your back pocket.
You're taking a lot of bribes these days.
You leave your work
incomplete and come back..
..to this bus stand sharp at 6 pm.
You disappear somewhere between 6-8 pm.
When you come back to
this shop again at 8 pm..
..there's dust and mud from
construction site on your shoes.
You order a tea and a smoke
and call your wife to tell her..
'Okay, darling.
I'm stuck in my office work.'
'I'll be home in half an hour.'
Sir, madam doesn't know
about the construction site.
You're building a second home.
You have a second phone.
But, you take your scooter
from the parking, buy flowers..
..and go back home as a loving husband.
Am I right, sir?
How do you know all this?
Sir, don't you drink tea here every day?
Bro, do you know him?
- No, I don't.
Do you know why?
- Why?
That's because he runs a tea stall.
You buy newspaper from
this stall daily. Right?
Grandpa, do you know him?
- I don't know him.
Why?
- That's because he sells newspaper.
But, how do I know everything about you?
That's because you're a detective.
I hope now you know
what kind of agent I am.
Yes, sir.
Get lost. The 10:30 bus has come.
Sir..
- Yes.
From your appearance I
think that you're an atheist.
Somebody has kept lemons on the road.
Be careful.
Convey my greetings to madam.
Bye, sir. Go.
He won't board the bus
from here from tomorrow.
Forget it.
I meet such people daily.
I came here to seek your help.
For what?
We need information
about unidentified bodies.
At least five such dead
bodies are found in Nellore daily.
Nobody can identify the bodies.
We don't know if they were
murdered or committed suicide.
The bodies don't match with
the ones in missing complaints.
There's a section for
unclaimed dead bodies.
They kept the bodies there for a week.
It's okay of anybody
identifies the bodies.
Or else they follow the
rules of a government hospital..
..and perform autopsy on
the body and they're cremated.
Actually, I want to find
the truth of these cases.
But unfortunately I'm
not getting time for this work.
Are you interested in this case?
Inform me when you find such a body again.
You know that I'm
interested in such cases.
Call me.
- Okay.
Sister, are you fine?
- Yes, Seenu. I'm fine.
What else? Everything okay?
Hello.
I'll reach in fifteen minutes.
Okay. Thanks.
I'll leave now.
- What happened?
See you soon. It's a murder case.
Listen, the lights and fan
in the office are switched on.
Put down the shutters at least.
He's strange.
Has a theft taken place in your home?
Is your husband involved
in an extra marital affair?
Do you suspect him?
Has anybody in your family been kidnapped?
Find the solution to
every problem in a jiffy.
What are you waiting for?
Pick up the phone, share your
problem and we'll solve your case.
FBI, Nellore.
We melt crime like ice-creams.
Friends, if you don't believe how
effective our detective techniques are..
..then I'll give you a small demo.
Send the criminal inside.
What's your name?
- Sri Hari.
You are under arrest.
Did you see that?
We give justice faster than lightning.
You won't find a better detective than me.
Call before 11 am and avail
our great offers especially for you.
The cases we get before 11
am will get an attractive and free..
Container.
Call us now.
World famous detective
Sneha will attend your call.
What do you say, Sneha?
Sneha!
We'll edit this part.
Agent Sai Srinivas Atreya.
Sir, take this. Call me.
FBI.
FBI, Nellore.
Hi.
Stop it. I'm tired.
Look behind, there's a pigeon.
Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
What are you doing?
It's very interesting.
Do it.
Stop!
Don't worry, I'll handle it.
Come and do it.
Uncle, where is mom?
I performed the final
rite in the afternoon.
An ominous time was to start soon.
It's ominous for the family to
perform final rites during this period.
So, I had to cremate her quickly.
Why didn't you wait for me, uncle?
You performed her final
rites in my absence.
Seenu, I didn't want to do it.
You know how the villagers
are and their customs.
I couldn't meet my mother for
the last time because of their customs.
You've to divide this number
with this number. Okay? Do it.
I'll divide this number with this number.
How did this happen?
Last week she went to attend
the Adi Mahotsav as she does every year.
You know the custom there.
Scared lines are chanted and coconut
is broken on the head of the devotees.
She was fine after that incident.
One day she fainted in the house.
The doctor said that the
nerves in her brain were damaged..
..and she went into coma.
She expired within two
hours after slipping into coma.
Why did you let her go there?
Leave me.
Mom..
Mom has left us.
Stop! Where are you running? Stop!
Oh mom!
- Look you've got hurt.
This is the reason why
I was trying to stop you.
Yes, Shirish.
A dead body has been found
near Venkatachalam bridge near Nellore.
What are you saying?
Come quickly.
Yes, I'm coming. Thanks.
- Okay, bye.
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
I hope you didn't murder this person.
Why will I kill him, sir?
I got a call and so I..
Were you sent to dispose the body?
Sir, I'm a detective.
Arrest him.
- Hey! Corrupt policeman.
I told you everything.
Sir, tell him that it's not
easy to arrest a famous detective.
I hope you know it.
- No, I don't. Arrest him.
Sir..
Sir, I've checked the file.
- If you want to go through it you can.
What a style! Wonderful!
A burger in one hand
and snacks in the other.
Sir, the sound of the wafers
is like the music of Rehman.
Can you hear it? Great!
What nonsense is he speaking, sir?
What a height! What an uniform!
Has he gone mad?
An inspector straight out of the films.
Sir, shall I go inside
and teach him a lesson?
Mr. Police.
I think he's mad.
Send this file to this address.
- Sir, I'm a detective.
Please..
- Okay, sir.
Hey Shirish! What's this?
I can't possibly tell you how
disappointed I am on your late arrival.
Please do the needful
to get me out of this prison.
Thank you so, so much.
What a bloody brilliant day!
Sir, I'm a crime reporter.
- So what?
Atreya, the man you've
arrested is my friend.
Your friend has become
a friend of the other prisoners.
Do you also want to get inside with him?
Sir, he's a famous detective.
You've made a mistake.
He must be famous in his house.
Nobody knows him except the vendors.
How can he be famous?
He went there because
I gave him the information.
So, you're a crime reporter?
I'll explain everything in your language.
The objects found at the
crime scene are the evidence.
And the people who are present
at the crime scene like your friend..
..are suspects for me.
I won't release him.
Get bail for him and take him with you.
The court is closed today.
We won't get a bail before tomorrow.
Let him stay here tonight.
Don't worry, we'll take good care of him.
If he wants water we'll give him milk.
We'll treat him well.
I know how to get him out.
Sneha, let's go.
Do what you can.
Why are you disturbing me?
Atreya, I'll be back soon.
- Do something quickly.
'The number is not reachable.'
Hello.
- 'The number is not reachable.'
It's okay.
Just one day. Right? I'll be fine.
It's considered auspicious
if a detective gets arrested.
When a biopic will be made
on my life this jail episode..
..will be an emotional one.
I'll try to get bail tomorrow at 10 am.
Don't worry. Everything is fine here.
Only problem is that
this person snores a lot.
Don't worry. I'll get out
in style after I get bail tomorrow.
Unfortunately, your meeting time is over.
Get out of here.
Your biopic will also be a flop.
If a biopic is made on him,
he'll have to play all the characters.
Sir, that's a fact.
How long will you lie to me?
I've gone bankrupt paying your fees.
When will u get bail?
- I'm trying my best.
I'll get you bailed out in a week.
Trust me.
I don't know when that day will come.
What happened, bro?
Nothing, bro.
There was a theft
in my village last month.
The thief escaped and I was caught.
They put me behind the bars.
I didn't steal.
I asked the lawyer to get bail for me.
He comes every week and
asks me to wait for a week.
Do something.
Tell your lawyer that you
weren't in the village that day.
Who will believe this?
Tell him that you went to hear
the sermons of Sai Baba in Chennai.
Get the accommodation bill
of a lodge in Chennai along..
..with the food bill
of any adjoining restaurant.
Take a couple of tickets from
a cinema hall next to that place.
Buy fake tickets of private
bus journey to and from Chennai.
Collect this evidence
and make a fake story.
You can easily prove that you were in
Chennai that day and not in the village.
You're great, sir.
- Thanks.
Tell your lawyer to stop reading books.
It's important to watch films.
How can they become lawyers
without watching films?
Sir.. sir.. please help me get bail.
Don't call me sir. Call me agent.
Agent Sai Srinivas Atreya.
Come on.
Stand in a queue.
- Sir.. sir..
He.. he.. he..and also he..
Everybody will be bailed
out by agent Atreya.
What did you do, bro?
I stole a vada.
- You've witness, prepare him.
He never thought that he
would be able to get out of jail.
Stand in a queue. Don't fight.
It's written all over his
face that he'll commit crime again.
You're not ashamed of stealing. Right?
Sir..
- Yes.
..this food is awful.
Get some food from a nice hotel.
Quietly at whatever
you've been given. Got it?
Go inside.
There's a new one.
Welcome, sir.
Please be seated, sir.
What are you doing here, sir?
Hello, sir.
What do you say?
You're quiet since you came.
Eat something.
What happened, sir? Any problem?
I can solve any problem.
Do you want to apply for bail?
Sir, I'm talking to you.
Okay, as you wish.
Divya..
- Who is Divya, sir?
Divya is my daughter.
What happened to her?
She would distribute
books to poor children.
She used to teach them.
She would help the poor and needy.
She went to Ongole for
work on the 18th of this month.
She called me at 10
in the night and told me..
Dad, I'm feeling very scared.
The three people won't spare me.
And her call got disconnected.
I tried several times
to connect her but couldn't.
I was confused and didn't know what to do.
I didn't know where to go for help.
I went to Ongole police
station with my friends that day..
..to register that complaint.
The policemen informed me
that they had found a dead body.
They told me to go and identify
if it was my daughter's body.
My Divya..
it was my daughter Divya's body.
The inspector told me that she
committed suicide for a boy she loved.
But, it was a lie.
Anybody could easily say
after seeing her dead body..
..that a monster raped
and then killed her.
The inspector refused to listen to me.
The doctor's mentioned
in the post-mortem report that..
..she died by hanging
herself from a ceiling fan.
Where shall I go for help?
What do I do?
Please calm down, sir.
Please tell me if you doubt anybody.
Did your daughter mention
anybody's name to you?
Her phone was found next to her dead body.
I told you that she called
me at 10 in the night.
I checked her phone records.
She got 3-4 calls from
three different numbers between..
..9 to 9:55 pm that night.
I had doubts and so I went to Ongole police
station and showed the, the evidence.
They said that they would
verify the numbers and tell me.
They told me to go back later.
When I went to meet them
again they refused to accept..
..that I gave them a phone.
I approached the local
police station also.
Somebody near Venkatachalam..
..had robbed people of their
money by luring them through chit fund.
They framed me for this
fraud and got me arrested.
You mentioned that she got
repeated calls from three numbers.
Do you know who called her?
I don't know their names.
But, I thought that
the numbers might help me..
..so I noted them down.
It's written in this paper.
Can I see it?
- Take it.
Do you've your daughter's photo?
- Yes.
Show me.
I'll enquire about these numbers.
Have patience, sir. Be strong.
When somebody very dear
to us leaves us forever..
..we just wish we could
meet and see the person just once.
But, after seeing my daughter's
dead body I prayed that..
..no father sees his
daughter in such a condition.
Hey! Get up. You've got bail.
What's wrong, agent?
You've got bail.
Then why do you look upset?
I met a man in the prison last night.
Somebody raped his
daughter and killed her.
When he tried to report
the crime at the police station..
..instead of registering his complaint..
..they framed him, seized his
belongings and put him behind the bars.
He was crying for his daughter all night.
I was shocked to hear the condition
in which daughter's body was found.
Just imagine how a father
feels when he hears..
..his daughter's dead body
has been found in this condition.
I always told you that
we'll get big case one day.
This is the case.
We'll solve this case.
Maruti Rao has given me three numbers.
The people involved have used
their power to suppress the case.
The police is also helping them.
Find out whose telephone
numbers these are.
Get the details.
- Okay, agent.
They'll shift me to
another prison tomorrow.
I'll come and meet
you there after two days.
My name is Maruti Rao.
What's your name?
- Agent Sai.
It's okay if you address me as Babu.
Agent.
- What happened?
I've got the details.
- Good.
The first number belongs
to a man named Ajay.
Vrindavan apartment,
behind railway station, Nellore.
Who's the second one?
The next one.
Harsha. Who's he? RK Puram, Nellore.
Who's the third one?
No photo? This is a girl. Vasudha.
The photo of the third person
is not there in the database.
Interesting.
Okay. Let's go to all
these three addresses.
Let's check if these people
live in the addresses mentioned.
We'll ask everybody
where they were on the 18th.
Hello, madam.
Our bathroom is clean.
No, I don't sell toilet cleaners.
Our clothes are already bright and clean.
I don't sell detergents.
Are you from the team
that surveys the toothpaste?
No, madam.
I'm from One Flight Courier service.
Oh!
I've a courier for Ajay sir.
I've been trying to
tell you but you were..
He was not in town on the 18th.
I couldn't connect with him on phone so..
He doesn't stay in town on 18th.
Yes, I spoke to sir and
he told me that he went somewhere.
He went to Ongole.
- Yes. Ongole.
He told me that he would go to Ongole.
So, I've brought the package today.
- Okay.
Give it to me.
Please don't mind, madam.
It's our company's policy that
I can give the parcel only to Ajay sir.
Is sir at home?
I told you that he's not at home,
he's in office.
He will come late.
It's okay, madam.
I'll come back in the evening.
Okay.
- Thank you, madam. Have a good day.
What are you thinking, agent?
This is Ajay's house.
He was in Ongole on 18th.
What shall we do now?
I'll take out the cap first.
I look like a toilet cleaner in this.
Remove Ajay's address from the packet
and replace it with Harsha's address.
I came on 18th, madam.
He was on Ongole on 18th
and so you couldn't meet him.
Okay. I spoke with sir.
He told me to come today, so I've come.
Okay. He's not at home right now.
He'll back soon.
- Okay.
I've few more parcels to deliver.
I'll deliver them and come back.
Is it okay if I come at
4-4:30 in the evening. - Okay.
Thank you, madam. Have a good day.
Harsha was also in Ongole on 18th.
I'm sure something happened
in Ongole that day.
Hello, madam.
There's a courier for Vasudha madam.
Who's Vasudha?
I got this address for delivery.
Nobody of this name lives here.
Doesn't she live here?
- No.
Are you new here?
- Yes.
Do you know the people
who lived here before you? - No.
It's okay.
Can I get the landlord's number?
Why do you want it?
It's an important courier.
9030693149.
Okay. Thanks.
Thank you.
call that number.
- Yes.
'The number is not reachable.'
It's not reachable.
Try Vasudha's number.
- Okay.
'The number is not reachable.'
Okay. Let's try the owner's number.
Ajay and Harsha both
were in Ongole on 18th.
I'm sure something happened there.
Vasudha definitely knows about it.
You and I'll follow
Ajay and Harsha separately.
Harsha looks like a murderer.
He seems dangerous.
For safety purpose you'll
follow him and I'll follow Ajay.
Since police is trying to
cover up we'll trace the activities..
..of Ajay and Harsha
for the next 2-3 days.
We need to be alert and see
where they go and whom they meet.
We've to note down every detail
of where they go and whom they meet.
Okay?
Could you connect with Vasudha?
- She's not reachable.
What about the owner?
- Not reachable.
Keep trying their number.
It's important that we talk to them.
Meet me outside Harsha's house at 8 am.
But agent, I don't have a bike.
I suddenly remembered that
Harsha's bike is also not working.
Walk. C'mon walk.
Stop!
A new hospital has opened.
It's offering free family check-up. Okay?
I'm an orphan.
Buy cotton candies.
Abdul Razzak, a Persian
traveler met Shri Krishna Devarai.
Abdul Razzak was a Pakistani cricketer.
How could he meet Krishna Devarai?
History books are so confusing.
Brother, please help me.
Read this book.
May god bless you.
Where are you, Sneha?
Outside his house.
Has Harsha come?
Not yet.
Not yet?
Agent, shall I go to his house
and tell him that I want to follow him?
Why aren't you coming out?
Don't act smart.
Do as you're instructed.
I'll call you later.
- Come home early.
Yes, I'll come.
Don't forget that we'll go out today.
Come home early.
Why do you interrupt me when I'm leaving?
Sir, can I talk to you for few minutes?
I've a good credit card offer for you.
- I'm not interested.
It's a card with lot of facilities.
You'll get lounge access at airports.
You won't have to wait in queue.
- Okay.
Sir, it's the best.
You can buy grocery,
veggies, book flight tickets with it.
Your entire family
can enjoy in the lounge.
Okay, tell me.
Hello. What about the offers?
Get lost.
- What?
Sorry, sir.
Thank you. The offers are over.
Okay, auntie. I'll get sugar for you.
How much? 2 kilos. Right?
What's up? Planning to rob the bank?
Sir, there's a very good offer for you.
If you buy this book
you'll become intelligent.
If you read this book your
IQ will reach from 0 to 150.
You'll get promoted
to the commissioner's post.
School students crack IIT
exams and quiz competitions..
..after reading or book.
The children who read
this book and grow up are..
..considered intelligent.
You should buy this book, sir.
I'll give you 50 rupees discount.
Will I be able to become smart in a week?
You'll start becoming smart
after reading it for 3-4 days.
If you read this book then
you won't have to sell this book.
Get lost.
- No problem, sir.
Thank you very much. Have a good day.
My wife irritates me at home
and people like him do the same outside.
Agent, I'm outside Nellore.
Harsha is sitting at an ice-cream shop.
There's a man with him.
He's talking to Ajay, right?
Turn around.
Agent, shall we follow them?
- It won't help.
Hold on. Sit and talk.
This is how detectives communicate.
We don't know each other.
Venkatachalam railway bride.
Newspaper office.
Car rental agency. Mortuary.
I've the feeling that they're connected
to the railway bridge murder also.
They look tensed as they're
trying to hide something.
There are two points.
We must find the man at Tirupati
and get information about Vasudha.
Second is Divya.
She was also at Ongole on 18th.
Why did she go there?
Did she go there for a NGO activity?
What was her work there?
We need answers to these questions.
Come early tomorrow morning.
We've lot of work.
Sir.
- Get my bill.
Get separate bills for us.
We're not together.
I don't know her.
Pay the bill, get out of
here and meet me at the parking.
Agent, it's the call from the
landlord whom we were calling yesterday.
Sir, I'm speaking from a courier company.
- Yes, tell me.
There's a parcel for
Vasudha madam at your address.
Okay.
I met your tenants who said
that Vasudha madam didn't live there.
What name did you mention? Vasudha?
- Yes, sir.
The tenants came here three
months back and so they don't know her.
Yes.
- The old tenants may know her.
A couple lived there before.
But, the girl's name wasn't Vasudha.
- Okay.
Where are the couple now?
Can you help me?
I think they shifted to America.
I don't have any other
knowledge about them.
Right, sir. Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay, sir.
We need to find out who this person is.
I'm sure Vasudha knows
what happened at Ongole that day.
Who killed Divya?
Divya..
Agent.
Oh God!
How is this possible?
You're Divya. Right?
Who are you?
Who is Divya?
- No.. no.. look..
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
What do you want?
Your dad Maruti Rao is in jail.
He thinks that you're dead.
- Dad!
Who is he?
Do you know him?
Is he your dad?
- Yes, he's my father.
How is this possible?
Sir, do you understand
what I'm trying to say?
Please try to understand
what I want to say.
There was an attempt to rape on her.
She is my daughter. What are you saying?
Sorry.
- Please talk with due respect.
Get lost from her.
- Sorry, sir.
Let's go, the bus is going to leave.
Let's go.
What were you saying?
She's the girl whose photo I saw.
She is Divya.
The photo that Maruti
Rao showed me was of this girl.
She is alive but that poor
man thinks that she's dead.
Are you sure?
Come.
Suri, see what he wants.
Hello, sir. We've come to meet Maruti Rao.
Visiting hours are over.
Come tomorrow.
Sir, please help. It's urgent.
I want to speak to him
for a couple of minutes.
Okay.
What name did you say?
Maruti Rao.
There's no person by this name here.
Maruti Rao, sir. He's an aged man.
He has been transferred from
rural police station to sub-jail.
Please check again.
Nobody has been brought
here from the village..
..in the last three days.
Nobody was brought here?
I said it. Don't you understand?
You are so coward.
'Somebody has been giving me
death threats for the last few days.'
Stop! Where are you going?
I want to talk to sir.
- He's busy, talk later.
It's urgent.
- Sit here.
'Somebody has been giving me
death threats for the last few days.'
Detective, sit down quietly.
'Sir, I don't know who's doing this.'
'Doesn't matter, come tomorrow.'
Sir, please make it quick.
- No. Wait here.
'Okay, let's go. We'll come tomorrow.'
Send the agent.
- Go.
Thank you.
Hello.
So, you're back.
The second incarnation of Sherlock Holmes.
Didn't you get burger for me?
Help me and I'll definitely
get burgers for you.
You arrested Maruti Rao few days back.
But, you didn't; transfer him to sub-jail.
Maruti Rao? Who is he?
Maruti Rao, sir, the old man
who was crying inside the lock-up.
He was dressed in loincloth and shirt.
His name was Gopalam and not Maruti Rao.
He was creating a ruckus
after getting drunk.
We arrested him for a night
and released him next morning.
Who is Gopalam? His name was Maruti Rao.
Was he arrested for creating
ruckus in a drunk state?
Tell him.
Sir, please give me his address.
- Address?
A VIP wants his address, give it to him.
Do you think we've nothing
better to do than note down..
..the address of every drunk person?
Get out. Get out.
Hey!
The police is hiding something from us.
I spoke with Maruti Rao that day.
I saw the pain in his eyes, Sneha.
Why don't we go to Ongole
police station and get information?
He said that the case
was registered at Ongole.
Let's go to Ongole.
Agent, I need to go home.
My mom has been repeatedly calling me.
Okay, you go home. I'll come with the car.
Tell your mom that we'll go to Ongole.
Where were you?
Mom needs some medicines.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
Agent, I need a week's leave.
- For what?
The Karni Mata festival
will start in Bikaner, Rajasthan.
So what?
It's believed that Goddess Durga
comes there in the disguise of rat.
My mother believes that if we can spot
a white rat it's considered very lucky.
We go there every week
but we couldn't go last year..
..as my mom was not well.
Do you believe in these superstitions?
You're an educated girl.
Can't you convince your mom?
It's not even a month that
you joined work and you want leave.
I'm supposed to work only from 10-5.
I'm already working over time.
I deserve leave.
- Okay.
Agent, will anybody at
Ongole police station help us?
Ongole's SI is Shirish's friend.
- Oh! That's good.
If the case is registered there
then we'll find out who's lying.
Hello, sir.
- Hello.
I'm from Nellore.
My friend Shirish must've called you.
- Yes. Tell me.
Sir, you must've registered the
death case of a girl named Divya on 18th.
I need the detail.
We found a dead body
but it was a male dead body.
Male dead body?
- Yes.
We couldn't identify the body.
Did we get the dead body
of a girl named Divya on 18th?
How did they get a male dead body?
Please check and tell me.
Do inform me if you get any information.
Thank you.
Sorry, Atreya. No complaint
registered in the name of Divya.
Something is definitely wrong, agent.
I'm totally confused. I'm baffled.
The old man said that
the case was registered here.
But, they're saying that it isn't.
Who is lying?
Something is wrong.
We're making some mistake.
The registered case is missing.
Maruti Rao is missing from the cell.
What has happened to him?
What happened at Ongole on 18th night?
One evidence.. I wish I get a small clue.
Agent, excuse me.
I want to go to the washroom.
Breaking news. A woman has been robbed.
Yes. Men riding on a bike targeted
her and escaped with her chain.
An employee of Nellore
bank was murdered today.
The body of this man
was found outside the city.
The deceased was a resident
of Nellore and his name was Ajay.
He has been brutally murdered.
His body was found near crematorium
in the outskirts of Nellore.
The police have started
their investigation.
The accused will soon be arrested.
The SP has promised to
arrest the murderer in 24 hours.
The police is investigating the case.
The murderer will soon
be in police custody.
Stay tuned for more news.
Mr. Srinivas Atreya.
- Yes.
You're under arrest.
- For what?
For killing a bank employee named Ajay.
Concentrate on your breathing.
Lift your little finger.
This one? Can't I use some other finger?
Stop the nonsense.
Place your little finger
on one side of the nose.
Take a deep breath.
Breathe.
Atreya.
Breathe out.
- Atreya.
Will I be able to get
out of jail if I do this?
I don't know if you'll get out of jail,
but I'm sure you'll be stress free.
What's going on?
I'm enjoying the air inside the jail,
my friend.
Okay.
The police arrested you and you're
not taking any action against them.
What shall I tell them?
Say that you're innocent.
Do you know what they
said when I asked them?
They said that you're
busy doing yoga here.
The CCTV footage of the hospital,
bank ATM, car rental agency..
..will prove easily
that I was following Ajay.
Ajay's washer-man or security
guard will also identify me.
The day Ajay was killed in was
following him in different disguises.
And there's proof.
You want me to tell the
police that I'm innocent.
They'll torture me badly.
So, I didn't say anything.
I'm the prime suspect in the preliminary
investigation of Ajay's murder.
I know this very well but who killed Ajay.
Ajay and Harsha..
Harsha..
Where's Harsha?
I don't know, agent.
Wasn't Harsha questioned
when Ajay was found dead?
No.
- Call Harsha now.
He's not taking the call.
- That's it.
Ajay and Harsha had an
argument outside the restaurant.
Yes.
- Ajay was killed and Harsha is missing.
Do anything to find out where Harsha is.
Harsha is the prime
suspect in Ajay's murder.
Quick.
- Okay.
Okay, agent.
Is Harsha at home?
When will you get his body?
Police verification is going on.
It'll take time.
- Okay.
Somebody killed Ajay
and Harsha ruthlessly.
Their belongings were checked
to identify their bodies.
All of their body parts
haven't been recovered yet.
Only the murder weapon has been found..
..which has your finger prints on it.
My finger prints?
That's not all.
They've found drugs
at Ajay and Harsha's house.
And the same drug has
been found in your house.
What?
The case against you has become strong.
They're connecting
this case with drug mafia.
The police believe that this
is the reason you killed them.
It'll be published and telecast
in every newspaper and channel tomorrow.
You're famous now. Happy?
Just a second. Just a second.
- I warned you.
Maruti Rao came in my
cell the day I got arrested.
I took up this case when he
told me about his daughter. Right?
I didn't know anything.
I thought I am helping him.
I thought that my agency will
become popular if I solve this case.
I was happy that I got an
important case after a long time.
I didn't get the case.
The case found us.
Think about it.
What was I doing?
I was following Ajay and Harsha
so that I could solve the case.
But, nothing happened.
The investigation wasn't successful.
They fooled me at every
step to plant evidence against me.
That knife was fallen on the streets.
I picked it up and kept it in its place.
They must've got my
finger prints from there.
What's the murder weapon?
A billhook machete used to cut coconuts.
That's it.
They planned Ajay and Harsha's murder.
They want to frame me for this
murder and make me the scapegoat.
The old man's name isn't Maruti Rao.
His name is Gopalam.
Gopalam lied to me.
Atreya, listen to me.
These people seem to be very dangerous.
I'll try my best to bail you out.
You're not Sherlock Holmes.
So, please forget this case.
Sherlock Holmes is a fictional character..
..but Agent Sai Srinivas
Atreya is a real detective.
They fooled me. Very good.
They did a great job.
The case has become interesting now.
I won't stop unless I find the culprits.
What can we do?
- Do three things?
First. Find out where Ajay and
Harsha went and the people they met.
Only then we'll find out
what they were really up to.
Second. Gopalam gave me three numbers.
Ajay, Harsha, Vasudha.
Two people are dead.
Vasudha is either dead
or soon going to die.
We need to find her quickly.
Third. Can you bail me out?
The case against you is very strong.
Apply for the bail.
- I'll try.
Okay.
I'll leave now.
Shirish, when did Ajay die?
- At 9 pm.
But, I was at sub-jail at 9 pm.
Really?
- I went there to ask about Gopalam.
Then how can I kill Ajay?
Go to the jail.
Get the CCTV footage
and apply bail stating that..
..I wasn't at the crime
scene at the time of murder.
Right.
I'll do it.
- Okay.
See you.
The camera footage
of the jail wasn't clear.
You've got interim bail for five days.
You need to find evidence
to prove your innocence.
You've only five days.
You've to go to the police
station and sign daily.
Okay.
Thanks, buddy.
Why don't you join us?
- No, I've to leave.
I've to go to Kabuli NGO.
I've lot of pending work there.
- Okay.
See you soon. I'll call you.
Thanks, buddy. Bye.
The Sherlock Holmes dialogue that..
..you said yesterday was awesome.
It was comic but very effective.
What's your next plan?
Listen to my plan carefully.
The MLA's son is getting
married at Nellore today.
We'll go there and..
Agent..
- I plan to go and dance there.
What's the next plan?
I've been framed for two murders.
Shall we solve this case first?
They've left.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Did this man come here?
- Who are you?
I'm from the special
investigation department.
Why do you know the information?
Sneha..
- Agent.
..we haven't found the
children's kidnapper yet.
No, agent.
I've found him.
- Who is he, agent?
Abdul, the owner of Imran Cars.
A man with a French
beard is kidnapping kids.
He's our regular customer.
He booked a cab for
Venkatachalam three days back.
He came back yesterday
as he left something in the car.
This is the truth, sir.
Did he come to take
his personal belongings?
Yes, sir. He took all his belongings.
He wanted the newspaper
articles of unidentified bodies..
..that were found in the last few days.
Unidentified bodies?
- Yes, sir.
He found a dead body
under Venkatachalam bridge.
He was after me to get the
post-mortem report of that body.
This is a government hospital.
Nobody has the time
to conduct post-mortem of..
..unidentified bodies.
They write anything in the report.
Heart attack. Kidney failure.
They write down anything they feel like.
That's how they try to finish their work.
That's not all.
Look at this.
This is the signature of Satish.
But, there's no doctor
named Satish in this hospital.
They used to come for these reports.
If these reports get exposed,
I'll be in trouble.
I won't share it with anybody.
I knew Harsha for a long time.
He was a student of criminology.
He and Ajay were working
on a case of unidentified bodies.
I found a dead body
near Venkatachalam bridge.
I called them for that.
Harsha was in great rush that day.
He dropped his bike keys somewhere.
So we went back to find the keys.
Sneha be careful as
there's a constable there.
I'll guide you on phone.
Who are you?
I've come for investigation.
But, some policemen already came before,
- Yes.
This is the second level of investigation.
Do you doubt anybody?
Who can I doubt?
Please leave me alone.
Did Mr. Ajay give you
any documents that night?
He didn't give me anything.
Please try to recall.
You may remember something.
Recall? What can I recall?
I told you that he didn't give
me anything. Please don't disturb me.
I don't intend to disturb you.
Sneha, do as I say.
Go near the door.
Stand there. Turn around.
Look at her and repeat what I say.
Madam..
..your husband has been ruthlessly killed.
Only we can help..
We're doing our best.
If you don't help us..
To find out why Ajay
was killed and by whom..
It'll remain a secret.
Ajay's death will be wasted.
The decision is yours.
Just a minute.
Yes!
Did you get anything?
These are the photos
of the unidentified bodies.
They went to Ongole on
the 18th to click these photos.
Agent, there's somebody at home.
The constable is sleeping.
He has woken up.
Turn around. Don't look at him.
Tell me..
Let's have a casual conversation.
Anything casual.
Did you feed the cat?
- Yes.
Does the cat drink buttermilk?
What's the name of your cat?
- I call him agent.
Has he left?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Agent.
- What happened?
Agent, this is the same
envelope that somebody gave..
..to Harsha at the supermarket that day.
My name is written here.
This has my details.
Let's go.
Agent, I've left my cell phone there.
Sneha, the constable will come back.
I'll be back soon.
- Get it quickly.
Agent!
Are you okay?
Are you fine?
Let's get out of here.
Why are you stressed?
Somebody tried to kill me.
This proves that we're on the right track.
Don't panic. I'll be fine.
They've come.
Hello, sir.
Sir, thanks for responding immediately.
It's okay, Atreya.
I overheard your conversation yesterday.
It isn't safe to discuss
such things at the police station.
So, I told you to meet me outside.
Explain this matter
right from the beginning.
Sneha, can you identify the
man who gave the envelope to Harsha?
I'll identify him if I see him.
I was concentrating on Harsha
and so I don't remember his bike's number.
But, I remember that
the first number was 7.
There are thousands of vehicles
whose number starts with 7.
It's not going to be easy.
Anyway, I'll get the list of the
all the bikes that start with number 7.
Thank you, sir.
I'm getting late.
Come to the station and sign.
See you tomorrow.
- Agent.
Agent, the bike that I
saw that day is parked outside.
It's not exactly the
same one but its similar.
It was like this
Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
This is a police bike, Sneha.
It was used by blue colts.
The constables use it now.
I remember it because
it had blue and red stripes.
Okay. Come with me.
Sagar.
- Sir.
Take out the list of the police
vehicles whose number starts with 7.
Quick.
Sir, here's the list.
Sneha, what'll be that man's age?
Between 35-40.
Make a list of the people
who come under the age of 35-40.
Photos.
Was he the one?
Next?
He's the one.
He gave the envelope to Harsha.
I've seen this man somewhere.
Sneha, are you sure?
- Damn sure, sir.
Suresh.
- Sir.
Call Narayan to the
police station immediately.
Go.
- Okay, sir.
Narayan, why are you late?
I went to the adjoining village.
Narayan, come.
- Yes, sir.
Did you meet Harsha two days ago?
Yes, sir.
Why did you meet him?
- Actually I..
- Sir..
Tell me.
Sir, Harsha spotted him
near the dead body found under..
..Venkatachalam bridge.
He was a prisoner in my police station,
so he wanted his detail.
And I gave him the detail. That's it.
Are you speaking the truth?
- I swear on my mother.
Okay, you can go.
- Sir.
I think he's speaking the truth, Atreya.
Ajay and Harsha must've
seen me near the dead body.
They knew that I was investigating
the case of unidentified bodies.
Why didn't they file a case against me?
Why did they want my details?
Maybe they wanted
to meet me for this case.
Maybe they knew something
about this case, sir.
Before they could share any detail,
they got killed.
So, they tried to kill me.
Sir, they could've framed
anybody for the murder.
Why did they frame me?
The connection between Ajay,
Harsha and me is the dead body.
The entire episode
started with the dead body.
Sir, I've a request.
Please get a postmortem of this body done.
If we find out the reason of death,
we'll also find the connection..
..between Ajay and Harsha's death.
Sure.
- Thank you, sir.
No problem.
I'll meet you tomorrow, sir.
- Okay.
Thank you, sir.
They told me to file a
complaint in this police station.
But, the area doesn't
come under our jurisdiction.
Everybody is ignoring my problem.
Why are you complaining here?
I've been receiving threats
since the last three days that..
..they'll kill my daughter.
But, you're not ready
to listen to my problem.
This is a police station.
Behave properly.
This is not an excuse, sir.
Why don't you understand my problem?
Why don't you throw away your uniform?
My daughter is missing.
What's the problem?
- Happy?
Who is he? What does he want?
If anything happens to my daughter,
I won't spare anyone.
Sir, he's saying that
his daughter is missing.
I told him that his address
doesn't come under our jurisdiction.
My daughter is missing, sir.
If anything happens to her..
Please find her, sir.
I don't know where she is right now.
Listen to me, sir. Please calm down.
Crying won't help.
Let me see what I can do for you.
Please come and sit here.
Give details of your daughter.
She's fair and 5'5" tall.
When she went out of the
house she was in a red dress.
Any identification mark?
She has a tattoo of her
mom which she got inked..
..on her hand when she was a child.
She went to the chemist's
shop at night two days ago.
She didn't return home.
I asked everybody.
But, nobody knows about her.
What's your daughter's name?
- Vasudha.
Vasudha?
- Yes, sir.
Sir, when was the last
time you met your daughter?
I spoke to her for the last time
when she was going to the chemist's shop.
She has been missing since then.
Did you try calling her?
Her phone is switched off.
Suresh.
- Sir.
Any information about a female dead body?
Yes, sir.
I've found a body under
Kawali bridge an hour ago.
Some officers have gone there.
- Okay.
Listen to me.
- Sir.
Come with me.
Good morning, sir.
What happened?
We've found a girl's dead body
but it hasn't been identified yet.
She has been ruthlessly killed.
Her face is disfigured.
The body has started decomposing
and is smelling awful.
Which colour clothes is she wearing?
- Red.
Come with me.
Sir, take a look.
What has happened, Vasu?
Vasudha.
Please don't touch the body.
Sir, I was telling you repeatedly.
- Sir, we got this.
They killed my daughter.
We found it next to the body.
Vasu..
What's up?
What are you doing here?
Who allowed you to come here
Why are you looking up in the sky?
Counting stars during day time?
Will you get stars for her?
Hey detective, he is talking to you.
Can't you hear me?
Why are you always
spotted near dead bodies?
What can I do about it?
You never do your job.
- Mind your language.
If you did your job properly
then the girl wouldn't have died.
Lower your voice.
- What will you do?
Do you know who killed her?
- Who?
You killed her.
- Yes.
You've killed her in the same
way as you killed Ajay and Harsha.
You've killed her.
You're not capable to solve this crime.
Call me and I'll solve the case for you.
What do you think of yourself?
- Agent, let's go from here.
What are you saying?
- You're speaking a lot.
Don't be sacred.
We haven't done anything wrong.
Agent, let's go.
- You don't worry.
Yes, tell me.
Listen.
- Yes.
The same detective has killed this girl.
Okay.
- Cancel his bail.
Okay? - Okay.
- Agent, let's go from here.
Will you arrest anybody you
see at the crime scene? - Agent.
Let's go.
- How dare you challenge?
The dead body is also at the crime scene.
Will you arrest her?
Cancel the bail of the dead body.
You can't do your work and
you consider yourself an inspector.
Go from here.
Go and start a street-side food stall.
Did you bring him here?
Are you taking his help?
- Sorry, sir.
Take him away from there.
Okay, sir.
- Take him away.
Clear the place.
Leave me. Vasu..
Vasu..
I told you to come and meet me tomorrow.
What's this, Atreya?
You've applied for bail and there
are strong chances of it being cancelled.
Why did you argue with them?
We couldn't save Vasudha, sir.
- So?
Sir, can you get the autopsy report
of the body found under railway bridge.
Hello, Aditya.
Hello, Vamsi.
I wanted to tell you about the dead body.
It's neither murder nor suicide.
It's a natural death. Liver failure.
Natural death?
How will we know whose body it is?
I've sent his fingerprints and hair
samples for matching with the database.
If we're lucky we'll find a match.
- No..no..
Okay, Aditya. Thank you.
How can it be a natural death?
Three people were killed
because of this death.
Ajay, Harsha and Vasudha.
All three of them were killed.
There's a serious problem.
How can it be natural death?
Let's meet Aditya and check the report.
Shall I help you.. kick the bike?
Who are you?
Why were you following us?
What's up?
Have you tied us or have we tied you?
You'll set me free and
salute me when you find out.
Is it?
If you see my track record
you'll see that I finish..
..dozens of criminals like you in a day.
This is the last time I'm asking you.
Who are you?
My name is Bal Venkata Subramanian Swami.
As it was a long name I call myself Bobby.
I'm from Hassan, Karnataka.
Come to the point.
I was following you for the last two days.
Why were you following me?
Why are you asking me?
I'm a detective.
What else will I do?
I run FBI.
FBI stands for?
- Friends Bureau of Investigation.
My friends helped me with it so..
Why are you laughing?
Check on social media and
you'll find a page on FBI Hassan.
Sherlock Holmes has liked it.
I thought there was only
one spirit of Sherlock Holmes.
What else?
One day when I was going home,
I saw a dead body on the road.
Nobody came to claim that body.
The police declared it
unidentified and cremated the body.
I got to know that you killed that person.
Since then I've investigating
the case and was following you.
Did you get a call?
- Yes.
They took my name.
- Of course.
And you started following me.
- Right.
Shut up! Shut up,
Bal Venkata Subramanian Swami.
They've fooled us.
They managed to dupe you more.
Didn't you get it, sir?
They confused me and made
me follow Ajay and Harsha.
They followed the same tactic
and made this fellow follow me.
They killed them and
framed me for the murders.
Now that I've got bail they
want to kill me and frame him for it.
It's a dangerous game, sir.
We're busy solving the case like fools.
Do you do drugs?
- No, only alcohol and smoke.
Start doing drugs as they'll
soon find drugs from your house.
They've managed to cover their
perfect crime and we're their scapegoats.
We're chasing each other
like fools and playing silly games.
You played well.
Very well-played. God bless you.
Was it a game?
Didn't you kill anybody?
You're a useless detective.
Shall I give it to you in writing?
Set him free.
Please.
If this is a game then who told me
about the dead body on the railway track.
I'm confused
What did you say?
- That I'm a detective.
No, after that.
I was going home.
No..no.. what did you say in the end?
A dead body was found
on the railway track.
Venkatachalam. Venkatachalam.
The body at Venkatachalam
was found near the railway track.
The body at Kawali was also
found under a railway bridge.
This body was also found
near the railway track.
So what?
It means..
Shirish..
- Yes, tell me.
Do you've the list of the places
where the unidentified dead bodies..
..were found in the past one year?
I've the list but I'm busy right now.
Can you send me the list right now?
I'm not in office right now.
Mail to me.
Okay, I'll tell my colleague
to mail it to you. Okay?
Okay. Do it quickly.
- Okay, bye.
Atreya, he has applied
for your bail cancellation.
The hearing is scheduled
at 11 in the morning tomorrow.
You may have to surrender
by tomorrow afternoon.
Agent. Shirish has sent the
list of the unidentified bodies.
52 unidentified dead bodies
have been found in our state..
..in the last six months.
24 bodies have been found near the
railway track or under the railway bridge.
Kakinada and Tada.
All the bodies have been
found between these two stations.
Some were found in Ongole,
some at Nellore.
All of them were found
near the railway tracks.
These cases are not separate.
All these cases are connected.
What?
- Yes.
How?
These bodies are being thrown
out of a train that runs on this route.
From a train.
Sir, we found a body near Venkatachalam.
What was the cause of death?
- Natural death.
Right?
- Hmm..
Then how did the body
reach the railway track.
One more point.
The places where these bodies were found..
..don't have a road
that leads to that spot.
How did the dead bodies reach
the place where there's no road?
It's definite that the bodies
are being thrown out of a train.
But, if dead bodies are transferred
by train they'll get caught.
What if it is a goods' train?
Agent, why can't it be a passenger train?
Think about it.
A passenger train
carries lot of travelers.
It's impossible there.
Sir, let me sit on the side
berth so that I can throw the dead body.
That's impossible.
I'm sure it's a goods' train.
This can't be done in broad
daylight even from a goods' train.
I'm sure it is done at night.
It's impossible during the day.
At night they do it at a
time when everybody is sleeping.
It means after 10 in
the night and before 5 am.
Bobby.
- Agent.
Find out the goods'
train that pass through..
..the Kakinada-Tada route after 10 pm.
Okay.
Sneha..
- Yes, agent.
Open the map.
Look at this.
This is Kakinada and this is Tada.
In the last six months..
I think these bodies are
being smuggled from Tamil Nadu.
How can you be sure that
they are coming from Tamil Nadu?
Look at this. This is Tada.
This comes in Tamil Nadu-Andhra border.
This train either goes through
Tami Nadu and enters Andhra through Tada.
As soon as they cross Tamil
Nadu border they throw the bodies..
..wherever they want in Andhra.
The police stations change
with the change in state.
The police fails to establish
a connection between these dead bodies.
The bodies are coming from another state.
So, they will not
be able to identify them.
Find out if you've any report
of unidentified bodies being..
..found in places beyond
Tada that come in Tamil Nadu.
Sure.
Sneha.
- Agent.
Which are the stations after Tada?
After Tada comes Arambakkam
and Gummidipoondi.
After that comes the areas near Chennai.
Agent.
- What happened?
A goods' train goes to Delhi from
Chennai every week. - Yes!
The train stops at a signal
near Arambakkam around 10-10:30 pm..
..to allow a superfast train go.
- Yes!
Atreya.
- Yes, tell me.
No unidentified bodies were
found between Tada and Chennai.
Yes!
This train stops at Arambakkam
station for 30 minutes.
The culprits know this fact.
They put the bodies inside
the train during this time.
They throw the bodies randomly anywhere
after they cross the state borders.
Agent, how can you be sure that
this happens at this particular station?
The stations that come before
Arambakkam comes under Chennai.
It's not possible to do
this job at any big station.
They need a small station for this job.
And that station is Arambakkam.
They're doing so much hard
work only to dispose dead bodies.
We need to go to Arambakkam
to find the truth.
Vamsi sir will also join us.
He'll come behind the market in his car.
Agent.. agent..
Agent..
- Agent..
Sister, call the senior doctor.
- Okay.
Hi!
It's fake, doctor.
It makes sound and smoke emits out of it.
Then why was he bleeding?
He had coffee in one hand
and vermilion in another hand.
I added water and rubbed
it and blood was ready.
They've their eyes on me.
If they find out that we're going to
Arambakkam then they'll attack us again.
If we want to reach
Arambakkam secretly then..
..Agent Sai Srinivas Atreya has
to be critical injured and hospitalized.
You shot me very well.
Go and lie down.
Do you know what you're going to do?
Perfect! Do it again.
Good. Great!
Cover him with a blanket.
They can come here too.
Will you help me, madam?
Go to the corridor after
five minutes and say..
Doc.. doc.. the patient is critical.
Atreya's BP is fluctuating.
Say something like this and come. Okay?
Give an audition.
Doctor, the patient is critical.
Doctor, his BP is falling.
Please come doctor.
Great!
- Let's go.
That's mine.
Go and change your clothes.
- Okay.
Somebody has shot Atreya. He's in ICU now.
Okay. Keep an eye on him.
What's wrong with you, Bobby?
Why have you put this band aid?
This is just a bandage.
Do you even know what we do with people?
This is not band aid but my shroud.
I was born in a grave.
Sorry, it's too melodramatic.
I would've understood the dialogue
if you said it in any other language.
Really?
It's a clichd dialogue in films
Hey! Same pinch.
My mom says that every
person has seven lookalikes.
Two are right in front of me.
Sir, let's go.
Yes tell me, Aditya.
The fingerprints of the
dead body found in Venkatachalam..
..matches that of a
murder suspect in Gujarat.
What?
- What?
I can provide the other details
only after a couple of hours.
Okay.
A murder case in Gujarat?
What's going on, sir?
Hello, sir.
I'm a sub-inspector from Nellore.
I want some information.
- Okay.
A goods' train passes this
station at 10 in the night. - Yes.
It goes to Delhi.
- So?
When the train halts here
dos any illegal activity.. I mean..
Who will come here, sir?
I've been the station in-charge for years.
The goods' train stopped
here for half an hour.
I never noticed any illegal activities.
Gopalam?
Sir, whose photos are these?
Sir, these photos were clicked at
a function of the railways five years ago.
There's a popular theatre
group in the next village.
They're artists of that group.
Theatre group?
- Yes, sir.
Where's this theatre group located?
It's been closed for a long time.
Where will I find him?
- I don't know, sir.
Sir, do you know?
- I know.
He lives 30 km from here.
Atreya is not in the hospital.
Kill Gopalam.
Okay, I'll do it.
Who drinks to tolerate everything?
I ordered whisky.
Why did you get beer for me?
This is wrong.
I'll tell everybody. Listen to me.
Police! Police!
Police!
Who are you?
You were calling the police.
Where am I, sir?
Who are you?
Give me a small drink
and I'll say everything.
Do you want a drink now?
I didn't have any work three years back.
We would keep wandering
from one village to another.
I got a phone call one day.
I was asked to do a task
and he promised to give me money.
Hello. Where do I have to go?
I'll be there. I'm coming.
I've got work. Let's go.
C'mon, let's go.
We were told to take the dead
bodies to the state border and..
..and cremate them quietly in the jungle.
In the beginning we got
3-4 dead bodies in a month.
Then we started getting 7-8 dead bodies.
We would get 5000 rupees per dead body.
We were very happy.
But, one day the forest
police caught us cremating a body.
We heard the siren and managed to escape.
The people who gave us the
contract came to know about it.
Do something.
Stop this work for few days.
Okay. Don't worry. I'll do as you say.
We would steal for livelihood.
But, this job helped us earn decent money.
But, we stopped getting money.
We were worried.
Two weeks after this
incident I got a call.
This time instead of cremating the
bodies we would take them to another van.
They would return the bodies
after keeping them for 7-8 hours.
Bring the dead bodies to
the place mentioned by us and..
..dispose them at the same time.
The dead bodies were treated
in such a way that nobody..
..could identify them
even if they were found.
After doing that we would
take the bodies to Arambakkam.
The train to Delhi stopped
at Arambakkam station for 30 minutes.
We carried the dead
bodies and took them there.
We would put them in the train.
After crossing the border of
the state they were randomly disposed..
..in different places.
Who are these people?
Why do they do this?
From where do the dead bodies come from?
We didn't know anything.
We never had the courage to ask.
But one day we understood the game.
Cremate him and dispose
the ashes in the holy Ganges.
Followers of Hinduism believe
that if the ashes of the cremated bodies..
..are immersed in the
Ganges the soul rests in peace.
People believe that if
a dead person is cremated on..
..the banks of Kashi the
soul goes straight to heaven..
..and is freed from the
cycle of birth and death.
Some people believe
these things from heart..
..but they don't have enough money
to take the body to Kashi for cremation.
The people who couldn't
go to Kashi were targeted by them.
We understood their game plan.
To win the confidence of the villagers..
..we pretended to offer prayers
before taking the dead body.
We would tie a talisman
of Goddess Durga on the bodies.
People's faith in us started growing.
We became popular in
the other villages and states.
The number of dead
bodies we got increased.
Cremation must take
place within a day or two..
..or the soul will always
keep wandering on the earth.
It'll never get peace.
The people were told that the
dead bodies would be taken to Kashi.
But, after taking money
from them the dead bodies were..
..thrown out of train compartments.
Nobody found out about
our work in the last three years.
Last month I fell sick and
I was hospitalized for two weeks.
The dead bodies we had were
decomposing in the warehouse.
We got a call saying that
they couldn't wait anymore.
But, I couldn't go from the hospital.
I sent somebody else in my place.
The person I sent didn't come back.
I got another call and they
told me to stop the work for some days.
That's not all.
They sent me three phone numbers.
They gave me the photo
of a missing girl and told me..
..to cook up a story and tell you.
Believe me, this is the truth.
What's the name of
the person who called you?
I don't know.
Why were the bodies
shifted to another van?
I don't know.
You don't know who
are the people involved.
I always got calls from landline numbers.
Who are the people involved?
What do they do?
How many people are involved?
I don't know anything.
I also don't know what they
do with the dead bodies inside the van.
I'm speaking the truth.
Let's go.
You carry on, I'll join you.
You'll see an old building.
That's the warehouse.
Okay, I got it.
- Come fast.
We are here.
Hey! Didn't your relatives
and neighbours ask you questions..
..when you took so many dead bodies?
If anybody asked questions we
would make up false stories and tell them.
For example it's important
to cremate the dead bodies or..
..the soul won't rest in peace.
It'll be ominous for
the family and village.
So, it was necessary
to cremate the bodies quickly.
We also made up a story that if
a body is cremated early in the morning..
..the soul goes straight to heaven.
It'll break the cycle of life and
death and the soul will attain salvation.
So, we couldn't wait for any relative.
But, this..
Uncle..
Yes, tell me Sheenu.
Why did you cremate
mom's body before I arrived?
I told you about the ominous time..
Uncle, speak the truth.
They were telling that we
should take your mother to Kashi.
When I was in school I
wrote a letter to mom saying..
..that I felt scared
to stay alone in the hostel.
She came to me in a couple
of days after getting the letter.
I've only one memory with my mom.
My father died when I was a child.
My mom was my family.
And one day even my mom left me alone.
She was not at home.
I was confused.
I couldn't even see my mom the last time.
I wasn't with her when she needed me.
This thought hurts me every day.
My mom did so much for me.
I couldn't even perform her last rites.
I'm so helpless.
What kind of son am I?
I thought she would never die.
And I couldn't see her the last time.
When somebody dies we
perform their last rites..
..to show respect to their life.
I couldn't even do that for my mother.
She was thrown out of a train
compartment the way garbage is disposed.
My mom was thrown out.
It's not only me.
There are many people like me.
Somebody mom,
somebody's dad, somebody's sister..
Many people couldn't see their
near and dear ones the last time..
..only because of these people.
Gopalam doesn't know who his boss is.
How will we find out?
Pass it to me.
Sir, I want to talk to your friend.
Hello.
- Hello, Aditya.
Atreya wants to talk to you.
Sir..
- Yes, tell me.
When did the murder in Gujarat take place?
Hold on.
Five days back.
When did the man whose body
was found in Venkatachalam die?
Ten days back.
Thank you, sir.
How can the man who died ten
days ago kill anybody five days back?
If you take out organs from
a body it'll be easily noticed.
But you can steal something
from a body without getting caught.
Our fingerprints.
These people need the fingerprints
and not the dead bodies.
What will they do with these fingerprints?
These fingerprints can
be planted in any crime scene.
They can turn the investigation
in another direction.
They can make a database of fake
fingerprints and sell it to the criminals.
The same has happened
in the Venkatachalam case.
The fingerprint of this
dead body has been planted..
..in a crime that happened in Gujarat.
They investigate the case
assuming that the person..
..whose finger print has
been found is the criminal.
But, they never find out whose
finger prints they actually are.
Even if they trace the
person he'll be found dead.
It means, the case will be
shut assuming the criminal to be dead.
It's a dangerous plan to
mislead a crime investigation.
This is not all that happens in this plan.
New voters can be registered
on the basis of the fake finger prints..
..and elections can be rigged.
The fake finger prints help
the terrorists to get fake passports.
They can easily enter
any country and attack.
They only need finger prints.
If they need finger prints then
they can take it from any dead body.
It's not easy to get the
finger print of a dead body, Bobby.
After we die the blood and
oxygen supply in our body stops.
It's difficult to get the
fingerprints when this stops.
As Gopalam said they took
their finger prints in the van.
I'm sure there's a
lab set-up inside the van.
They take the finger prints
with the help of chemicals.
This work takes 6-7 hours.
This entire racket is
being conducted for this.
After taking their finger prints
the bodies are stored in warehouses.
After that they are carried to
the trains from where they're disposed.
Do you know why?
That's because it's a rule
in the railway department that..
..an unidentified body should
be cremated within 3-4 days.
They're aware of this loophole.
And this is how they're
conducting this racket.
Gopalam said that they
were going to stop this business.
If anybody wants to shut
this systematic business then..
..it's evident that they were
aware that they would be exposed.
And a person who's
afraid commits a mistake.
Sneha..
- Agent.
Where's the photos clicked by
Ajay and the file of unidentified bodies?
In the office.
Sir.. sir, Bobby and I'll
go to office to study the photos.
Okay.
- I've request.
Will you speak with Narayan
and get the objects that were..
..found with the dead
body at Venkatachalam?
Sure.
- We're missing some clues.
We need to study the case again.
One more thing.
Can you go to Ajay and Harsha's college?
College?
- Yes.
But why?
Any information about
them will be important for us.
Okay.
Sir, these were the objects
found with the dead body..
..near the Venkatachalam bridge.
Sir, any problem?
- No problem.
Give the envelope of the constable.
We want to meet the principal.
The last room in the ground floor.
- Okay.
Haven't you made it yet?
- Almost done.
How long will you take?
- Just a couple of minutes.
Sir, Atreya's bail has been
cancelled and an arrest warrant..
..has been issued.
Narayan..
- Sir.
..start the car.
- Okay, sir.
Ajay took these photos
of dead bodies in Ongole.
This was on the body of Venkatachalam.
How come both the bodies
have the same talisman?
This is the talisman of a Devi.
The people of the Vellore
district in Tamil Nadu..
..are her devotees.
The talisman of a Devi?
Do you remember what Gopalam said?
They would perform fake prayers
and tie fake talisman on the bodies.
They would take out the talisman
before throwing out the bodies.
Gopalam didn't go to work that day.
The person who replaced Gopalam
may not be aware about the talisman.
That's the reason why these
two bodies still have talisman on them.
These people came
looking for the talisman.
They throw the bodies anywhere randomly.
Before they found the bodies..
..Ajay and Harsha found the bodies in
Ongole and I spotted one at Venkatachalam.
They must've spotted
us with the dead bodies.
What's wrong if the talisman is found?
I need the details of your ex-students
Ajay and Harsha regarding a case.
Their classmate works
a lecturer in our college.
I think she can help you.
Raghu, take them to her.
Go to Atreya's office.
Why are they worried about this talisman?
There's some connection between
these people and this talisman.
What's the connection?
What do we know about these people?
They fool people by promising
to cremate dead bodies in Varanasi.
They are also involved
in another serious crime with it.
They're misusing the name of God.
Sai Baba industries,
Balaji textile and what not.
What if they run their business
in the name of the goddess?
This maybe the logo of their company.
Do something.
Find the businesses run in the
locality in the name of the goddess.
Make the list of small shops
and businesses. Do it quickly.
Something must be common between them.
For instance friends or enemies.
Were they involved in
any mishap that you remember?
Nothing like that.
They worked together
on the final year project.
What was that project about?
Can I check that record?
Here it is.
Was it on religious crimes in India?
- Yes.
They wrote their paper on how criminals
fool people in the name of religion.
They worked on this
topic for almost six months.
Vasudha?
Vasudha was their friend.
Three of them worked on this project.
It means all three of them were friends.
It means all three of
them knew about this crime.
That's why all three of them were killed.
You'll get more details in this file.
Ma'am, can I take these
photos and project materials?
Here it is.
Is this a goddess?
- Yes.
Bethaballi Amman milk dairy.
Bethaballi Amman textiles.
Bethaballi Amman NGO.
Did you get any information from college?
- Yes, agent.
Ajay, Harsha and Vasudha were
classmates and very good friends.
What?
- Yes.
This college project is
common between the three of them.
Religious crimes in India.
Here are few photos.
Since they worked on
religious crimes in India..
..I'm sure they knew about this crime.
So, they were killed.
Business of dead bodies.
They're very smart.
The bodies are already dead.
No complaint, no risk.
What did you say?
The relatives think that
the bodies have been taken to Kashi.
Then who'll file a complaint?
No missing complaint
was made about the bodies..
..found near railway tracks. Right?
Except one body.
Whose body, agent?
The body found at Kawali.
The father registered a missing complaint.
Red dress.
Tattoo of the mother on the girl's hand.
Tell me something, sir.
The tattoo she made when she was a child..
..was also found on her dead body.
Why did it disappear from this photo?
That's because Vasudha is still alive.
The father and the daughter
are the masterminds.
If Vasudha is alive then why
did they pretend that she's dead.
They made me believe that
a girl named Divya was killed.
I was framed for Ajay and Harsha's murder.
If this plan worked then
I would've been sentenced..
..for at least ten years.
But, there were two mistakes in this plan.
The first one was that I found Divya.
Second one is that I've
a CCTV footage of myself..
..of the time when Ajay was killed.
So, I got bail.
It was only Ajay and Harsha before.
But now Atreya is also dangerous for us.
If the three of them ever
meet then the information..
..Atreya has will go to Ajay and Harsha.
If they investigate then they'll
find the secret behind the talisman.
If they find the talisman they'll find us.
Where's Gopalam?
Tell him to get a photo of a missing girl.
Tell him to give her the name
Divya and tell Atreya the story I said.
Along with Ajay and Harsha's
number give him one of my numbers..
..which doesn't have a photo record.
Didn't you get a photo with this number?
The photo of the third person
isn't available in the database.
Atreya will find every
detail of the three numbers.
He'll definitely try
to find all three of us.
When he'll fail to get
any information about me.
He'll concentrate on Ajay and Harsha.
We'll kill Ajay and Harsha after that.
We'll keep creating
evidence against Atreya.
Atreya will be arrested
for killing Ajay and Harsha.
Their plan failed because I got bail.
If I went to Ajay and Harsha's
college to investigate their murder..
..then I would've found out
that Vasudha was their classmate.
They made another plan to
divert my attention from Vasudha.
They assured me that Vasudha is dead.
They went to the police station.
The father registered a
police complaint stating that..
..his daughter's life was in danger.
Then he came and filed
his daughter's missing complaint.
All of us were trying to save Vasudha.
When her dad showed us a dead
body we believed that Vasudha was dead.
The drama would've ended with
the news of three criminology students..
..being killed while
investigating a religious crime.
How did Atreya doubt Gopalam?
I'm sure we made some mistake.
He'll hardly take a couple
of days to expose our business.
I thought that the matter would
be sorted by getting him arrested.
But the CCTV footage helped him get bail.
Kill him before he goes to jail again.
Hassan is a detective from Karnataka.
Set him after Atreya.
Do the same things
we did for Ajay and Harsha.
The police should find
drug packets in their houses.
This should look like
the work of a drug mafia.
Let's file a fake police
complaint stating that..
..we're getting death threats.
After that we'll fake my death.
I'll provide a number which
doesn't have a photo record.
When Atreya will find out
about my death he'll think that..
..the people who killed
Ajay and Harsha have killed me.
Even if he goes to college
to get our detail, we'll be safe.
Three criminology graduates,
experts of religious crimes.
Ones who knew a lot about crimes.
Ajay and Harsha used their
knowledge for a good purpose.
But, this girl used it for evil purpose.
We're safe this time.
But, we can't take this risk again.
If we bury the dead bodies
they'll get exposed at some time.
Let's take advantage of the
loophole in railway department.
If they find a dead
body they wait for 72 hours.
If nobody claims the body they cremate it.
Call me if you face any problem.
People who fool others
and rob them follow a technique.
They give a lot of donations
to create a good image in the society.
It maybe distributing food,
opening a hospital, blood donation camps.
Anything they can do to
win the confidence of people.
All the details are mentioned
in this religious crime project.
They're also using a
technique to hide their crime.
The technique is Bethaballi Amman NGO.
Bobby, go in that direction.
Bobby.
Sneha.
- There's nobody here, agent.
She escaped from here
after we caught Gopalam.
We are late.
She has escaped.
Let's go to Rajasthan.
Why will we go to Rajasthan?
- To catch Vasudha.
But, what's there in Rajasthan?
Do I need to explain everything?
You've followed all
my instructions properly.
I think we're safe now.
Everything is going on well till now.
What next?
I'll tell you what the next plan will be.
Look at the beer bottles.
Somebody drank it half
and left it just like that.
That's because they left in a hurry.
The land is wet which
means it rained in the morning.
They tried to burn the evidence
but the fire is still burning.
The fire was lit after the rain stopped.
It's been only a couple of hours.
Look at the footprints.
Three people have left the NGO.
But, there are no tire marks.
It means they didn't take the road.
There's only one option
to escape from here quickly.
It's the railway station.
It's very clear from this place
that they were here an hour ago.
Only one train has left
the station within an hour.
A train to Bikaner, Rajasthan.
Last week you booked your
mom's ticket to Rajasthan.
Yes, agent.
We're going to Karnimata
festival by this train next week.
Exactly! People believe that
the goddess comes in the form of a rat..
..during this festival.
People who believe this will go
there from different parts of the world.
These people are easy targets
for people like Vasudha.
I've solved the case.
I'll take a selfie now.
Hey! Hey!
What's wrong, auntie? C'mon smile.
It seems that somebody has died.
But, you're happy when anybody dies..
..because you get a new
finger print that you can sell.
Mentally retarded criminal.
Uncle, come and click a photo with me.
Why are you feeling shy?
Come on.
Vasudha, my daughter is dead.
They killed my daughter.
Petty actor.
A father slaps his children
to teach them something good.
Instead of that you've brought
your daughter to Rajasthan..
..to start a new business.
I'll thrash you badly.
Both the father and daughter are mad.
Come on.
The goddess will come in the
form of a rat when you're in jail.
You'll get white rat,
black rat, all varieties of rat.
You can behold them.
Agent.
- Yes. Come and join us.
Don't feel shy.
Let's go.
Thank you.
- No problem, sir.
What's going on, sir?
Okay, agent. I'll leave now.
My train will leave in a couple of hours.
If you need any help think of me.
Hassan, Karnataka.
My headquarters are located there.
Ask about the famous detective
and they'll guide you to me.
Okay, bye.
- Okay.
Hold on.
It was a pleasure working with you,
Agent Bobby.
Like my page on social media.
Bye.
- Bye.
Sir, you've contacts in Rajasthan?
The department has contacts everywhere.
You know that your mother
wasn't cremated here.
Then why do you always come here?
Only agent Atreya knows
that Mahalakshmi is not here.
But, Mahalakshmi's
son Seenu doesn't know it.
How did they manage to fool
so many people and run their business?
People believe anything
if you tie a talisman on them.
We think that black cat is a bad omen.
Some people believe that human sacrifice..
..can help you get treasure
or avoid ghosts and spirits.
Everybody wants their well-being.
They don't want anything
bad in their life.
This fear forces humans
to believe in anything.
They were not fooling people.
They were betraying their belief.
I was watching 'Bahubali
2' on Goldmine last night.
Do you know that I solved why
Katappa killed Bahubali long back?
I knew the answer well before
Rajamouli sir wrote the script.
Why did Katappa kill Bahubali?
Haven't you watched Bahubali?
- No.
Why did Katappa kill Bahubali?
The victim fell down
from the building last night.
People think that he jumped
early in the morning at 4 am.
We need to find out if it's
a suicide or murder. Let's go.
We got no clue.
Then what did you get?
- Murder weapon.
FBI.
- FBI?
Isn't FBI in America?
Fatima Bureau of Investigation.
Fatima was my first girlfriend.
Our head office is
near the vegetable market.
We give discount to the police department.
Please. Take my card.
Do visit me.
The case has been solved.
Take back the empty box.
Case solved.
Sir, did it hurt?
Actually Katappa killed Bahubali because..