Friends, today we have brought for you an
exclusive unboxing of iQOO Neo 9
which can be called
iQOO Neo 9 Pro in India
which will have Snapdragon 8 Gen 2
In China, there were two variants,
Neo 9 and Neo 9 Pro
The Pro variant of China
had Dimensity 9300
But the Neo 9 of China
is Snapdragon 8 Gen 2
So the Neo 9 Pro in India will be
with Snapdragon 8 Gen 2
Big confusion
Now friends, the interesting thing is that you get
Android 14 Origin OS with Snapdragon 8 Gen 2
and we hope that iQOO
brings Origin OS in India
because we have tested it
and matched it with Funtouch OS
and what difference we have seen,
you will see everything in this video
Now the box is like this, the box of the Indian variant can be completely different
In the box, you get a bag case, 120W
adapter, Type C cable, everything
Now we will keep this box at the back
Now let's talk about the
design and build of the phone
So here you get 8.34mm
thickness and 190 grams
So the weight and thickness
of this phone is quite acceptable
and in boxy style, you will
get to see it in a square shape
You get to see rounded edges here
and at the back, you get this dual
texture design and leather bag
You will get the feel of leather here
and I got to know that the
other colors don't have leather
Rest, the design is completely
different and the phone looks great
It feels good that iQOO gives some different combinations when it comes to leather
Rest, you get to see the frames in plastic
Below, you can put dual nano sims
You get a mic hole, Type
C port, one speaker below
and one speaker above at earpiece
So dual stereo speakers
are provided here
Rest, you get a mic hole
and IR blaster above
On the right, you get a power button,
volume up and down key
and under display
fingerprint scanner
Now the unlock system of
the origin OS was very fast
As soon as we unlock it,
it opens up quickly
and the animation
was also very different
When we compared it
with the funtouch OS
So we saw a lot of difference in its
animation and its animation
and this unlock was very fast
Its haptics are very different,
it has an X-axis linear motor
Multitasking is very
good at different places
The fun was very different there
I forgot to say one thing,
you also get IP54 ratings
For performance,
it has Snapdragon 8 Gen 2
and I liked this thing that iQOO decided to put two variants
in China, one with MediaTek and othere is with Snapdragon
but they have decided to put only
Snapdragon variant in India
They know that the audience of
Snapdragon is more
They did the same in
iQOO Neo 7 Pro
They gave Snapdragon 8 Plus Gen 1
iQOO Neo 9 Pro is coming
with Snapdragon 8 Gen 2
I liked this thing very much
This is officially confirmed
The performance is top notch
This is the flagship chipset of 2023
Now it has come to the
upper mid-range category
The Antutu scores were amazing,
around 1.6 million
The CPU throttling was very good,
79%, being a Chinese variant
Still it was seated at 44 degrees Celsius
But I am sure that when it comes to India
so we will not see such high
thermals in the Indian variant
LPDDR5X, UFS4 is also a big upgrade
and the app open-close, multitasking
It is smooth as it has Origin OS
We noticed that we have
iQOO 12 with Funtouch OS 14
It has Funtouch
OS 14 and Android 14
Both have Android 14
Let me show you the difference between Origin OS and Funtouch OS 14
All the apps are closed here
We have only Call of Duty here
If I give you a comparison of both the
animations and speed
It is very close
don't forget that we have
Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 in iQOO 12
even after that, it is almost close
In fact, if I open the gallery
app, it is very close
But we noticed one thing
If I close all the apps in it
And when I bring Funtouch OS 13
There is a difference
If I open this, now we will see
Now we will know how fast Origin OS is
You will see the loading
speed in front of you
So I have seen the difference
here in Origin OS
There are many other things that
we will talk about software in this
But overall experience is amazing
You can play gaming on high graphics
And there is 4D Vibration,
so when I was playing the game
the haptics that I was getting here
It was amazing
They have done this very well
And they have given
dedicated Q1 chip
Which works in both
performance and display
Let's talk about the display
You get 6.7 inch with 1.5k resolution
In an LTPO AMOLED display
It gives you a 144 Hz high refresh rate
In fact, its smoothness was better
Because this is Origin OS
You can't judge this because
it is Chinese varient
Who knows they might
bring Origin OS in India
And optimize it separately
But I am not sure that it
will come with Origin OS
But it is good if it comes
But its smoothness when we compared
it with Funtouch OS 13
It was very fast
You get 3000 nits peak brightness
Outdoor visibility was very good
View angles were also very good
Its panel is used very well
punch hole is in centre,
you get very less chin
And it is a flat display,
not a curved display
And as I told you,
Q1 in display is also given
which is the extra chip
Frame rate interpolation,
you got that everything here
Overall, display panel
is used very well
For software, it has Android 14
And it is based on Origin OS
Which is for China
I recommend it for India as well
I have told you in two things
that how fast it is in
multitasking and swipes
Apart from that, its dialer is different
If we compare it with Funtouch OS
Notification panel is
completely different
When we matched it
Smoothness overall has improved
Animation has also improved
If you look at the
notification panel carefully
You get to see it transparent
App opens speed is fast
Game loading speed is fast
Text has been highlighted
Animation pattern lock is also different
In fact, when you unlock the phone
It is also different
Here I am noticing that there is a lot of difference
Between Funtouch and Origin
This is my experience
We recommend to iQOO,
that they should bring it
And you also go and tell iQOO
That bring Origin OS
It will be fun
Camera is impressive
You have 50MP primary sensor
IMX 920 is given
It is very good
It comes with OIS
and max you can shoot
8k video at 30fps
It also has an ultra wide sensor
But they have done a good job
that no 2MP game is played,
apart from that
Slow motion is at FHD 240 fps
You can shoot
good slow motion videos
Night mode features
Portrait features, everything is here
and 20x zoom in photo given
10x zoom in video
as for selfie, you get 16MP selfie
FHD 30fps, I don't like it
they still stuck at FHD
4K should be in selfie
well it is Chinese
variant so can't be judged
still i am showing you some photos
it is good photo, portrait is good
Dynamic range is good, rear and selfie
both are good there is no problem
video Stabilization is good
You can see in rear selfie
I have left the link on google drive
Indian variant has different optimization
then we can judge in detail
Battery is 5160 mAh
Capacity is a bit high
They have maintained the phone well
It is slim
120W adapter is given in the box
You can charge it in 25 minutes
We tested battery drain
We left 8K video recording for 1.5 hours
at 100% at the morning 8 am
when we checked it
at 10 am, it was 72%
It is quite impressive
because 8K video takes a lot of resources
Even hotspot takes a lot of resources
You should test more in these 2 things
Overall battery results were good
But I won't come to conclusion,
because it is Chinese varient
You will get 5G connectivity
in India, you will get multiple 5G bands
But you get WiFi 7
It is quite impressive
Bluetooth version 5.3
and NFC is also given
It will definitely retain in India
You get support of all sensors
Let's talk about prices
It is quite aggressive
You won't believe
It is launched in China under 30K
It starts around 26K
and with 12GB RAM and 256GB storage
It has Snapdragon 8Gen2
It has many other features also
It has higher variants like
16-256, 16-512, 16-1TB
But pricing is quite aggressive
I can guess that maybe it
will be around 35K in India
I have expectations from iQOO
Because they have aggressive pricing
I think iQOO Neo 9 Pro will
come around that price
I am just speculating
I don't have any confirmation
You comment below and tell us
what its price should be.
Overall phone is good
It is Chinese variant
but i am waiting for Indian variant
You should also wait for our Indian
variant varient unboxing
Because there is a big difference,
between Chinese and Indian varient
till then, subscribe if you
want exclusive videos
Press the button to get colorful,
yes now it's colour change
Press the notification bell icon
Like, support and always keep smiling