- "Slab City" is a community
located in the middle of the desert.
It has no electricity, no running water,
and no law enforcement.
Out of curiosity,
me and the boys decided to
spend 24 hours in the slabs.
So we're getting close to Slab City,
and as you see, there's roads and stuff.
And then once we take
this turn, it's nothing.
No buildings, no nothing.
So we're on the outskirts of Slab City.
This right here is "Salvation Mountain."
It's a tourist attraction,
and they recommend you don't
go any further that way.
It says "keep out," Chandler.
It says...
Ah, I guess there's no laws.
So we're at the top of Candy Mountain,
and Slab City is that
way a little bit more.
And yeah, guys.
So we discovered this cave
and it has art on the walls.
- I'm not doing it, I'm not going in.
- Chandler, go in.
Go in! Go!
Chandler!
- This looks like something
out of a horror video game.
- I know.
- A hundred percent.
Ooh, what's in here?
- Dude, I don't want to go in there.
Nope, we're not going in there.
Oh, this is incredible.
Look up, guys. Just look up.
- I have so many questions
about how all this got here,
like, we're literally in
the middle of a desert.
So we're at the info thing for Slab City,
"The Last Free Place on Earth."
Dask Meme. Egor dot.
- E-N-O-D.
- Guys, it's Chris, look.
- Oh, Chris.
- Well, who's FedEx delivering to?
That's what I wanna know.
Uh, I think we should go now, guys.
- Yeah.
- I agree.
- It's kind of creepy.
- Garret.
- Don't.
- Knock.
At least knock.
- I'm not going in there.
Garret, you have fun.
I'm going back to the car.
- What is this?
- It's Winnie the Pooh.
On a grave.
- That was a bad move anyways.
- I don't know where we're going.
- I'm just scared something's
gonna jump out at me
at any second.
- Dude, this is very scary.
- Yeah, let's get outta here.
I'm done.
We're moving on.
- Hey, Garret, look, it's you.
- That's creepy.
- Oh, lit.
You're right.
- Does actually look
like Garret, actually.
- All right. Hey, Tareq.
Fly a drone over that so
we can see what's in it.
- Okay.
- Next, we're going to an art museum
owned by this guy named Wizard,
in the middle of a desert,
with no laws.
- I only have three rules.
One, you don't have to
stay on the carpeting.
Two, everything is touchable.
Three, you touch it and it breaks,
tell 'em it was broke when you got here.
- Bowl in the bowling alley,
all we ask, you put the pins back.
We've been homicide-free for three days.
We're shooting for a week.
All right.
- All right, Chris.
You guys are doing Seesaw?
- Yes, sir.
- This is the seesaw here.
- I don't think I'm tall enough.
- I don't like this.
- He got scared.
- I've been on scary
rides in amusement parks.
- But I've also had straps
on those scary rides, Chris.
- You don't need straps in life, man.
- Don't get down yet, Garret.
- No, I wanna get down.
- No, I go-
- I thought I was gonna die.
Not gonna lie. It was not fun.
I lost my shirt 'cause you
don't need clothes in Slab City.
I'm slab.
Guys, they got memes in here.
- Hypertension, stress, Christmas.
Yes.
Come to the desert.
If you want fire memes.
- It's dangerous.
- First one to use the
bathroom gets 10 grand.
- Hi, he's a good boy.
Ah!
Scaredy-cat .
- It's an elephant.
- It's a cage full of Spider-man.
They're free range.
- They look discolored.
- Have Jimmy walk in
the middle of that room
and we're all gonna hide behind a door.
- I'm in a room full of doors
and they're all hiding
behind a random door.
If I pick the door, they're hiding behind.
They owe me a grand.
I don't know what door I opened.
I'm just gonna close that one.
I guess we'll try this one.
Can I have my thousand dollars.
Hey boys, go down the scary tunnel first,
so I don't die.
Be my shield, Chandler.
- Hey guys, what the heck is-
What are you doing?
- Chandler, you choked so hard.
- It's got a bunch of kazoos in it.
- You won't blow one.
- Please don't, Chris.
- Chris.
- Chris, don't do it.
- This is where the outbreak starts.
- So Chris, what do you
think of this place so far?
- I think I wanna live here.
It's beautiful.
And it's art.
Wait, hold on one more thing.
- They've got a lot of bowling
balls, but not enough water.
- So Garret, what do you
think of this place so far?
- No.
- What do you mean?
- Okay.
Hey, so Chandler, what do you
think of this place so far?
Chandler?
- What?
- So Chris?
- Yeah. What's up, man?
- This seems a little familiar here.
Did this happen before?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
What's happening here.
That was back in the desert, right?
So Chris here used to be a boy scout.
- Yes, sir.
- He used to do this all the time.
- Chris is the only reason
we're gonna survive this challenge.
Chris, can you heat this up for me?
- Yeah. Hold on.
- I'm hungry.
- Hold on.
- Chris, what do these sticks mean?
- Cheese Butt, come here.
- Don't call me Cheese Butt.
I'm not doing anything if
you call me Cheese Butt.
- If he calls you Cheese Butt.
Guys, we don't need Chris.
Let's figure it out.
- Yeah.
All right. You heard it.
- Remember what happened
last time you said that.
- Yeah. He helped us.
- So what's your plan
with this, Garret here?
How are you gonna do this tent?
- Chris?
- What's up?
- There's no I in slab, Chris.
When you guys buy merch, use code "Chris."
- Liked that a lot.
- Yeah.
- Like I said in that one Twitch video,
whenever you check out at shopmrbeast.
If you put in one of their codes
they get a little kickback.
Here, let me help you with that.
- The easiest part.
- Man, I love Chris.
He just does everything.
- I'm just sick of everybody
relying on me for everything.
Ah, don't go in my tent.
- Thank you for letting me stay-
- No, get outta my tent.
Your shoes are on...
Don't put your shoes in my tent.
I either set up your tent or make food.
So which one do you want?
- Can I just give you a
thousand dollars to do both?
- You heard it, folks.
- There we go.
- Tried to kill me.
- It's out of there.
- Yo, Mr Beast!
You rock, brother
- Yeah, I'd rather not be
recognized in Slab City.
I am just a tourist
- Chandler, there's no
McDonald's out here.
- So when are we leaving?
There's no McDonald's out here.
They told me there was restaurants.
They lied to me.
Chris, make the food.
- Might not get any food at all.
- Is there Uber Eats out here?
- Wait. Y'all didn't get me a drink?
- Yeah.
- This happened last time.
Why does this keep happening?
- I think it's at Walmart.
- It's at Walmart?
- So what's going on here?
- Walmart sucks.
- Chris said he was an expert.
He lied.
- Well-
- You just got demerited.
- Oh, okay.
All right. Figure this out then.
- We did. It doesn't work.
- This does not fit in here.
So Walmart lied to us.
- So are we gonna have to
just make our own fire?
- Or we could ask locals for food.
- Yes. We're gonna have
to make our own fire.
- Somebody's job is to get big sticks.
Somebody's job is to get big rocks.
- Me and Chandler will get rocks.
You and Garret get sticks.
- Why'd you guys pick rocks over sticks.
- Sticks are pokey.
- All right. So you're
getting some stickers.
- Yeah. We're getting some sticks.
I'm sick and I have to do everything
and it's not very fire.
- Thank you, Chris.
- Did you just spill all the matches?
- Yeah.
Remember I am sick.
Chandler, can you go away.
You literally have no constructive-
- He told me to come over
here and say dumb things.
You got a couple on the ground.
- I see that, buddy.
- Do we have more food?
- I take it you guys just got here?
- Yeah.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh no. No, I just want
to give you guys a heads up
on good stuff.
Okay. You know about the show tonight?
- No.
- There's a show?
- Every Saturday night at sundown.
Open mic, live music, BYOB.
Anybody's skateboard?
- Did you bring...
- I didn't bring my skateboard.
- You up!
- Anything else?
- That should do it right there.
- That should do it. All right.
Are you gonna be at the open mic tonight?
- I'll be there for a little while.
- Okay. All right.
- I love how you called it open mic.
- Yeah, he does...
- He does open mic comedy.
- You do comedy?
Sign up and you go on stage.
- Oh, nice.
- Dude, that'd be so cool.
- That would be cool if you did comedy.
We would like record you.
- Go back to your own country,
you son of a .
- I heard that one before.
This guy's tearing up our basketball goal.
- You're gonna die.
- So far a lot of the people
have actually been really nice to us.
- You're gonna die.
- I guess that guy was just on something
and he just didn't know what was going on.
- Chandler, you ate all the weenies.
- I did not.
- Dude, no,
I saw you eat them all.
- Let's play basketball right now.
- I'm not gonna play basketball
'cause I don't like sports.
Give me that, boy.
- Oh!
- Ooh!
- Hey, I'm cooking some eggs.
- So what kind of eggs are these here?
- Cheesy, scrambled.
- Yes sir.
- That looks delicious.
Can I go tell the boys the food is ready?
- Yeah. Weren't they having a
fight about food or something?
- Yeah, I think that's the reason
why they're playing.
- Oh.
- So are we all dressed up
and ready to go to the party?
- We are.
And we were just thinking
that going to this party
is the weirdest thing we've ever done.
- Except for the time
we all sat in a circle.
- Or the time we were in straight-jackets
in the insane asylum.
- What about the time we
counted to a hundred thousand?
Oh, that was just me.
- I went to Ohio.
- That's pretty crazy.
- That old man with the
beard came over here
and told us there's a party.
- Wait, the old man
told us about the party.
- Yeah.
- Oh, great.
- It's my kind of party.
- We scoped it out with the drone.
It looks pretty good.
- It was lit up.
- Yeah.
- And there was empty seats.
Apparently it was a
show or like a open mic.
- And there was lights.
So yeah, we're going.
- That's all it takes.
Lights?
- We like lights.
♪ Baby, I can't sleep. ♪
- I just signed up for the open mic here
and I'm gonna try to do
some stand up comedy.
If I'm doing bad, just get the car ready.
- I was actually born in Saudi Arabia.
Do you guys know where that is?
- Yeah.
First memory was that all the
women there dressed the same.
They covered everything except their eyes.
My second memory was
that I kept losing my mom
in retail stores.
- Thank you guys so much.
Thank you for letting me doing this.
I appreciate it.
- To be honest, I was not expecting this.
There's kinda like a community
and everyone here just seems super chill.
- They were playing a lot of music
that I really enjoy and love.
I had no clue that something like this
was gonna be just randomly
in the middle of the desert.
- For a place with no laws,
this is actually pretty chill.
And it's kinda like a community,
everyone's getting along.
I'm just kind of surprised
in the middle of the desert you have this.
- There's a lot of different
people out here, you know?
- This is awesome.
I honestly didn't expect this.
I didn't wanna come
here in the first place,
but this, crazy.
- You wanna go dance, I'll donate.
- I can't.
- Let's go do it.
♪ Out in stormy weather. ♪
- All right, boys.
I'm staying here.
I'm gonna live here.
- No
- Garret, you wouldn't
last five seconds out here.
- Whoa.
- We've been out here for 24 hours, dude.
- Yeah, you wouldn't last
five more seconds out here.
- Yeah, you're right.
- All right.
- Oh, I was right.
- Garret's gone.
- What if three-knife guy comes back?
- What if you literally just popped up
right behind you and
grabbed you by the throat?
- I mean it's my time to go
and get stabbed with three rusty knife.
- I'm sorry, dude.
If you're listening, we don't mean this.
- I thought you said
you wanted to live here, man.
- Yeah. I talked to some of the locals.
They denounced three-knife men.
- They don't like him.
- No, they don't like him.
- Chris wanted to go up on
stage and dance with somebody.
- I didn't wanna go on stage, you liar.
- But he can't dance so he chickened out,
and now we're making fun of him for it.
- Wow. Great play-by-play.
Who are you? Joe Madden.
- Oh my goodness.
Chandler, you might as well just walk
into the abyss after that one.
- All right. See you guys.
I'm outta here.
- So the boys don't
understand how this works.
You can't just approach to Slab City
and just be like, "Yo, dance with me."
They have to accept you.
And so he was-
- You can't dance.
- You don't know if he was
vibing with me or not, man.
- You just can't dance.
- You can't dance.
- Oh God, no.
- Stop it, man.
Honestly don't care if
Chris can or can't dance
but I just like making fun of him.
So it's really funny that he didn't dance.
- I'm gonna be honest.
Chris is starting to get arrogant,
'cause he built the tents.
It happens every time.
I was told to talk about
how Chris didn't dance.
Haha, Chris
- He won't do it 'cause
he can't dance either.
- Yeah, I know.
That's literally what I was thinking.
Why would I make fun of
him when I can't dance?
So I'm in the tent and I'm not gonna lie.
I feel exhausted.
It's been a pretty fun day.
I'm gonna go to bed soon.
- All right, guys, it's been a long day.
I'm pretty tired.
Okay. God is telling me to go to sleep.
- It was a crazy experience,
but it's time for bed.
So peace out.
- I think I'm gonna hit the hay.
I'm not gonna lie,
I'm not feeling too well.
I'm gonna go ahead and go to bed.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I am not feeling too good.
I'm really sick.
I think I need to go to like
the doctor or something.
You guys look cute
spooning together though.
- Scoot off.
- Seriously. I'm feeling really bad.
I think I might have a fever.
- What happened?
- We'll get you some meds
and we'll get you to-
Chris is apparently sick, even worse now.
So we gotta go take him to the doctor.
- Yeah. I get kidney stones really bad.
I've had three within like the last year.
Shout out to kidney stones, I guess
- We picked up the campsite.
We're gonna skirt-skirt out.
Take care of Chris.
So apparently, Chandler,
the only thing dangerous about Slab City
is Chris's kidney stones
- And three-knife man
- And three-knife man.
♪ MrBeast 6,000 ♪
♪ MrBeast 6,000, yeah you know his name ♪
♪ He changed it once or twice ♪
♪ But I think it's here to stay ♪