- Today, we will be testing
the world's greatest experiments,
like lava versus ice.
What?
Safe versus lava.
The safe is on fire.
Clock versus rock.
Kite versus Maverick.
Be a Maverick.
Lava versus ice cream.
All right, I'm about to be a Maverick
and move some molting hot lava.
This could end really bad.
- All right. Come straight this way.
Now come on.
- Boom.
- Oh my God.
- I just move
molting hot lava.
- Be careful, that's
- Now we're gonna pour
this lava that I move.
- Oh, that was really cool.
- Wow. Wow.
See that?
- Oh.
Why is the ice cream on fire?
- Lava versus Legos.
We're gonna see if this
impenetrable fortress.
can withstand lava.
- Ah, that's hot.
- Will Smith would approve.
- Ah.
- Know what else is hot?
- What?
- Parent merch.
- Loganpaul.com/shop
Ouch.
- Oh, wow. That was hot.
- Oh, dude.
- Oh, our fortress. No.
- Oh my God. That's hot.
- Oh, my goodness. Fire stays right there.
- And she's on fire.
- Trumpet versus chili.
Play me a song.
No. I need something more chill.
My Maverick hoodie enjoyed.
- Doctor versus apples.
All right. Well, a hundred
apples keep the doctor away.
- Oh, wait, hold on.
Just for good measures.
Hit.
- Ah.
- UMG versus me.
- Hey, did you get the
horses for that video?
- Yeah, the horses are in the .
Yo, do you remember? .
You've been staring at
the sun for a while.
You must have the eye of the .
- Chris versus mirror.
- Ah, beautiful.
Now I can look at myself all day.
I guess I'm ugly.
- Lava versus microwave.
The hot pocket's cold. It needs some heat.
Think we might have
overcooked the hot pocket.
- Oh, it should be fine.
- My hot pocket.
- Lava versus phone.
Cool. Cool.
Don't call this phone again.
Burn it.
- Oh, fuck .
Table.
- Now we don't have to
worry about the FBI.
We're good.
- Oh, man. We lost him.
- Miracle whip versus miracle whip.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
- Trust me. I'm a doctor.
How are you feeling?
- It still doesn't work.
- All right. Well, let me try my miracle
whip.
- Oh, wow. It works.
But now I have cancer.
- Those are the side effects.
- Chandler versus poop.
The toilet's clogged.
I need a plunger.
The plunger is gone.
- Lava versus steak.
How would you like your steak done?
- Well done.
- Like, well, well-done?
- Yeah, pretty well-done.
- Bring the lava.
- Lava?
- Here you go, Chan-chan.
- Lava versus toilet.
So what's gonna happen to the toilet?
- Right through it.
- Old man, standing outside our store
versus Chandler.
- Is that your wife?
- Can a stop sign stop lava?
- He's pouring it.
- I told it was gonna happen.
- It's a is out of
there. Get back in there.
- That's hot.
- That's too hot.
- All right. So, if you're
ever driving down the road,
you see lava, grab a stop
sign, use it as a shield.
You're welcome.
- Wow. That's real smart.
- Baseball bat versus coconut.
Are you okay?
- I did not expect it.
- Coconut shards in my neck
- Can you confirm,
let's not use coconuts.
- Oh. Oh my God.
Why? I'm a Maverick, we do it different.
- Okay.
- Safe versus lava.
A Maverick would get the code right.
- You know what a Maverick will do though?
- What?
- Use lava.
- The safe is on fire.
- I don't think...
what was in the safe?
- More Maverick merch.
- Donuts.
Oh, this isn't a skit. I'm just hungry.
- Charger versus lava.
So in case in Enemy Nation dropped an EMP
and there's no electricity.
I wanna see if I can
charge my phone using lava.
Am I gonna get electrocute?
- No. You're good. You're good.
- There's literally no...
- That's what I'm saying.
- All right. Now, plug it in.
- All right. So look at this.
This phone is not charging.
Let's see if it charges.
- Whoa.
- It didn't work. Not charging.
Whoa. Don't do that.
- Explorers versus Dora.
- That was a great expedition boys.
- Yeah. We're explorers now.
- Yeah.
- Did you just say explorers?
- Soy, Dora. Which one of
you is the main explorer?
- That'd be me.
I'm a Maverick. Get off of me.
- Lava versus glass.
Now we're gonna try to
pour some shots of lava.
Oh, God. That's so hot.
I got you. Chandler, I will protect you.
- Oh, fuck. That was cute.
- Yeah.
Can I down my shot?
- The glass kind of cracked.
- Chandler versus challenges.
Last person to speak wins
$50,000. Starting now.
- What? What'd he say?
- Lava versus candle.
Do you have a lighter Jake?
- I do not, man.
- Do you have a lighter?
- No.
- Do you?
- Nah.
Just give it to me.
- Okay.
- Chris, do your thing.
Oh.
- Where y'all going?
- Away.
- Guys, now we have a nice, fresh scent.
- PS4 versus Xbox One.
So being a Maverick
and doing it different,
and my car battery died.
So I'm gonna keep
innovating like a Maverick
and charge my car battery with a console.
- Come on. It's not rocket size.
- All right, Jake. Is it starting?
- No.
- Okay.
All right. Let's see if
a PlayStation 4 work.
Is it starting?
- Hey.
- Oh, it works.
They don't call PlayStation,
the console of the Maverick for nothing.
- Lava versus ice.
- Chris it's just, hold it.
Yeah.
It's starting to get
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, my goodness.
- What? Whoa.
Take it.
- All right.
- Idiots versus safe.
Pour the lava right here.
- Oh, it's moving.
- What?
- Uh-oh.
- I got nothing else, chief.
I'm out of lava.
- Attempt number one. Didn't quite work.
My wallet still stuck.
We're going for round two.
- We're gonna try the lock this...
Oh.
And who would've thought the
exact same thing happened.
- I guess you're not getting
through your wallet, man.
- But how, I have a credit
card that lets me spend
as much money as I want.
I need it.
- What?
- It's still locked. I
still can't pay you guys.
Give it to-
- Oh.
- Oh, that's empty.
- Where is the money you are promising?
That's my wallet.
So, guys now here. Look, gather around.
- Mm-hmm. Uh-huh.
- Chad, get him, get him, get him.
♪ Mr.beast six thousand, oh ♪
♪ Mr.beast six thousand,
yeah, you know his name ♪
♪ He changed it once or twice,
but I think it's here to stay ♪
- If you ever wanna melt something
and you need to get it really
hot or you wanna do casting,
like our logo right here,
we put up on our wall,
go to PMCsupplies.
They helped us out. They
got a ton of cool stuff.
And without them, this video
wouldn't have been possible.