[Music]
[Applause]
steady got it good
oh my goodness look at this the entire
tech mafia meetup who do we have here
it's big dom
there he is we got john or two you're
not so average consumer oh gosh
sensitive the only mr line is tech tips
oh my
could be worse we got mr austin evans i
don't really know what to say about
austin linus why don't you say something
about austin hey guys
no no we got mr who's the boss over here
what do you got you got something to
drink or something going on there well
done over here we have marquez here's
the reason here's what we're doing today
we're going to find out once and for all
which smartphone is in the pocket of
each of these very important individuals
so we're going to start with dom which
smartphone is in your pocket right now
do i reveal it right now or got the
iphone 10. oh there it is there it is
sometimes it's hard to break away from
that ecosystem what is it about this
ecosystem you're talking about more
specifically just imessage i guess i've
heard this argument i truly don't
understand it what is it is it is this a
green bubble a green bubble blue bubble
type of prejudice going on here it's a
green bubble blue bubble war what do you
think about face id though it works for
me though it's really iffy with
sunglasses sometimes right there's no
reamer rising or reason to rhyme for it
it's just no reamer rising rising
reasoning
right right i hear austin just cracking
up everyone over there is giggling and
covering their mouths
what happened what's going on no for
sake hey let's give a lap to austin
because obviously he wants the attention
here
i was about to do a hilarious joke about
how i love rechargeable batteries it's
not really funny all right iphone 10 why
why is that your choice i love the
hardware on this phone the speakers are
great the camera's great i legitimately
really do enjoy face id this is like the
best hardware i've ever tried on a
smartphone like i love the pixel 2
but i'm excited okay hey man this is
your moment like i'm not going to
interrupt you you make your case right
that doesn't bother me there's so little
that i don't like about this phone do
you consider yourself to just be an ios
guy like it's going to be hard to break
away from that's not it so what was the
last android device you used extensively
that was
it's like my main phone yeah
okay so that's your there's your answer
there's your answer all right moving on
who wants to be next thrown in the fire
into the flames of the tech world it's
linus tech tips hi how many videos did
you make a ces 45 45 videos round of
applause everybody
who is this man
and what is he made of
which smartphone is in your pocket and
why so i'm on the pixel 2 xl my galaxy
s8 something i have installed on it is
making the battery drain really fast i
haven't had the time to deal with it are
you trying to say you preferred it is
that on my trip i actually have five
phones with me i can give you the
reasons for all of them this one i'm on
because i popped the sim out of the mate
10 pro there was some software that
wasn't installed on it i needed to use
so i put my sim in here you sound like
the most reluctant pixel user i've ever
heard in my life
it's okay oh so you're not a big fan of
it yeah
um
round roblox
[Applause]
it's good it's really good i love the
i haven't used a phone for longer than a
month at a time in over half a year part
of my deal is i switched the eight i was
using the a plus the pixel 2 not the xl
this was the last one i was on before i
switched to the razer phone which i
frankly didn't like that much so the sim
went back in this one if you could put
any one of them in your pocket not not
the most convenient at that moment which
one would it be i'm really happy with
this one okay so what is this one
sort of
look at these hands i can't handle this
much phone
so really what i want is the s8 back but
with not my batteries how about this in
the form factor of just the pixels yeah
that'd be fine yeah i like this watch
better than i like my phone
[Applause]
i want to be fed to the lines next
if we're talking pixel then we're
talking me a pixel 2 xl and if you guys
have been following me in this recent
trip how about this view i've taken
pictures of this view and i truly
believe this is the best camera on a
smartphone right now period i have not
taken a bad picture with this phone plus
i like stock android and all the usual
things that you know about this is in my
pocket for now there's no lies here it
either is or it isn't
all right who's next
judner you're next man the pressure's on
iphone 10. wow it's just two phones so
far i'm gonna be straight up it's
imessage man in the ecosystem whoa
that's what it is for me i don't even
know what this means this imessage thing
it's not about the blue and green okay
what is it about i'm always on my
computer always on the phone somebody
hits me up usually it's a family member
who's also on imessage i get it wherever
i am yeah i mean you could do the whole
haircut a lot of things
some other messenger you know a lot of
the world they use whatsapp for example
yeah i mean i've got that comment a lot
yeah but it's like okay
i gotta tell you go download something
what would it take for you to switch
over i message on android honestly i
mean that's not gonna happen obviously
but yeah what are we sitting at right
now three to two oh
can't wait a hotly anticipated take from
the man himself mkbhd what did you have
you had a smartphone awards uh the best
phone the best this the best that it was
a lot of bests but i think what the
people really want to know is what's in
the pocket what's in the pocket and why
which pocket first of all because i do
carry
firing back right now you have two
phones yes main sim card the number you
have this phone number pixel 2 xl naked
pixel 2 xl panda the colored power
button stock android great camera all
the same reasons you said fingerprint
reader is in a good spot i have big
hands so i couldn't even use the smaller
version of this phone i'm a big phone
person if there's an xl that's where i'm
going but the other pocket i do carry an
iphone oh can you believe this are you
running for president next there are
things that just work better on ios i
use the best iphone i can i use my
favorite android phone wow this diplomat
right here came prepared pick a damn
phone right now if you had to drop one
is that it i'm dropping the iphone yes
there it is there it is
[Applause]
no cop out in here no compounds in here
i don't like this whispering
collusion just two phones in the whole
room what are we sitting at now three
three tie breaker happening now mister
who's the boss what's happening
so no preamble no banter i came from the
note8 i couldn't stand it because of the
battery and pixel 2 the great the screen
is not fantastic
but
you kind of get used to it show someone
a meme they might comment on this like
blueness but it's not terrible the pixel
the pixel is better in every way 4 3
pixel 2 xl to iphone 10. i got gotta be
honest i'm a little disappointed that it
broke down that simply there's a lot of
amazing phones out there maybe this says
something about us maybe we're a little
too predictable maybe we need to get out
there a little more often i'm not really
sure this has been incredible this is
unprecedented i don't know maybe you
want to see something like this next
year you people there in the audience if
you do i think you know what to do you
use your thumb to let jack know that
that's the case i want to say thank you
to everybody that's been in this video i
hope to do it again that is the
smartphone that's in their pocket no
lies it's the real deal here in las
vegas ces 2018 yes
[Applause]
oh it's good it's good it's really good
[Music]
you