Dr. Chaturvedi
-Yes Sir
The Tumour operation conducted
on the patient was successfu
Then why is so nervous?
Sir, This rich people expect
to get well in just two days
When you are not around, this
patient give me a lot of trouble
He asks me a lot of questions
like when you will come…
Where You have gone
-Look Doctor…
Whether the patient
is rich or poor..
The patient won’t come to a Doctor
if he doesn’t have faith in him
No matter whether the
doctor is big or small
Sir, That Mrs. Mehra
-Oh yes, have yo checked her?
Yes, I have examined her
Give her an injection
of guardeni -Ok Sir
I will check her later on
-Fine Sir
Good Morning Sir
-Good Morning
You brought
-Yes Sir, it's all ready
Show me
Sir…
- Who’s it?
Justice Desai is on line
Off Oh..
Hello, yes Good Morning
Is my report alright?
Don’t worry, I have
checked everything
You can have whatever you
want to, but within limits
Okay? Bye
Please sit down
-This is your passage
This is the patients room
This is your Dinning Hall
And this is your lift, Sir
Could we have an extra lift
–Yes Sir.
You can put here in the back,
there is a space
Back Side?
- Yes there is a space
Ok than, Keep one extra lift
Ok, I note it down
Where did you plan the
operation theater?
On the first floor, sir
I told you to plan it on
the ground floor, Change it
Bring it to the ground floor
–it’s to late, sir
Construction work has
already commenced
But before the construction work
Has begun, in the final plan…
The operation theater was supposed
to be on the ground floor
Some complication had cropped
up and you were not available…
But Mr.Chaturvedi
asked me to go ahead
Who is Chaturvedi?
Go and get me Mr.Chaturvedi
From the very begining
I been telling you,
I want this Operation theatre on the
ground floor and you..
It’s me – Me, who?
Me! – Oh, well …go ahead
I was taking a bath this morning
And you left without telling me
I told you I was In hurry, Is
this why you’ve called me?
I have drawn a sketch, I want you
to see it, Will you come for lunch?
I could also have seen the
sketch in evening…You…
Yes Sir -One second
Did you tell him to shift the
operation theater to the first floor?
Yes, sir -Why?
I thought it wouldn’t
make a difference
What do you mean by that? As
a doctor, don’t you know…
A patient could have loose his life during
an emergency? -I am sorry sir
Keep the plan with you
and let’s go to the site
Sunil, so many Indian doctors
have settled in the U.S.
Why mustn’t I do the same thing?
I think he is right, Sir
-Thank You
Really? but the doctors
think like this…
What will happen of India? -what
can you find here anyway?
If I settle down there, I’ll get
a lot more money and facilities.
And here we are facing
population explosion
If the population is more,
more people will be ill
If the people are ill, more
doctors will be required
And lady, here you can’t get
your work done by servants
Out there, you will have to
do everything on your own
Not right away, We have
just arrived, You may eat
That’s good, in fact
One need not go on a diet
What are you doing? I have just started
This is my second drink
Guys, this is my second drink, right?
–Right…
Go ahead and eat. And
it’s only 10pm
What are you going
to do at home?
You don’t want to show
me a new sketch, do you?
Sketch?
- Oh Yes, Of late, she’s is very much
Today I was very busy in
the hospital, she rang me up
I asked whether it was important
She said yes
“I got to show you anew sketch”
I have seen her paintings
a couple of times
I didn’t know which
side to look it from
Left, Right, Top or bottom? it
looked the same from everywhere
Are you angry with me?
What’s up? You are so quite,
You just don’t speak
If you don’t wish to talk,
May I get a book for you?
Write all your complaints in that
Complaints from me?
I have got such a big house,
servants to work for me, …
A car to move about in, a TV and
a radio for entertainment, …
And a telephone to communicate
All these things are there
I have no complaints
You never promised to
give me all these things
Hello -How are you Aarti?
I am fine, what about you
-We are fine
I hope you are coming?
–Of course…I am coming
And what about Sunil?
- You talk to him
Call from Khandala
Hello -Sunil are you coming?
-Yes
This time I have informed you 7 days
in advance, No excuses this time
I will definitely make this time..
Your bungalow’s being decorated..
You want to take a look at it?
My husband says that it if you..
If upu don’t come for Raju’s birthday,
you will be court martilled!
We will definitely come.
Who’s Raju?
My sister’s son. Tomorrow you
will want to know who Aarti is
What time will you be arriving?
–by the evening
Promise!
- Yes, Promise
You -Sir have sent you a car
Where is sir?
- Sir told you go, he will come tomorrow
“why’s he drifting
away from me?”
“why are all my desires and
dreams all being shattered?”
“why’s he drifting
away from me?”
“Adorned with flowers Was
my life of recent years”
“Those days will never return.
Those days are past”
“Those days are in the past”
“What smoke engulfs my world…?”
“why’s he drifting
away from me?”
“In my eyes are tears,
waiting to spill”
"It rains, but I am still thirsty"
"But I am still thirsty"
"life, how did you become
a human being like this"
“why’s he drifting
away from me?”
Greetings Madam!
How Are you, Bahadur-
-I am fine, as always..
It's raining in this season.
Remove the luggage
If it remove luggaage,
it will wet
Take car in the garage,
than remove it -Hurry up.
Common move on..
What Happaned?
You, Aunty don't save him,
the one who is scared, he is died
What is this Raju?
Not Raju, I am Gabbar Singh!
My God.
- Aarti Never loses
But, You..
St. Xaier College, Bombay
Vini Vinod Sinha.
- Oh Yes, We met after long time
Aunty he is my friend
-Friend? -Yes, Raju's friend
Mother's Pappu, Father's Babbu,
Colleg's Lad and Homes Useless
And here rented horse,
That means I. D.
I. D.? -Interior Decorator
On Major's instruction decorating
this house, but what are you doing here?
Me... -Wait let me guess
You are Raju's Ant, His mother's
sister, his father's sister in law
Means Dr. Sunil's wife, Right?
- Right -congrats
You have not changed.
- Aarti -Sister -Aarti
How R Y? -Fine -Why you came
here, instead coming to my home
I thought -Hello
-Hello, he is Mr. Vinod
Who is decorating your house
-We were in same college
Not to Study, we were just going
to college
In that case, you should
not charge her single penny
Absolutely, I will not charge her,
will charge only her Husband.
Sir -Excuse me
Where is Sunil?
He has not come
How is brother in law? -He is been
wating for you from long, Come
Welcome, sister in law,
I was wating for you only
Hope your journey was
trouble free
Not at all, How are you
-Fine
You did not tell me
-What?
Regarding home decoration,
-It's as per Sunil's instruction
Didn't he inform you?
- No
Where is Sunil?
Ha has come
It's good, I got chance bacause
of that
Look sister what Brother in Law
is doing -Why are bothereing her
Why not? she is my sister in law,
means half wife
Half Wife, tell same to Sunil,
he will shoot you
In salim's arm
Anarkali will be bride of Hindustan
Don't make dust of earth,
crown of head
It is already done
I can see the Hindustan of
King Akbar
Will accept you
If King see me here, I will be
buried in your arms
Love which is afraid is not love,
It's crime
Salim, Your fearless love
Challange to Moghal Empire
Inspector
What happened? Where is he?
Arrest this girl
No, This is not possible,
till I am alive
Your impossible attempt,
is disobey of royal order
I can't see this crime
-Stand up
If you love this servant
Than you will have to try,
your full life
Anarkali is not fit for you
Why Not?
Because, for your love, can not change
destiny of Hindustan
Everything changed
But in this changing world
You can not change your love
But, Salim you have to change
Aarti -Yes
-Aarti never loses
You have done wonderful job
-You have done excellent
You are good in dialouge
-What differnce it makes
Many times you can express
youself without saying anything
You have said nothing but did
a good job -Thank You
You did good job
Vinod, even today you could not
tell her your feelings
You speak well on stage, If you could speak
in real life, your work would have done
Uncle, I think today I should tell her
Now love her in your dream,
-What do you mean
I mean, her marrige is fixed
Isn't it good place
In wet rain, in green hills,
train looks so beautiifull
God knows, how many stories
hidden in it
Everyday so many passnger traval
through this
To take others to their
destination is its destination
What are you thinking?
You deliver dialogue very well
Seems the habit of acting is not gone
How it can go, every person is actor,
you me we all
In drama of life everybody
has to do their role and go
Yes, sound good -It's a fact
Why you lauged
-It remind me college insident
Do you remember you used
to deliver items on stage
I used to do lot, which one
you talking about
Yes Mr. & Mrs. Laila Majnu
-Yes I got it
Laila Majnu are married now
It was their wedding night
With procession of mad people
Majnu says, come in arms
Laila said first sew your torn cloths
Love was dream, come into reality,
It seems got into trouble
The question of earning started
reminded of bread when felt hungry
Laila used to ask when Majnu
reaches home
Even today we have come empty handed,
No ladyfingar, no cabbage, no pumpkin
There is no chilli and no masala,
You put me in trouble
Laila do you want fight with me,
we have promised to love each other
Shall I wear it or spread it your love,
what shold feed to our hungry kids
Don't cry, till Majnu is alive
you don't have to worry
This is Doctors Majnu’s house
-Who is Majnu?
I am sorry, this is doctor’s
Sunil’s house
What’s the matter?
You sound very happy
No, that Majnu was…
- who is the Majnu?
What I meant is that Vinod
Why didn’t you tell me about it?
Doesn’t matte, Why did you call?
Oh yes, I want to renew
My revolver license
I looked eveywhere but couldn’t
findit, Could it be in you bag?
Yes, I have it
-Have it! You could have atleast
Told me before leaving
That give you a reason to call
-I was going to call you anyway
Listen, I told you yesterday
About Raju’s birthday
Why don’t you come over? Sister
and brother in law would
be happy
What do you mean by trying?
Please come over, Okay
Who's call?
Sister, he is coming
-I knew it
By morning everything will be
alright -You are right
Every morning brings new exaltation,
Gives message of good news
You are having tea in Glass? -Cup
-I like tea in glass
becuse first you get more tea in it,
secondly it remains hot for longer
three.. -enough..
Sister, this time we will celebrate
Raju's birtday here
Here? Yes Aunty let's do it
It's OK, but -Yes Aunty
But your house is not ready yet
-Don't worry, it will be ready by evening
Come on Raju, Come on Raju..
What's going on? -Blink an eye
-Means?
War of an eye, The one who will
blink an eye first will lose the game
And the one who will lose?
- He has to pay fine
What fine? -What the winner wish
Come on Raju, Come on Raju..
Yes... Very Good..
Come on Vinod
Steady steady
Your call Aarti
Greetings sister in law,
This is Chaturvedi speaking
Tell me what is it? -Doctor won't
be able to come to Khandala
But why? -He has gone for some
urgent visit
He will be coming late, so he
asked me to inform you
It's OK
What Happened?
- He is not coming
Anyway leave it, Why you filling sad?
- Atleat he could himself
He must be bussy with urgent work
Yo  u take care of Guest,
I go to kitchen
You lost, You lost..
Be quiet, quiet
You have won, you decide
I will tell in your ears
In the ears? Go ahed
Children be ready
"Speak, speak, life's gamut"
"Be Happy in every colour of life"
"Speak, speak, life's gamut
-well done"
"Speak, speak, life's gamut"
"You look at lovely flowers"
"They laugh even when broken"
"Who laugh in such style,
remains in everybody's heart"
"Remains in everybody's heart"
"We can find happiness in every situation"
"Speak, speak, life's gamut
-well done"
"Speak, speak, life's gamut"
"What is the sadness
of what did not come yet"
"What a cry for what you spent in past"
"Whole Life is hidden in Today's
Do not waste today just like that"
"Do not waste today just like that"
"Whole life worth of two words of love"
"Need just smile to change the atmosphere"
"Speak, speak, life's gamut"
"Be Happy in every colour of life"
"Repeat the same"
"Well Done"
"Speak, speak, life's gamut"
Wait, I will just ask Mrs. Sunil Gupta
and let you know
I can not stand anymore, Sister
-But
Sunil was not like that
He was not, but now a day he
is so much lost in his own work
He has no value fore me
As if I do not exist
What are saying, Sunil has given
you everything
Car, Bunglow...
- I did not ask for all these
Sister, I'm not one of those women
Who are satisfied with all these
I just wanted his love, his company
We were so happy in that small house
As wealth grows,
happiness gets away from me
And the distance between us kept growing
It was heard that after marriage,
the two get together
But, we two remain two
It was good to be alone
No aarti, Don't feel so bad about it
Sister, you won't understand
The one who feels lonely knows
What she goes through
You don't worry, this time
I personally come with you
and explain Sunil
No sister, that is of no use
He should understand himself,
my pain
I have decided
Unless he come himself and take
me with him, I won't go from here
Rosy, Did you change it's location?
- No Sir
If I change, madam will replace me
and send me to Goa
So did it move by itself
-I think so -What?
No Sir, Madam told watchman to keep it here
Bahadur
Get Ladder -I won't
Why? -Once I climb the ladder
One person took away ladder
Full day I was on top and
The mosquito ate me
If you want I can get small table
-OK get that -I will get that
Sister, can we go for picnic tomorrow?
- Not picnic, will go to see film
No mom will go to see Circus
-Not at all -In circus there are lions
No, No... there is lot of confusion
We will make slips -wonderfull
See in slip we will get Picture only
-no mama we will get circus
Tell me what yours, spell the circus
Whereyou want to go?
Picnic -Aunty Circus -You?
- Film
No mama circus -Keep quiet, You?
I wanted to go for hunting, but
will go where my wife want to go
Film -Major will go to see film,
-You -and me it's secret
Now see amazing
-See it will be film only
See mummy I only will win, not you
let me see, not you,
partner you select -Circus
Well done, ley me read
Let us see awesome slip
What is it? It's Picnic
Look, it's picnic -We lost hunting
as well as film
If we are going for picnis, why don't
we go to Nandgaon? -Will go to Bhushi Dam
Hunting, Hunting, you know anything else
Raju, why are sitting sad
-He exactly like his mother
Your partner only removed the slip,
we will go to circus some other time
Will show you elephant, hourse, camal,
everything, Come on get up
So tomorrow at what time?-At 9:30
-Ok Raju tomorrow at 9:30 sharp
My big rose -Yes
-It smells good
Just open the lid, let me test it
-What are you doing?
You can not test it
Rosy -Whenever I try to test it
someone comes in
Is food ready, It ready from tomorrow,
-What? -I mean it's from long
Good morning, Good morning everybody,
lovely weather no rain, everything ready
Where is Majer?
- Good morning
Good Morning -Army man never late
-Good Morning sir
Where is Sister & Raju?
- There is small problem
Raju got wet in rain yesterday so he
is having fever, if goes out it may incrase
Let's go and see him -No no hold on
Somehave I manage to convence him
If you go, he will again start crying
You both carry on,
What say Vinod?
I don't get into fight of sis and bro
in law, if you want we will put slips
There is no need of slips
-Correct, no need of slips
Brother in law, picnic cancelled
That's right, picnic cancelled
-Why to cancelled picnic for this
This is also right,
why to cancell picnic?
It doesn't look nice, there is
more fun, if we go together
This is also right, we all shold
go together
Aarti, you rearly come to this place,
we have gone there many times
This is also right, they
have gone there many times
Now I am not going to remove my
glasses any more, decide fast
You both just go -let's go
Good -She is gone
Even after retirment, your habit
of giving orders not gone
You sent her alone -How alone?
Vinod is also with her
So what? Aarti is our responsibility
If Sunil comes to know about it,
what will he think?
But you were saying,
Both studied together
May be, but now Aarti is married
After marriage, women become more
intelligent, except you
What did you say?
Nothing, speak softly, Raju will get up
Don't talk
Don't know, Where both will be
roaming alone?
Listen one more, in winter a person
was giving bath to his cat
A passerby said, cat will die in this cold
He said go away and let
me do my job
second is person went away,
After some time
Same person saw, the first person
crying carrying cat on his lap
I had told, she will die
he said she died by not bathing
by squeezing
What's wrong, I keep on talking
and you are so quiet
If you wanted to be so silent,
why did you come for picnic?
Picnic was just a excuse
I had heard, Here a monk lives,
who is good at hand reading
Not met -How not met?
That wise man is in front of you
Anything -Show me your hand, till date,
whatever was told has come true
What a lines? You have age of 99
The line of fate is so strong,
Whoever comes near becomes lucky
But, But, Shadow of saturn on mars
Got nothing even after having everything,
that's why mind is worried
But, thumb is straight
That means will power
-What? -self power
whatever you think, you do it
-Yes -Yes
your hand shows, it's going to rain now
-You are lying -I am not lying, you saw
You will get wet -I don't need this
-Take it
You -Don't worry, I am waterproof,
you will get wet, wear it
The rain is increasing
-Yes, it is increasing
Keep raining...
You are really crazy, rain is already
increasing and you are singing for rain
OK than, I will sing to stop the rain
Do not rain...
Ever in your life you were serious
Aarti, if person is always appears happy,
that does not mean he has no sadness
What can make you sad, You are alone,
you don't have anybody
May be that is the reason
Sadness can be shared,
Someone has said it correct
You share your happiness, it gets double
and if you share your sorrows it gets half
But, With whom to share
-Find someone
Don't get so easily -If you try sincerely
you will definitely get
Rain Stopped, Let's go
God bless you
Appearing waterproof,
You realised now
What is this -tea with ginger
Medicine for cold
Tell me one thing, When you got married
Then your husband put the garland
or stethoscope
You became doctor -quiet
Is it must -Absolutely must
Wow, I enjoyed
-Than why you were acting
Mind was seeking happiness
-Yes I was, But..
But means, I mean
Why you came yourself,
could have sent through someone
Why, you were not keeping well,
What is wrong If I get it
Nothing happened
Realized one thing
You must have someone
That's why I am saying,
make someone yours quickly
A wise companion should also be found
You will get it
it's not that easy
Find the right partner at the right time
It's a coincidence
See, If you meet someone sometimes
Within two to four days it seems
like you know for years
And sometimes even after staying
together for years
Kept reading book of life and
never came to know the story
Listen, there is more tea in thermos,
If you want you can have it
How is Raju? You know kids
get seek fast and get well soon
Hello, God morning everybody
-Good morning -Good morning Vinod
How are you -Fine -How
was picnic? -first class
still sneezing, Why didn't you
wear a sweater? -It's nothing
the only medicine for cold is two
large whisky, What say major?
Correct, I too.. -Major, Hats off to Aarti
Yesterday we walk too far, but she did
not tired -Why? You forgot
Aarti never loses
After all, she is my sister in law
of army man
That means major, you are taking
credit of this -Why not?
I chose Sunil for her
I got her bungalow
I fixed it and it's decoration etc..
-That was by me
That's true, but hurry up, it
taking long time
Major this is not like fighting,
to happen fast
It's a matter of art, slowly...
Even we are not in hurry
Saw, she understand it
-Listen
You are leaving? -No major it's not
like that -Why brother in law?
What is the matter -Aarti you won't
understand, this person sometime
has a habit of disappearing
-No major no slander
Very intresting person -Yes
-Laughing most of the time
Aarti, just listen
You shoul not mix up with unknown man
-What sister, you too...
Speak softly -You started lecture
It's not lecture, I know you have
habit of talking friendly
But, you don't know, what is in
his mind? -Sister I am not a kid
Speak softly -Mummy my bat
broke down
Ok, we will get new one
-When will you get?
You told me to give Camera on Birthday
that is also not given -Go and paly
Raju dear, how are you?
- Fine
I am going to give you, your
mom will not give you anything
No need to give me...
- Shooo...
You will spoil his habits -Yes
-let's go aunty
It's nice, isn't it, take this money
You, What are doing here?
In photo studio, certainly not to
have food
Oho Partner, You are here
to buy camera? -Yes -very good
Not this one, give that one
How much for this?
- 300 Rupees madam
Give me roll as well -One roll
please
Well done, that's great
Let's go -Are you happy?
- Where you will you take first picture
This is how you change it, buddy
look there, Where are you looking at?
Friend, Corn
Corn
Let's have it -Withdraw money
-What?
I am the master, give me my fees,
you feed me corn
Have you run out of money?
Will play eye fight -let's play
-Whoever lose will feed corn
Agree. -Agree, Ok
Oh.. you lost -No friend
You made me laugh, it's cheating
No No.. I have not done any cheating,
-Look aunty friend is cheating me
What cheating -you cheated him
I saw it -What I did?
You were not making strange
faces to make him laugh
First of all you are playing with kids,
on top of that doing cheating with them
You are not a kid, let's play
-Yes aunty let's play
Let's play -Ok start
One Two Three start
Do you remember,
Aarti never looses
Let us see, who wins and
who looses
What happened? Show me,
let me see
Come on, feed us corn
- Why should I?
What do you mean by Why?
You lost the game
You are forcing me,
-Yes forcing you
Come on, give is corns,
Give us three forcefully corn
Put some lime on it, give lime to me
What are looking at?-
You looks like a kid
Childhood is so good
Really, childhood days are the best,
not aware of troubles of life
Sometimes I feel like going back
into my old days and restart as new
What? Miscarriage
I am sorry, I could not
save the baby
How is Aarti? -She is fine
Sunil, it would be
better if you plan
Your next child after some years
It’s not your fault at all..
Maybe it’s not in our destiny so soon..
You can atleast cry, You don’t know
what I am going Through
I can’t even cry
To forget this trauma, we will
Have to support each other
Hello -Hello It’s me
Why did you hang up?
Are you angry?
I wanted to get there and
give you a surprise
Are you coming? -and listen
the food ought to be just great
Shall I invite my sister
And brother-in-law?
No, only me and you tonight
I will be there by eight
Are you sure? -what?
Be here by eight -okay
Thank god, you checked my diary
and told me, What’s my schedule today?
You got an appointment with
Doctor Prakash at 7.30 pm
Let me pour you another drink
-No Prakash, it’s already late
Why is Sinha talking so long?
Did you tell him, I have to go
to Khandala after the meeting?
Yes sir, he had told me that,
he will come by 7.30pm
It’s already 8.30pm -you may
go if you are getting late..
When sinha comes, he will
Explain to me the plan
Go and find out why
He’s getting late
Prakash I don’t trust this man
He is already messed up earlier
What? He has not come yet?
If he comes tell him
We are waiting for him and he should
reach here immediately
Let me fill your glass atleast now
Good Evening Sir, Good Evening?
It’s 10.30pm in the night. I
forgot to carry plan with me
When I went home and so… It’s okay
Don’t waste time
Let’s get stared
Stop
Aarti, where are you going
so late in the night
Going to Hell, Move on please
-What Happan Aarti?
What are you doing Aarti?
Drive Slowly
-leave it
What has happaned to you?
Aarti!
Have you gone mad?
Aarti
stop aarti
For God sake, Stop Aarti
What are you doing Aarti?
Aarti, Aarti, what happaned?
- Leave me, Leave me
Leave me, Leave me
-What has happaned to you?
Aarti, Sorry
What did I dream and What I Got
I did not ask lot from life
Just sought company and love
Did not get even that
That doesn's mean,
you hate your life
Is life called breathing
My life is such a dark night
No matter how long and ldark the night is
The morning definitely comes
And than you used to always says
Aarti never loses
Lost so soon?
You are right, I can live
I will live
Will fight alone with the world
Alone -No Aarti
You are not alone, Aarti
let us go back
Good morning
Will you have tea?
- Off course
Rosy
I will get the tea
Aarti, I could not sleep all night
Kept thinking about you
was thinking
Work is over and I have to go
I was thinking
You also
I want to... -Madam
Bus goes in the evening from here
I told you I have to go
You can go
If I can get some money
You need money? -Yes
-Come with me
Sir, the telephone line to
Khandala is out of order
Okey! Evening I am going there only
Ok Madam, I am leaving
In such heavy rain
-I have umbrella
OK, take care
Madam, Vinod sir has given letter
for you
Letter? -Yes
OK, Madam
You will surprised to have this letter
Matter is like that
Even after staying nearby and
meeting daily, why I wrote letter
The thing which I could not tell in
the college, which remains in my heart
Could not express so far, at last
I had to take help of pen
Aarti, we have met once again,
in our second phase of life
We stayed together for few days,
got chance to understand each other
Came to know, how lonely you
are in your life
You are still alone,
even after getting married
Something missing,
even after having everything
Why is it so?
I understand your helplessness
And as much as I understand,
I feel so close to you
If you wish, I can get new
life for you
Just need your signal
If you are afraid of making a decision,
Than I can support you
I can face every trouble for your happiness
Your Vinod
Yes this is Arti here,
Wher are you?
From Where?
I can't hear you,
please speak loudly
I understand your helplessness, Aarti
If you wish, I can get new
life for you
If you are afraid of making a decision,
Than I can support you
Bahadur, Rosy
Bahadur -Dr. Sunil
Who are you? -Vinod
I see, the interior decorator
I will meet Aarti and come
-Do you care about Aarti?
Why? What happened to her? -how
can you care mental illness?
But then, you don’t have a
mental Relationship with her
What do you want to say? -that
which aarti couldn’t tell you
How could she tell you something
That she couldn’t tell me?
You have been called here to
Decorate the house, not to break it
A house isn’t a house just
Because it has been decorated
I see? -A house is
made of love..
Sharing happiness and sadness,
Supporting each other in hardships
And those are the things that
were never given to her by you
Shut up.. -It’s true
It’s a fact, If you don’t
Believe me, ask her.
Its true, Aarti? Don’t
be scared Aarti
Tell him everything today
Tell him how happy And
peacefull you are
Tell him you were so happy that
You tried to commit suicide
Tell him
Is it true?
Answer me? Is it true?
Sister -tell me
What is the matter?
For tonight come and slip with me
Rosy is also not there,
Alone I'm scared, stormy night
You come here
No, Sunil had called, He is on his
way, any moment he can come
OK than I will come after Raju
sleeps -OK, come soon
I knew, You will come
Got the letter? -Yes, I am
here answer that letter
You decorated house, it's your fees,
-Fees?
But the love it is decorated with,
Can't be settle with the money
Yes, You have got money in
return of Love
May be because of that
I thought -I understand everything
Aarti, I want to share your sorrows
By supporting you
I have already given this rights
-But it can be taken back
Such rights can't be taken back,
Whom I have made my principles
Principles, which doesn't have feelings
for your pain
Whose negligence forced you to make suicide
In whose eyes the value of your love,
Nothing except money
This money has made you blind
-You are blind
You need the light, you will get
only darkness in this house
Go away from here
-Aarti
Aarti
Aarti, Listen to me -I don't want
to listen anything from you
Didn't you say,
In few days we will start understanding
each other very well
We can start a new life,
Didn't you say that
No partner, no love
If you try sincerely you will
definitely get your partner
Aarti, didn't you say that?
- Yes I said that
Unknowingly to lighten my mind
I said that, but you misunderstood
Lie has many faces,
Just one of the truth
I never told you a lie
But, What you wanted to understand,
that you understood in your own way
No, I understood it correctly Aarti
You are running from truth, You are
scared
you want to Suicide due to
pressure from society
I will never live like that
I will now never allow you to
do that
You have to decide it now
Today just now
Decision -Yes
You want decision
Don't get ahead
I say go back -No Aarti
You can't kill me
-Don't get ahead
No Aarti -Don't get ahead
-You can't kill me
I can kill myself
What are you doing
No -Leave me
Let me die
Frightened?
You! -Who else can touch you?
What are you looking at?
I was stuck in the storm
Look at my condition
I look like a ghost
I will freshen up
No Aarti, you can't kill me
Leave me
Aarti, what did you do,
You killed him
Killed him, how this happened?
Tell me
What will happen now
Police, If the police come
No, No, No...
Aarti, Nothing will happen to you
Nothing can happen to you,
Aarti I, I...
Aarti come fast
You sit in a car
Let me take a look at you, Wow!
You took a long time to come
-Be thankful I came
Can I ask you something?
I am famished
I am starving since last night..
Has Sunil arrived?
Don't cry, Aarti
Sister, what has happened
Looks like... Whenever
Happiness comes near me
Why does this happen to me
Be brave
The more you think about it,
the more upset you will be
I also tremble when I think about it
The brain doesn't work
This we can not even tell anyone
If anyone comes to know
Then your life will be ruined
Respect of our house,
Sunil's big name...
But Sister, How can I hide it from him
Tell me -No No.. Don't
tell anything to Sunil
Even if he gets suspicious
But then, he was
Your college mate..
What will sunil think?
He will lose his trust in you
I don’t know what to do -Make it fast!
I am starved
Sister, you go now
How are you Sunil?
- Hello sister-in-law
What did you say?
- Sister-in-law
How are you? -I am fine
The weather here is peculiar
Last night there was a storm and
Today there’s bright
sunshine Its normal here
Yes, Here it is like that only
You have made such a beautiful
house, But you never come down
What can I do? My work requires
My attention 24 hours a day
Good, The house is beautiful, But
were is the interior decorator?
He must be around be somewhere
Give it to me
You get the tea
Hello, out of work major
-Again! Again!
I mean, retired major -yes
you know how I shoot
Tell me, will you
stay For 3-4 days?
Yes, I have planned to
stay For 3-4 days
You are a doctor, You should
take Care of your health, …
Or else how will you take
Care of you patients?
And then your reputation is
such thatonce a patient…
visits you, he never again
goes to any other doctor
What do you mean? You mean to
Say, the patient who visits me…
No, no..what I meant was he will
Not visit any other doctor
What happened? -breakfast?
Oh yes...
Get cracking!
Wont you have some? -why not?
Sister-in-law fetch more,
This won't do
We have met in a long time.
Here is a butter
Shall I spread it? -To Whom?
On the toast. -sure
The house has been
Beautifully decorated
I selected the interior decorator
-Brother-in-law, how about sugar?
Three spoons? -no, only one
After forty, your sugar
intake Should be reduced
How many times I have told you not
To mention my age in front of women
What’s your programme today?
Going out or sitting at home?
We will go out. I have not
came Here to sit at home
Okay. we will come
in the evening -okay
What are you looking at?
- Nothing
You appear as if you
have seen a ghost
No -yes
No. -What happened to you?
I was just a bit dizzy
Let me take a look.
They’re here. Should we
Call off the programme?
I am okay. Lets go.
We are leaving
You are going out? -Yes,
We are going out
Good
What are you saying? -Yes,
I have seen his ghost
You saw him again? -Yes
I saw him from the top floor
When I came down,
He had disappeared
It must be your imagination.
There are no ghosts
What are you talking about?
Nothing at all. -Uncle, she
is talking about ghosts
Again? You have seen
a ghost here also?
Tell me something, was the
ghost A male or female?
Sunil, if the woman must be
beautiful, The ghost must be a man
I see. Then the ghost doesn’t know
That she is a doctor Sunil’s wife
If I see him, I will shoot him
With your third rate life
Sunil you have scared me
From now on I won’t be able
to joke with her
You are a big boss. -Yes, I am
Because the more jealous a man
Becomes, the more he loves his wife
Now see, you are not jealous.
- I have other options
What happened? Too much sugar? -you
haven’t added any sugar to it
Is doctor sunil at home?
Yes. -Who is it?
Let's go driver
Aarti, Why did the police come?
Did he ask you anything? -No
Why did he take sunil along?
May be... -Where is that tourch
Which tourch? -Same I had that day
Where is it? -With me
What you doing here,
search inside, let's go
Sister, it's not here -It's not there also,
let's see on 1st floor
Sister can't find it, even I can't find it,
Where it could be?
In the car?
No sister -It's not here also,
Where it could be? may be there
It's here, Must have fallan from
your hand -Sister
How it can go down?
If the corpse fell down from here,
it should be here -Than where is it?
Than.. We shouldn't have come here
Let’s go
What will happen now?
What are you doing here?
We came to see the Mahakali Temple.
Have you came here with a wish?
Inspector, I will go with them.
Why did you go tot the police station?
To enquiry about a dead body
-Dead Body?
Yes, yesterday when I was coming, I
came across a womens dead body
I intimated the police. At first
I thought it was a accident,
On investigation it was found out
That her husband was suspicious…
About her, and so he killed her.
Since I intimated the police,
They wanted my statement.
Lets go.
Go on, Chaturvedi. Who, me?
No, I will be
Staying here for 3-4 days.
Who? Mr.Biharilal?
If he has problem with his sleep,
Give him some tranquilizer
Yes, its okay. It’s
not a big problem,
You take care of it.
It's not big problem
No, I will be here for another
3-4 days. Anything else?
No Problems, OK.
If there is any urgency,
We will go back.
What happened? -Why?
Why? When I am there you always
Complain that I don’t give the company
When I give the company,
You want me to go back
I thought it was something very urgent.
- Its not urgent there, but here
What’s so urgent here?
It is urgent, isn’t it?
Get in
Sunil, please come soon
What happened? -Look,
He is wounded.
Sit down here. Rosy,
fetch some warm water
Bring my bag. -OK sir
Who is he? -Vinod, your
interior decorator.
Yes, He is the man
What happened to him? He’s
is the habit of drinking
He might have been hit by some truck
Doesn’t look like
An accident injury
Didn’t you ask him?
- He wont say a word
What? What are they saying?
How can it happen?
I am speaking the truth.
He is sitting right there
Inside? -Yes
Let’s go and see. Doesn’t
-he have any relatives here?
I don’t think so. He
never mentioned any
Good Morning, What happened to him?
- Exactly what I suspected.
What suspicion? -An
injury to the brain
He has lost his memory
Will he always be like this?
- It will take some time.
Will he stay here until then?
Where he will get the
Better doctor than Sunil?
Bahadur… -Coming, Sir
Have you made the bed? -Yes Sir
Take him inside.
Aarti, that means,
We.. to live man
It's good, at least
We are saved from sin
Now it's better we forget
this incident
Sister, I will tell everything to Sunil
-No No, Are you gone mad
Don't you know Sunil?
If Sunil comes to know
Vinod used to study with you and
used to love him
But I did not like him -But how will
you make Sunil understand this
He will misunderstand you
-But you know everything, Sister
I know, God knows, But Sunil
doesn't know
Blood stains may disappear, but
Doubt never fades
If Sunil misunderstood you,
nobody will trust you
And than, You will never be able to
proove yourself innocent
Lest it happen, that your little mistake,
may ruin your family life
Aarti, These secrets will remain
with us
If Vinod said anything to Sunil?
He has lots of misunderstaning
regarding me
There is only one way, before he regain
his memory
somehow he shuold be removed
from this house
You are throwing your the best cards.
- I don’t need your help
Okay, try this
Doctor, I didn’t get a
single card till now
I’ve got a full hand!
Your turn, madam
Come in -Me pack -Vinod come sit down
-You packed?
You want to play? -you are
a strange man, major
He has lost his memory,
-oh, I forgot
But you had told me that he will
Regain his memory gradually
In such cases patient tries
to Remember old memories
Like school or college days
And then slowly he tries to
Remember his recent past
I think we should try to make
Him remember his old days
Aarti can solve this problem
-How?
They were college
mates, -Right, vidya?
Yes. -Really? You never
told me about it
I thought I told you
Madam, the food is ready.
- Let me see
Then I think it will
be easy for me.
Aarti, Do you have another pen? The
refill In this pen has exhausted
Put a refill in this
What’s the matter?
- Will he stay here
Who? -He
Vinod? -Yes
Yes. -Is it necessary?
Why? He use to stay
Here even earlier
But not in this condition
Why don’t you admit him
to A government hospital?
I see. So you know his
Condition better than me?
He is not that serious to Be
admitted in the hospital
Besides, I’m here too. Why…?
You have a problem with him?
Why should I be worried?
Mr. Sharma
-Don’t talk to me
I am angry with you -Why?
What happened?
You never met me
after coming here
I came two days back. -Two days? I
met your wife here last Sunday
She has been here for some time
-Has she come all alone?
Yes
But I have seen a young, handsome
Man with her..forget it
What’s the matter? -Forget it
You come to my house today
-What’s special day?
Todays my birthday -But I got
some guest at my place
Bring them along too -Okay
What are you doing here?
Sir told to give him medicine
Where is Sir? -To get medicine
-You go to kitchen
Bahadur, go and clean the garage
-OK madam
Whast are looking at? -Where?
Are you really forgottan everything?
How is it possible? So many things have
happened and you don't know anything
Yes
It's Good Vinod, that you are escaped
but tell me onething
Why you came here? -Do you want to
spoil my life?
I didn't get you? you know everything
You are acting now, What do you want
from me after all
You know it very well, you won't get
anything from me,
Didn't I tell you same thing that night?
Night -Yes, that night
That dark night, worst night of my life
I want to forget it
I want to forget it forever
Whatever happened that night
Should remain between us
It will be good for both of us
Listen. If you really love me..
Then for me, for my life
Please forget that night.
Go away from here
But I have seen a young, handsome
Man with her..forget it.
Whatever happened that night
Should remain between us
It will be good for both of us
"What should I
compliment these beauties?
"Not getting words"
"Their each style is a way of cheating"
"What should I compliment these beauties?
- Not getting words"
"Their each style is a way of cheating"
"They are such cheater,
who can cheat cheater"
“it’s a secret known only to those
That have been deceived by them”
“These pretty women are
true friends to no one”
"These pretty women Are
“Even if they are friends,
They can never be loyal”
"These pretty women Are
true friends to no one”
“The nature of rose is a habit"
"The pretty ones have cultivated”
“like all roses pretty,"
'
"They smile at everyone”
“Like the stars,"
"They dazzle Everbody’s eyes”
“This pretty women just can’t,"
"Belong to a single man..”
“such is the stone like"
"Heart nature has given them”
“God has crafted them
With his own hands…”
“to them, He has Given
all the beauty”
“The attraction they wield,"
"Make everyone crazy about them”
“Such is the charm
bestowed upon them"
"Nature has been kind to them”
“They have been taught not
To be loyal or love…”
“They have got everthing else”
“These pretty women are
true friends to no one”
“Even if they are friends,
They can never be loyal”
“These pretty women Are
true friends to no one”
“These pretty women are
“They are not to
blame, however..”
“what they do is so little”
“There’s someone they think about,
But get linked with someone else”
“Even when you think they’re
yours, They’re complete strangers”
“Even God couldn’t figure them
out, What is a mortal capable of?"
"What is a mortal capable of?"
“They’ll sway in stranger arms,
They will forget ties ages old”
"They will forget ties ages old”
“They keep changing their
minds Like the season change”
"Minds Like the season change”
“Their love is
always suspect…”
“they belong not
to anyone Forever”
“They are as deceitful
As they are beautiful”
“to deceive is the profession
Of beautiful women”
“These pretty women are
true friends to no one”
“Even if they are friends,
They can never be loyal”
“These pretty women Are
true friends to no one”
“These pretty women are
Which flowers are that? What are
you looking at? -Your eyes
What do you see in them?
- What not?
Can I say something? -Go ahead
Will you keep it a secret? -Yes
Close your eyes when somebody
Comes in front of you. Why?
Seeing those eyes any one…
Will fall in love with you. Just
like I fell in love with you
My eyes have only your image
Try again -no..
Sir…
Sir.. -Buddy, you have won!
Good Morning
-God Morning
Dear, go have your breakfast
-Buddy, I will have my breakfast
Tell me something. Have
you ever been in love?
Love? -Yes, Love
No. -Try to recall
When you were kid?
No. -In school
No. -In college
Yes
What kind of girl was she? I mean
Was she fair or dark of skin?
Fair
Her hair? -was long
What was the thing in her
That had you captivated?
Her eyes
Shall I switch off the light?
- No..
Coming to bed? -You
sleep, I am sitting here
I told you, I wont be coming now
It’s dawn already?
You slept here?
Tell rosy to fetch some tea
Rosy, bring my lighter
Here you are
Listen, I have
something to tell you
Are you angry with me?
What’s the matter?
Don’t you know?
You are misunderstanding me
I used to misunderstand you
It’s not as you are thinking it is
What? What did you say?
If you can’t diagnose the disease
by looking at the patient face…
Then you are not a doctor at all
-Won’t you listen to me?
What is left to listen to?
Yes, there is. There’s so
much I said until today?
I have only been listening
And enduring until now
You have no right to suspect
me without clarifying with me
Those who have no proof of the truth
Resort to raising there voices
Sister, I am going, Where?
Even I do not know
Sunil's suspicion has turned into hatred
And I do not have any evidence,
by which he can trust me
Only you know the truth
If husband does not have any respect for
his wife then she starts burdening him
If I stay here,
He will be sad to see me
I don't want this, I
wish he knew the truth,
So we don't get separated like this
No!
Doctor, I want to tell you something.
- I don’t want to hear anything
Aarti -You -Come with me
No -Come on -Where?
- Where you should go
You were going away,
Leaving me all alone?
Vinod told me.. -I came
to do the interiors here
But I created misunderstanding
Between the two of you
I can’t even apologise to you
For the mistake I have made
You can be a friend
I know that misunderstanding can
Cause a lot of problems. But
sometimes the problem itself
Can solve the misunderstanding. And
thus, I have realized my mistake
I have drifted far away from Aarti.
But now I am closer to
Her than ever before
I recognize every disease in the world
But you r mind, which is part of life
Couldn't recognize it
Please forgive...
The End…