youtuber gaurav taneja aka flying
beast made a tweet a few days back
he's an iit graduate and i was surprised
to see him buy into this kind of [ __ ]
just goes to show no matter how educated you
are you can still fall prey to it w're gonna look at
this claim analyze where it comes from and talk
about such religious science claims in general
for those who don't know gaurav tanija which i
think is very few of you his youtube channel is
called flying beast he uploads daily vlogs and
uses the cuteness of his children for clickbait
this he has been criticized for a lot but whatever
you might think he is a very skilled youtuber very
well respected in the vlogging community his vlogs
get a million plus views every day he has a loyal
fan base and i expect this video to be getting
a ton of dislikes soon but i must do what i do
on this channel which is fight irrationality being
spread by these pages but this time it's not just
another huge youtube channel it's run by an iit
kharagpur alumnus a qualified pilot a bodybuilder
and someone who has recently gotten into studying
law but no amount of education can remove the
years of religious indoctrination as shown by
this tweet but you know what let's not jump to
conclusions let's actually analyze what he said in
this tweet because hey you can make extraordinary
claims you just have to back it up with
extraordinary evidence let's see what evidence
he actually provides two families survived the
bhopal gas tragedy uh by doing agni hotra that's
the fire ceremony that you can see him doing in
this picture here now the bhopal gas tragedy was
a factory accident that took place in 1984 where
this highly toxic gas called mic methyl isocyanate
leaked in the city of bhopal leaked into residence
houses and thousands of people lost their lives
now if you want to learn what led up to the
accident and what happened after it i highly
recommend dhruv rathee's video i've linked it
in the description now where does this claim
come from all sources point to a newspaper article
that was apparently published in 1985 which talks
about these two families that woke up in the on
the night of the tragedy vomiting because of the
poisonous gases toxic gases and instead of
evacuating like any sane family would they decide
to sit and do agnihotra and within 20 minutes
their symptoms of gas parsoning vanished now
how can that be possible when methyl isocyanate is
flammable it burns producing even more toxic gases
like hydrogen cyanide and carbon monoxide etc how
on earth can you perform a fire ceremony in its
presence hey in case you don't die by breathing
in mic you can ensure that you burn your entire
house down by doing this okay let's assume that
the gas is not flammable or maybe it wasn't
in sufficient enough quantity to catch fire
noticeably even then there is a logical fallacy
when you come to this conclusion when you say that
the agni hotra is what saved the lives of those
people let's see what it is we don't know how much
of this claim is true especially given that mic is
flammable this newspaper article sounds like a
whatsapp forward by someone who wanted to use a
tragedy involving the the deaths of thousands of
people to promote their version of superiority of
their religion even if you assume the details of
the story to be true this conclusion that has been
drawn has a logical flaw in it when you say that
a happened and then b happened therefore a caused b
you're mistaking correlation for causation the agni
hotra and the families surviving the tragedy are
two events that are correlated but if you conclude
that they survived because of this agnihotra then
you are committing this fallacy you're ignoring
all the other factors that may have been bigger
reasons for why they survived like how much of
the toxic gas was in the air what was the airflow
like that night with respect to the houses
uh what was the wind speed and direction in
the location and how far away was the house from
the factory and how did all these factors affect
how much toxic gases were in the air we shouldn't
jump to conclusions without a clear knowledge of
all these factors especially when the claim we're
making is extraordinary like this extraordinary
claims require extraordinary evidence i'm not
rejecting the claim i'm simply not accepting it
because there is no convincing evidence but when
it comes to Gaurav Taneja's claims on the
uh scientific superiority of the vedic scriptures
it doesn't stop there let's see what else he said
in this video uploaded on august 8 2019 he talks
about how although we see things from this lens
of modern science in the world today as we
get older and we learn more about the world we
start losing our belief in modern science and
we start trusting the vedas in our scriptures
he says how there's all the science in the
bhagavad-gita how it talks about atoms and
electrons and protons which honestly is a load
of bull[_] and i'll explain why science is a method
it is not a body of knowledge it is not a list
of facts and theories or our list of solutions
to problems it is a way of thinking a way of
learning things about the world primarily through
observation a way of figuring out how true
something is and if it should go in such a list
or not i have an entire playlist on my channel
on this scientific method feel free to watch
now someone comes to me and says that there's
this book from centuries ago which talks about
atoms and electrons and protons and the theory of
evolution and they figured all this out without
using the scientific method then whatever that
book says cannot be called scientific they may
be true or false but definitely not scientific
we learned about electrons and protons through
careful experimentation and observation we learned
about evolution through observation can you tell
me back when the bhagavad-gita was written how
could they have performed the experiments that led
to those conclusions they couldn't have but pranav
you ask if they weren't using the scientific
method how were they right i have two answers for
your question one given what you know today you
try and force fit modern discoveries and try and
find parallels that are there in the scriptures
that match with modern discoveries modern theories
modern facts that we discovered recently and you
tend to ignore everything else that doesn't
match with anything that we know today
this is a combination of hindsight bias
and confirmation bias the other reason is
imagine you're in a dark room somewhere in the
room there is a dart board and you have a bunch
of darts if you start throwing the darts what
percentage of them will hit the mark a very
low percentage right you can see how it's not
zero percent even if you throw randomly in some
direction you could hit the bullseye it's unlikely
but you could hit it right now imagine if the room
was dimly lit you can make out some details
in the room you can see roughly where the dart
board is and that helps you throw better making
your throws get a higher percentage accuracy
and what if the room was well lit your accuracy
would go up tremendously right the chance of you
not hitting the mark will only depend on how
good or bad your aim is the same way back when
these books were written if there are things that
turned out to be factually correct in these books
those small percentage of shorts in the
dark that hit their mark a huge number
of these statements are just plain false but you
ignore them and pick only the ones that are true
knowing what you know today and you call
them scientific what logic is this things
like ayurveda probably did a lot of trial
and error before arriving at their results
and they probably had better accuracy much
like the dimly lit room from my example
but simple trial and error is prone to a lot of
mistakes which are overcome by modern medical
trials i've gone to that extensively in this video
plus we had no knowledge of germ theory before the
17th century plus with advancements in chemistry
and biology we know the mechanisms in which these
medicines work and that has helped us design much
more better medications for certain conditions
we also have ways of evaluating the safety
of medicines which we didn't have back then
ayurveda may have achieved results many centuries
ago doesn't mean it's the best tool we have today
there is a very prevalent narrative that i whether
superior to modern medicine i've heard many people
say it please don't buy into it what we have today
is like my third example a much brighter room of
course we can miss but the chance of hitting
are much much higher than anything we had in the
past and plus you don't need to establish your
religion cultural tradition as scientific only
people with an inferiority complex will do that
your culture is beautiful as it is don't embarrass
yourself by posting tweets like this now there is
a chance that he knew exactly what he was doing
he didn't actually believe what he said but he
said that only to please the uh his audience or
he knew his audience really well and
he knew the majority of his audience
would like a post like that and that's why he
posted it in which case i don't really have
a lot to say about him he's just being really
manipulative and if people don't recognize that
they can fall to traps like these so yeah and
the next time you see someone say some modern
scientific fact is mentioned in scripture just
remember they just shots in the dark some may hit
the mark doesn't mean they were aimed i'll see you
in the next one till then remember science is dope