Hello, friends!
Shahrukh Khan's newly released film Jawan,
is breaking all records.
This film is getting a lot of love from the public.
But do you know that more than half of the incidents shown in this film
are inspired by real life?
You will be shocked to know how
significant is the connection between
the things shown in this film and real life.
Let's find out in today's video.
In this video, I won't give any major spoilers of plot points of the film.
So, even if you haven't seen the film,
you can watch this video without any hesitation.
In fact, if you haven't seen the film,
you may get more curious to watch the film
after seeing the real issues in this video.
Let's start with the second big scene
of the first half of the film,
which is set in a government hospital.
In the film Jawan, it is shown how
young children in government hospitals die of encephalitis
because oxygen may not be available.
In the film, a very sincere doctor, Iram, is shown
who tries her best to save the children.
But after this incident is made public,
the government frames this doctor instead.
A false accusation is put on her
and she goes to jail.
Something similar happened in August 2017
in real life, in the city of Gorakhpur.
In a government hospital, BRD Medical College,
63 children died within 3 days
when the piped oxygen supply of the hospital ran out.
Dr Kafeel Khan was working as a paediatrician at that time.
When he came to know that the oxygen
supply in the hospital was nearly over,
he tried to inform the authorities.
Since there was no response,
he tried to procure oxygen supply from himself
at his own expense.
He is seen as a real-life hero.
But when the news of this incident reached the media,
the blame is shifted on the Dr Kafeel.
The government accused him of medical negligence and corruption.
He was suspended from his job,
arrested and then he was in jail for 9 months.
In an interview, he reveals how mercilessly he was beaten in jail.
He was starved for 4-5 days.
He was in such a bad condition that
he couldn't sleep on his back for months.
"They used to make me naked,
they used to beat me with a stick.
They didn't give me food and water for 4-5 days!"
In April 2018, he finally got bail from Allahabad High Court.
The court stated that there was no evidence of his wrongdoing.
In 2017, an inquiry panel was set up
to investigate the allegations against him.
Even the panel stated that
the allegations against him are baseless and inconsistent.
In fact, this panel report states that
on 11th and 12th August,
due to his honest efforts,
more than 500 jumbo oxygen cylinders were
delivered to this hospital by different companies.
The film Jawan shows how when the doctor had no other option,
she started giving Ambu bags to the parents.
This happened in real life too.
During the Gorakhpur tragedy, there were reports
that when oxygen was depleted,
parents were using Ambu bags to save their children's lives.
They were trying their best
and many parents saw their children dying in front of their eyes.
Dr Kafeel said that
he was made a scapegoat
and that it was a man-made tragedy.
More than 30 letters were written to the authorities of BRD Medical College
and to the UP government.
Bills of 6.3 million rupees were pending
to the oxygen suppliers
which were not paid for months.
Again and again, the letters asked them
to pay the oxygen suppliers
so that the oxygen supply to the hospital would not be disrupted.
Just one day before the Gorakhpur tragedy,
on 9th August,
Uttar Pradesh's Chief Minister Adityanath visited this hospital himself.
I made a video on everything that happened at that time,
if you haven't seen it, I'll put the link in the description.
We often hear that the state of government
hospitals in the country is very bad,
but how bad is it actually?
And what impact does it have on people's lives?
We got to know this from this film
and from Gorakhpur Tragedy.
To improve the condition of these government hospitals,
a bold statement is given in the film.
It is said that if there is a will,
then all these hospitals nationwide
can be improved in just 5 hours.
This thing is quite filmy,
but in real life, I believe that
even if not in 5 hours,
but definitely, in 2 to 3 weeks,
all hospitals can be improved.
And you can bring this efficiency and speed to your life
if you use AI tools like ChatGPT.
Believe me, I use ChatGPT daily
and my efficiency has skyrocketed to the next level.
Latest studies also show that
ChatGPT can give innovative ideas faster
and better compared to MBA students.
It can easily pass law exams, business school exams.
That's why, friends, I have created a
4.5-hour-long Master ChatGPT course in Hindi
so that I can teach you the unique ways and use cases of using it.
Thousands of people have taken this course and found it very useful.
And those who are not using it,
don't know what they are missing.
If you haven't joined yet,
then there is a special offer for you.
Use the coupon code SRK40 to get 40% off on this course.
You can scan the QR code
or you can find the link in the description.
It will be applicable for the first 400 people,
so you can try it out quickly.
Now let's get back to the topic.
The second major issue that has been shown in the film is
faulty weapons.
Our soldiers are martyred in our country
not by the bullets of the enemy,
but because of our own faulty weapons,
which are manufactured
by some crony capitalists.
In reality, there have been many reports on this over the years.
In 2012, the Chief General of the Indian Army, V.K. Singh,
wrote to PM Manmohan Singh
and said that the Army's tank fleet
was in dire need of critical ammunition.
In 2015, retired Lieutenant Colonel Deepak Malhotra
filed a PIL in the Delhi High Court,
with the accusation that due to bureaucratic hurdles,
our soldiers have to use weapons of poor quality,
which puts their lives at risk.
In this PIL, an interview of an injured soldier was mentioned,
in which he talked about how due to defective INSAS
a massacre took place in Chhattisgarh.
In 2017, a CAG report mentioned that
40% of the Indian Army's ammunition
is at such low levels that
if a war breaks out,
they will not last more than 10 days.
In 2018, the Indian Army rejected
Made in India rifles for the second time.
Because these Made in India rifles failed badly during trials.
These reports are not yet over.
Listen to more.
In 2020, an internal army assessment flagged that
due to such bad weapons,
In the last 6 years, 403 accidents have taken place
and 27 soldiers have been martyred
at a loss of 9.6 billion rupees.
These weapons were supplied by the Ordnance Factory Board.
After this, in September 2022,
last year's Bloomberg report states that
because of PM Modi's Make-In-India push,
our defence forces are not able to import some critical weapons systems.
Because of this, India is quite vulnerable to
threats coming from China and Pakistan.
I would like to show you a report from this year.
In the last 5 years, around 55 soldiers have lost their lives
in more than 50 aircraft and helicopter accidents.
In a bigger time frame,
there was a report in 2022,
which stated that more than 400 MiG-21s crashed in the last 60 years.
Due to this 200 pilots and 60 civilians lost their lives.
This issue was also raised in the film Rang De Basanti if you remember.
This is a major plot point of the film.
Now let's come to our third big issue,
Corporate Funding.
In the film Jawan, it is shown how
corporate money is secretly used
for funding the political parties.
In 2017, there was a major development regarding this.
Modi government had passed the Finance Bill, 2017
through which giving secret donations to political parties was allowed
through Electoral Bonds.
This bill also removed the limit
on how much money can be given to a political party in donations.
How much money was given?
This year, in January, a report was published,
which said that during 2018-2022, BJP
received ₹52.70 billion of funding secretly.
We don't know who provided this funding,
because that was the aim of the bill they passed.
They wanted to hide their funding.
According to this report, during this time
Congress party received ₹9.60 billion in funding
and Trinamool Congress received ₹7.67 billion.
In 2014, Narendra Modi had promised that
he would bring the black money from Swiss banks back to India.
"For once,
the money that has been deposited in
foreign banks by these thieves and robbers,
if we bring back the money,
even by doing so,
every single poor man in India
will get ₹1.5-₹2 million for free."
But what have they done here?
They have hidden all the money that is received by their parties.
Now, whether it is BJP, Congress or any other party,
the public cannot know who is funding them.
We can just take a guess from the outside.
Another thing worth mentioning here is that
there is an expenditure limit
to what a candidate can spend on his political campaign.
This depends on the state
but in Lok Sabha elections, this limit is
between ₹7.5 million to ₹9.5 million.
If we take the upper limit for every seat in Lok Sabha,
543 seats multiplied by ₹9.5 million,
it is around ₹5 billion.
So, technically, no political party can spend more than ₹5 billion.
Going over the expenditure limit is not allowed.
However, the report of the Centre for Media Studies has shown that
the BJP has spent ₹270 billion
in the Lok Sabha elections of 2019.
Just think about the difference.
Even if you ignore this report,
in November 2019, BJP submitted to the Election Commission
as it is written on the website of the Election Commission
that BJP has spent ₹12.64 billion for the 2019 Lok Sabha elections.
The maximum limit here is ₹5 billion
and they are spending ₹12 billion.
How?
Is this a joke?
In the film Jawan, it is shown that the villain of the film
is telling foreign investors how
voters in India can be bought.
If you pay ₹10,000 to each voter,
they will vote for the payer's preferred political party.
This is shown wrongly in the film
because ₹10,000 is a huge amount.
In our country, we see that
people sell their vote for a kilogram of chicken
or a quarter of whisky.
Obviously, it depends from region to region
on how much money is used to buy voters.
But in the 2019 Lok Sabha elections,
there were seizures worth ₹34.56 billion.
It includes cash, gold, silver, alcohol, drugs, everything.
And forget about buying voters,
there's a new trend in the market.
Political parties buy MLAs,
they buy media houses.
"Casinos, horse trading, horse racing."
And then these MLAs and media houses that have sold themselves
play a game of divide and rule with the public,
spreading hatred among the people
so that their political masters can remain in power.
The film also raises the issue of the environment of the country.
How several industrial factories
pollute our air and water.
In the film, there was a reference to the Bhopal gas tragedy
which happened in December 1984.
I will not talk about this here because
I have made a separate video on this.
If you haven't seen it, I will put the link in the description.
But it is not about just one tragedy,
not about just one incident.
This has become so common that it is unbelievable.
Just do a random Google search
and see the numerous articles pop up.
Let's start in 2006.
In Chhattisgarh, due to iron ore mining,
the water of two rivers got polluted
and 100 villages that were on the banks of the rivers,
the villagers living there had to use contaminated water
for their daily needs.
In 2013, a report by the Center for Science and Environment shows that
80% of Indian sewage
is dumped untreated into rivers.
Who is doing this?
Thousands of factories are dumping untreated sewage in rivers.
In 2017, "Maharashtra's polluting factories
are making its rivers the filthiest in India."
In September 2018,
Magsaysay Award winner
environmentalist Rajendra Singh said that
the government's Namami Ganga project is failing.
In October 2018, G.D. Agarwal, a pass-out of IIT,
became a sadhu.
Swami Gyan Swaroop Sananand.
To save the River Ganga, he went on a fast.
His demand was that a Ganga Protection Act be drafted by the government
and a total ban be imposed on
quarrying and stone crushing on the banks of the River Ganga.
He had also written a letter to PM Modi,
but there was no reply.
His fast lasted 111 days,
after which he passed away due to starvation.
"The man who dedicated his life to get River Ganga cleaned,
environmentalist G.D. Agarwal
finally sacrificed himself for River Ganga."
After that PM Modi did express his condolences.
The budget of the Namami Ganga project was
₹200 billion.
Its deadline was 2021.
This year, Namami Ganga Mission 2 was approved.
With a budget of ₹225 billion.
The deadline was set for 2026.
The Minister of State for Jal Shakti [Water Resources]
clearly told the Rajya Sabha that
this time their main objective
is to meet the water quality criteria of outdoor bathing.
Not to make the water of River Ganga drinkable.
Only so clean that it becomes bathable.
They will try to make it happen by 2026.
Let's move ahead, there are other rivers as well.
This article from 2021,
Karnataka dumps 1,746 million litres of sewage in the rivers every day.
40% untreated.
Experts say that factories and industries should be blamed for this.
April 2022,
the water of the River Hindon in Noida, Uttar Pradesh
is so bad that it is not even safe to bathe there.
September 2022,
the water of the River Damodar in Jharkhand
has become toxic.
People are getting sick by using this water.
Local power stations and mining companies
dump large mountains of ash in this river to save money.
In 2023, the Central Pollution Control Board says that
there are 413 industries in Haryana in total
which are discharging untreated wastes into the river.
Panipat is at number one
with 181 polluting factories.
Gurgaon is at number two
with more than 100 such factories.
This is why the villain in the film Jawan
openly tells foreign investors in the film
to invest their money in winning elections,
to invest in donating to the parties,
so that they will get the freedom to do anything in India.
To set up as many factories as they want,
to use as much cheap labour as they want,
to spread pollution and waste,
and no one would care.
The villain of the film also says that
India's environmental regulations are very favourable
for big companies.
In other developed countries, there are a lot of restrictions
that are not there in India.
For example, some pesticides are banned in other countries
but are allowed in India.
The Supreme Court was hearing a petition
demanding a ban on 116 dangerous pesticides.
In 2013 the Anupam Verma Committee was constituted
to investigate these dangerous pesticides.
This committee reviewed only 66 pesticides
and submitted its report to the government in 2015.
But the government remained inactive for years
and when the government took action in 2018,
only 12 pesticides were banned by the government.
And it said that 6 other dangerous pesticides would be slowly phased out.
Out of the 116 dangerous pesticides,
they took steps to ban only 18.
After this, another committee was formed under SK Malhotra
in which some more pesticides were to be reviewed.
This committee in 2020 said that
27 pesticides should be banned in India.
In 2022, the government formed another committee.
And what action did that committee take?
Only 3 pesticides were banned.
That too in February 2023.
So now you can understand the attitude of the government.
They are not worried about the citizens
but about the crony capitalists.
If they ban any more pesticides,
then the business of these billionaires will be affected.
They should not have to bear the loss.
In July 2023, the Supreme Court questioned the government.
The Supreme Court said that whenever a committee issues a report,
instead of taking action on that report,
the government makes a second committee.
Why is it so difficult
to ban these dangerous pesticides
which are already banned in other countries?
After this, we can talk about food safety regulations.
Look at this 2017 news.
Experts say that poultry farms in India
are using antibiotics.
Antibiotics are being given to hens in such heavy doses that
this antibiotic resistance is reaching humans.
This means that if humans catch a disease
that has become antibiotic-resistant,
then the antibiotics will not help these humans.
After this, the government did something good here
in 2017, they set a permissible limit
on how much antibiotics can be given to hens.
But look at this news from 2018.
"India's farmed chickens
are dosed with the world's strongest antibiotics."
This study was done by the Bureau of Investigative Journalism
which found that a last resort antibiotic, Colistin,
is being given in heavy doses to many chickens in India.
Only in 2019, the Union Health Ministries took action on it
and banned this antibiotic.
So, even where action is being taken,
they are waiting for a report first,
only then any action is taken.
This should tell you the importance of free media.
If all the media in a country has been turned into political representatives,
then such reports will not be published
and the government will never have to take any action.
Without these reports, the government
never takes any action on these things.
Compare it with other countries.
The European Union banned antibiotics
from being used in animal feed in 2006.
They took action so many years ago.
This year, in January, the European Union
came out with a new legislation
which has banned all kinds of antibiotics in farming.
And they have also banned
meat that has antibiotics in it
being imported from foreign countries to the European Union.
Now see how these multinational food companies
take advantage of the indifference of the Indian government.
In 2017, KFC was praised in America
because they committed not to use antibiotics in their chicken.
In the same year, Burger King, McDonald's, Pizza Hut, and Taco Bell,
all took this pledge.
There will be no antibiotics in their chicken.
But did any of these fast food companies
make such a commitment in India?
Center for Science and Environment
reached out to these companies in 2020
and they did not respond to this issue.
In the movie Jawan, it is also shown how
the government forgives the bad loans of these billionaires.
If you want to compare it with real life,
see this news from just last month.
The Minister of State for Finance told the Lok Sabha,
that in the last 9 years, the banks
have written off ₹14.56 trillion in NPAs.
More than half of these were owed by large corporates.
And when the banks try to recover these loans,
the banks are unable to recover the entire amount.
Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman
told the Rajya Sabha this year in March
that in the last 5 years, the public sector banks
could recover only 14% of the written-off loans.
Apart from these NPS, there are cases of such billionaires
who have taken loans from banks
and fled the country.
Like Vijay Mallya, Nirav Modi, and Mehul Choksi.
The film Jawan drew an interesting comparison
of loan write-offs for these billionaires and crony capitalists.
And the loans owed by common farmers in the country.
Look at this India Spend report of 2019.
The cost of the top 12 corporate NPAs
is twice as much as compared to farm loan waivers.
Between FY 2017-18 and February 2019,
10 state governments issued farm loan waivers
whose total amount was ₹1.848 billion.
But the top 12 NPAs,
their total amount is almost twice this.
At ₹3.45 billion.
And when the farmers' loan is waived,
there is another big difference.
If the farmer is unable to repay his loan,
he often commits s____de.
But these billionaires,
have you ever heard that they committed s____de
because they couldn't repay their loans?
There is a very powerful scene related to this in Jawan.
I won't talk much about it.
If you have seen the film, you will understand
what I am talking about.
When a farmer takes a loan,
it affects his life entirely.
If you see just one year, in 2021,
more than 10,000 people committed s____de in the farm sector.
The number shown in the film was quite shocking.
But the number in real life is close to it.
There are farmers in our country that earn substantially.
They should be seen as positive examples
so that other farmers can learn from them.
Watch this video of Down to Earth.
How can a small farmer earn ₹1.5 million?
Or watch this video featuring Padma Shree awardee Bharat Bhushan Tyagi
which shows how a farmer earns more
than ₹500,000 per acre annually.
Or you can read this article of The Better India
which shows the story of a farmer Raju Titus.
All these farmers can earn so much money
because they follow the NFC model.
NFC means Nature Farmer Consumer.
There may be some minor differences,
but what do these farmers do in general?
Number 1, seed preservation.
They preserve the seeds in seed banks.
They are often members of friendly seed banks.
Number 2, they do not use chemical fertilizers.
Instead, they restore soil fertility
by planting cover crops in between the cash crops.
This increases microbial activity in the soil
and increases nitrogen availability.
And such farmers often use a compost pit for manure.
Number 3, they often get their soil tested in local labs
to find out the most suitable crop to grow in the soil.
They also practice crop rotation.
Number 4. Monoculture.
Instead of planting one type of crop,
they carry out intercropping.
Multiple crops in one field
That would support each other.
Number 5. They do multi-layer farming.
3 to 4 crops are grown on the same field at different heights.
For example, coconut, coffee, and black pepper
can be a combination.
Or maize, green gram and ground nut
can be another combination.
Next, they don't use a tractor.
They often use no-till farming techniques.
And they don't use flood irrigation either.
Instead, they use techniques like sprinkler irrigation or drip irrigation.
And instead of using pesticides and insecticides,
they use marigolds, garlic or bright-coloured sheets.
Next, they follow the practice of mulching.
They cover the remaining area with organic matter
so that weeds can be suppressed
and that water can be retained in the ground.
And finally, these people don't dump their produce in the market.
Instead, they are organised in cooperatives
and reach the consumers directly.
They don't let middlemen in.
This is an amazing model in which
the farmer is happy, the consumer is happy,
and the environment is also happy.
But this model is used rarely
because most of the people who are practising this model
are educated and intelligent.
However, poor farmers use the corporate model of farming.
They buy seeds, fertilizers, insecticides,
pesticides, and tractors.
They use diesel to run the tube well.
They rent a harvesting machine.
They burn the leftover stubble
which causes air pollution.
As time goes by, their soil becomes less fertile.
So they keep adding more fertilizers to it.
And in the end, they dump all their stuff in the market.
Often, they take a loan for a tractor as well.
And their crop often gets destroyed during the rains.
This model is very expensive.
The revenue for the farmers is meagre.
And it has a bad impact on the environment.
And because these corporate companies work like middlemen,
the consumers have to pay a high price.
And most of the profits are taken by these companies in the middle.
These companies that make tractors,
fertilizers, and insecticides,
are billion-dollar companies.
And often, the profits cannot reach these farmers
because this knowledge has not reached most of the farmers.
The government had promised that by 2022,
they would double the farmers' income.
But it's 2023
and the farmers are in the same condition.
A while ago, the government tried to bring in 3 unfavourable laws
which would have increased the corporate income.
But thankfully, it didn't pass.
What should the government do?
Educate the farmers.
To inform the farmers which models they should adopt.
What they should be doing to maintain their livelihood.
If there is a political will,
the government can bring down these farmer s____des to zero.
But will this happen?
Or will the YouTubers have to educate the farmers?
Only time will tell.
If you liked the video, do keep these
issues in mind while watching the film.
And if you liked the video, you can click here
to watch the video on the Bhopal Gas Tragedy.
See you in the next video.
Thank you very much!