- Chris and Chandler both have five lives
and every time they laugh in
this video, they lose one.
- I don't wanna die.
- I'm not laughing.
- And whoever has the most
lives at the end of this video,
move, wins whatever's in this briefcase.
- What's inside it, Jimmy?
- It's an amazing,
super expensive, insane,
one of kind prize that you wanna win.
- I wanna win it. He said it. I want it.
- Yo.
- Stop.
- She just said stop like it was okay.
- He said no.
- Bro, we're trying to free you.
- Oof.
Oh, wait, what?
- Bill!
- How many drinks are in there?
- Wow.
- I'm trying so hard not to laugh.
- Let it out.
- Oh, I've seen this.
Let.
- You thought.
- Seen that one.
- This is my impression of 40th president
of the United States, Ronald Reagan,
attempting to communicate
through the mortal coil
but the only open channel
is through your Wiimote.
Well I'm in hell.
- All right, we got Chandler for sure.
- There was so oddly specific
and it really did
actually sound like that.
- Both the boys lost
life, we must continue.
- See, yeah, this is funny.
Can't even eat in Ohio, bro.
What is going on in Ohio right now?
- Oh my gosh.
When your husband asks to bring home
a piece of cake from the
neighbor's kid's birthday.
Ha.
- Oh.
- Oh okay, I like that.
- That's not funny, that's painful.
- She better wake up
right now, I'm so hungry.
- Ain't no way she's falling asleep.
- That's why you should
eat at Beast Burger
instead of Subway.
- That's not funny.
- Don't laugh.
- Oh.
- Walt, was it a laugh?
- Yes.
- According to referee Walt,
they both just lost another life.
- Can we ask the committee to review that?
- Sure.
- Can you guys review that?
- No.
- Argh, prick.
That's how I feel right now
'cause I was trying to
make Chandler laugh.
- Wait, show me what to do.
- No I'm not gonna do
it now, I'm not dumb.
Go away, ew, ew.
- Brayden, go back in your bed.
- What you doing if Tucker pulls that?
- We're gonna have to go
sit down with a therapist
and have a long conversation
about how we deal with emotions.
Are you okay, buddy?
You doing all right?
Talk, say something, react,
it's a reacts channel.
- I'll cry.
- I'm here.
- Oh my god, Mike Tyson would
love that pigeon though.
- Look at his eye.
- We just witnessed a murder.
Good thing they paused it.
- If they didn't pause it we would've seen
something bad happen.
- Well something would've
happened to that bird.
But since they paused it, the bird's fine.
- I actually said this to Chris.
- Yeah you're gonna have to do better.
- I accurately found what you guys like.
He sent it you 'cause you liked it.
- Here's the thing, the
one we saw originally,
there's a change, it said,
"What going on in Ohio."
- Bring up Ohio at the end of the video.
- Hey, what are you doing in here?
I said don't come in here
when we're recording.
- Oh, that was a scam.
- That had to have been fake, right?
- That was, of course, fake.
- Oh Jesus.
- Have no fear, Spiderman is here.
- Damn.
Tom Holland got a little less attractive.
- What happened?
- I was bitten by a regular spider.
- A radial spider.
- I have the power of
minutes left to live.
- Hundreds gather today to
say their final goodbyes
to this fallen Louisville police officer,
Dee Dee Mega Doo Doo.
- Chandler has officially taken the lead.
Come up here.
Hey, you can laugh now.
- Oh my God, she didn't realize it
'til after she said it.
God damn, what was the name?
- She's crazy.
- Chandler, it is now your game to lose.
Are you gonna rise to the
occasion or are you gonna laugh?
If you laugh, you lose.
- All right, I'm never laughing.
- If Jimmy was doing these
videos, he would lose.
Jimmy laughs at literally everything.
The goat's a nice touch.
That guy's muscular.
That guy's not.
- Beans.
- But good for him.
- Oh he missed the trick.
You can't even break your board?
- Can't even break his board.
- Oh!
What is this kid doing?
- Oh.
- Why did the other one throw up?
- What?
- It's a little German kid,
little German kids are hilarious.
Yippee!
Good, harder, more aggressive.
- Cat, this is what you were made to do.
- You can't throw a brick, it's too heavy.
But a can of soup, you can really put
some power into that, right?
- Did he say that?
- You didn't know that?
- No.
- And this soup is just for my family,
it's just for my family.
- Ah!
- What are you so mad about,
you little sucker?
- Let's see if the snake gets him.
- What'd he say?
- He bunked it.
- These are very southern memes.
- This a red neck thing?
That was on purpose.
- Yeah that was a little staged.
- If I shoot you, you're in the clan.
- Please, please, please, please,
please, please, please, please,
please, please, please, please.
- Does he make it?
- Sorry, you didn't make it the clan.
- Oh.
- I love those videos.
- Is it gonna lift?
- Refried beans.
- Oh my gosh.
- Beautiful.
- I didn't know that was a thing.
I want it.
- Oh, that's.
I laughed.
- He did laugh.
- Wait, did he laugh?
Play it back.
- Oh, that's.
- It is now tied 2-2, hey,
screw what you're gonna say
about that.
- Wait, wait, wait,
tutu is what a ballerina wears.
- But the score's also 2 to 2.
- Hey, you got a napkin?
- Yeah I got you.
- Why is he so close?
- That's probably one of
the best ones I've seen.
- Thank you.
- That one was really good.
- Gosh, that's hard, this is so hard.
- Banana.
- Is he playing the-
- Whoa!
- Is the kid farting the whole way?
- He was, he was farting the whole way.
- What are the rules, Walt?
Huh? Was there no laughing on that?
- Walt, was there a laugh?
- Chris laughed.
- It was a little walking fart.
- That little walking
fart brought you down
to your last life.
- I don't wanna die, Jimmy.
- Then stop laughing.
You know what happens when you die?
- I can't go to Ohio?
- No.
- Ooh, collect his loot?
- That was so hard not to laugh at.
- Take a look at this nice break
and a little love tap on the ten pin.
- Little love tap.
- Chris via just feeding it out to that
4 5 board down lane
- Beautiful.
- And look at this pin action.
Oh.
- Ooh.
- Oh.
Countries whose leaders pooped
themselves in McDonald's.
- Who did that?
- That was good.
- Are you a cowboy?
- Aw, no way, I just laughed.
- He laughed so he loses.
- Walt, laugh?
- Now you both have one life.
- Does neither of you
want the super secret
one of a kind original
crazy prize behind you?
- Is it Mucinex 'cause I'm sick?
- It's better than curing all
the diseases on the planet.
- I don't know if I'd say that.
- It is.
Whoever loses will regret
it 'til the day they die.
- Oh gosh, I'm never laughing.
- My parents making sure
10 year old me is asleep.
- Me playing my Game Boy Advance.
- What they see.
- I've seen this.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- All right, why we looking at the coach?
- Go.
- You got it, kid.
What if he just punches him?
Is he going the wrong way?
- What are you doing?
Give me that.
- Okay, I haven't done
this since I was a kid.
- Oh my gosh.
- What's in your hand?
- It's a harmonica, mama.
- What happened to my vase?
- Oh.
- Yes! He did it.
- Oh, Chris officially lost
- He tried to play it off.
- His final laugh.
Chandler, are you ready for
your one of a kind prize?
- I'm ready.
- What do you think's in here?
- 20 grand.
- A trip to Ohio.
- Yes!
Ohio!
- Pre-paid tickets to Ohio.
We have an Ohio shirt, an Ohio hat,
we got some Ohio bumper stickers
to go along with your tickets to Ohio.
- I'm actually kinda glad I lost.
- How excited are you?
- This is not 20 grand.
- See you in the next video.
- Subscribe if you wanna go to Ohio.