- I tied up an FBI agent.
(words pop)
If he steals this hundred
thousand dollars from me
before midnight, he keeps it.
This is a knife.
Good luck. Let's go, Tareq.
- [The Boys] Oh, oh, what do we do?
- [Tareq] Oh my gosh, we gotta go.
- [Jimmy] Tareq, our first
stop's through the woods.
- [Tareq] Jimmy, why are we
doing this again already?
- Relax for one second.
I've been tied up before.
- [Chris] He's getting
so much time ahead of us.
- [Jimmy] We're coming out
the other side of the woods.
Our getaway car is over here.
- [Tareq] Whoa, that's a nice car, Jim.
- [Jimmy] The car matches my bag.
- [Tareq] We gotta go. We gotta go.
- [Chris] How are you gonna catch him
if your hands are tied?
- And now we drive down this path.
You guys have no idea what I
have in store for the boys.
I rented an NFL football
stadium, an island, a maze,
and tons of other cool things.
And stop!
- [Tareq] Oh! Why are we stopping already?
- Just watch.
You see this giant telephone pole?
- [Tareq] Uh huh.
- Watch this.
- [Tareq] Oh, oh, oh my gosh-
- Let's get back in the car.
(car revving)
- Buckle up.
- Now there's a giant telephone
pole blocking the exit.
- [The Boys] Oh.
- Oh, here we go.
- [The Boys] Hurry.
- Grab on. Push it over.
- Ohh!
- Push go.
- [Karl] Guys, hurry up!
- We put a GPS in my underwear
so the FBI agent and the boys
will always know where I'm at.
- [Nolan] Jimmy turned.
- [Chris] Oh, wait, he turned?
- [Nolan] He turned left.
- If you zoom in-
- It's a maze!
It gives us the layout of the maze.
- We're now at the Hedge Maze
and I got the hundred thousand dollars.
Look at how huge this maze is.
We gotta be careful because
it'd be easy to get lost
and for them to catch us in here.
- [Jimmy] Uh, I think it's this way.
- [Tareq] Okay...Uh, how do you know?
- I've done this maze like 10 times,
but the boys have never been here.
- We're just gonna push him and push him,
get him out of the area,
and then as he's tiring,
we'll handle this.
- I'm gonna leave them some money here
so they know they're going the right way.
Or a random person's
just gonna find a grand.
(Jimmy chuckles)
- [The Boys] Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
- [Nolan] It says open 11 to five.
- [Kurt] See if we can
actually get right through it.
- [Chris] Ooh.
- [Kurt] Here we go.
- [Jimmy] It was right,
right, left, right,
left, right, right, left.
Perfect. Okay.
If you're in the cave,
you're in the right spot,
which means if we go here,
now we are officially in the watch tower.
We can see the entire maze.
- I'm gonna do a perimeter check.
Make sure he is not outside.
We gotta find the getaway car.
- Hey Karl, come on.
- There's that nerd.
- Hey, there he is!
- Ooh!
- Okay!
- [Jimmy] I bet you can't get me.
- Ooh. The only exit is right here.
- [Chris] Why is there money over here?
- That was just to let you know
you were going the right way.
- [Chris] Jimmy, we're almost there.
Just wait.
- Oh, they are getting close.
Shoot, okay. We gotta go, we gotta go.
They're getting closer.
I don't know how long I
planned on staying there.
(Tareq laughs)
- [Chris] He's older than us,
but he's got so much more energy.
Isn't this where Jimmy was?
- [Kurt] Yes, it was.
- I know you're looking at this, Jimmy.
I'm taking your camera now.
- The only exit outside
of this entire maze
is all the way up there,
which is why yesterday
we put in a secret door.
- [Tareq] Oh wow. Jimmy, this is crazy.
Wait, Jimmy, is that our getaway car?
- Notice how this says,
"Authorized Maze Personnel Only".
Now it says, "Jimmy's Getaway Car".
- [Kurt] Hey guys, let's
go back to the car.
The tracker's showing him up on the hill.
- [Karl] All right. To the car!
- [The Boys] Let's go!
- [Kurt] Let's go-
- [Karl] Go, go, go, go, go.
- [Nolan] Get in.
- I wonder if they've noticed
we're not in the maze anymore.
- [Nolan] He's getting on the highway.
- [Chris] Which way? Left or right?
- Right.
- We can make all the
mistakes in the world-
- Doesn't matter-
- He's just gotta make one-
- He gotta make one.
- Yeah.
- Yo, there were parts where
we were so close to them
in the maze.
That was terrifying.
If they would've caught us there,
this video would've been
only like two minutes.
I made a mistake.
Tareq's supposed to be
driving. Let's switch.
- [Tareq] Let's switch.
- Karl is the, is that money real?
- Oh, it's real real.
- Oh good.
(boys laughing)
- And the reason Tareq is driving,
is because I need to put on a disguise.
(soft, exciting music)
I look so old.
Now we put the hat on, throw
on a pair of glasses, and boom.
I'm Boomer Jim.
And we're heading to Walmart
where I'm gonna try to
blend in with normal people.
- Do you think he went to the mall to shop
and we all go shopping?
- We're pulling up to Walmart
and I'm gonna go inside
with the hundred thousand
dollars and the tracker.
There's a pickax back here.
And while they're inside searching for me,
you need to pop all the tires
on their car to strand them.
- Jimmy, I've never
popped a tire in my life.
- Let's do this.
- [Chris] Wait. It says
we're on top of him-
- [The Boys] Hey!
- [Kurt] Yeah. It says
we're right on top of him-
- Take a, take a right down here-
- [Karl] He's right here.
- Don't let me down
with popping the tires.
- [Tareq] I won't. God speed.
- Park away from cars and
let's assess the situation.
- And now I'm inside Walmart.
And before I blend in, I
need to disguise this bag.
Now I'm gonna take the hundred
thousand dollar backpack
and put it in this bag.
Now they'll never catch me.
- You and I will go inside.
You two stay, stay together.
And let's see if we can search 'em out.
Inside! Hold his hand, there ya go.
- We're staying together.
(phone ringing)
- Are they here yet?
- They're walking out right
now. They're going inside.
- All right. They're going inside?
- Yes, yes, yes.
(phone call ends)
- The boys are about to
come inside. We gotta go.
- [Tareq] They have no idea
I'm gonna smash all their tires.
Look at 'em running.
- [Chris] Looking for a six foot four guy,
with a weird beard.
- I can literally see the boys
walking down the gaming aisle.
- I know that Jimmy told
me to pop all the tires,
but I'm just gonna do one.
Cuz I think I'm running low on time.
FBI? More like, FB flat tire!
(air hissing)
(Tareq running)
Oh, I gotta get the camera.
- He's not walking around
anywhere. He's gotta be hiding.
(phone ringing)
- [Jimmy] Did you do the deed?
- The deed is done.
- They're so close to me.
I'm getting outta here.
- [Tareq] Hurry up, grandpa.
- I can't believe that worked.
They were literally one
aisle beside me at one point.
- What's the tracker say?
- [Kurt] The tracker's
moving. The vehicle's moved.
- Wait, it's moving?
- In the parking lot?
- He's outta the...he's outta Walmart?
- It feels amazing to have that mask off.
We've knocked over a telephone pole,
had a goose chase through a maze,
and then hid in a Walmart as an old man.
And the video's just getting started.
I have so much more cool stuff planned.
Like I'm literally heading to the airport
to board a private jet right now.
- Wait a second!
- What's that?
Who popped our tires?
There's a pickax in our tire.
- Well, if we don't have a
car, we're gonna change a flat.
- [Nolan] Do you know
how to change a tire?
- Of course I know how to change a tire.
- [Chris] Remember you wanna go two or-
(car falling)
Yeah. That's why I don't like those jacks.
- [Kurt] Yep.
- Karl?
- [Karl] Yeah?
- Do you know where I
was hiding at Walmart?
- No!
- Basically I put on an old man suit,
changed my clothes, and used a cane.
Did you see a really old guy limping?
- I don't pay attention to old people.
- Well if you did see one
in Walmart, it was me.
Good luck, nerd!
(phone call ends)
- Brah!
(Chris groaning)
- [Nolan] Chris, you working hard?
- [Chris] You're hardly working.
- We're getting close to the airport.
I'm gonna call the private jet
and make sure they're ready.
- It looks like he's on a taxiing runway.
- He's gonna get in a plane and fly away.
- This is why he slashed the tires.
- And there's our private jet. Let's go.
I'm getting on a private
jet with the dumbest outfit
and a Cars backpack.
What am I doing with my life?
Come on. You're taking forever.
I'm gonna try to time it where
the private jet takes off
when they get here so they
can see me flying away.
- What's up, Jimmy?
- Hey buddy. How far away are you?
- We're at the Walmart
man. Still fixing the tire.
- Okay. Well-
- Hey Jimmy, if you had to
pick a terminal to go into,
would it be the passenger terminal?-
- Oh, so that means you're here.
Pilot, you can take off.
- [Chris] Run, run, run.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
(upbeat music)
- [Kurt] Last door.
- Later, nerds.
- That's him.
That's him on that jet right there.
- [Karl] Dude!
- I have no idea how they're
gonna track where we're going.
- We're gonna follow the airplane.
Let's check inside where it's going.
- Can we just do that?
- Yes. Why not?
- Oh. I guess he is FBI.
- How you doing? FBI.
Where did the airplane that
just left, where is it going?
- Uh. Washington, D.C..
(boys gasp)
- [The Boys] What!
- Wonderful.
- Is there another flight
to Washington, D.C.?
- [Kurt] Anytime soon.
- I don't see anything today. No.
- Do we have to drive all
the way to Washington, D.C.?
That's like-
- Hey, at least we got-
- Three hours!
- We gotta, we gotta new
tire for it. So we're good.
- New tire. Let's go.
- Private jet with stacks of money?
For the first time ever, I
actually feel like a YouTuber.
And now we're in Washington, D.C..
We got about a three hour lead.
And conveniently our driver is Nick.
You might remember him from this video.
He's so much nicer when
he's not chasing me.
- Ha ha! You ready to get outta here?
- Let's go.
- Guys! He just landed in D.C..
- [Chris] What?
- [Karl] Actually?
- [Nolan] Yeah.
- That's over two hours away now still.
- Are we finally in Washington, D.C.?
- Holy cow-
- What does it say-
- Wait, Washington the state?
Cuz that would suck.
- And now we're at our
next location; the U-Store.
So like we talked about on the phone,
distract the boys, okay?
- Okay.
- He's right beside Costa Rica trading.
Whatever that is, it's right beside it.
- I just bought this storage locker
and I'm gonna put this sign
right here with this message:
"Time is running out. I was in the box."
If that doesn't make any sense,
just gimme a few seconds.
- Maybe we can approach from the back.
- Hey, I tried that
with your mom one time.
(boys laughing)
- Me and you are gonna
hide in these boxes.
We're literally about
to get shipped alive.
- Jimmy, what is this?
What do you have me doing bro?
- Oh, that was probably
the worst drive ever.
- Ahhh!
- Karl. You stay here
and watch the vehicle.
Make sure no one pops our tire again.
- I'll sit right here.
- [The Boys] You're standing.
- I'm wondering if you've
seen this individual.
- Oh yeah, I saw him.
- Still around here?
- Yeah. I think he's downstairs.
Let me take you there.
- Downstairs!
- Downstairs?
- Should we just be
following random people
to their basement?
Is this okay?
I just don't understand why
all this is necessary, Jimmy.
- Let me get something to cut it.
Can you wait for me here, sir?
- Yeah.
- That truck you see
right here is my getaway.
I'm being transported right now.
Karl was right above us.
- Holy crap.
(blade cutting)
- [The Boys] This is so extra!
Hey, here we go.
- [Chris] "Time is
running out. Karl sucks.
I was in the box."
- Hey, hey. Check the tracker right now.
- [Chris] We're gonna have to go upstairs
to get service, to check.
- Are we free to get out?
- [Tareq] Um. Hold on. Not yet.
- I got Jimmy right here. He's gone.
He's long gone-
- Here's the thing.
There was a box truck when we got here.
He's gone in the box truck!
- [Karl] Guys! Where have you been?
- Come on. We just gotta go.
- I can't believe that worked.
Up next, we're going to a private island.
- Jimmy looks like he's crossed a bridge
and now going to a boathouse.
- Oh my goodness.
So we got a plane, a boat, a box truck.
What else is he gonna do?
- Thanks for the trip. Have a good day.
Even though that was really cool.
The box truck moves incredibly slow,
so they could be here any second.
What's up, man?
You ready to take us to the island?
Let's do this.
- Jimmy's calling. What's up, Jimmy?
- [Jimmy] Okay. What up, Chris?
Hey, how's it going?
You getting in a boat?
- No, actually I'm not.
- That's a nice pier you're at.
- Wait. Where are you?
- Maybe we might be about to
tackle you in about 10 seconds-
- Maybe I'm under-
- I hung up.
Look now we're turning the tables.
He thinks we're right
by him and we're not!
- Wait. I was calling him
to brag about the boxes,
but now I'm confused.
- [Karl] There are so many
boats here. What is going on?
- All right. There he is go, go, go, go.
- [Tareq] That's Karl. That's Karl.
- You nerd!
- [Tareq] They're coming!
- [Jimmy] Go, go, go.
- [Tareq] They're coming in strong.
- I got you some swan boats.
- It's always boats with you.
- Hey, get to pedaling
on your little swan.
- We'll go after him-
- Go.
- Go!
- We'll get in the next one.
- I'm gonna be honest.
I never tested those swans.
For all I know, they could be really fast.
- Wow. This is slow.
This is unreasonably slow.
- Did you ever chase
anyone on a swan before?
- This will be a first.
`- I'm gonna act like the boat broke.
Hey, Karl!
- Yes?
- My boat isn't working.
So I'd hurry up.
- His boat's broken.
Here's our chance. Hurry!
(boys grunting)
- This is the most
anti-climatic thing ever.
- [Tareq] Yeah.
- You got four hours left
until I keep the hundred grand.
See you later.
- You'll pay!
- And now we're at the island.
Hurry up, nerds!
- Come on over, let's talk.
The sun's not even down yet, my friend.
- They just docked.
- [Tareq] Go, go, go, go. They're close!
- [Chris] Hey, come on, guys.
- [Kurt] You're going right in.
You're fine.
- What the heck are we doing?
- I think we're lost.
We went the wrong way.
Oh where do we go? Please help us.
Help us. Help us.
We asked some people
on the island for help.
Cause to be honest, I'm lost.
- [Tareq] Me too.
- Jimmy, I will end you!
We're stuck. We're lost.
(indistinct)
Now we found a path. This has
to be where Jimmy's going.
- I only have three more hours here.
We need to get going here.
He's on the other side of the island.
- We make it outta here
without getting found,
then we're finally going
to the NFL stadium.
Are you subscribed?
- Uh yeah.
- [Tareq] Jimmy we don't have time.
- We always have time for this.
- [Tareq] That's fair.
- I don't care to fact check
you. Here's some money.
- Uh what?
- Thanks for subscribing. Now
I gotta run to regain my time.
- [Tareq] Yes!
- Guys?
What!
Kurt. There's nothing.
- We made it off the island
to our getaway vehicle.
And now it's time for my
favorite part of the video.
We're heading to an NFL
stadium that I rented.
- We should have never got on this island.
- Let's see where he is now.
- [The Boys] Oh, he's still driving?
- He's going towards Capitol Hill.
- I can't believe we rented
an entire NFL stadium.
Look at how huge this place is!
This is gonna be so much fun.
- [Karl] Let's get to our car. Come on.
We have like two hours left.
- I hate to break the bad news to you,
but it ain't a spa.
- What is it?
- A football stadium.
- He's at a football stadium?
- That sounds like running...
- I have a pre-recorded
video of me on loop
telling them they'll never find me.
"You'll never find me in this stadium.
Losers."
Isn't that so funny?
And not only do I have
that video playing on loop,
but I've filled the
stadium with mannequins
so they'll think it's me.
They literally only have
two and a half hours left
to get this money.
- Let's go, go, go, go, go.
- Did he just rent an entire stadium?
Unbelievable. Let's see where he is.
So we have, he looks
like he's in the center.
- Wait, Jimmy's on the TV!
- [Chris] Aw.
- [Kurt] Oh no.
- [Chris] Come on.
- All right, I think
that's a little too much.
- Oh, he tortured me for a whole day here.
- Let's go get him.
- Can we go catch him?
- [Jimmy] "You'll never
find me in this stadium-
- Holy cow.
- "You'll never find me-
- [Kurt] Oh my Lord.
- [Nolan] Look at all the mannequins!
- As you can see, the boys
just walked into the stadium.
They're probably so confused.
Can you cut the audio for me please?
"You'll never find me in this stadium."
Wait for it...
Boom. Now the audio's off. It's my time.
- How did this man-
- [Jimmy] Hello, boys.
- Hello?
- As you can see, there
is over 70,000 seats
and unlimited rooms in this stadium.
I need you guys to expect the unexpected.
Cuz, I could literally be anywhere.
And don't forget; you literally
only have two hours left
to win this hundred thousand dollars.
Good luck!
- This place is huge!
- What a jerk-
- Oh also, Karl's a nerd.
- [Karl] Stop man! What the heck!
(Jimmy laughing)
- Yo, this is so much fun.
- Hey, hey! I saw movement in that window-
- [Chris] He has to be in a box
where he can reach this mic-
- I swear I just saw movement.
- Nolan, what are you pointing at?
- I saw you! I saw movement!
- Wait, where is he pointing?
Turn to your left a little bit.
- I see him!
Run!
- [Chris] I told you he was in a box.
- And now they're coming
straight towards us.
- [Tareq] Why'd you do this?
- We should probably move.
- [Tareq] We should go.
(Tareq and Jimmy laughing)
- [Chris] He's on the run!
- And now we're heading out the back way.
And the cool part is, they
don't know what the back way is.
Good luck, nerds. I believe in you.
- Hey guys, over here!
- He just called the boys!
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
- Second level. He is moving around.
- [Nolan] Kurt!
- He's going that way.
- [Nolan] How do we get up there?
- This way! Escalators.
- [Jimmy] Let's go up.
- [Tareq] Let's just go up?
- [Nolan] Oh no! They're not working!
(intense music)
That's Jimmy!
- [Jimmy] It's Nolan!
- Hurry, it's Jimmy!
- Tareq! Sacrifice yourself!
- [Tareq] Sacrifice myself?
- Yeah.
- [Tareq] He went that way.
- [Nolan] No, he didn't, there's a door!
Get out of the way, Tareq!
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
- Here's my strategy.
I'm gonna go fake pose like a mannequin
and pray they don't find me
for the next hour and a half.
Okay?
They've seen what I'm wearing.
So I'm gonna steal this
mannequins clothes.
Do I look like a mannequin?
- Jimmy, come on out and play.
- I know he's one of the
mannequins over there.
Let's pretend like we don't know that.
These stupid mannequins, man.
Where is this nerd?
- [Chris] If I was Jimmy,
where would I hide?
- [Nolan] Kurt? Kurt.
- [Tareq] Jimmy, go, go, go, go.
- [The Boys] Yes! Let's go!
- Honestly, I've been
running for like 14 hours.
When he was right there, I was like,
I don't feel like getting tackled.
He can just have the money.
What are you gonna spend
the hundred grand on?
- I'm gonna spend it on my wife.
- Really?
- I'm gonna make sure that
my family is enjoys it.
- Aw-
- that's the important thing-
- That's really sweet.
- One of the best
experiences I've ever had.
- In our last video, I mentioned
that every single person
that buys this executive
producer shirt or hoodie
will get their name at
the end of this video,
which is why you see names on
the left side of your screen.
Because that is every single person
that purchased this shirt or hoodie.
And I didn't tell you
guys I would do this,
but on top of that,
we also wrote every
single one of your names
on the wall of my studio.
Literally every day,
when I come in to film,
I'm gonna see your name on this wall.
Like Peter Wild, when I film,
I'm gonna be reminded of you.
And same with Knox and
Knox Tucker and Koda
and Koda G and all these Michaels.
And on top of that,
Chandler, bring it on in.
I also got all your
names put on this Tesla.
That's right. Not only are all
your names on my studio wall,
but your names are also on this Tesla.
And this is the fun part.
Chandler, I want you to pick
a random name on this Tesla
and we're gonna give it to
them in like 30 seconds.
All right, let's do it.
Matt Liggett.
- [Jimmy] What about him?
- [Chandler] He didn't win.
- [Jimmy] Oh, he didn't win?
Well, tell me when you have the winner.
- Hey Jimmy, you have
Peyton Chicken Nugget
as one of your fans.
- Can you investigate that?
See if that's their real name.
- I'm thinking probably not.
- Derpyfish, 89.
I told you to use your real name,
but I didn't actually fact check it.
You go in the S category.
There's a bunch of Sponge Bobs.
And I know your names aren't SpongeBob.
- Jimmy!
- Yeah?
- Tell me when to stop.
- Uh, wait for it, now stop.
- Oh. Which finger?
- I'm a pinky kinda guy.
- Alexander Hedge, this Tesla...
- [The Boys] Yeah! All right-
- I don't know if that made any sense.
Congratulations, Alexander.
You just won a brand new Tesla.
Sorry that it's covered in names.
If you want, you can remove 'em.
Thank you so much.
Subscribe.
(fire exploding)