guys, this is our third episode.
For unboxing the merchandise of your favorite
youtubers sold by them.
Here, i have the overlays box.
Since, I started unboxing on this channel.
many people commented things like these:
i speak in tech burner's style.
i talk like a tech burner.
Don't copy tech burner.
And one person keeps commenting on each video:
Tech burner's of men fashion.
but on a true note, your any comment does
not hurt me.
bcoz, if you attach gangadhar with truth
then it will become shaktiman only.
it's a compliment!
in the box of overlays, you will get its brand
name on the top.
thier logo!
with the website name!
www.
overlaysclothing.com
here its written: Unbox the desire.
nothing else.
The box is made of cardboard.
looks like a very sustainable material.
afterwards, you can use at is as a gift wrap
for your relatives.
After you open the box, you get to see burnt
hakka noodles.
a card from team overlays and the rest you
can read over here.
you get a tag of overlays on the t-shirt with
a piece of paper that is cut and stuck on
it.
the colour of the t-shirt is white with no
design, its a solid t-shirt.
now, lets talk about the fabric because this
is the only thing that makes this t-shirt
unique.
the fabric is cotton and is known as waffled-
textured cotton.
this means that the entire body of the t-shirt
is made like waffles.
if you have eaten a waffle or not, it looks
like this:
the pattern is like this:
similarly, the pattern is made.
The first thing is, that it is very breathable.
literally, if you look like this, you have
got many see-through holes.
this makes a lot of air to come in and makes
you comfortable.
you can use it as a channi for karwachauth
also when your spouse dont get a channi!
your karwachauth will be complete!
this t-shirt is very stretchable bringing
squeeziness inside your body.
the cloth grabs your body.
out of hundred things, the cloth looks definitely
premium.
looking down you get a patch of brand overlays.
i found 2 to 3 things missing in this t-shirt,
which i will tell you later on.
talking about the look, it is white suits
for very occassion, time and season.
just looks perfect!
so here we have the next tshirt!
if you remember, overlay's first launch!
in that overlays,
hypily the word "supima cotton usage'" was
used.
world's finest cotton was being used.
so continuing that thing, these fabrics are
also designed in the same way.
that waffle one was not the supima cotton.
first of all, if you purchase this t-shirt,
the first thing you will feel is the weight
of this t-shirt.
compared to other t-shirts which you shop
around from other brands..
the t shirt is very heavy and the thickness
of
and the quaity of the cloth is very nice.
the same tag is present over here.
The name of the t-shirt is a variant white
and black oversized t-shirt.
the price written over here is 1699, which
means 1700 is the mrp.
it is sold nearby to thousand rupees.
it is also a full white t shirt in the front.
but the designing in the corners and at the
neck area is made of black.
which is a stripped design.
but can you tell whom you remember by looking
at this t-shirt?
ben-ten!!!
the only thing is the middle design is shifted
to the corner design.
overall it looks like a ben-ten t-shirt only.
down, you get the branding of overlays which
is attached through a rubber patch.
in the neck area, you get one more overlays
tag attached with L size written.
sings song..
talking about the t- shirt, one thing that
increases the level of experience is...
the fabric of the t-shirt is thick and is
very dense.
in this t-shirt, 230 is used.
if you dont know what is this?
basically, the thickness of the fabric is
measured..
to check the thickness of the fabric so in
this t-shirt the fabric thickness is..
so in this 230 gsm is used and literally,
the premium texture will be felt by you.
the fabric is very stretchy inspite of being
cotton.
stretches like elastic.
if you want to know my reviews on this t-shirt,
then you will have to watch the video till
the end.
now lets move to the next amazing t-shirt.
so here we have the t-shirt..
you must have watched people wearing the same
t-shirt.
The name of the t-shirt is messed -it!
which means a mess is created!
we get a tag of overlays.
mrp is 1599 but you have to very less amount
if the product will be left or not.
this t-shirt is oversized and come with a
design of multiple patch work.
with multiple colours in it.
one side you will have a lot of dark grey,
another side little bit of cream color,
another side is the blue color.
the neckline is black in colour.
not only with the difference in colour patches,
but you get different fabric material with
each color.
the whole t-shirt is from supima but the texture
and feeling is different from one another.
the 4 patches you see over here is..
this dedicates to any sign of space
it's that alien which tried to communicate
with others,
who threw the stone?
down you have the branding of overlays.
at the back of the neck, we have the overlays
branding.
the next thing you will notice is,
that not only through the colour it is made,
but the fabrics are properly cut and stitched
to make this t-shirt.
definitely, it took a lot of work for sure.
the grey part you see here..
these fabrics is made at 230 gsm.
moreover, the texture is a little bit rough
according to me.
if you have to wear comfy wear, then these
blue and cream part feels the same.
t shirt is very good, very comfortable and
nice fitting and is a oversized t-shirt.
it matches with the trend indeed.
lets move to the next t-shirt!
we bought 5 t-shirts and here we have another
box with burnt hakka noodles in it.
we talked to the team of overlays clothing
at their old launch.
but don't know what happened after that but
this is not a sponsored video...
i have purchased all these products with my
own money so that i show you.
and i get to experience about everything.
this white t-shirtb which you saw at the beginning,
with the same design, the same cloth, and
the same waffle fabric.
the only thing is it has different elements,
In the front we have a pocket with a thread
design on the sides,
The colour of the thread is grey, with the
same grey neckline with more thread designs
at the back.
at the end of the sleeves, you have grey borders,
and this t-shirt is designed as an oversized
fit,
the name of the t-shirt is a white waffle
oversized t-shirt with olive rib.
the team says it is as an olive green t-shirt
but it looks grey to me and us.
maybe it has some magic inside.
the mrp of this t-shirt is 1399/- but you
dont have to pay this much.
i dont have more to say about this t-shirt,
if we talk about looks?
again its a very fine t-shirt, the b-roll
will tell you how am i looking in this t-shirt.
next, we move to the last t-shirt!
by the grace of the god, we will also do such
things one day!
lets open the next t-shirt, the name of the
t-shirt is...
RUNWAY!
its a full black t-shirt....
with some grey design in the middle.
about that, i will explain...
lets talk about the price, the price written
here is 1399/- which you dont have to pay..
tag with overlays branding,
inside you have a patch of overlays, down
you have one more small patch.
this t-shirt is also made of supima fabrics.
definitely the thickness, its the same very
good,
and this t-shirt is made at 222..
.....
222 gsm made.
it has a round neck and short sleeves..
you dont get a lot of design in it.
a runway sort of thing is made on the t-shirt
and some strokes on the sleeve is made.
thus, this is a small design element which
looks cool.
these t-shirts speak more of the quality and
not the designs.
might happen you dont like the design on the
website but when you,
touch it, you will feel a different experience.
that you never have hold such a piece of cloth
neither wore it.
if you loved watching these t-shirts then
you can like it and go.
lets talk about the pros and cons..
pros is the cloth of these t-shirts are of
very good quality.
and literally, any youtuber or any website,
will never serve these premium clothes.
from packaging to the clothes there were no
use of plastic,
i found that
a very good thing!
lets talk about the cons..
now all the cons i will be talking about is
they are not cons but improvements..
which the company can hear as a customer advice.
about what they can improve and what not?
the first problem which i found was..
that in any cloth among these 5, there is
no instructions given about...
the fabric, like the type of fabric? is that
supima or anything else?
the second thing was, the body fitting was
good but...
but the sleeves were not so flattering and
looks as if they were running...
if i have wore this t-shirt and the sleeve
is running,
then this thing personally does not looks
good.
the t-shirt mounting freely doesn't look nice.
if you liked this video, then make sure you
like it,
subscribe to this channel.
if anyone is watching from the tech team or
overlays team,
try from next time you send review units,
because the clothes you have is liked by all
of our audience.
till then bye!
Jai hind!