Hello, friends!
Picture yourself on a ship at sea,
relishing the fresh and invigorating sea breeze.
Suddenly, a remarkable sight unfolds before you
a colossal missile emerges from the water.
Not just any missile,
but a nuclear missile
with the capability to reach a target
on the other side of the globe,
spanning thousands of kilometers.
This isn't a mere imagination;
it's a reality today, thanks to submarines.
The footage you just witnessed
was a test of a Trident 2 missile
conducted by the US Navy,
launched from a US Ohio-class submarine.
The Trident 2 falls under the category of
submarine-launched ballistic missiles (SLBMs),
representing one of the most formidable weapons globally.
These SLBMs boast an estimated yield of 475 kilotons,
a stark contrast to the 12-13 kiloton yield of
the nuclear bomb dropped on Hiroshima.
Presently, these potent weapons
are housed within submarines,
stealthily traversing the world's oceans
in highly classified, undisclosed locations.
In today's video, let's delve into
the intricacies of these submarines
understanding the technology that propels them
and unravelling their operational mechanisms.
Fundamentally, all submarines operate based on
Archimedes' principle,
a concept likely familiar from school.
As an object sinks,
it experiences a buoyant force
equivalent to the weight of the fluid displaced
due to this object's sinking.
When a submarine's weight
matches that of the water it displaces,
it achieves a level of neutral buoyancy.
Allowing it to maintain a constant depth.
When the objective is to submerge,
the gravitational force applied must exceed
the buoyant force,
prompting the use of ballast tanks.
Typically, these two tanks are located at the submarine's ends,
they are filled with air at the surface,
enabling the vessel to float.
To descend into the water,
these ballast tanks are flooded with water,
increasing the submarine's weight
and initiating the descent.
Such scenarios are labelled to have negative buoyancy.
It indicates the control of a submarine's depth
by adjusting the water level in its ballast tanks.
This mechanism governs vertical
movement for ascending and descending.
For lateral movement,
such as turning sideways in the water,
a Rudder is employed.
It looks like this.
It is known as a Vertical Rudder.
This facilitates horizontal movement in the water.
Similar rudders are used in boats, ships, and aircraft.
Additionally, forward and backward motion
is achieved through the use of a propeller,
essentially a fan.
While navigating underwater,
a reliable means of orientation is essential.
Sonar technology serves this purpose.
It operates based on sound.
There are two main types of sonar technologies:
active sonar and passive sonar.
Active sonar involves emitting sound from the submarine.
The sound travels through the water,
collides with objects, and upon
reflection back to the submarine,
the time and distance calculations
provide information about the submarine's
location and the surrounding environment.
In contrast, passive sonar does not emit sound
but rather detects sounds from other
sources, such as enemy submarines,
by listening to their engine and propeller noises
to determine their distance.
However, the use of sonar technology
has adverse effects on marine life,
impacting creatures like whales and dolphins,
which also rely on sonar for communication.
To address this concern, some submarines
are exploring alternative technologies
such as LiDAR,
Light Detection and Ranging.
LiDAR employs light to estimate distance
and is already integrated into many modern smartphones.
Another alternative is using RADAR
Radio Detection and Ranging,
it is effective above water and in aircrafts
which utilizes radio waves to calculate distances.
but is limited underwater due to the
restricted transmission of radio waves.
Lastly, emerging technologies are being
explored as potential alternatives like
MRS
Magnetic Anomaly Detection System
or Gravitational Anomaly Detection System.
However, the bottom line is that today,
the predominant technology employed
in submarines is Sonar.
Multiple Sonar sensors are strategically
installed around submarines
to continuously collect and monitor data,
ensuring there are no obstacles or hazards in their path.
This underscores the vital role of data science,
whether in space, on ground or underwater,
it is a necessity in almost every domain.
Unsurprisingly, data science has emerged
as one of the most lucrative career options.
If you're keen on upskilling in this field,
Scaler.com, our video sponsor,
is an excellent choice.
Scaler is an online tech learning academy
offering programs in software development,
data science, and machine learning.
Collaborating with top tech companies,
Scaler provides guidance from industry experts,
to guide and mentor the learners.
If you enroll with them, you will get access
to three-hours worth of learning daily
and to over 80 real-world case studies.
Scaler reports that those who work hard and complete these programs
report an average salary increase of 126%,
and an impressive 93.5% of learners
secure placements in leading tech firms
such as Google, Facebook, Flipkart, Myntra,
Amazon, and Zomato.
Scaler also offers an easy 2-year EMI option
with 0% interest.
If you think this can be useful to you
to give a boost to your career
you can check out Scaler's website
using the link in the description below.
You can also attend a free live class to
experience their offerings firsthand.
The link is in the description below.
Now, let's delve into the inner workings of a submarine.
Typically, an armed military submarine
consists of three levels or decks.
This video will mostly focus on military submarines,
as they constitute the majority of submarines worldwide.
It's worth noting that the designs of
research and tourism submarines may differ.
For instance, the Titan submersible gained attention a few months ago
due to its accident,
and I've covered it in a separate video if you're interested in learning more.
If you're interested, you can check out the
detailed video.
The link is in the description.
Now, turning our attention to military submarines.
The topmost deck of a military submarine
is typically outfitted with torpedoes,
which serve as weapons.
The lowest deck houses battery rooms
that supply electricity to the submarine,
and sandwiched in between are the diesel machine,
motor room, and the nerve center
known as the control room.
Positioned above the control room,
you'll usually find a conning tower
an essential component serving as
the submarine's attack center.
The conning tower is equipped with various instruments,
including periscopes for observing the surroundings,
electronic antennas, and access points for arms.
It also serves as the main entry and exit point
for individuals entering or leaving the submarine.
Torpedoes are stored in torpedo tubes.
These are basically self-propelled underwater missiles.
These tubes are cylindrical containers
designed to house these cylindrical missiles.
In modern submarines, torpedoes
are typically placed at the front.
However, in the 2017 Bollywood film 'Ghazi Attack,'
the depiction of a submarine featured
torpedoes at both the front and back.
This was historically accurate as powerful submarines back then
indeed had torpedoes at both ends
because torpedoes could only travel
in a straight line at the time.
An intriguing aspect is that
these torpedo tubes can also be used as
emergency escape routes from submarines.
Nevertheless, escaping through them is no easy feat.
The tubes have a narrow diameter,
measuring only 12.75 inches for light torpedoes
and 21 inches for heavy torpedoes.
First of all, this is an extremely narrow space.
Additionally, individuals attempting to escape
must wear a 23 kg escape
suit due to the immense water pressure at those depths.
One can't simply exit the submarine at those depths.
The immense pressure of the water
would crush the unprepared instantly.
Officers working in submarines
undergo rigorous training for six months.
India's sole military submarine training establishment,
INS Satavahana,
is located in Vishakhapatnam city.
At this training facility, numerous replicas
of torpedo tubes are available
for officers to practice emergency escapes.
Now, let's delve into the submarine's power source
where does it get the energy to operate?
The answer depends on the type of submarine,
with two primary categories in India:
conventional submarines and nuclear submarines.
Conventional submarines utilize large electrical batteries,
akin to car batteries, but these
require recharging every 2-3 days.
To recharge these batteries,
a diesel engine is needed.
However, operating a diesel engine
necessitates oxygen from the air.
Since submarines operate underwater,
they must resurface to run the
diesel engine and recharge the batteries.
In contrast, nuclear submarines don't have this problem.
They employ a nuclear reactor instead
of a diesel engine to generate electricity.
This allows them to remain submerged for extended periods,
limited only by the human factors,
such as the availability of food
and provisions for the crew.
The submarines can remained submerged
as long as there's sufficient provisions for the crew.
Examining the structure of a submarine,
the outer layer is typically composed of rubber.
This reason for strategic choice is quite simple actually.
Because rubber effectively absorbs sound,
making it challenging to detect submarines in the water.
Military submarines are designed to be elusive,
ensuring they are not easily spotted by enemy counterparts.
The black layer visible in submarine photos
is made of rubber.
Moving to the interior, the primary body
of the submarine within the rubber layer
is referred to as the Hull.
There are two common types of hulls:
single hull and double hull.
Single hull submarines have only one layer of the main body,
while double hull submarines consist of two layers of the main body.
In the double hull design,
the ballast tank is integrated,
with water filling the space between the two layers,
effectively serving as a ballast tank.
The clear advantage of a double hull configuration
lies in providing an additional layer of protection.
In the event of a collision,
a double hull submarine offers enhanced security.
Most modern military submarines
adopt the double hull design,
not only for added protection
but also to better withstand water pressure
as illustrated by the incident involving the Titan submersible's
implosion under water pressure.
At the water's surface, the atmospheric pressure is 1 atmosphere,
equivalent to 1 kilogram per square centimeter.
As one descends underwater, pressure increases.
For every 10 meters of depth,
there's an additional 1 kilogram per square meter of pressure.
Military submarines are typically designed
to operate at depths of 300-400 meters,
with some capable of reaching depths of 500 meters.
At this depth, the pressure reaches 50 atmospheres
50 times greater than at the surface.
Obviously, constructing submarine
hulls requires robust materials.
Not using the right materials
might cause failures or accidents.
As with the Titan submersible.
Military submarines use high-quality steel alloys,
blending steel with titanium, carbon,
aluminium, and other elements.
The complexity of designing a submarine is underscored
by the fact that it takes approximately
10 years to design a diesel-electric submarine,
while a nuclear submarine demands a
minimum of 15-17 years at the designing stage.
This intricacy is why India often outsources submarine design
to other countries, such as Russia, Germany, or France.
However, India manufactures its own submarines.
India's first domestically manufactured
submarine was INS Shalki,
launched in 1987 during
Prime Minister Rajiv Gandhi's tenure.
and commissioned by the Indian Navy in 1992.
On Indian Navy's website, you will see that
there are different categories of submarines,
which are divided into classes.
In India, there are four classes.
Sindhughosh, Shishumar, Kalvari, and Arihant.
The first three classes
are of conventional submarines:
the Sindhughosh class comprises Russian diesel-powered EKMs,
the Shishumar class features German SSKs,
and the Kalvari class showcases new French-designed and Indian-built SCORPENEs.
Here, EKMs, SSKs, and SCORPENEs
are the nomenclature used for submarines in other countries.
But we classify these submarines into these classes,
These classes of submarines
can be compared to the models of cars.
Specifically, Sindhughosh comprises 7 submarines,
Shishumar has 4,
and the Kalvari class has 5 operational submarines.
Detailed information about each submarine,
including names, can be found on the Indian Navy website,
and the link is provided in the description below.
Moving to the category of nuclear submarines,
India has named its class Arihant,
Currently, there are two active nuclear submarines in this class,
with two more under construction in Vishakhapatnam.
The Arihant-class submarines have the
capability to carry ballistic missiles,
Ballistic missiles are self-guided missiles
that can be equipped with nuclear bombs.
INS Arihant is presently armed with
K-15 submarine-launched ballistic missile,
an SLBM like the one I mentioned earlier in the video.
The range of the K-15 missile is
between 750 km and 1,900 km.
Talking about the other developed countries,
the American Navy's Ohio-class submarines
are considered among the most powerful in the world.
The U.S. possesses a total of 18 Ohio-class submarines,
each capable of carrying 24 Trident 2 ballistic missiles.
Furthermore, each Trident 2 missile can
potentially accommodate 14 nuclear bombs.
When the United States and Russia
aimed to decrease the number of nuclear weapons they had,
they entered into the START 1 agreement.
The terms of the agreement specified
a reduction limit from 14 to 8.
This START I treaty, officially known
as the Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty,
was the first treaty between the U.S. and the Soviet Union
to reduce strategic nuclear weapons.
Beyond these, the U.S. Navy features other submarine classes,
such as Los Angeles, Columbia, and Virginia classes.
In Russia, the Yasen class stands out as the
most powerful nuclear attack submarine.
Besides India, Russia, and the U.S., other countries like
China, the UK, France, and Germany
also possess similar submarines.
The actual capacity of these submarines in terms of personnel
varies between submarines
and the actual data is confidential in these countries
due to military reasons.
The estimated capacity of a submarine
generally ranges between 50 and 80 people,
50 to 80 people can be onboard these submaries.
With nuclear submarines being even larger,
it can accommodate approximately 100 individuals.
The size of these submarines is truly
remarkable, as depicted in the video.
It's unbelievable.
For those eager to witness these marvels in person,
a visit to Vishakhapatnam, home to a
submarine museum, is recommended.
The museum features INS Kursura,
a retired Indian Navy submarine
commissioned in 1969.
Notably, the museum was inaugurated in 2002
by the then Chief Minister of Andhra Pradesh,
Mr Chandra Babu Naidu.
If you desire the firsthand experience
of being inside a submarine,
tourism submarines or research
submarines offer such opportunities.
Typically, non-military submarines do not
venture too deep into the water.
The Titan submersible was an exception.
Such deep-sea submarines are
rare in the tourism sector.
A few companies in Europe, the USA, and the UK,
provide submarine and submersible dives.
Such as the companies Atlantis and Seabourn.
They offer expeditions to locations like Alaska.
I trust you've gained valuable insights from this video.
Check out Scaler with the link in the description below.
Additionally, for a detailed account
of the Titan submersible accident,
you can watch this video by clicking here.
It's a truly heart-wrenching story.
Thank you very much!