Friends, here a boy has come for a walk in the forest, then he
sees a poisonous plant in the jungle, then here he starts eating it, then there is a poisonous plant, this boy
has got his hand and cat's litter due to which he gets infection in his hand, now doctor how to cure it?
I will fix it, I will understand with the help of animation video but before that, if you
are cute then give this video a like and subscribe the channel and if you are an ass then don't do it
and if you want to write then definitely write Jai Shri Ram in the comment box friends first. So the doctor
injects NSIC in the hand and then
cleans the hand thoroughly with iodine liquid. Then an incision is made in the hand with a knife and the pus
is taken out in such a way as you can see. And then the pus
is cleaned thoroughly with a cloth, then the poisonous plant
is taken out from inside the hand in this way, then a tank is placed on the hand and the hand is bandaged
so that the person can get some relief. both are fine