post his arrest and the subsequent bail
youtuber gaurav tanija aka flying beast
shared hilarious memes made by his fans
on his social media page
the social media influencer was arrested
after his fans gathered outside sector
51 metro station to celebrate his
birthday on saturday
most of the memes made by his fans on
the incident were either about his
fitness or his wife rituarati
one of them mentioned that not
re-stacking the weights was his crime
while another one spoke about how
unbothered he is even after getting
arrested
taneja also tweeted that he is not
afraid of getting slapped but of his
wife's surprises thereby teasing his
wife ritu rathi taneja apart from the
memes gaurav also shared a family
picture with his wife ritu and his two
daughters on instagram and took a dig at
ritu as he wrote thank you for all the
lovely wishes you guys made my day also
thanks to riturathi for making it the
most memorable birthday literally
ritu rathi taneja on the occasion of her
husband's birthday invited his fans to
celebrate his birthday with them at a
metro station in noida post which gaurav
taneja was arrested for breaching
section 144 which is in place in noida
currently
gaurav was arrested on saturday and was
taken to noida sector 49 police station
for questioning post which he was
granted bail
subscribe to one india channel and never
miss an update