- This person is fast,
but this person is faster.
This person might even be a robot.
- Sonic speed.
- We're going to react, once again,
to the fastest workers on the planet.
- Because it got a lot of views.
Yay!
- So, this is the world's fastest cashier.
- That boy crazy.
(mumbles)
- Oh my gosh.
You're walking with your car to checkout
and you see that man and you go,
I'm just gonna take this
mountain dew and put it back.
- Yeah.
You get home and you got to open your soda
it's just blows up (mumbles)
- You cut open your
chicken and it explodes it.
And it's not even supposed to explode.
- That doesn't even make any sense.
- Those are propane tank.
- He's just hitting them.
- Those are propane tanks
and he's just throwing them.
- He's like flipping them.
That's so unsafe for no reason.
- Oh, so he's painting the
little thing on the cross walk.
- I always thought that was
like a thing they put on it
and then they spray paint
like a stint, so I guess.
- Wow.
This guy's about the
flink something in here.
- Oh, he's putting ice in it.
He nice with the ice.
- What is that for?
- In some places.
- Don't act like you know.
- In some places they don't have fridges.
They just produce ice.
So they have to transport ice.
- That's how they move it?
- And he throwing it in there,
because he nice with it.
He nice with the ice.
- Nice with the ice.
Oh, I've seen this clip.
This guy filmed the a hundred meter dash
and somehow ran faster than them.
- Look at him.
- He's doing it in like jeans too.
- That's one of those animated
moments where you were like,
wait a minute, you put
down the camera, you go.
- I could win.
But then who would film him?
Because he's.
(crosstalk)
To find somebody faster than him.
- Which might not be possible.
Maybe that's why he's doing that job.
- Yeah.
- What if that's how
Usain Bolt turned into
just into camera man.
- He is the next guy.
- For the a hundred meter dash.
So like, Usain Bolt, you're the guy.
So this is apparently the
world's fastest dealer.
(mouth mumbling)
I feel like I can do it fast.
- I think Chandler can do it faster.
Chandler is pretty fast.
(gasps)
I want this.
- Oh wait.
- But.
- If this video gets 1 million likes,
I'll buy him a pancake bot.
Please I want it.
I want to build Tucker
Tyrannosaurus Rex pancakes.
- That's pretty convincing.
All right, I'm upping it to 1.5 million.
- What?
If it's more convincing.
- If this turns out to be
do-do I'm going to be mad.
- Look at that.
That's beautiful.
- I need that in my life.
- I need that.
- So he's just putting
some white scribbles.
I'm sure nothing's going to come up this.
- I don't really see what.
- Wait, is that Anderson Cooper?
- Yeah.
Anderson Cooper is on everything.
I don't.
- Is he going to throw paint?
- Oh!
That's so cool.
You don't see it unil it's upside down.
And now I see it.
- I thought he was going to
like throw a bucket of paint to.
(burps)
- I'll just shut up.
- You should.
- Is this how they load a plane?
- Yeah.
Except for, they're missing all
the parts where they slam it
into the ground and stop.
(laughing)
- And break everything
fragile in your bag.
- Fast car.
- Nothing beats watching them.
(makes car sounds)
Change to formula one.
- Gone.
Hey!
Archery girl.
It's Legolas.
- Watch those arrows just
not be hitting anything.
They're just flying out into the stands.
Oh, well.
- They're hitting a rug.
- Oh, nevermind.
I take it back.
You're actually pretty active.
Is that a duck?
- He's laying his duck.
Oh!
He gone.
- Oh.
Oh!
That boy gone.
- That duck was like
"Hey, I never loved you."
- That looks like a cartoon
thing where they're like.
(mouth running sounds)
- Yeah, like Bugs Bunny.
- Yeah, add some cartoon sound effect.
- Okay, this is Five Guys.
- I only see one girl though.
(drums plays)
- Just order from Beast Burger.
I didn't realize they made
the fries at the restaurant.
- They do.
And Five Guys fries are B tier.
- I agree.
A tier is Beast Burger and nothing else.
Oh, he's rolling pipes.
- Who knows what it's going for.
But he's doing it.
And he's got his hat backwards like I do.
- Oh my gosh.
- Yo, that guy's fast at climbing logs.
Yo, with the thing dangling behind.
- Looks like a monkey?
- Yeah.
Dude, we're in sync.
- Pancakes.
- I was thinking it.
My mouth just doesn't think
as fast as my brain does.
That's like 400 something pounds.
That's insane.
Is that how you want to be like?
- I don't want to be swollen.
I want to be a chad.
- That's chad.
- I've seen some chads that are smaller.
He is a chad.
But you can be smaller
and still be a chad.
No.
Do you want to be a sigma, chad, daddy?
- No.
Do you want to be a beta, simp, cuck?
- I want to be in the middle.
- I can't do this anymore.
(laughing)
So that's how your.
That guy has muscles on his ribs.
What it like?
I don't even have, like
look, there's nothing there.
He has like an entire addition.
What is that?
- It's, he had an entire (mumbles)
where he just every single
rib just got muscle.
- Somebody broke that man.
Chad!
- This man was about to
propose and got heartbroken.
- Something.
He walked in and saw her
with another man or something
because he is a god.
- That is the sign.
Rib muscles is the sign
you got cheated on.
He just has a happy marriage,
been in love for 30 years.
We're just projecting on him.
- Sorry, bud.
- What's going on?
- Ball go fast.
Oh, that's satisfying.
This is how they did
Star Wars sound effects?
(light engine roaring)
- Yeah, this definitely has to be it.
There's no way any of that's accurate.
Look at the signing.
It just looks like scribbled.
I don't think
no, he's not signing.
He's just stamped.
Wait is he signing and stamping?
- He's signing and stamping.
(rock music)
(whispers)
There's just no way.
- Yo.
- Hey, that's Russian, bro.
Very slob.
I have a strong urge to
spend 10 years trying
to master whatever he just did.
- All right, who you got money on?
(crosstalk)
Oh, come on.
All right, fine.
I'll take green.
- I want green now.
- Okay, I'll take yellow.
A hundred dollars yellow.
Okay, 100 dollars green.
- Yellow.
- Green.
- Wait.
- Yes!
Yellow!
Pum!
- Okay, well.
I will only include the 100 dollars
if this it's 1.5 million likes.
- Guys, go.
I need money.
- Wait, wait.
- Wait.
Fastest workers.
What's fast about that?
Oh.
- Oh!
- That cop is a fast worker.
- Yo, how do people stack cups like this?
I have a strong masculine
urge to try to master this
in a under a day.
Because it looks so
much easier than it is.
Although I know it's very hard.
- I have a strong
masculine urge to cut off
from civilization and live
in the middle of nowhere.
And never talk to anyone.
- Literally nothing to do
with what I was talking about.
(cricket cricking)
Speaking of strong masculine
urges, they just lifted a car.
- They had the strong masculine
urge to take apart a vehicle
for no reason.
- Is this if your car gets stuck?
And that's how unstuck it?
- Yeah, wait.
So imagine you can't get
over something, right?
There's like something blocking the way.
You take your car apart.
Move it over the obstacle
and put it back together.
- That's interesting.
Is that like a military thing or?
- It's gotta be, right?
- That looks like they fire department.
That's fire department.
- They're carrying
camouflage pants though.
Fire doesn't need to camouflage.
(crosstalk)
- What are you?
Dumb?
- What an idiot.
- It doesn't have eyes.
Me and the boys at 3:00 AM.
- I love concrete, man.
I love me some con queet, yeah.
- Some green guacamole and lettuce.
- [Man] Yes sir.
- Why this guy kind of sound like me.
- Dumb?
Just kidding.
- Okay.
All right.
Walter you got it.
You got it, Walter.
- Oh no.
Now we're stuck with Walter.
- Stuck?
Walter's a beautiful creature.
- All right, Walter, what is he painting?
Oh.
Okay, now some black paint.
Agreed, Walter?
Oh, snap!
Oh my gosh, that looks so good.
Is that a pyramid?
Yeah those are pyramids with
the Jupiter in the background.
- [Man 2] Are you talking to Walt?
- I'm talking to Walter, shut up.
So these are two professional climbers.
- All right.
Who's the faster climber?
Oh, guy on the right, killing it.
- Oh, leaning backwards like that,
would scare the mess out of me.
- Yeah.
How do you get used to doing that?
- Is this a marketing stunt?
Because if so it's working.
- Aren't these like ancient stairs?
Tell your phone to shut up.
- (Mumbles) Robert texted me.
- Oh, I get it.
You're Mr. Famous.
(crosstalk)
Oh my gosh.
Someone tell Tesla.
They should do that.
This is just literally
laying concrete on a wall
and it's beautiful.
But here's the thing, it was
covering up the exposed brick,
which I like.
I'm an interior design kind of guy.
- Yeah, you're a brick over concrete.
- Yeah.
My wife makes me watch a
lot of home design shows.
- Here, keep talking that way.
- Yeah, apparently exposed beams
and exposed bricks are very important.
Very interesting.
Why?
Well, because they say
it has a lot of the value
to the house.
Because it's more of a natural look.
Hey, melon.
I'm a big melon guy.
- That's zucchini.
- That is not.
- Just kidding.
- That's a cantaloupe.
Wait, that's a cantaloupe, not a melon.
- Oh!
- Wait, it's a cantaloupe
in the melon family?
- I don't know.
This guy is punching a ball.
- That's a weight ball too.
- That's how Goku trains.
- These all look like MPCs.
- They do.
I can't tell if he told them
what to do in the background.
- Yeah!
Yo, that kid's fast.
Oh my God.
Wait, he might become
a camera man one day.
- Wait, is this how they make brooms?
- You didn't know that.
- Don't act like you knew that.
- Bro, I used to work in a broom factory.
- No you didn't.
- Yeah, I had to quit though.
Because it just really swept me away.
- All right, with that one,
we're going to end the video.
If you haven't already, subscribe.
Good bye.