After finishing the Kerala Boat Race,
I went to my friend's
house in Cochin at night.
And took a flight to
Delhi in the morning.
One good thing about Cochin
Airport is that there are sofas here.
It's very comfortable.
There are individual sofas
too, unlike any other airport.
I start my morning normally like, drink
water, brush my teeth and have tea.
But there's one thing
common in all these things.
You need water.
And the day you don't
have water at home...
Ritu, come upstairs once.
There's not a single
drop of water at home.
There were monkeys at night.
They broke these water pipes.
It's all over.
This is our tank.
There's a plastic
tanki under it.
It's pipe melted completely.
It's build like this, I'm
scared to climb up on this.
I might slip.
Yes, but there's no way to climb up.
There is no trick to climb,
how will a man climb?
It's completely temporary.
Haha
Look at this.
If a person slips from here,
he will go down by swinging.
Come on i'll hold it.
Even if you slip from above,
you may go straight to the garden.
Haha
That's why grass has
been planted below brother.
Hahaha
I feel like I've become
an action movie hero.
Brother, finish our work.
Please.
I didn't even brush my
teeth in the morning.
The first plumber who
came here gave up.
Now the second plumber has come.
There's no way to climb up.
I'm scared to climb up.
I feel like in Mai Hu Na Movie Shahrukh
Khan climb up & done a slidey, just like it.
It's scary.
There is not a drop of
water to flush in the toilet.
Noni, find Pihu.
Where's Pihu? Where's Pihu?
I can't see Pihu.
Pihu is hidden.
Noni, can you see Pihu?
No
Can you see her?
Where are you Pihu?
Pihu, Pihu, Pihu.
She's there.
Where did you see her?
I saw Pihu.
Haha
Come out.
I saw you, I saw you.
I have to pick up
Rashi from school now.
Yesterday was a cricket match.
I was playing well.
Look, there's no tension
about the runs right now.
Catch it.
But our match got abandoned
due to some reason.
The ball hit the bottom edge
and went through the leg.
He was saying
earlier that it's not.
Don't curse.
What's tomorrow?
It's our country's birthday.
It's our country's birthday tomorrow?
Yes.
Today was your celebration
of Independence Day?
Yes.
So what did you do at school today?
Today we made Indian flag.
And? And we...
Dad, can I tell you something?
Yes, tell me.
Today...
Sometimes I get hungry in school.
Mummy had given me the tiffin
and had given me the money in it.
Cashew, almond,
chips and butter in this.
Oh, wow.
There's no water at all at home.
I am saying Ritu, Pihu.
Rashi, come on.
There's no water
to drink at all.
Look at this.
Wow, wow.
Look, look, look.
Brother, it is a matter of great
difficulty, I have got pressure.
But there's no water at
home to relieve the pressure.
So what should we do?
Should we ask the neighbors?
First we bring it from this side.
I will bring it, hold this.
What do you know about the cost
of 2 buckets of water Ramesh Babu..
I've fooled, bro.
Our neighbors have gone outside.
What will we do?
I think it's better
to say to uncle,
I'll do it in your washroom,
till then I can't hold it.
When people from the village
bring water from 5 km away,
How do they bring it?
Why water is the dirty?
It's coming dirty.
Great success.
How hard it was to open the new pen.
The new pen was in this.
All the pens were opened.
I said, it's broken.
It's broken.
All the pens.
This is the packet of new pen.
All the pens are broken.
And this bangle isn't open.
It's broken, brother, look.
It's all broken from one place.
We did an economical thing by
taking out the refill and keep it.
There is no water at all in our house.
So Ritu and I decided that
we are going to the hotel.
We will take a bath there.
We are going to pretext
of having coffee there.
We will take a room
and take a bath.
So Nisha's children have
also come to our house.
All the kids have to pee today,
when there is no water at home.
Brother, it was fun.
We went there in
this building it's mall.
We went there and took a bath.
They gave us a gift, Sir, you
took a very good bath here.
Great success.
Dad,
First do the studies.
Dad, look at this one thing.
- Your teacher has come
- Look at it
Show what is it.
Did you teach this to Pihu?
Is she was able to run it?
She runs it like this.
But she collides in this.
Your teacher has
come go n study now.
Has the water come,
sister? Has the water come?
What a thing, brother!
let me take a bath.
Look at them.
When father had said that no child will come to
father's office and not will touch office items.
Then what is this happening?
What is happening?
Pihu, what's going on?
Han?
Rashi, ..you're doing here and there
they have made mess in the office.
Look, they are making a mess.
JAI..
I got this specially for
Pihu from Hong Kong.
Rashi, hold it. Let me
show you how it looks.
One goes down like this.
This one goes like this.
And this one goes like this.
Pihu didn't have a bag,
Pihu's shoulder is small..
So, you can carry it like this.
I saw in Hong Kong every kid...
Our captain is getting
ready for the morning.
She's ironing her dress.
Which flight is tomorrow?
where are you going tomorrow.
Tomorrow, Bombay - Madurai.
You're going to Madurai?
There's a really nice
temple in Madurai.
It's called Lipakshi, right?
- Do you know what happened yesterday?
- What happened?
Yesterday, on my flight,
when the crew breifs,
The people sitting at the
overwing exit were like,
If there's an emergency, the
captain will say, evacuate, evacuate,
So, you have to get off.
So, there were a few people.
He got off the flap.
- The one who was sitting
- Hmm
Came to me.
I sent him.
Because he was talking about the crew.
- How did he do it?
- Yes
So, the crew said, sir,
this is a punishable offence.
You can't do it like this.
So, he said, who
would punish me?
So, I said, really?
So, she said, sir, the
government would punish you.
It's a punishable offence.
So, he said, I'm the government.
Huh?
He said this.
Did Modi was sitting there?
No, he didn't.
So, what happened next.
The crew came and told me.
Okay, ma'am, he was saying this.
I said, brother, then call security.
So, when the security
came, so, generally,
When the security comes,
as they say, get off from here.
So, they said,
Captain, is very
angry about this.
Do you know what the problem was?
Attitude.
There was no problem.
If that guy says, okay,
ma'am, sorry, I made a mistake.
Okay, I won't do it again.
I said, if that guy has such an
attitude, that I am the government.
I said, he will do it anyway.
I said, take him down.
So, after that, he
started saying sorry.
Then I said, brother,
make him sit in the front.
I made him sit
on the first seat.
I said, lead, you take care of him.
I said, it's a matter of people
they don't understand seriousness.
All these things
are very important.
I remembered a story.
We were about to
land in Hyderabad.
So, there were kids.
Like, for the first and second
time, they are traveling.
So, they were bothering our crew.
As in, a little bit,
I don't know what term to use.
They were hitting a little line or
bothering us them do this and that.
They were bothering, basically.
So, my crew came and
said, they are bothering us, sir.
So, then I announced that, look,
sir, if you will continue to bother us.
Then I will announce this to
the Hyderabad security team.
So, they went straight like this.
They said, sir, we are apologizing.
We are sitting in the back.
But the line comes.
All these things are very legal.
And people don't know how
much authority there is in this case.
- You can literally be jailed for all these
things so be careful - If the police comes..
If the police comes, they will take you.
Yes.
They will put you in jail.
It doesn't work here.
They say, we're
hitting just a line.
So, what?
When you are in air, it's a serious
offense in terms of a lot of things.
Tokyo Convention, 1947.
Something like this, right?
Oh, you remember that.
Subtitles by Mohit