Body Language coach & key note Speaker:Deepa Kaur
Trust Indicators,ab main lapse ek sawaal poochungi, app
jab kisiko  dekte hon,for eg.if
some one had to walk in this room an come and stand in front
of you,which part of their body would you
notice first?Audience: eyes,Speaker:great...
Audience:face.. ladies?really! Audience response:entire body .Speaker:entire body,what is she
wearing,what are her shoes like,watch and
bag like!Audience:the way the person is moving.fantastic.Audience:you
would notice the clothes.Speaker:i ideally
notice the shoes!so for me assessment begins
from below to top,something different.Speaker:my
answer in the next slide is going to suprise
you.we may think what it is but trust me we
do things differently.body party which you
actually notice first are actually your HANDS Ladies and gentleman.reason
being..let me take you years back when we
were apes,ek tribal system hota tha,jab ek
tribe ko dusre tribe ki territory se guzarna
padta hon?do you know how they use to move?Audience:move
across with hands up.Speaker: Thank you.so
the entire group of villagers/tribe would
cross territory with hands up.sign and signal
for the people in the territory jo usko claim
karma hain that hey mere pass na patharr hain,na
spear hain na teer kamaan hain,i am not here
to hurt you.just let me pass.you may think
that eyes are the first thing that you notice
first,or clothes but subconsciously you are actually
assessing are the hands!jab aap apna haat dikhate
hon you are giving two indication to people
that wether i am a friend or a foe!agar main
as a speaker main aise khadi rahoon,and i
don't show my hand,15 secs down,20
secs down,you will start feeling curious that
what is it that she is hiding behind...chal
kya rahan hain,what is it that she is hiding
behind,show me your hands...i have nothing
in hand.i am your friend.ok so now when we want
to tell ,communicate this kind of feeling
that hey you can trust me,hey i have a winning
idea,hey i am here for you .Hand are the first
thing that indicate trust. Body language coach & key note speaker:Deepa
Kaur