[Music]
youtuber gaurav taneja also known as the
flying beast was on july 9th arrested
after his followers gathered at a noida
metro station to celebrate his birthday
taneja had reportedly booked a metro
coach at sector 51 metro station of the
aqua line for his birthday celebration
his wife riturati taneja had allegedly
invited followers to celebrate his
birthday following which hundreds of
people thronged the sector 51 metro
station to meet the youtuber
according to the news agency a and i
noida sector 49 police booked him for
allegedly violating section 144 of the
crpc which is currently in force in
noida gaurav taneja's wife who has over
1.6 million followers on instagram had
told her fans that she will meet them at
around 1 30 p.m for his birthday
celebration
taneja is reportedly a civil engineering
graduate from iit kharagpur and is also
currently pursuing law from the faculty
of law delhi university
subscribe to one india channel and never
miss an update