- The people in this video take
being lucky to the extreme,
from finding a $250 million
lottery ticket on the street
to winning the championship game
with a full court basketball shot.
- That's extremely lucky.
- NASCAR crew dodges two cars.
- Dude, I love NASCAR.
- Into the danger zone.
- Jason-
- Jason!
You're in the danger zone!
- Jason, man.
- Jason, gosh darn it.
Get out of the danger zone!
- Jason,
you're not Jason Bourne!
- Jason don't know nothing but jacking.
Look at him.
He jumped with a floor jack.
Those things weigh like 60 pounds.
That's insane.
- Right, so they're riding a rollercoaster
and he catches someone's phone
that fell off a different rollercoaster.
- Wait, 'cause now he can probably look
through that guy's phone
and embarrass him and stuff
and that's pretty funny.
- Imagine falling from this.
- Imagine dragon.
Yo, they were asking for
that to happen once, dude.
- Oh, boy.
- Those are blanks.
Okay, those are blanks.
Yeah, it was probably just the air.
I don't know.
Well, mm.
I saw like a little,
it looked like there might
have been a little projectile.
- So this is, uh.
- No way.
- Your local WWE.
- Did you see the guy on the side?
He was like, "Yo, turn around.
You just did the coolest
thing I've ever seen."
- Okay, so he's jumping up.
Oh!
- Wow.
- Oh!
- I don't know if that was luck.
That looked like skill.
- What is this?
- This is tree falling.
- Nani?
- Nice. He made a new tree.
- Oh, there we go.
Okay, okay, I'll approve, I'll approve.
All right gentlemen,
this is why you should
always wear safety goggles.
- Number one, I saw this on TikTok.
Number two, it's proven fake.
- I wanna believe it's real.
- No, it's on the internet.
It's fake.
- No!
- Everything on the internet's fake.
- I just wanna believe that he's sawing,
it snaps in half and that catches it.
That's so cool.
- I watched a long video about this.
He was in a submarine.
- Uh-huh.
- It sank to the bottom,
it had an air pocket.
It was on the bottom of the ocean.
He was living in an air pocket
in pitch black for four days.
He felt sharks swimming
around him and everything.
- Oh my gosh.
- In freezing cold water, dude.
- And they got him out?
- Yeah, they got him out.
- Let's high five for that guy.
This is a state championship game.
The team in black is
currently up by three points.
He misses.
- Oh, that's a miss.
That's a big miss.
- Okay, look.
Half a second is left on the clock.
- Wait a minute, Jimmy,
where he's standing at,
approximately would be worth three points.
No chance he makes it, Jimmy.
Wow, that's sick.
- Ooh.
- This is why I'm scared of baseball.
I got hit in the face with
a ball like that one time.
Look at that.
- Dude, it literally
went across his chest.
- Just catch it.
- What do you mean just catch it?
He tried.
- Just catch it.
This is why I don't ice climb.
- This is like that "Modern
Warfare II" mission.
It kind of looks like he hit it.
- He's only climbing
with those two sheaths.
- And his feet have spikes on him.
That's the only other thing.
- Oh my God.
- No rope, no nothing, dude.
- If you lose your footing,
it's just that one thing holding you up.
- Mm-hm.
- No, never ice climbing.
- Whoa.
That's in.
- Oh, might have been an accident.
- Stay in your lane.
Yeah, it's an accident.
- So they collided.
This guy's knocked out.
- Just blacked out.
- Wow.
- Nice.
- He just saved his life.
All right, so these workers
are working on a building.
Whoa.
That's like a Minecraft sand trap.
- Oh my god.
Look at that guy on the pole.
- He's just like,
"This is the safest spot. I know it."
- He bought a lottery ticket,
a winning lottery ticket,
but he left it at the store.
And thankfully, an honest
cashier came to the rescue.
- You work at a gas station,
someone buys a lottery ticket.
- Mm-hmm.
- They leave it there.
- You grab it.
Next day you find out,
it wins a quarter of a billion dollars.
You giving it back or you keeping it?
- To the bank.
I would anonymously leave
him a million dollars.
- Yeah, maybe two.
- To be nice.
- Two million.
- But look, that's on you.
Finders, keepers.
- Losers, weepers.
Oh.
- Wow.
- Bro, come on.
We do Team Trees
and this is how he pays
back Mother Nature.
- Geez, that tree said,
"Mm, it's your time."
- Right, this guy's on the ladder.
- Oh, Christmas lights.
This is why I don't hang Christmas lights.
- Oh, oh.
- Dude, imagine not being alive anymore
because you were hanging Christmas lights.
- Oh, thank gosh he had help.
- Wow, he had a lot of help.
- It's like they were just
waiting for it to happen.
- Yo, if I ever fall off a roof,
I better have six dudes come help me.
- Okay, so he's driving.
- Getting a lot of sway going.
- He seems to swerve.
Yeah, he's noticing.
- Oh, Lord have mercy.
- He's noticing.
Dang.
- Oh, what's gonna happen?
Oh, wait, is it loose?
- No, it's still connected.
It's a trailer but it's getting sideways.
Man, he handled that incredibly.
- Never let 'em know your next move.
- I was about to say.
- This clip has the title
card of an inch away.
And before we watch the clip,
I just wanna say I don't understand
why that's in the World's luckiest clips.
- Because-
- That seems pretty far away.
- An inch is a ton of space.
Some would say it's
almost a little too much.
- I mean, he still hit that sign.
Through that sign.
- Move your car now.
- Skater.
- Oh.
That was a pretty cool trick in itself.
- Kid, you are what Chris wishes he was.
- Hey, no.
What I wish I was,
was that Sabrett hot dog.
'Cause that thing look good.
- The best evasive
maneuver I've ever seen.
- Whoa, oh.
Kicking drywall is so much fun.
Oh.
A lot went wrong so quick.
- But also right.
Oh.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- Don't have to know sports
to know that was sick.
- West Brick capitalized on the Brick.
- He did, that was beautiful.
- That was very cool.
Crazy ping pong saves.
Oh, he's only got one arm.
Whoa.
- Whoa.
That's cool.
Congrats to you.
- He didn't even react.
That's how you know
he's been there before.
Oh, that's a giant hole, right?
Am I looking at a hole?
What am I looking at?
- Oh.
- Oh my goodness.
- Wow.
How does the guy who's currently
standing there feel safe?
He's like, "Let me get closer to the edge
just so you can see it."
Humans are dumb.
I love people, but humans are really dumb.
- We've all seen this clip, all right?
He's getting interviewed.
Boom.
- Was that fake? Did that happen?
Did that turn out fake?
- I don't know, it's kinda hard
to believe it's real 'cause watch, see,
it's coming, coming, he gets it.
- Oh but wait, you can't,
this isn't a picture, you
can only Photoshop pictures,
you can't Photoshop video.
- So far, I'd say these
people are pretty lucky.
- Yeah, lucky we didn't
call 'em out sooner
on the fakeness.
- He hit the mother load.
- Three or four other
people's unluckiest days
became his luckiest day ever.
- Does he get it?
- Oh.
No way.
- Really?
He's in too deep.
- Oh, shake it, shake it, shake it.
Why would you not just kick it? Come on.
- This is intense.
- He can do it.
- Come on, come on.
- Nice, he got the whole lot.
- Bro, look at that genuine excitement.
- He's like, "I only had to
pay for half these chips,
oh my God!"
- If you haven't already,
hit the subscribe button,
we're gonna let someone
random that subscribes
in the next seven days fly here
and lightly punch Chris like this.
So if you wanna punch Chris, subscribe.
- Gotta be light.