I am dead!
Don't hit me!
You won't listen otherwise!
This is your punishment!
I won't make a mistake again, madam!
Don't hit me!
Idiot!
You broke my chandelier
worth 10,000!
Who will pay for the damages?
Answer me!
Secretary!
- Yes madam!
Deduct the damage costs every
month from his salary!
But madam!
- But what?
This man has been kept on
a 15 days trial basis!
His salary has not been fixed!
Then fix it, and deduct
the costs from it!
I will fix it and..
- You shut up!
Shut up!
Secretary, please keep quiet!
All of you listen carefully!
If anyone makes a mistake,
or does such a damage.
Then I will teach him a lesson!
Secretary!
- It hasn't been fixed.
Shut up and follow me!
Definitely! Definitely!
"Heartless,
gave me so much pain.."
"..without knowing
how delicate my heart is.."
"This cruel world.."
Bravo Saigal sir.
I am fed up of your tape.
I am standing here!
You always listen to
such ancient songs.
What has happened to you?
Why didn't you drink this milk?
Milk! What milk?
- This milk!
It was very hot.
So I thought once it cools down..
Whether it is hot or cold,
you will have to drink it.
Come on, give him the milk.
- Yes madam.
The servants have other work too.
They don't have time to listen
to the tape like you.
Quickly drink the milk.
You have work too.
I stopped drinking milk
in my childhood..
..why are you giving me again?
Madam's orders.
What does your madam care?
First she gives me milk, then
eggs and then thrashes me.
Do one thing, you drink this milk.
Me!
- Yes. - How can I drink this milk?
From your mouth, how else?
Here, keep these pills too.
Drink it.
Bravo, drink it.
1!
2!
Brother Suraj!
- Yes!
Why are you gasping?
Nothing, I was just jogging.
The neighbour's dog
was scared seeing me.
And so he ran ahead
and I was behind him.
So I am gasping.
Okay!
So you mean,
you were exercising..
..and the dog came after you.
That's what I am saying.
I am telling the same thing.
But are you giving me
morning tea or not?
Why not, surely I will.
But this is a special tea.
Okay, so this is Mr. Vicky's tea.
It is so strange brother.
Until he doesn't drink the
tea prepared by me..
..he doesn't wake up.
He wakes up only listening
to disco and pop music.
But you are fulfilling your duty
by mixing your love in this tea.
But just see that useless,
does he care at all.
Heard that!
Now he will wake up!
Go!
Fulfill your duty, go.
Vicky!
Aarti you!
Why did you switch off the music?
First drink the tea, then
you can dance all you want.
Why do you come to disturb
me every morning?
Why do you bring tea
for me every morning?
Because I like doing things for you.
After all,
we are childhood friends.
Aarti, I am fed up of you!
We are no more children,
we have grown up!
The feelings of a person
doesn't change..
..when they grow up.
This girl won't understand.
Keep the tea!
Go! Go!
What are you saying Mrs. Poonawala.
That's just like darkness
under the lamp.
Just see, you are searching for
a groom for your daughters.
And I am looking for
girls for my son.
And both of us are looking
here and there.
Yes, yes for my son Suraj.
Do one thing.
Come home at 5 o'clock in
the evening for tea..
..along with your daughters.
This way, the children will
see each other too.
Okay then, see you
at 5 o'clock. Bye.
May I come in madam?
- Come in.
Good morning madam.
- Good morning.
Secretary, today at 5 o'clock my
best friend is coming for tea.
Along with her daughters.
To fix the alliance.
Be ready and..
- It's very nice of you madam.
There are very few women
like you in our country.
5 years after my wife died,
you thought about me.
Shut up you fool!
- Why shut up madam.
They are coming for Suraj.
- Oh! My fault! I am sorry!
Secretary.
- Yes.
Cancel all the appointments
that are in the afternoon!
How is that possible madam?
Today afternoon you have
to go to the widow home..
Secretary, do as I say!
- Yes.
Because today's tea party
is more important for me.
No arguments go home and make
all the arrangements.
Diary closed.
Come, come.
Come.
Miscreant, fell asleep standing.
There is always a party
in this house.
But today's party is very
important for madam.
Her son's alliance is
about to be fixed.
None of you should make a mistake.
If anyone of you makes a mistake..
..then I will be court-marshaled
along with you..
Secretary!
- Madam, good morning.
Good afternoon!
- Oh, good afternoon.
Have you explained them properly?
I was just doing that, madam.
If anyone makes a mistake.
Then I will flog him,
where is your uniform.
Madam, my child urinated on it.
Shut up!
Go and change your uniform!
Secretary, explain him!
I will explain him, madam.
Stupid, quickly go and
change your uniform.
Or else, you will also
do what your child did.
Correct.
Greetings mummy.
- What is this nonsense?
Even the servants of this
house speak English.
And even after doing M.A, you are
still stuck up in ancient era.
Greetings mother! Greetings father!
What is all this?
Look, if you want to live
in today's society..
..then learn its etiquette too!
And what are you wearing?
I want to see you well dressed,
up to date, but..
Mummy, a man's character is
reflected from his behaviour..
..and not his clothes.
Wow! What great thoughts.
Instead of taking birth in this
family, you should have..
Been born in a respected family.
Mr. Bhandari.
- Yes.
When I am talking to my son,
please don't interfere!
I know that he is your son..
..but co-incidentally I am his
father too. - Keep quiet!
I have been quiet right
from my marriage.
What was I saying?
I don't know.
I was saying, Suraj today
evening Mr. Poonawala..
..is coming for tea along
with her three daughters.
Really!
But why?
Because she is searching for
a groom for her daughters.
So, will he marry all
those three girls?
Mr. Bhandari again you..
- Good afternoon everybody.
Hi! Hi mom!
Hi dad!
Hi brother, how are you?
You are looking so
smart and handsome!
Where are you going?
There is a tennis match
in the college.
I am getting late, mom.
- Wish you all the best! - See you.
Bye.
By dad.
- Bye.
Did you see your younger brother?
He is so smart and mod.
- A lot.
I had dreamt the same
things about you, but..
Yes, the dreams she had seen
for me, those are shattered.
Now she wants to make
you the scapegoat.
Mr. Bhandari, I told you..
- I am sorry.
Suraj!
- There.
Please keep quiet!
- Alright.
Suraj, guests are arriving
in the evening.
Before that, you will
come in my room.
Because I will select
your dress, understood.
Mummy, I will..
- No arguments, that's all!
Father..
- No arguments.
There is no place for arguments
in this government.
Didn't you hear? Go!
This government has to change.
First you change you clothes.
Gopi.
- Yes madam.
I am getting Suraj ready.
Inform me as soon as Mr. and
Mrs. Poonawala arrive.
Go.
No good.
O yes! This is the colour.
Wear this Suraj you will
look very cute in this.
What a beautiful colour!
Mummy.
- I like this.
Mummy, you are treating
me like a child.
Can't I..
- Will you keep quiet?
Do as I say!
They will be arriving.
Come on wear this, no arguments.
Thank you.
Come, come Mrs. Chunawala.
Oh no Mr. Bhandari.
How many times have I told you!
I am Mrs. Poonawala
and not Chunawala.
It is so, rose called by any
other name is still rose.
It won't turn into a cauliflower.
What?
I didn't understand what you meant!
You will not understand,
your husband would have.
I say, your husband is so fortunate.
He got such a lovely wife like you.
You are married.
But you don't look like you are
a mother of three children.
Thank you very much
for the compliment.
You have maintained
your figure so well.
So nice.
Tell the secret to my wife too.
Her waistline is increasing.
Mr. Bhandari.
Come, come you have
a very long life.
We were just talking about you.
There is a call for you, please go.
No, there is always a call
for me at such occasions.
Forgive me Mrs. Chuanawala..
Kathawala!
No, no Tambakuwala..
- Poonawala.
What difference does it make?
Rose flower, cauliflower,
did it make any difference.
Mr. Bhandari!
- Yes, I am leaving.
Mrs. Bhandari, your husband
is so interesting.
He talks so well, how sweet of him.
Mrs. Poonawala, Thank you very much.
This is my son, Suraj Bhandari, M.A.
Greetings aunt.
- Greetings.
Son, these are my daughters.
Anita.
- Hi.
And she is Vanita.
- Hello.
And this is Sunita.
- Hi.
I have come for her alliance.
- O, I see.
Aunt, if you don't mind.
Can I see your bungalow
along with Suraj?
Why not?
There is no need to ask for that.
Suraj, show her our bungalow.
But mummy, there is nothing
to show.. - Come on.
Come on.
Listen, bring tea, coffee, cold
drinks and something to eat.
Yes madam!
- Go!
Mrs. Bhandari.
The pair of your Suraj and my
Sunita will be very nice.
Come.
Seeing the house is
just an pretence.
What is your opinion about me?
Very nice, but first see the house.
These long stairs,
they go to the sky.
And my mummy's bedroom is there.
And down there is
my daddy's bedroom.
These stairs lead that way.
Really?
- Yes.
But where is your bedroom?
I am stuck in the middle.
Come on.
Mrs. Poonawala, I don't have any
objection to this alliance.
But all of this depends
on Mr. Bhandari.
Last week, Mr. Bhandari had come
with her daughter's hand.
And he has promised to give
lakhs of rupees in dowry.
Just say yes to this alliance.
We will give so much
to Mr. Bhandari.
He will be fed up of counting it.
There you are, so sweet.
And the both of us will teach
them such a lesson..
..they will never forget.
I am against taking dowry.
But now that you are forcing me.
I cannot hurt you.
We are not giving anything to you.
We are giving our daughter.
And this is our cold water fountain.
Very beautiful.
And this is its cold water.
And this is our ancestral cheetah.
Is it alive?
No, it died seeing our mummy.
And our mummy had brought
this whip as dowry.
Come on.
Mrs. Bhandari, see a good
date and inform us.
We will complete the ritual
of the engagement.
You are very, very interesting
person Mrs. Poonawala.
Thank you very much
Mrs. Bhandari.
This is my bedroom.
Bedroom!
- Yes!
Wow! Lovely.
Our bedroom is so nice.
Our bedroom!
- Yes.
Our mummy is fixing our alliance.
There is a pain in my head
so I suddenly remembered..
..that I have a bad eyesight.
So I have to go to the doctor
to have my eyesight checked.
If I miss this, then it will
be delayed for a month.
Because the doctor is suddenly
going to America.
So you rest in my bedroom.
- Okay.
I will just come.
Listen to me.
Chunawala!
I knew that you will be shocked.
Its fine son, get married.
You will become a millionaire.
To hell with such money father.
I don't want such money.
Father, I want a simple girl.
Someone who can take care of me.
Who can share my happiness
and sorrows!
Can understand my emotions.
Son, if you want such a wife.
I feel you won't find her
in this life. - Why?
Because your mother won't allow..
..such a daughter-in-law
in this house.
There aren't such daughter-in-law's
in modern families.
I feel so suffocated here.
I don't know how you have
been tolerating..
..this modern house for so long.
For that you need a
very strong heart.
And son, the tolerance that
you always talk about.
I will tell you.
My father was a very poor man.
And I had a very peasant job in
your mother's father's office.
Seeing my honesty and sincerity.
He married his daughter to me.
Thinking that I will show his
daughter the right path.
But I was a very sincere
and simple person.
I couldn't bring her
on the right path.
But she brought me in this house
as a live in son-in-law.
Then.. instead of a husband
I was more like her slave!
Father.
Anyway, it is our fate.
You feel suffocated, isn't it?
Do one thing, go to
some hill station
Lakhanpur is close-by.
A friend of mine stays there
Lakhanpur, please alight.
Alight quickly, we have
to get down too.
It is too late.
In the front.
Come on, let us have tea Ramesh.
Listen brother.
- Yes, what is it?
Which way is the guest house.
- That side.
There.
- Yes, on the left.
Thank you.
"I am a betel leaf seller."
"Without a shop."
"The entire village
eats my betel leaf."
"Whether it is Delhi or Chennai."
"Or whether it is
Mumbai or Kolkata."
"This green leaf is the antidote
for all the ailments."
"Mister, have a betel leaf."
"My betel leaf is very nice."
"My betel leaf.."
"My betel leaf is famous
all over India."
"Hey mister."
"Hey sir."
"Boy, have a betel leaf."
"My betel leaf is very nice."
"Mister, have a betel leaf."
"After eating it,
there is redness on the lips."
"And a glow on the face."
"After eating it,
there is redness on the lips."
"And a glow on the face."
"Have a betel leaf."
"Your wife will be floored."
"A gentle smile will solve
all your problems."
"Mister, have a betel leaf."
"My betel leaf is very nice."
"If you want to appease
your beloved."
"You want to fix your
broken alliance."
"If you want to appease
your beloved."
"You want to fix your
broken alliance."
"Take this betel leaf along."
"Everything will be right."
"The youngsters, children and
old are fan of my betel leaf."
"Mister, have a betel leaf."
"My betel leaf is very nice."
"Whether it is a jamboree."
"Or singing or dancing."
"Eat a betel leaf."
"And entice the entire jamboree."
"Every jamboree is incomplete
without a betel leaf."
"Mister, have a betel leaf."
"My betel leaf is very nice."
"My betel leaf is famous
all over India."
"Hey mister."
"Hey sir."
"Boy, have a betel leaf."
"My betel leaf is very nice."
"Mister, have a betel leaf."
1.. 2.. 3.. 4 and 5!
What is it mister?
Do you want a betel leaf?
Yes, I want a betel leaf!
Then take it.
Take it.
What are you staring at?
Haven't you seen a girl before?
I have, why won't I?
But not in this form.
Do you come here
to sell betel leaf?
No, no I just arrived
here few days ago.
To visit my uncle.
This mobile betel leaf shop is
not Shalu's, but her uncles'.
He is ill today, that's
why I brought it.
Fine.
You sing very well.
No sir, I sing because these
days everything is sold..
..while singing.
You have to take trouble to
allure the customers, mister.
Have you come from the city?
Yes, I just arrived.
The guest house..
Where is the guest house here?
There it is.
That one.
- Yes.
How much for your betel leaf, Shalu?
No mister. Today you
are a guest here.
I won't take money from you.
It is not the tradition to
take money from the guest.
If you take betel leaf tomorrow..
..then I will take money first.
Fine.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Watchman! Watchman!
Coming sir.
Greetings sir.
- Greetings.
Is there a room available
in your guesthouse?
Room! Sir, the entire
guesthouse is empty.
Give me the luggage.
- Come sir, come.
Come, come.
Jaggu dada is here!
Run!
Hey, run!
Run for your lives!
Mister, just wait.
What is it?
Has someone
died in the village?
Donations are being collected.
Keep quiet, speak softly.
If Jaggu dada hears you.
Then he won't spare you.
Jaggu dada, why?
He comes here every week,
and collects money.
Everyone has to put something
in that cap.
And the one that doesn't,
he doesn't spare him.
Is that so?
Listen to me, and put
something in that cap.
Otherwise he
will not spare you..
..and smash your betel
leaf shop too.
Understood.
- Yes, I understood.
You go!
- Okay!
Which scoundrel did this?
I don't know Jaggu dada!
I don't know!
Tell me, who did this?
I don't know Jaggu dada!
I don't know! - Tell me!
I don't know! I don't know!
- Tell me!
I will beat you to a pulp!
You don't know.
Hey, I am dead. I am dead.
Jaggu dada,
why are you asking that weakling.
I have done this.
Really, you have done this.
What is your name?
My name is Shalu.
Shalu!
Here!
Where will you go!
No one should cast an evil eye.
Quiet!
Shalu, where will you go!
You!
Thrash him!
Leave me!
I will not spare anyone!
Hit him!
Hit him, smash him.
Here sister, adorn him.
O wow, this is absolutely
an original garland.
I'll be right back.
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Get up! Get up!
Forgive me!
If you ever come to
this village again.
Then I will beat you to a pulp.
What?
- Beat me to a pulp.
Yes! Run!
Run!
Great Shalu, you taught
that goon a nice lesson.
Look at how he ran.
He must have learned his lesson!
He would bother us everyday.
Now he will never come
to this village again.
Live peacefully.
May God bless you!
Shalu, you were really great.
You taught a nice lesson
to that strong goon.
Mister, this was a
very small example.
Whoever has locked
horns with Shalu..
..she has always taught
him a lesson like this.
Oh yes, did you get a room
in the guest house?
Yes I did.
Bye then.
Suraj has crossed all limits.
He has been missing from
home since yesterday.
Without informing!
Do you know anything?
No.. maybe he went with
his friends for a picnic.
With whose permission?
Only your permission is
followed in this house.
But if you..
- Keep quiet, please!
Secretary.
- Yes madam.
What are you looking at?
Quickly take the car out and go!
I understood!
Go and search for Suraj sir,
and bring him before you..
..either dead or alive.
Shut up!
Understand the situation
before speaking!
Go and search for him, shut up.
Yes madam! Sorry.
Shall I keep seated
or shall I get up?
Keep seated!
- Thank you!
This boy has really troubled me.
If Suraj is not found by evening..
..then what will I tell
Mrs. Poonawala.
Mrs. Chunawala..
- Mrs. Poonawala, not Chunawala.
Yes, slip of tongue.
I will explain to Mrs. Chunawala..
no, Mrs. Poonawala nicely.
Mr. Bhandari!
Don't try to be too
free with my friends!
You know my nature.
What else do I know in this
world other than your nature?
Then listen one thing carefully.
- Yes.
My son should be here
within 24 hours!
Look that depends on the Lord.
But as far as 24 hours are
concerned, that's impossible.
You need at least 9 months for that.
Mr. Bhandari! - Slowly, or oil
will sprout out from earth.
My head is about to explode!
Do you need an atom bomb?
No, isn't it?
She is enough to blast
the entire world.
Think what my condition is.
Greetings sir.
- Greetings.
I have brought tea for you.
Bring it, I need tea.
Tell me sir, did you face any
difficulty in the night?
And did you sleep peacefully?
I slept very peacefully.
Really sir!
- And I saw very nice dreams.
Dreams!
Watchman! The first thing that I
sighted entering this village..
..her name is Shalu.
What a beautiful face!
What melodious voice!
She talks nicely too!
And she is so brave!
Sir, it is so great if 1 girl has
so many qualities. - Isn't it?
And watchman, I have been dreaming
about her the entire night.
Really!
That's why you are looking so happy.
Sir, where does that girl live?
Even I don't know that!
I was thinking about asking you.
What does her parents do,
where does she live?
Sir, I will find that out.
- Yes!
Sir! Sir!
Hide me somewhere, sir!
Hide me somewhere!
What is the matter, Shalu?
Why are you so scared?
What shall I tell you,
this is what you say..
..l didn't do anything
and fell into trouble.
Yesterday I had thrashed that goon.
- Yes.
Today he has come with his goons.
And Shalu is in trouble.
He might come here too.
Hide me somewhere!
Why are you worried, I am there!
I will take care of everything.
- Yes.
You will take care of everything!
- Yes, of course I will.
Mister, then may your children
have a long life.
For your information I must tell
you, I don't have children!
Why, you couldn't have them.
Of course I would have.
If I would have been married.
You are not married.
I am unmarried too.
You are not married!
Then I am happier to meet you!
Yes!
Watchman, Shalu has come.
Go bring tea for her!
I will just bring it sir.
-Please come.
Why are you turning back,
no one will come.
Come, come.
Sit on the sofa, not down there.
Here.
- Then, what is this sofa for.
Sit, sit.
Shall I tell you one thing, mister?
- Yes.
You have so much respect
for the poor.
This difference between
rich and the poor.
We humans have made it.
For the Lord, all human
beings are the same.
They are, isn't it?
Shall I tell you one
more thing, sir? - Yes tell me.
I don't understand what you say.
But it feels very nice to hear.
Shalu, shall I ask you something?
- Ask.
Where is your house?
- Very close-by.
You can come now if you want.
I will give you corn bread and
leafy vegetable curry to eat.
We will eat that later.
Shall we first take a
look at your village?
Village! Come on.
- Come on.
Wrapped in the arms
of the mountains..
..your Lakhanpur really
is very beautiful, Shalu.
I feel like staying back here.
There is such serenity here.
That means you liked
my village very much.
Very nice.
But not as nice as you.
Why are you joking mister.
What is so special about Shalu?
You won't understand Shalu.
By seeing some faces
you understand..
..the Lord has taken a lot of
effort in their creation.
And seeing your face, I feel
framing it in my eyes.
Don't move! Don't move! Yes.
You move a lot.
If you move the photograph
will not be nice.
Smile.
Are you ready now?
What?
What are you saying, mister?
It means, are you ready or not.
I am ready.
Yes, very good.
Don't move.
Done.
- First class.
Come on.
Except for an uncle, I don't
have anyone else mister.
Really.
He is my mother and my father.
He loves me so much.
I feel like taking care
of him all my life.
All your life!
That's fine Shalu, but you will
have to leave him someday.
Why?
Don't you want to get married?
Who knows mister, whether
I will get married or not?
You will, why you won't get married!
It is said, matches
are made in heaven.
There must be someone
in your fate too.
On that note I remembered..
..an astrologer told
me the same thing.
That your fate lies on your palms.
Mister, do you know
how to read palms?
Read palms.
- Yes.
Read your palm.
Yes, I can.
Read my palm.
Shall I see your palm?
- Yes. - Sit.
Mister, you have been holding
my hand for so long.
What's written in my hands,
what do the lines say..
..tell me something.
In your palms.
It is written Shalu..
Shalu your hands are very beautiful.
You have already said that.
Let go of my hand.
Mister. This Lord Shiva
temple is very famous.
There is a Shiva's veneration
held here every year too.
Really.
- Yes.
Whatever you wish for with the
true heart, it is fulfilled.
This temple is so powerful.
Shalu.
Let us wish for something together.
Yes, but tell me what
we should wish for.
Leave my hand, mister.
You want to free this hand.
And I want to ask for
you from Lord Shiva.
This is my desire Shalu.
That we are bonded
in such a relation.
That no one can ever break.
Look mister, I am a simple
girl from the village.
I can't understand what you say.
What are your intentions?
Shall I tell you?
Yes, say it.
Shalu, I have fallen
in love with you.
What? Really mister?
Yes Shalu.
Shalu!
Shameless! Characterless!
Weren't you ashamed defaming me!
Why didn't you die of shame!
But uncle..
- I am no more your uncle!
Listen! You are needlessly
getting angry on her!
It is not her fault!
Keep quiet mister!
I have seen everything
with my own eyes.
You city people always do
this with us village people.
We sow the seeds.
We look after it.
When the harvest is ready..
then you people come to cut it.
Get one thing clear, sir.
She is my child! Jagat Dada's!
I will kill her,
but I will not let anyone touch her!
Come on shameless!
- Uncle.
Come on!
Your uncle is dead!
Mister, you!
Shalu!
Shalu, I am very sorry that..
Why mister!
Lovers have to face more sorrows.
No Shalu.
I am responsible for these sorrows.
And it has brought me here.
At least my sorrows
were of some use.
But mister, you..
- Shalu!
Mister, you are so stubborn!
You have come again to meet Shalu.
I ask you, do you rich people
have some respect for us poor?
Uncle, why are you taunting
me of being a rich man!
It is true that I was
born in a rich family.
But being poor is neither
a fault nor a crime!
And actually, I haven't
come to meet Shalu..
..I have come to meet you.
- Why?
Uncle.. I want to marry Shalu.
You are capable and close too.
Shall I look at you or talk to you.
Tell me.
What can I say mister?
From today, you are my lord
and Shalu is your servant.
You are not my servant, you
are the queen of my heart.
Shalu, I never thought I will
find you in the village..
..and we will get married so soon.
It is the magic of your love.
Mister, it is not magic.
You used to say, matches
are made in heaven.
That's right too.
But look, enough waiting.
Now remove this veil.
You are very foolish mister.
How can I remove the
veil, I feel shy.
You are feeling shy, and
I am losing patience!
I want to see how my Shalu
looks as a bride.
No, no!
Will you see my face for free?
Won't you give me a token?
I will give a nice token but
not to you, to your pink lips.
Shalu!
Shalu, what is this misbehaviour?
It is a mischief.
A wife's face should be like this.
Not this, like this.
Like the rose flower.
"The rose flower."
"One in a million is the
face of my beloved."
"The rose flower."
"The cool breeze."
"Someone should learn from
my beloved to praise."
"The rose flower."
"The cool breeze."
"The fragrant henna
in your fair hands."
"The bangles tinkle in
your delicate wrists."
"The bangles tinkle."
"The attitude of my beloved."
"My beloved is feeling shy."
"The rose flower."
"In the shelter of fragrance
there are so many flowers."
"The colour of love
sister-in-law true."
"The rest are false."
"The ambience is so beautiful."
"What can I say, I am in trouble."
"The cool breeze."
"The waves are stable."
"The current is steady."
"Our eyes narrate our
saga of the night."
"Saga of the night."
"The promising ambience."
"All our life, we will sing
the melody of love."
"The rose flower."
"One in a million is the
face of my beloved."
"The cool breeze."
"Someone should learn from
my beloved to praise."
"The rose flower."
"One in a million is the
face of my beloved."
"The rose flower."
"One in a million is the
face of my beloved."
Vicky, you..
What are you looking at?
You are looking very handsome today.
What is this misbehaviour?
This is not called misbehaviour.
I have applied the black
spot on your cheek..
..so that no one casts
an evil eye on you.
I don't believe in
all this nonsense.
What is the matter?
Today you are going to the
college very well dressed.
Look, I have told you not
to interfere in my matters.
You always obstruct
my path like a cat.
What did you say?
I look like a cat!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
The cats will feel bad.
You are a bat.
Fine, you can say whatever you want.
I have noted down everything.
Let us get married,
then I will take my revenge.
Aarti!
Don't forget your status..
..before dreaming to become this
family's daughter-in-law!
I didn't take mercy on a helpless
and orphan child..
..so that when she grows up,
she considers herself..
..the daughter-in-law
of this family.
There is no comparison
between my son and you!
Correct mummy.
That's what I keep explaining
this girl.
But she doesn't understand?
Go! Go and do your work! Go!
Get out!
Well done mummy!
Mrs. Forgive me, but I didn't
like your behaviour with Aarti.
Mr. Bhandari, will.. - Let me
tell you for your information.
This girl is not the servant
of this house.
She is the daughter of your
late father's friend..
..Dharamdas, whom he handed
to you while dying.
I think that girl needs more
love than Vicky and Suraj.
Look dad.
You can give all the love
you want to Aarti.
But I don't have any soft
corner for Aarti. - Really.
Goodbye mom. See you.
- Bye Sunny.
Did you hear your son's decision?
Remember it.
Yes I heard it. I spent
all my life listening.
Dear.
Yes.. yes uncle.
Aunt scolded you, didn't she?
That's her habit, you know that.
She always speaks bitterly.
I am her husband, when
she doesn't spare me..
..then how can she spare you.
No uncle, maybe I forgot my status.
What is a status?
In this world, your deeds
decide your status..
..and not wealth and money.
I had come to say.
Until I am there, I will
always be with you.
The Lord will surely heed you.
Come on smile.
Why are you acting miserly?
Come on.
Hi Pinky.
So you found time to meet me.
Sorry, I am late again.
There is a black cat in my house,
she crossed my path.
That's your everyday reason.
But today I am not going
to listen to you.
I am angry with you.
No my darling, Pinky.
Don't do that darling.
If you get upset with me, then
my heart will stop beating.
You know how much I love you.
Please.
Forgive me this time.
You can be forgiven.
But on one condition.
I accept all your conditions.
Really!
- Really!
Shalu, you are crying as
if I am going on war!
It is just a question of 4 days.
I will be back soon.
Then you will have to
take me along too.
I have explained you so many times,
but you don't listen.
It's not right for you to come
along with me right now.
Why? Why isn't it right?
I have married you, I haven't
committed any sin.
I agree you married me.
Can't you wait for me for 4 days?
I have explained you everything
about my family..
..about my mother.
Still you are being stubborn.
Don't you have faith in me?
Then swear on me, you
won't forget me.
What are you saying?
You are now a part of my life.
Can I stay alive forgetting you?
Fine.
I agree.
But if you take more than 4
days, I will give up my life.
Don't say that.
Look, now that I am leaving.
Let us part happily.
Uncle, take care of Shalu.
I am giving you her responsibility.
Return soon.
The life of my daughter
rests in your hands.
Don't leave her in a dilemma.
How can that be?
Don't worry at all.
I will return soon
and take her along.
Oh, Joker!
Declare!
Take a look.
Damn it!
Full hand again!
I haven't declared a
game since morning.
Aunt, brother Suraj has returned.
Suraj! Come here!
Yes mummy!
Where were you?
Mummy, I was feeling
very uneasy here.
So I went to Lakhanpur.
What, Lakhanpur!
Yes, the atmosphere
there is very nice.
Stop it!
I am not asking you about
Lakhanpur's climate, idiot!
Answer me!
I had informed.. daddy.
Who is daddy?
Am I no one in this house?
Don't I have any position
in your view?
No mummy, why not.
You have a very dynamic position!
Then why did you dare to
commit such a mistake?
Do you know how ashamed I felt
in front of Mrs. Poonawala?
I am sorry Mummy.
It should never happen again.
Nothing can happen in this house
without my permission.
Understood! Go to your room!
Go!
Stupid!
Come on lets change our bets.
Brother Suraj!
Here, have tea.
I don't want to drink it.
Calm down and have tea.
You know aunt's habit.
She has..
- What?
Did she have to insult me
in front of all her friends?
Am I a child?
Don't I have any respect?
Then why don't you talk to aunt?
Why don't you talk to aunt!
Have you ever heard
the name of Hitler?
When he used to speak, all
the colonels would shiver.
People would become silent.
And you say, try talking to mummy.
My mummy is no less than a Hitler.
But seems like I will
have to talk to mummy.
Tomorrow, Monday 15th February.
10 o'clock in the morning
you have to inaugurate..
..the new showroom of Magnum Videos.
Then 11:00, a debate..
..in the oppressed women's
committee office.
At 12 o'clock, lunch at
Mrs. Bhanupratap's.
At 13 o'clock..
- What?
Sorry, sorry, sorry
madam my mistake.
I mean, tonight you have to attend
the dinner at Khanna brothers.
And you have to give a
small speech there too.
Oh yes. I remembered.
The speech that I had given in
the last fashion show. - Yes.
Did its photographs arrive?
Arrived!
I also sent it for getting it
published in the newspapers.
How were the photographs?
Don't ask me madam, only your
photographs are nice..
Superb! Superb!
One of the photographs is so
nice, so nice I tell you.
Even Ms. India '88 will feel shy.
And if it would have
been in Technicolor.
Then Cleopatra would
have died of shame.
I tell you. Lovely.
The editor has written
a caption below it.
What?
- Shameless..
Excuse me mummy, can I come in?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Mummy, I wanted to talk to you..
..about something very
important and personal.
Sorry, sorry.
- Can't you see how busy I am?
We were discussing such
an important topic.
Mummy, for a mother what
can be more important..
..then her child?
- Suraj!
I don't like your behaviour at all!
Now you go to your room!
And I will call you
when I get the time!
Please go!
Get out!
Everyone is getting so bold.
This is the limit!
Madam.
- What is it?
Can I give you an idea?
- What idea?
Someone has right said.
When the horse starts getting
out of control..
..then you should put
a muzzle on him.
My idea!
Good, I know.
I will talk to Mrs. Poonawala
for his engagement.
But before that, you have
to give a small speech..
..in the anti-dowry committee.
I know, I know. Please keep quiet.
Sorry, sorry.
'If you take more than 4 days,
then I will give up my life.'
Suraj!
Come, come. Come mummy.
Why did you take the trouble,
you could have called me.
At least you got time.
I don't even have time to die.
Then how can I get time to
listen to your nonsense!
Its not nonsense mummy..
I have come to tell you
that tomorrow evening..
..the Poonawala family,
are arriving for your engagement.
My engagement!
- Yes.
Don't disappear again!
But mummy..
- I don't want to hear anything.
This is my order, and you
be ready! Understood!
Mummy, listen to..
Mummy!
Father, good that you have come.
I was waiting for you.
I know why you were waiting for me.
Your mother has sold you..
..and she has made
quite a good deal.
Now you will be a millionaire
too, like me.
Father, why are you sprinkling
salt on my wounds?
So soon you have got wounds too.
What will you do if you have
to tolerate it like me?
Don't worry I will heal your wounds.
Come into my room.
Yes, come on father.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very much.
If I had known I will get
so much to eat here..
..then I wouldn't have
eaten anything at home.
Seems like you don't get
anything to eat at home.
I do, but it is not that tasty.
Is it not tasty or you don't
get to eat at all.
Greetings.
- He is..
I will tell you.
I am Mrs. Kamla Bhandari's husband.
But you might have a position
in this house too.
No, I don't have a position.
Since my name was connected
with my Mrs..
..I lost my position.
Just like the attached bathroom
is not mentioned..
..with the bedroom.
You can call me Mrs. Bhandari's
attached bathroom.
It is not something to laugh about.
It's a damn fact.
Have you inquired about
the character of the boy?
Yes, we have inquired about
your son's character.
Your son has a very good character.
Yes, he has a very good character.
But we don't want to
keep you in the dark..
..because we have to face
the Lord too, after death.
The boy does have a vice.
What do you mean..
The boy.. don't tell anyone.
I feel ashamed saying it.
Drinks alcohol.
Gambles.
Goes to brothel.
Is non
- vegetarian.
He eats onions.
What does he eat?
- Onions! Onions!
Mr. Bhandari, you scared me.
- I was just tying.
But where is your onion eater?
Good evening, Mr and Mrs. Poonawala.
Good evening Mrs. Bhandari.
Mrs. Bhandari, before you begin.
Was there a call for me?
No Mr. Bhandari.
Until the engagement
is not complete..
..there won't be any calls for you.
- So sweet of you.
Come.
Take a seat.
Suraj.
- Yes.
Meet him.
He is your father-in-law,
Mr. Poonawala.
Hello, God bless you.
Sit, sit why are you standing.
Thank you, thank you.
Mrs. Poonawala, it took
me a while to get ready.
I am sorry.
Did you mind?
Not at all.
If women don't take time to
get ready, then who will?
Isn't it?
- You are absolutely right.
I think we should commence
the engagement ritual.
Yes, yes.
Mrs. Bhandari, there is nothing
wrong if we wait a while.
There is a possibility that
Vicky might arrive too.
Oh yes.
Here come the trumpets!
- What?
I mean, the band is here.
- Band!
Mrs. Poonawala, you brought a
band for the engagement too.
Not at all.
Why would I bring a band?
You are done for?
- What?
I mean, if the band has arrived
then we should go..
..and take a look, Mrs. Chunawala..
..Mrs. Kathawala! Mrs. Koylawala!
Which one is it?
- Poonawala.
It's one and the some.
- Come on
Let us take a look.
- Come on.
You might have never
seen such a band.
"When the groom doesn't
take the bride..
..along after marriage."
"Then the bride arrives in the
palanquin to take the groom."
"My beloved!"
"My beloved! Come to me,
come before me."
"I have come to pick you up."
"I have come to pick you
up along with the band."
"My beloved! Come to me,
come before me."
"The promise that you made."
"Don't forget that promise."
"Don't bring a mistress
until I am alive."
"Don't bring a mistress."
"Take a look."
"Take a look, don't turn away."
"My beloved! Come to me,
come before me."
"I didn't tell a lie."
"I didn't say anything wrong."
"Then why do you sweat
seeing me, my beloved."
"Why do you sweat?"
"Take me inside the house."
"Open the door."
"My beloved! Come to me,
come before me."
How did you like my song and dance?
You are a very ill-mannered girl!
I thought you have come
on the occasion..
..of my son's engagement.
And will take some reward
by singing and dancing.
But you needlessly created a stir!
My beloved was getting engaged..
..that's why I created a stir.
It's my mistake, forgive
me mother-in-law.
What?
How can I be your mother-in-law?
What else will I call the
mother of my husband?
Husband! What husband?
This mister, who else?
What nonsense!
Suraj is your husband!
Then what?
Am I insane to come here from
Lakhanpur in the palanquin?
Along with the band.
Ask your son.
Mrs. Bhandari, what is all this?
Suraj, what is all this?
Is she your wife?
Mummy, the thing is that..
Tell her, tell her.
When we have fallen in love,
then why to be scared!
Yes, there is nothing
to be scared.
Say it, come on say it.
That's the flaw in your mummy..
I mean good quality.
She likes the truth, isn't it?
Look, she is saying yes.
Tell me son.
Yes mummy, I have married her.
What?
I am so unfortunate!
Mrs. Bhandari, we are
the unfortunate ones!
We didn't know, that
your entire family..
..was such great liars!
Weren't you ashamed getting
my spinster daughter..
..engaged to your married son?
When the snacks were tasty,
I felt something was suspicious!
There is something wrong!
Forget about that!
If we want, we can sue them for..
..10 lakh for this cheating!
But we.. we are not
so lowly like them!
Come on! Come on!
- Listen to me!
Keep it to yourself!
Come on children, come on.
Suraj!
Suraj, I feel like strangling you
or swallowing poison myself!
You made this performer
our daughter-in-law!
Mr. Bhandari, what
are you looking at!
..Then what should I see?
What, can't you say something?
What should I say?
Your son has defamed
us so shamelessly!
Then why are we yelling
outside here.
Let us do one thing,
let us go inside.
We will sit at the round
table and think..
..how we can get your fame back.
Science has progressed a lot.
Anything can happen.
My idea!
- There.
My idea.
- To hell with your idea!
Secretary.
- Yes madam!
Follow me!
- I am following! I am following!
Definitely, definitely madam.
Don't feel bad about what
your mother-in-law said.
It is her habit.
But this child is innocent.
Why are you still standing
here silently?
Go!
Take my daughter-in-law inside.
Mummy..
- Nothing. Go!
Bless you, dear.
Come Shalu.
Ramayana is over, now
Mahabharata will start.
Pray for me.
Sister-in-law wait.
Let me perform the lamp veneration..
..before you enter the house.
Aarti!
Get rid of all this!
I can never accept this uneducated..
..ignorant girl as
my daughter-in-law.
"Let's built a nice bungalow.."
Mr. Bhandari!
- Who is it?
What do you mean?
Here you are dreaming, and I
am facing so much trouble!
What?
- What do you mean?
Do you have time to
do anything else?
I have Saigal sir to listen to,
and you are there to scold me!
What else do I need?
Tell me how I can serve you!
As if you don't know anything.
Your son Suraj has
done such a thing..
..that I cannot face anyone!
What are you saying? What happened..
Thank God, atleast he
heeded to my request.
..What do you mean?
I mean, when there such a
good husband in the house..
..then what is the need to show
this face to anyone else.
You always take everything jokingly.
And here, I am burning up.
I can smell something
rotten burning.
I am sorry, it is your heart.
Shall I inform the fire brigade?
They will come quickly
and douse the fire.
Mr. Bhandari, this fire can
never be doused! - Really.
Foolish Suraj has brought an
uneducated and ignorant girl..
And tarnished your desires
and smoked your emotions.
Isn't it? - Keep quiet,
for Gods sake keep quiet.
I had seen so many dreams
for my son Suraj.
But he brought a performer
in this house!
What had to happen has happened.
Forget it.
She will stay in this house,
and have a meagre meal.
What difference does it make?
You are talking about meagre meals.
Mr. Bhadari, if I let that
ignorant, uneducated girl..
..stay in this house
for a second more.
Then my name isn't Kamla Bhandari!
Understood!
I want to build a nice bungalow!
Keep making bungalows
the entire day!
Seems like there is a horse-shoe
affixed in her feet.
She will not let me
build a bungalow.
Shut up.
Call me mother-in-law, will you!
Come on.
What is the matter mother-in-law?
Come with me!
What are you doing mother-in-law?
I understand the mentality
of village people like you.
And I know your motive of
coming in this house.
Marriage is just an act
that you have put up!
All you want is money!
Here. Here is what you want!
Take all you want.
And get out of this house.
Right now.
Didn't you hear what I am saying?
Take all the money and
wealth you want!
And please leave my son alone!
What are you saying mother-in-law?
He is my husband.
And husband is considered
as the Lord!
And you never sell your husband,
mother-in-law.
I have not come in this
house for the money.
I have come for your love,
mother-in-law.
For out love!
I understand you very well!
I don't want to hear another word!
Get out of here!
then mother-in-law,
my answer is that..
..a daughter-in-law comes
in the in-laws house..
..in the palanquin, and
leaves on the pyre!
Now I will not leave this
house till I am alive!
I agree that you were helpless.
But, you couldn't
even send a letter.
Look, whatever the Lord
does it is for our good.
If I would have written
you a letter..
..I would have asked
you for more time.
Then this wouldn't have happened!
But Shalu!
I have told you a lot of
things about my family.
You have a small example yourself.
I think will you be able to
live in this atmosphere.
Why not!
For a married woman, the in-laws'
house means everything.
Now I will bring happiness
in this house.
A man gets rewarded by
the men's committee.
It is said, that husband beat
his coarse wife to pulp.
For that.. he was awarded
a gold medal.
Father-in-law.
Come dear.
Greetings father-in-law.
- Bless you dear.
I have brought tea for you.
Why did you bring it, isn't
there a servant in the house?
There are a many servants in
the house, father-in-law.
But it is my duty
to look after you.
Here.
May God bless you, dear!
I have brought tea for
mother-in-law too.
No, Wait! Wait! Wait!
The serpent is asleep,
don't wake her up..
..or else she will wake
up and bite you.
Don't worry father-in-law.
Why won't I worry for you, you
are advancing towards trouble.
Mother-in-law.
Who the hell is it?
You!
How dare you come in my room?
With whose permission
have you come here?
Why have you come here?
I have brought tea for
you, mother-in-law.
Who asked you to bring the tea?
Where are all the servants
of the house?
I said get out!
But..
- I said get out!
Mother-in-law.
Get out of my room!
Get lost!
God knows why this uneducated..
..ignorant girl comes here?
Why has she come here?
She ruined my entire mood.
I had warned you.
Don't provoke your mother-in-law,
you didn't agree.
Everything went wrong, right?
This..
- No need to be shocked.
Every morning in this house,
the English ghost wakes up..
..then you get to hear such music.
And then you can hear
the utensils clinking.
But father-in-law,
this is not right.
It is not right it is
a very bad thing.
But what can I do, who
will speak against it.
Father-in-law,
can I say something?
What?
From tomorrow, this will
not happen in this house.
It has been happening
since many years..
..what's so different
about tomorrow.
Just watch, my name is Shalu.
"You name is true."
"You solve all our problems."
"You are merciful like the ocean."
"And it has no shores."
"You solve all the problems."
"Whenever anyone calls you."
"I recite your name!
I recite your name!"
"In the morning and evening."
"You solve all our problems."
"You name is true."
"Lord, show the right path to
the ones that have strayed."
"Let love blossom in every house."
"You help everyone."
"Without being asked
or any expectations."
"You solve all our problems."
"You name is true."
Stop singing!
Didn't you like my devotional song?
No, no dear, that's not it.
After so many years, I have heard
something good in this house.
Otherwise, everyday in this house..
..all we hear is disco
and rock music.
All day, we have to hearing
horrible sounds.
What do you mean Mr. Bhandari?
You call our western
music, horrible.
Your music!
Don't mind madam, but just
like someone else's wife..
..cannot be yours when
brought in the house.
Just like that playing someone
else's music in our country..
..doesn't make it ours.
Dad, mummy means that we are
a fan of western music.
Why are you looking up there?
I thought this fan.
Western music has become a part
of our house and culture.
Won't we feel bad if someone
insults our western music?
Yes, of course you will.
You are absolutely right my son.
I cannot wake up until
I don't hear pop music.
I don't get the mood
to do anything.
It's the same about
you too, isn't it?
Correct mummy, correct.
From 7 -8 o'clock in the
morning we are so used..
..to hearing pop music, just like
father likes to read the newspaper..
..and brother, likes to exercise.
Vicky, there is a big difference
between your likes and ours.
Reading the newspaper gives
you a sharp mind..
..and by exercising
you remain healthy.
Just great!
Since this ignorant
girl has arrived..
..you have got a tongue too.
That's not it, mother-in-law.
There is a saying, when
the morning is fine..
..the entire day goes well.
If you take the Lords
name in the morning..
..you find peace and serenity.
Wealth flourishes in the house.
Wealth flourishes!
- Yes.
What nonsense!
Secretary!
- Yes madam.
Find out when will
the electricity come back
There is no point
in doing that, madam.
Something that is not gone,
cannot come back.
And something that cannot
come back, how can it go.
What do you mean?
I will tell you mother-in-law.
The electric fuse, I
have taken it out.
Now everyday from 7-8 o'clock
in the morning..
..this will happen.
- What?
Yes.
- Disgusting!
Come on son.
Secretary, follow me!
- Yes madam.
Is this a house or an asylum?
I can't stay in this house!
These are mad people!
God, please save me.
She is a very dangerous woman.
This girl has already started
doing as she pleases!
I can never tolerate this.
She has just taken the electric
fuse out now madam.
That day is not far, when she
will devour your happiness.
And there will be darkness
in your life forever.
That will happen only when I will
let her stay in this house!
You shouldn't let her stay, madam.
What I am there for?
Nut for that I will have
to think of an idea.
I will tell you tomorrow.
Why tomorrow, why not today?
Today, it is very inauspicious
for you.
What?
- I mean tomorrow.
Tomorrow is a good day to
start anything auspicious.
Tomorrow is the tenth day
of the auspicious month.
Right you are.
- Thank you madam.
My token.
I was just a bit late in coming,
and my beloved is ready..
..to go to the factory.
Here, have milk.
I don't want it.
Don't want it! Beloved,
are you upset with me.
I should be upset with you.
You switched off the electricity,
Shalu.
What?
I mean..
- You mean the fuse!
Yes, that.
Why did you raise such a
stir in the house, Shalu.
Beloved, this house belongs to
me as much as it does to you.
I am the daughter-in-law
of this house.
And it is my duty to mend anything
that's wrong in this house.
Shalu, my mother.. mummy.
Nothing happens in this house
without her permission!
Why are you locking horns with her?
Why are you worried?
It is between me and
my mother-in-law.
I will deal with her myself.
Here, drink the milk.
"What can I do my joys turned
into sorrows.."
Father-in-law.
Father-in-law!
"What can I do my joys.."
Come dear, sit.
I haven't come here to sit, but
to give you your medicine.
Medicine!
Why, what's wrong with me?
You.. you are suffering
from pressure cooker.
Pressure cooker.
- Yes! - Me!
Speak softly, or else the
police will arrest you.
Can any man have pressure cooker!
- No.
What is it called in Hindi?
Yes, you have blood pressure.
Blood pressure!
What is there to laugh?
Father-in-law!
You should take this medicine
every morning, right?
Right!
Then why don't you take it.
Come on, take it.
- Not now dear.
I will take it later.
You go, I will take it later.
- You will have to take it.
Right now.
Happy.
If you don't take your medicine
regularly from now on.
Then I will be very angry.
No dear.
Let the entire world be angry
with me, but not you.
But dear, tell me one thing.
Who told you that I
have blood pressure?
Who will tell me?
I live in this house father-in-law!
It is my duty to look
after this house.
And father-in-law, there
is one more thing.
Tell me dear.
Whether there is chaos or
destruction in the world.
Always be happy.
Dear, I was never happy before.
But now that you have come,
I will surely be.
I will.
At least there is someone in this
house to take care of me.
Go dear, go.
Good afternoon Mrs. Bhandari.
What a pleasant surprise,
chairman sir!
No phone, no cable, when
did you arrive brother?
If I had known, I would've come
to the airport to receive you.
Take a seat.
No, no.
I don't have any right
to sit on that chair.
Because that chair belongs
to the managing director.
Okay, okay.
- You sit there.
And I will sit here.
You were supposed
to come next month.
How did you return so soon?
That was my schedule, but the
chairman of Tokyo's firm..
..is here these days.
I have a very important
meeting with him today.
If that meeting is successful, then
tonight we will leave for Frankfurt.
Leave these business talks aside.
Tell me, how is my friend, wife
devotee Mr. Kailash Bhandari.
Come on brother.
He is very happy.
He always thinks about you.
But you don't get time to come home.
I will come the next time.
- Promise.
Promise.
So madam Bhandari, tell me how
is your company running?
The company is running fine.
But I need some money
for a new business.
Actually, the entire capital of
our company is in rotation.
I don't know what to do and
how to arrange for the money.
Mrs. Bhandari this is foul.
You cannot say that
until I am there.
Don't forget, I am the chairman
of this company..
..and the financer too.
Oh yes.
Tell me,
how much money do you need.
Right now I need 10 lakh.
If I require more,
I will ask you for it.
O sure, why not.
Why did you leave the dance?
I was very tired.
Then order for something cold,
you will feel fresh!
Waiter!
- No, let it be.
Vicky, I had told you
something yesterday.
I completely forgot about
it because of this disco.
Here, this sister-in-law 3,000.
Will this do?
Of course.
I have taken money from
you earlier too.
I will return it as soon
as I get daddy's draft.
Don't be silly.
Is there any difference between
your money and mine?
I can even give my life for you.
Now come on.
Let's go and dance, come on.
Come on.
Ramu! Sevak! Gopi!
Where are you all?
Yes Vicky sir.
Who did this to my room?
I will tell you brother-in-law.
The happiness that you got seeing
the decoration of this room.
I should be awarded for it.
Give me my reward.
I feel like giving you
such a fitting reward..
..that you will never dare
to come into my room again.
Why? Why?
Have I made a mistake?
Look, you can do whatever
you want in this room!
I don't care!
Just like that, you shouldn't
have any relation..
..with me and my room!
If you try to lock horns with
me, then remember this..
..I am a very bad man.
You don't have to tell
me that brother-in-law.
What did you say?
Vicky!
Sister-in-law is considered
respectable!
And you are raising
your hand on her!
No, no it is not
brother-in-law's fault.
It is my fault.
Forgive me brother-in-law.
Forgive me.
You should be ashamed.
Who cares!
Gopi!
Ramu! Sevak!
Why doesn't anyone listen?
Has everyone gone deaf?
- Madam! Madam! Madam!
Sevak went to the
market a while ago.
Where are rest of them?
Don't they know there is a kitty
party in the house today?
There is a lot
of work in the house!
How innocent, you don't
know anything.
What?
The servants of this house
have been given leave.
Leave!
- I mean dismiss.
I mean, they have been thrown
out of this house.
Who threw them out?
Follow me.
- What?
Sorry, I mean I'll tell you.
Uneducated! Ignorant! Rude!
You are telling me!
No, your daughter-in-law.
How dare she?
Hey secretary.
Here she comes.
Why do you provoke
her against me?
I have thrown the useless
servants out of the house..
..I haven't committed any sin.
Who are you to give
orders in this house?
Being the daughter-in-law
of this house..
..don't I have that much
right, mother-in-law?
I can see that you are
crossing your limits.
Is this your father's house?
Not, but it is my mother-in-law's
house.
And then I haven't committed
any crime.
A house where only 4 people live..
..what's the use of
8 servants there.
I do half the work.
Shut up!
- What's that?
Secretary!
- Yes madam.
Explain this ignorant woman!
Calm down! Calm down!
I mean, keep quiet!
Shut up means keep quiet.
Say it that way.
Secretary!
- Madam.
Follow me!
- Yes, yes.
There is an interesting story
behind this necklace.
I had gone to buy something else..
..in Trikamdas Khimji Zaveri's
shop, I spotted this necklace.
It is worth 5 lakh rupees.
This necklace was made
to order by someone.
Then how did you get it?
Why wouldn't he give it?
I told him clearly, if you don't
give me this necklace..
..the I won't come to your
shop the next time!
And poor guy, gave it to me.
And anyway, I am their
regular customer.
You are really great Kamla.
Wherever you go, you get your
work done with your influence.
Leela, why are you sitting
with a sad face?
I am not in the mood at all.
Why?
What shall I tell you?
When there is a ignorant
daughter-in-law in the house.
Then how can the mother-in-law
be happy.
We argue everyday for something.
Now you tell me, I am the
owner of this house.
And she gives the orders.
How can I be in a good mood then?
Kamla, who is she?
I never saw her before.
Her! She is our new maid!
She is very decked up.
Mrs. Bhandari, be careful.
In a house of bachelor boys,
such maids sometimes..
..play their tricks.
Why are you sitting here?
Then should I sit on your lap!
There was space, so I sat here.
Will you have grams?
It is good for your metabolism.
Seems like she has forgotten
her position.
I know my position.
Isn't it mother-in-law?
Mother-in-law!
- Yes.
Kamla, what nonsense
is your maid talking?
Excuse me madam,
don't be deceived!
I am not the maid, but the
madam of this house!
I mean, daughter-in-law.
Mother-in-law, why don't
you tell them?
Okay, if you don't then
I will tell them.
Listen carefully.
I am the wife of his
elder son, Suraj.
And I know all of you quite nicely.
All of you come here to brag or
to insult your daughter-in-laws.
And that's what you teach
my mother-in-law too.
But listen carefully.
If that's what you want
to do, then from today..
..you are not welcome
in this house!
Did you understand?
You didn't understand!
This is too much.
Come on, to hell with
this kitty party.
We will not come here again.
Where are you all going?
Please stay.
Why should we stay?
Your daughter-in-law
insulted us so much..
..but you didn't say a word.
Shame on you!
Come on!
Listen.
Keep listening to your
daughter-in-law.
Mother-in-law, did I
commit any mistake.
I only said the truth.
Stop this nonsense!
You defamed me in front
of my friends.
Today I will bring
you under control.
Mother-in-law!
I have taught a lesson
to many with this whip!
If I don't teach you
a lesson today..
..then my name isn't Kamla!
Don't think I am a helpless
woman, mother-in-law.
I am a strong village girl.
If I make a mistake, then you
can punish me in anyway.
I won't say anything.
But if you ever raise your hand
on Shalu without any reason..
..then be prepared for
the consequences.
Secretary!
Save me!
Fool! Idiot!
- I know!
She is not weak and delicate
like the city girls.
She is a solid woman of the village.
Please excuse me madam.
If woman would have
been a solid thing..
..then her name would have been
Dara Singh, Dilawar Khan..
..Muhammad Ali etcetera.
Women are delicate.
She doesn't have any value
in front of a man.
No, no, except for you.
Not every woman can be Mrs.
Kamla Bhandari.
Don't talk nonsense!
I am getting furious, and you
are blabbering nonsense.
Think of an idea to defame her..
..so that the work is done
without much effort.
I have an action idea.
With your permission can I say?
- Quickly.
Look madam, when things cannot
be done the right way..
..then it's best to
use wrong methods.
The idea is to shatter her pride.
Then why don't we hire some
goons and teach her a lesson.
There you are.
The idea is not bad.
But we have to be very careful.
Don't worry, no one
will know about it.
Just that, she should go
out of the house alone.
Alone!
That can happen only on Tuesday.
Because she goes to the
temple for veneration.
Then let Tuesday be the day.
Come! Come!
What is it brother, do
you want the offering?
..Here.
No dear, we want you
not the offering.
Wait, wait.
You want me, isn't it?
- Yes.
Then I will come along with you.
Just a minute.
Hail Lord Krishna!
Tell me! Who sent you here?
Tell me, or else I will kill you!
Tell me!
I will tell you! I will tell
you! I will tell you!
I will tell you!
Thank God you weren't hurt
much sister-in-law.
Shalu!
What happened, why have
you tied a bandage?
Sister-in-law was hurt brother.
Hurt! Shalu, again you..
- Why are you worried?
I didn't fight with anyone.
I had gone to the temple, and there
are monkeys in the temple.
Seeing the offering in my
hands they came before me.
While shooing them off,
I slipped and fell!
Is it paining a lot?
Shall I call the doctor?
Doctor! What will the doctor do?
I have applied clarified
butter and turmeric!
Even the biggest wounds heal.
And until I have the grace
of Lord Krishna..
..and the blessings
of my mother-in-law.
No one can harm me.
Isn't it secretary?
Yes, blessings are very powerful
like electricity.
Secretary!
- Madam!
Follow me.
- That way.
Pinky, how long will we
keep meeting like this?
I want to get rid of this
distance between us.
And come along with me to
my home day after tomorrow.
I will introduce you to my mummy.
Why is that?
Until mummy doesn't see how..
..how can she say yes for
our marriage? - Marriage!
But Vicky, what's the
haste to get married.
Right now.. That's fine.
What's the objection
in meeting mummy?
She is going to like you.
That's fine, but I don't have
a proper dress to wear.
And how can I meet your
mother is these clothes?
That is no problem.
You don't have clothes.
But there are a lot of
clothes in the shops.
Finish this, after that I
will take you for shopping!
Buy anything. Okay.
- Okay.
Let us go. Drink it quickly.
Flop! Flop! Flop!
Every idea of your flops
in front of that girl! - I know.
She is always two steps
ahead of you. - I know.
She has made my life hell!
I don't know what to do!
Sorry madam, even I can't
understand what to do.
Die of shame!
You can't think of a good idea.
That's it.
I have it madam, I have it.
- What?
As you said die of shame,
an idea immerged..
..from the depths of my mind..
Then say it, you fool!
Madam, not here.
Anyone can hear it!
Follow me.
- Secretary!
My mistake!
I mean, come here.
Say that.
- My mistake.
It is such a beautiful
place, isn't it?
That's fine,
mother-in-law.
But I cannot understand one thing.
Why are you so grateful to me?
It is not that confusing dear.
The relation of a mother-in-law
and daughter-in-law..
..is stronger than the relation
of mother and daughter.
That's right!
And there isn't any
mother in the world..
..who won't be grateful
to her daughter.
Just wait here for a while, I will
arrange for something to eat.
Okay.
- Nice.
Don't go anywhere, stay here.
Mother-in-law!
- Save me!
Doctor sir, what's the
condition of my wife?
Slowly, why are you
taking the trouble?
I mean..
- There is nothing to be scared.
It is a mild attack of pneumonia.
She will be fine soon.
She will be fine!
- Sure.
No, I was just..
Okay Mr. Bhandari,
I will leave now.
I will come again in the evening.
It's fine even if you don't come.
I mean.. such a big injection
it will pain here.
But mummy, what was the need
for you to go to the river.
I was getting bored at home.
You were getting bored.
- Yes.
I thought it will be
a nice outing.
And I will take
daughter-in-law out too.
Inside the water.
Tell me one thing.
How did you fall in the water?
The water is very scared of you.
I mean, you are very
scared of water.
Daddy, someone must have
surely pushed mummy.
Shall I tell them the truth,
mother-in-law?
Why are you all so worried?
I slipped near the shore of the
river and I fell in the water.
You slipped.
- Yes.
That means,
along with the tongue..
..now you can't even control
your feet, isn't it?
Mr. Bhandari!
- I was just giving an example.
Every joke has a limit.
Vicky.
Why don't you understand
my feelings?
I love you.
But even though we stay
under the same roof.
We are strangers to each other.
I love you Vicky, I love you.
Aarti!
What are you doing in my room?
Staying in the company
of the ignorant woman..
..you are becoming ignorant too!
I ask you, why do you
trouble me always?
Because I love you.
But I love someone else.
I hate you!
Do you understand?
Get out of here.
Vicky, someone has instigated you.
Now stop this nonsense, stop it!
Look Aarti, I will not tolerate
you in my room again.
Don't come here!
Why are you still standing here?
Get out! Get lost!
I could never have thought, you
will behave like this with me.
I am going! I will never
bother you again.
I will not love you too.
You hate me, don't you?
I will hate you too!
Now I won't come back
even if you call me!
I will never return!
Aarti, tears are the
symbol of cowardice.
Yes I am a coward,
sister-in-law.
I have lost and my heart
has been shattered.
Yes, I know.
My brother-in-law has broken
your heart, isn't it? - Yes.
So what?
There are sorrows and happiness
on the path of love.
But Vicky hates me
sister-in-law.
Some other girl
dwells in his heart.
Who is she?
I don't know.
Whoever she is, she can't
be sweeter than you!
Because you love
my brother-in-law.
And love is very strong.
One day he will surely melt.
But he is so heartless.
Foolish, everyone has
feelings in his heart.
Have patience.
I will tell you what to do.
Wipe your tears, and come with me.
Sanjay, you take everything lightly.
Why don't you understand?
The matter is very serious.
I understand everything, darling.
Let this act continue
for some more time.
It is for our own benefit.
This act cannot continue any longer.
I fooled Vicky as much as I can.
He is getting serious day-by-day.
He is going to take me along with
him to introduce me to his mummy.
And I cannot do that.
I love you Sanjay.
Think of something, how can
we solve this problem?
He must be arriving.
Then come on, let
us go to the beach.
We will think of something there.
Okay.
- Come on.
Aarti.
Follow him!
And find out who the
wicked woman is..
..that's creating an obstruction
in the path of your love!
But sister-in-law.
- No ifs and buts.
Go quickly. I am telling you.
Listen Sangita.
- Yes.
Have you seen Pinky?
Maybe she has gone
on the beach.
Which way?
- This way.
This way!
- Yes
Darling,
I don't want to meet Vicky.
This problem should be solved
anyhow, understood.
Don't worry darling, I will
take care of Vicky.
Pinky!
Vicky!
You cheat! Deceiver!
You betrayed me!
I will kill you!
- You!
I won't spare you too!
Scoundrel! You rascal!
No!
Cheat! Betrayer! I
will not spare you!
Vicky!
Aarti!
- Vicky!
Aarti, what did you do?
Vicky I..
- What did you do Aarti?
I have answered your hatred, Vicky!
No Aarti, I will not let you die.
Doctor sir, how is Aarti?
We cannot say anything until the
patient doesn't regain conscious.
We are trying our best.
Get this injection.
- Okay.
I will get the injection,
don't worry.
Lord, till today I haven't
done any good work in life.
But still I beg of you
for Aarti's life.
Save her Lord!
Save her!
Brother-in-law!
You are pleading for
that girl's life.
Don't be a fool, brother-in-law.
Let that unfortunate girl die!
She has no one in this
world to cry for her!
Brother-in-law, you kept
hating her all your life.
Then why is there sadness
on your face.
Who are you pleading for,
brother-in-law?
For her sister-in-law, whose love
I could never understand.
For saving my life,
she risked her life.
If something happens to her,
then I will die too.
I will die too, sister-in-law.
Don't worry brother-in-law.
Nothing will happen to Aarti.
The love for her in your heart.
It will heal her wounds.
Yes.
Sister-in-law, I misunderstood
you too.
Forgive me sister-in-law.
What are you doing brother-in-law?
Humans make mistakes.
Not Lords.
Shalu, doctor says
there is no danger..
..Aarti has regained conscious.
You go!
Thank God!
My brother-in-law has
come to his senses too.
Wow madam, wow.
You are great.
Whenever I see you sitting with
all the family members.
I think about the great
empress Noorjahan!
She used to sit like this
in her court. I tell you.
Secretary sir.
- Yes.
Where did you see empress
Noorjahan's court?
You must have seen it in heaven.
Great!
Seeing all the members
sitting together
Talking to each other, it
is such a pleasant sight!
Here mother-in-law, offering.
Take it.
Why are you distributing sweets?
I had asked for a boon.
This offering is for that.
Can I have it?
Yes, why not.
You should give the offering
to the beggars first.
Secretary. Here.
Thank you.
At least someone started the
tradition of offerings and boons.
But dear, what boon
had you asked for?
For the marriage of
my brother-in-law.
He has agreed.
Now we will get him
married very grandly.
Isn't it brother-in-law..
- What did you say?
Who are you to decide
my son's marriage?
I will get him married. To Mr.
Bhanupratap's daughter.
That will bring a lot.. - She will
bring a flow of money in this house.
And we will have to change
the name of this house..
..from Swarg to Gangotri.
I don't want wealth daddy,
I don't want to be lost in it.
And that's why I have
decided to marry..
..an orphan and helpless girl.
Who is that girl?
She is standing before you, mummy.
She! This girl!
We brought her up, and now..
..she will be the daughter-in-law
of this house!
Have you gone mad!
No mummy, I was mad
but now I am fine.
And now I have decided,
I will marry only Aarti.
It's not you, but this ignorant
woman speaking!
You have learnt to
misbehave from her.
Mummy, learn to speak properly.
Sister-in-law is considered
respectable.
Bravo son, for the first time
you have talked sense.
Secretary!
- Madam.
Follow me.
- Definitely.
Daughter-in-law.
Give me this offering first.
I will sweeten my mouth first.
- Here.
"No body should cast
an evil eye on you.."
"You are very beautiful.."
Stop this music!
- Sorry, sorry!
I was just trying
to divert your mind, madam.
Tonight is a very painful
night for me!
I didn't expect this from Vicky,
at least.
No, no madam.
If you ask me, then it
is not Vicky's fault.
He has been instigated against you.
And it is entirely that
woman's doing..
- You are right.
What magic does she have,
that enchants everyone.
Like P.C Sarkar.
Great magician.
One by one,
she has captivated everyone.
Only Vicky was remaining.
But today he was captivated too.
What?
I mean, he was enchanted
by her too.
The only thing that's
troubling you..
..is that simple girl
has made my life hell!
Get rid of her.
What do you mean?
You are misunderstanding me madam.
I have such a great idea,
that will get rid of her.
What's that?
Sorry!
Secretary.
- Madam!
Follow me.
- Definitely.
Wherever you say!
What are you saying,
mother-in-law?
Why would I steal?
Does anyone commit robbery
in their own house?
Please explain her.
Yes mother, how that is possible.
Shalu can never do such a thing.
I know her very well.
Why are you talking childishly,
Suraj?
It doesn't take time for
the milk to get spoiled.
And the intentions to change!
This girl had seen
what's in my safe!
And I am completely sure.
She has committed the theft.
And that's why she has come in
this house from the village.
You can say whatever you
want, mother-in-law.
But don't accuse me of theft.
May I die, if I have even
touched your safe!
Mummy, I saying it again.
She cannot do such a thing.
She doesn't have any
greed for anything.
And still if you are not satisfied..
..then you can search our room!
Secretary! Search the place.
Sevak, search the place!
Below the watch!
Behind the statue!
Below the bed!
Now tell me!
Answer me!
How was this jewellery
found in this room?
And that too, it was found
in your cupboard.
No!
You said, may I die if I
have touched your safe.
Then, have I kept this
in your cupboard.
Mother-in-law, I don't know.
How this came here?
Dear, you know your
Shalu is not a thief.
Say something.
What will he say?
Secretary!
- Madam.
Call the police.
- Yes madam.
Mummy, there is no need
to call the police.
It will create a scene.
Fine.
Ask her to leave this
house right now.
Sevakram, bring this to my room.
Secretary. Follow me!
Yes madam!
Dear, are you very upset?
Look, you are dearest to me!
I swear on you.. I am innocent.
Yes.
That's what you say, Shalu.
But what difference does that make.
In this house, until my mother
doesn't consider your innocent.
Neither can I say anything
nor do anything.
That means.. that means you
feel the same thing.
That your Shalu is a thief!
I don't point fingers at anyone
Shalu, I really don't.
For Gods sake, leave me
alone Shalu, please.
Mother-in-law.
You!
You still haven't left this house!
What harm have I done
to you, mother-in-law?
The Lord knows, I didn't
marry your son.
It was him who made me his wife.
Not at all!
A thief can never be our
family's daughter-in-law!
Don't call me a thief mother-in-law.
I haven't stolen anything from you.
You know that very well.
Why are you ruining my
happily married life?
Your married life!
Dreaming about something
more than your status..
..causes humans downfall.
- No!
But you didn't think about that!
That's why, you will
be punished for it.
There is no place for you
neither in our hearts..
..nor in our house! Get out of here!
No! This house is venerable
for me, mother-in-law.
Get lost.
Don't call me by that name.
We don't have any relation!
Get up.
- No.
Get out of here!
- I say, get out!
Thank God!
Sister-in-law! Sister-in-law!
Sister-in-law!
Where are you sister-in-law?
Look, what I have brought for you?
Vicky.
- Sister-in-law!
Aarti, where is sister-in-law?
Aunt threw sister-in-law
out of the house.
What! Threw her out of the house!
But why?
Aunt accused her of thieving.
And the stolen goods were found
from sister-in-law's cupboard.
No, that's a lie.
Sister-in-law can never
do such a thing.
This is surely someone's conspiracy.
'Sevak, what are you doing
in brothers room so late.'
'In brother's room.'
'I had gone to keep sweet porridge
in brother's room.'
'Sweet porridge!
- No.'
'But brother doesn't
eat sweet porridge.'
'I had gone to keep
in brother's house.'
'Milk!'
'Fine go.'
Vicky!
What are you thinking about?
Nothing, I will just come.
My name is Chameli..
- Sevak.
Yes Vicky sir, do you want tea,
coffee, Bournvita or Horlicks.
I don't want anything.
Tell me, what were you doing
last night in brother..
..and sister-in-law's room?
What was I doing?
I had told you, I had gone
there to lay the bed.
Lay the bed!
- Yes, to lay the bed.
But you had something
else at that time.
Said something else.
What had I said!
I remembered.
I had gone to keep the milk.
To keep the milk.
- Yes, to keep the milk.
You scoundrel!
Deceiver, sometimes
its sweet porridge..
..sometimes you say
to lay the bed.
And sometimes you say
to keep the milk.
Tell me the truth, or
else I will stab you.
I will tell the truth,
don't hit me.
Will you tell the truth?
- Yes, I will!
Come on.
Say it!
Tell everyone!
- Tell everyone what the truth is!
Or else I will thrash you!
What happened?
He will tell you that, tell them!
- I will tell them.
I will tell them!
Daughter-in-law is innocent!
She did not commit the theft!
Madam had asked me to
keep the jewellery..
..in daughter-in-law's cupboard.
When she isn't in the room!
Your scoundrel, I will kill you!
I will kill you! I will kill you!
Leave him!
What's the use beating him up!
The real culprit is your mother.
Leave him!
Get out of this house right now.
And if you ever come
in this house again..
..then I will kill you, understood.
Get out! Get out! Get out!
The scoundrel! Liar!
Brother, let mummy come.
If I don't make her admit her
crime, then my name isn't Vicky!
No Vicky, don't say anything
to anyone right now.
First we have to find
out where Shalu is.
God knows where and in what
condition the poor thing will be.
Look son.
In our country, girls that are
thrown out of their in-law's house..
..have only two choices.
Either she commits suicide.
Or she returns to her in-laws house.
"Lord, show the right path to
the ones that have strayed."
"Let love blossom in every house."
"You help everyone."
"Without being asked
or any expectations."
"You solve all our problems."
"You name is true."
Shalu!
Have you come alone?
Or have you brought the police
along to arrest me?
I have brought the bond
of love to bind you..
..which shattered somehow
without my knowledge.
I always knew that
you were innocent.
But the situation was such that,
I couldn't say anything.
And now I have come to apologise
to you, Shalu.
Everyone knows that it was
my mother's conspiracy.
I apologise on behalf
of my mummy too, Shalu.
I don't have any complaints
with anyone, dear.
I will surely get
what's in my fate.
But now I have taken
a decision, Shalu.
I have decided that we will
not go back to that house.
We'll go somewhere else, we
will live somewhere else.
We will live in a rented house.
Only we both will be there.
Where there will be only love!
And there will be no one to
commit atrocity on you.
What are you saying, dear?
I am not the type of girl that
separates a son from his parents!
I will return with
you to that house.
But on one condition.
Yes, tell me.
Promise me one thing.
You won't defame mother-in-law
for what you found out.
What are you thinking, beloved?
I can't understand Shalu.
What are you made up of?
Even after going through so much..
..still you don't have any grievance
against my mother.
You don't have any complaints
against her.
Dear, she isn't just your mother.
She is my mother-in-law too.
And mother-in-law is
just like a mother.
Isn't she?
Yes.
Then promise me.
Shut up!
Except for me, no one ever
took decision, no one can..
..and no one ever will!
Understood!
Day after tomorrow is
my wedding anniversary.
On the same day, I will announce
your engagement..
..with the daughter
of Bhanupratap.
Not at all, mummy.
I can leave your house,
but not Aarti.
I will marry only Aarti.
- What?
Can I dare to say something?
I think these days you should
agree to the children's advice.
This is my advice, the rest..
You keep quiet!
You have spoilt them!
No..
- Mummy!
Sister-in-law!
Where had you gone,
sister-in-law?
It was my mistake,
brother-in-law..
Move!
You have brought your beloved back!
You know she is a thief and not
worthy of living in this house.
Mummy, anyone can make a mistake!
Anyways, I have explained Shalu.
She will try not to give you
any reason to complain.
Yes mother-in-law.
There is no question of that at all.
Once I lose respect for
a banished woman..
..then I can't respect her again.
She doesn't want your respect..
..she just wants your blessings.
And I won't even curse her.
She is a thief!
Mummy!
- Brother-in-law!
I don't like mummy's behaviour.
Vicky, don't say anything right now.
Just calm down.
Come Shalu.
80! 85! 95! 100!
Secretary!
Why are you counting wrongly, idiot?
Count again!
- Again!
O God.
I swear on your father.
I swear on your great grandfather,
I will never listen to you..
Why are you speaking in Punjabi,
idiot!
I am speaking in Punjabi,
so that you get strength.
The food of Punjab is good.
Corn flour roti
and mustard spinach.
That song "Color me up.."
Shut up! Shut up you fool!
Forgive me my madam!
I will never forgive you.
You have taken so much
money from me..
..and all of your
ideas have flopped.
And that illiterate, uneducated,
ignorant girl..
..has come back in this house
to make my life hell.
I am sorry madam.
If you can forgive my last mistake.
Then I can present the
last idea of my life.
And I won't charge you
anything for it.
Free of charge.
What is it, tell me.
Come on get up!
You must have heard of the
great emperor Akbar.
One of my forefathers,
had give this idea..
..to the emperor Akbar.
Because of which, Anarkali
forever went away..
..from Salim's life.
You fool, what is the idea tell me.
It is not just an idea madam,
it is an atom bomb.
It can never fail.
If Suraj's Anarkali isn't
thrown out of this house..
..then your name isn't Mrs.
Kamla Bhandari.
What?
No, no, I mean my name isn't
secretary P.K Patiyalewala.
Tell me, what is it?
Move your specs and listen.
Specs! Why?
Good evening!
Happy wedding anniversary,
Mrs. Kamla Bhandari.
Come.
Greetings.
- Come, come.
Congratulations.
Mehra.
- Yes.
For the last 10 years, Kamla
has been celebrating..
..her 25th marriage anniversary.
But no matter what, my
sister-in-law still looks gorgeous.
Then what do I look like to you?
No, no you look like
a dazzling star too.
Happy now.
- Yes.
Excuse me!
I can't see your daughter-in-law
anywhere Mrs. Bhandari.
Where is she?
She is upstairs. She
is getting ready.
You please carry on.
"Mother-in-law, you.."
"You.."
"Mother-in-law, you didn't
know my value!"
"You never considered me
as a daughter-in-law."
"Always considered
me as a servant."
"Mother-in-law, you didn't
know my value!"
"Mother-in-law,
you didn't know my value!"
"Since I entered your home."
"I could never stay in
peace a single day."
"Since I entered your home."
"I could never stay in
peace a single day."
"You never listened to me,
always did as you pleased."
"Mother-in-law, you.."
"Mother-in-law, you didn't
know my value!"
"Abused me."
"Whipped me."
"Accused me of theft."
"Today I will tell everyone
about your atrocity."
"Mother-in-law, you.."
"Mother-in-law, you didn't
know my value!"
"I turned this house into heaven."
"Served you, tolerated
your attitude."
"I turned this house into heaven."
"Served you, tolerated
your attitude."
"I won over everyone with my love,
but you still remained a stranger."
"Mother-in-law, you.."
"Mother-in-law, you didn't
know my value!"
"You never considered me
as a daughter-in-law."
"Always considered me
as a servant."
"Mother-in-law, you didn't
know my value!"
"Mother-in-law.."
- Shalu!
What is this misbehaviour?
You are drunk?
Don't you care about the respect
of my family and me!
To whom are you saying that, son?
What will this shameless know
about honour of the family.
She is a stigma for this house
and not the daughter-in-law!
I am telling you son,
come to your senses.
And get rid of her.
This ignorant girl is not from
a respectable bloodline.
Mind your language!
You have no right what so
ever to abuse my father!
You committed atrocity
on me, I tolerated it.
Whatever you said to me,
I listened calmly.
But I cannot hear a single
world against my father!
What do you think, I am
ignorant, illiterate.
Uneducated!
For your kind information..
..I am much better educated
than you are!
I am an Oxford graduate.
Shalu.. - There is no need
to be shocked Suraj.
I have evidence of my truth.
Then.. till today whatever
happened, was that an act?
Yes, all this was an act.
And I ended it today.
Because there is a
limit to tolerance!
My mother-in-law tried every means
to throw me out of this house.
She had also made the
plan to get me drunk..
..and have me insulted
in front of everyone.
So that you develop
hatred towards me.
And you throw me out of
this house and your life.
But mother-in-law, I didn't
drink alcohol today.
I just swallowed my pride,
and created this scene..
..so that I get rid
of your ignorance!
You are very proud of your
wealth and your family.
I am not from a lowly family too.
Like you, I am the daughter
of a well-known rich person.
Do you know who my daddy is?
Mr. Ashok Mehra!
Mehra brother, you.. all this..
Is Shalu your daughter?
Yes, Mrs. Bhandari.
I am very proud of my daughter.
Actually you had seen her
when she was very small.
Then she went to London
for education.
But.. but why didn't Shalu
tell us that before?
Because it was your husband's order.
This act was put up on his will.
Daddy and uncle Bhandari wanted me..
..to come in this house
as Suraj's wife.
When he kept this problem
in front of me.
I accepted it as a challenge.
And I came in this house
by marrying Suraj.
I tried every way,
mother-in-law.
But I couldn't make a place for
myself in your heart, mother-in-law.
God knows, I have a lot
of respect for you.
Because you are the
mother of my husband.
I.. lost my mother
in my childhood.
I thought I will get a
mother's love from you.
But, I was not destined
for mother's love.
You didn't even consider me
as your daughter-in-law.
But today, I want to ask
everyone a question!
Why is a daughter-in-law
always destined..
..for her mother-in-law's abuses.
Is that why she leaves
her parents house..
..and accepts a strangers family.
Doesn't she have the right
to any happiness?
Mother-in-law.
You can keep your wealth,
your honour and your pride.
I am leaving.
Shalu! No!
As soon as you leave, this house
will turn back into hell.
And if you still want to leave,
then I will come along too.
No Suraj, you will find
a wife like me.
But you won't find a mother.
No matter how the mother is,
she is respectable.
Don't leave her for me.
Shalu.
- Let me go, Suraj.
If I have committed any mistake,
the please forgive me.
Come on daddy.
Wait daughter-in-law.
Even I want to say
something today.
For years I kept quiet.
Even though I knew what is
wrong and what is right.
I just kept watching
everything silently.
But today, I have found
my voice again.
And for the first time
I announce that..
..neither me or any of my son
will stay in this house.
What are you saying father-in-law?
This house belongs to you.
Dear, firstly this isn't a house.
It is a prison.
And this arrogant woman is the
owner of the grand prison.
And she rules with her stiff
neck, puffed nostrils..
..and a bitter mouth.
She gave birth to her sons.
But she took care of them
like a post dated cheque.
So that when they are
of marriageable age.
She can use them.
She doesn't know.
What sons are?
What duties a mother
has towards her sons.
When she doesn't know that!
How will she know what
is a daughter-in-law!
What a mother-in-law's duties
are towards her daughter-in-law?
I had created this scene.
With the help of my friend.
So that I can bring my
wife on the right path.
But I was unsuccessful.
She didn't come on the right path.
But I made Shalu's life hell by
bringing her in this house.
Shalu..
Just like for Sita, Ayodhya
was wherever Ram dwelled.
Just like that, our house
will be wherever you live.
That's heaven for us.
And after today, this
arrogant woman..
..will stay in her grand prison
like a wandering soul!
And will rule her safe, her
jewellery and her furniture.
And the day she dies,
there won't be anyone..
..to perform her last rites!
That day she will remember what
I said and die suffering!
Come on dear.
No, no stop!
Don't punish me so severely!
I am ashamed of myself.
Please forgive me!
Yes Kailash, forgive her.
She is the mother-in-law
of my daughter.
And my sister-in-law too.
Then ask her to apologise to
her daughter-in-law..
..take her in her arms and say..
..daughter-in-law's
should be like you.
Tell her.
Dear.
- No, what are you doing?
My child.
Secretary!
Secretary where are you going?
- No, no.
Come on get up, you
are ruining my shoes.
I was cleaning it.
So secretary, won't you give your
madam a mischievous idea.
No sir. Swear on you.
Swear on your father.
Do you have a father?
I don't know that sir.
- But your idea, wonderful sir.
Just wonderful.
Stop praising, and apologise.
Yes sir, forgive me.
- Not me, apologise to her.
To her, yes.
Forgive me.
Are you apologising or begging.
Sorry, sorry, my fault.
Come on, go there.
- Yes sir, definitely.
Children..
- Forgive me too.
So, you have come
on the right track.
Come children!
Why are you standing far,
come on.
Come dear.
Bless you.
Mehra.
- Yes Kailash.
Today even I can say proudly.
- What?
That wife should be..
- Like her!
"The rose flower."
"One in a million is the
face of my beloved."
"The rose flower."