The year 2022 is about to go
so let's take a look at the top ten Indian films of the year 2022 today
number 10 in this list is "777 Charlie"
which is the story of a loyal dog
at number 9 is Mani Ratnam's "PS-1"
a historical film based on the story of the Chola kings
at number 8 is "SitaRaman"
which is a love story based Telugu film
at number 7 is "Major"
this film is the story of the terrorist attack on Taj Hotel
at number 6 is "Rocketry"
R. Madhavan's film is the story of the struggle of a space engineer of ISRO
at number 5 is Rishabh Shetty's "Kantara"
which is a fight to save our culture and religious beliefs
at number 4 is "Vikram"
Kamal Haasan's strong action movie
at number 3 is "KGF Chapter 2"
the most wanted film of Superstar Yash
number 2 is "The Kashmir Files"
Vivek Agnihotri's film is a true incident of atrocities on Kashmiri Pandits
and now the number 1 film of the year "RRR"
which is a brilliant film by famous director S.S Rajamouli
who broke all records and earned more than ₹1200 crores
well guys, which one did you like the best? definitely write in the comment section
and for more such amazing videos subscribe to the "A2 Motivation" channel
see you in the next video.