Raipur is 285 Km ahead.
This is Indravati river.
And
It go's there and make fall.
What's up guys, welcome back to the vlog.
Yesterday I stopped here, Ghee Desi.
I come here to eat again because
the food here was very tasty.
Let's go.
I am just leaving for Raipur,
my flight ticket was for yesterday.
I will get it Pre-Pon for today.
But the plan has changed.
There is nothing to do here.
And nothing is needed, No No.
Just have to leave.
I am on Cut to Cut to time.
I have a 5 hour drive from here.
I have driven this a lot.
but if I will tell you
honestly the biggest fear is,
To reverse and now specially,
Ever since I have taken my
BMW, there's a camera behind it.
So I have become so used to camera now,
that I don't know what to do without it.
This is Keshkai market this is
where I bought my underwears.
Terrible mountain road starts from here.
Today i woke up at 5:30 am.
Then in morning went to,
The falls .
So it's 4 o'clock now
that's why  i'm sleepy now.
The person who is used to got up
at 11am in day got up at 5:30am.
Look at the front, I will show you.
When we used to travel because of desh Ka
Dhoni, Ritu and I used to rest here like this.
You used to sit at such a place,
you used to leg massage of me.
We used to rest.
I am feeling much better after facewash.
What happened  to Pushparaj,
they were taking wood.
Look at this, bro.
This is Instagram tease.
Oh brother.
Take this Gau Mata.
Eat this.
She eats.
Thank you.
I got the corn and will go on
eating now to reach Raipur.
Bro, why I am feeling like this,
That this road won't
take me to the airport.
Gau Mata!
Is there a way to the airport from here?
Is this road going to the airport?
- Ok, Thank you.
But the surprising thing is that.
Off to the national highway,
This is the way to the airport.
Gau Mata move out.
how can I pass.
It is not even written here
where is the way to the airport
GPS is saying I have reached airport.
From where will the
Plane take off from here.
Where did this GPS has reach us.
Have reached the airport,
the hunger is terrible.
Dosa followed by a coffee.
Coffee is over.
The Dosa was average,
coffee was good.
The whole airport is
empty, only I am sitting here.
Our flight is from above and it is the last
flight of the day after that the airport is closed
Since morning, I was carrying heavy camera bag in my backpack
and was roaming all around fall and now my neck is paining
my condition has worsened by night now
Because I am an old man now.
And traveling solo with
so much stuff is hurting.
I am having terrible neck pain.
Earlier I was down there was silence now when
I came up there is silence everyone went down.
I have to lift this heavy bag again.
No worries.
In the last vlog you have saw that
i have to go to explore the caves.
But there, water level was
increased then I thought,
I am leaving for Delhi today
itself, it was my unplanned travel.
On the airport I was about,
To board then I thought I message
the Ritu that I am coming delhi today.
You know what, Ritu messaged me?
The captain of this flight was,
Our Captain Ritu Rathi.
I was so happy
I sat on my seat, I didn't go to meet her
as she has just learned to fly the plane.
Let not disturb her.
Let's fly and i will
meet her after landing.
I didn't told anyone that the
captain of this flight is my wife
And I thoght let's do some fun, I asked my nearby
passengers that how did you like today's take off.
It was nice.
I am feeling like I am
in roller coaster now.
You liked it or not.
- It was okay
- Could have been better
Yeah
Actually it is my first time.
So, yes it was ok-ok.
- Yes
I have flown a lot, usually
take offs are better than this.
- Okay
Yeah, it was nice.
- It's quite
- You liked it?
I think she is flying for the first time.
And I am myself pilot so.
So, it was pretty smooth
Let us see how's the landing goes.
Descent is started
landing is going to be done.
I hope she will land pretty good.
And if she doen't do it well.
I will tease her till one year.
Whenever she say, I said i landed better.
I have been in her
flight for 1-2 times only.
And she always land ok-ok so,
today she has to do a good landing.
But i am sure she will land good.
Because i said to Ritu,
Whenever you will fly, I
will come in your flight.
And I leaved on that day,
she doen't have a flight today.
Today she got flying.
And imagine I have to
go tomorrow and today.
Those caves were closed today,
so I thought that I will leave today.
And I am on that flight.
God
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much
Mau please open the door.
Open it, Open it.
He is following Mumma.
I have came after so many days.
What are you saying?
I was not supposed to come
Then after i came.
When the descent started,
I went to the washroom.
I didn't go to washroom.
As soon as i left the
washroom, she went in it.
Just after me.
Before that you were sleeping.
See the coincidence, I was not sleeping.
Means she has to go
washroom even with the husband.
Wow
You have wearing my socks
I have bought my underwear
from roadside while travelling.
I am sleeping with kids
you sleep in another room.