It's 12 o'clock, we've reached home.
Finally met Pihu. She came
running and hugged dad.
Right bro? Where did you go for a walk?
Where's Didi?
Dad! Pihu!
Didi went to sleep.
Didi went to sleep?
She's asleep.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning
I just realized that I had a
cricket match on Sunday.
In 6 o'clock in the morning. I
have to cancel the cricket now.
I'm not feeling well. I
have fever, cold.
And she said that I'll put desi ghee in my nose.
Really, One more time.
I'll not put desi ghee in my nose.
- I'm telling you the truth just one time
- No No
I have a bad problem at home.
- Give me where it is, It's broken?
- Where
My fever is not going.
I thought I'll measure my
fever with a thermometer.
But the thermometer broke.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning. I've
taken 2 tablets, fever is not going away.
I was measuring my fever.
I'll go in the morning.
As soon as I put it
in my mouth, it fell off.
Here it is.
Ritu, here's the mercury.
Here..
Don't pick it up with your hand.
- Ohhh
- Bring me a broom
Yes, it will hold here like this.
Fun and interesting fact.
It's not allowed to take the
thermometer on the aircraft.
Because the aircraft is
mostly made of carbon fiber.
But it's mostly made of aluminum.
So, Mercury is 13.6 relative density.
If it breaks, it will make
a hole in the aluminum.
When I get sick, and
I wake up late at
night, I do this cheating.
What's up, guys? Welcome back to the vlog.
I had a bad cold in the morning.
I had a bad headache.
I woke up at 5.30 or 5.00 a.m.
I was having a teribble
headache, my nerves was like this.
I woke up in the morning
and Ritu put this on my head.
I didn't feel good.
I asked Ritu to give me a disprin.
Ritu gave me a disprin.
I took the disprin with hot water.
As soon as I took the
dispenser, I had vomiting.
I feel much better now.
Feeling much betetr.
Come on, Pihu.
Rashi went to school.
Rashi took out his lunch box in the
morning because she has a holiday today.
Both the kids are eating lunch boxes.
Eat, son.
Eat it.
You also come, eat.
Don't give cash to Mau.
Hello, plane.
The plane goes just right above our house.
What happened?
There is a fly, remove the fly.
It's bothering my son.
What did you do in my absence, Mau?
What happened to Rashi today?
Balle Balle, shawa shawa.
Because today is school holiday.
Did Pihu give you a hug in the morning?
Yes
Where is my hug?
She did not hug first, then gave again.
Where is your sister's hug?
Did you give a hug to your dad?
Hello, you have grown up.
Show me your nails,
how did they get so big.
Oh God.
Today is Sunday.
I thought I would take a day off.
I am going to the doctor.
Put the umbrella back son.
Have taken the cat and
also took the umbrella.
We are going to the doctor or what?
- Who is she? Cat
- Cat
Meow
Ritu and I was discussing about Rashi.
Rashi, If mom and dad can talk in English have
you understand, we were talking about you.
Yes.
Yes, you know what
we just talked about.
You talked about my play.
About your play?
Yes, exactly.
We were discussing
about Rashi's play style.
How did she behave before and now?
She can understand.
Child's behavior depends on
with whom she's plays,
walks or sits in school.
Now, Rashi's behavior has changed.
Ritu, let's drink coffee?
There is a good coffee shop here.
Is this a good market?
Which sector is this?
I am on the market for the first time
since we moved into the new house.
Otherwise, everything is on home delivery.
We didn't get the doctor before
Now I have got so many that I
am confused as to whom to go.
Everyone is good here.
Here is also good.
Everyone is good.
We are asking whom to go.
Which doctor is here now?
Where did he go, this is where he sit.
We are in a new place.
Here are all the doctors.
All are doctors, doctors..
Today is sunday.
Today is sunday all
doctors clinic is closed.
Now what will a man do
if he gets sick on Sunday?
We are buying medicines
from homeopathic store.
Anyway we didn't get it.
Tomorrow morning I
have to go on a trip again.
I know I have lot of
travel involved in my life.
That's why I asked for medicine,
but it's not available right now.
Now we have come to the stationery shop,
I have bought some stationery for myself.
But how much in childhood.
You will not have to keep it,
I am not buying anything for you.
See, it feels so good
after seeing them.
Pen?
When I was young, I was used
to like, Mom take this pencil.
It used to cost 5 rupees.
How much is it now?
80 rupees.
People are enjoying
Chole Bhature on Sunday.
The fever does not go away from the
Dolo, now we will take the good one.
We have been roaming here for an hour.
We can't find our car.
I won. I won.
Let's go. Let's go.
No, No
Pihu, who won? Dad won or sister won?
Say Dad won.
Noo
Pihu is not here.
Pihu doesn't here.
Pihu
What's up guys?
Today we have to go out for a shoot.
And we have to do beautification.
Today let's try Mama
Earth's charcoal face pack.
This has active charcoal.
But there is a confusion.
Should I apply it on my beard or not?
And how much should I
apply is also a confusion.
Cleanse your face with Mama
Earth charcoal face wash.
Dab your face dry.
Apply a generous layer.
Face should be dry, let's on the AC.
Keep it for 15 minutes.
Oh Bro, it's been 18 minutes.
We only had to apply it for 15 minutes.
Where is Pihu?
Hold the camera.
Don't show Pihu.
She got it.
I was a little scared in the beginning.
Then she understood.
Recently I used this product.
I liked it a lot.
It's very helpful.
It feels very fresh.
It cleanses all the pores
with activated charchol.
And one tip.
Wash it with warm water.
It will stick to your face with cold water.
You may have heard a lot
about  activated charcoal.
It's good for the skin.
But what is this?
It increases the surface area of carbon
making it porous and you may see,
If you see the water filtration process.
You must have read it in school.
They uses the charcoal,
which is the same charchol.
It's very good for health,
If you want to buy it.
The link is in the description.
The code is flyingbeast2023.
All the products of Mama Earth are natural.
Made with natural ingredients.
It's paraben free.
They also.
Mamaearth is known for it's goodness.
Because we plant trees.
Bro
what did I get
Close your eyes.
I got a thing, close your eyes..
Open
Elbow guard.
This is not, something
else got from the car.
Close your eyes.
Got our key.
It was missing since a month.
Do you know where it was.
In the car itself.
Think.
So, how did you locked the car?
I didn't know how.
Came home with a duplicate key.
One day I lost my car key while
playing cricket, I was worried.
The match ended at 11 o'clock
at night I came home at 1 o'clock.
I left my car there.
Next day i took duplicate key of the car.
Told the ground man to search,
it has fallen while playing.
Went again the next day.
But I couldn't find it.
Today i find it while
cleaning the car.
Where did you find it?
It was in the trunk of
my car don't know how.
Trunk? while have taken out your cricket
kit, you must have left it in the trunk.
Listen, I put out the cricket kit.
I was 100% sure.
I locked the car after
taking out the cricket kit.
How can it fall inside?
You must have lock the car first
You must have left it in the trunk.
OHHH
You are right baby.
Let's go.
Come, come.
This is last come fast.
Come on Ritu, let me show
you what your kids are doing
Look what game they are playing.
Rashi, this is not allowed, get up.
- Wipe is off
- Which game is this?
What? show me your hand, show me your face.
Wah
Look, she is laughing.
Which ink is this? from
where did you take this.
This is not ink, it is color.
Rashi
Which game is this?
Don't do with that, get this wipe off.
Rashi, Even though you are elder, will
you play with small children like this?.
She is the most naughty one.
She has became naughty.
You and your sister will clean up.
She has rubbed his
face, Didn't you see?
Have fun but do it gentally.
What do you want?
This is the last round.
No.
Don't you get up for school in the morning.
Kids's momma has gone to flying.
The father of the children is walking the
children because the children are crying
Papa.
Yes
Baby woke up.
Whose baby got up.
Pihu is sleepy.
My walk was successful.
The cats have came
everyone is so hungry.
All has come.
He has one mother and three daughters.
He dropped the tiffin.
Eat it gently.
Give me some chocolate
Ritu, look at your
girl, she doesn't eat.
And she is asking me to make avocado toast
I am making it.
Yeah
Don't waste it, go from here.
It's a very simple recipe
You have to take out the whole avocado.
Here it comes like this.
Add tomatoes and onions to the avocado
And mix it
Add some salt And it's ready.
Finally, mam's avocado toast is ready.
You have more fun with dad or  mom?
Dad
I am going to office to do the work.
You go to sleep.
I can't see anything.
No no.