Come, dear.
Dear, do you want
to ask anything to him?
Once my parents are okay with him
then there is nothing to talk.
Why are you wearing this attire?
Where is the sari?
Where are the jewelleries?
You dreamt it again?
You don't have any other work?
If you marry and have children
then why will I dream of it.
Will I get any chance in this life
of having a function in this house?
God knows.
You can think of that later.
First prepare my tiffin.
Good morning, Daddy. - Morning.
What's the news? - Same old thing.
Crime here and scam there. - Lunch.
Take it. - Nothing will change.
First think about
marrying your daughter
then you can think
about the whole world.
She started early in the morning.
- She didn't even stop.
She was even dreaming of it.
Bye, daddy. - Bye.
Just wave your hand
and send her to office.
Don't you think, you should
be sending her to in-laws house.
Yes, Mr. Sachin. Please wait.
I am leaving. I am on the way.
It's Sachin.
Bhumi. You go to the
supermarket lane, right?
Yes. - Drop me there.
No, I won't drop you.
- Why? Even the car is empty.
This is not a share
auto to drop everybody
when it's empty.
Tada!
What's going on?
Photo session.
For followers.
#MondayMotivation
If they see you
early in the morning,
how will they get motivated?
Madam. - Not you,
those who invented the
front camera should be punished.
I can't punish him so,
from tomorrow I will ban
cell phones inside the office.
Hi, ma'am. I made a beautiful plan
for the factory/warehouse/office.
You will love it. Check it out.
It's so nice, right?
Yes, it is. - Thank you.
Use it for your house.
Sorry, ma'am.
- This is not your hostel
that you can come at anytime.
It's an office.
I am just 10 minutes late, ma'am.
- 10 minutes?
Leaving holidays,
your working days are 280.
If you are late for
10 minutes everyday,
then you are late for
2800 minutes for a year.
That means, it's nearly 47 hours.
If one working day is of 9 hours,
then it is roughly 5 days.
So, calculate your
pay minus 5 days loss.
Oh, God! Whoever marries her...
Yes, whoever marries me...
Did I say it out loud?
- Bring that phone here.
Bring it here.
I want this month's sales
report on my table by evening.
Ma'am. - Bring me the report
and take your phone back.
Uncle! Good morning. Please come.
Hi, morning.
Sit, sit. - Please come in.
So, this is the project idea,
uncle. - Nice.
And this concept is pretty good.
- I really liked that too.
Yeah.
Why do you scare them so much?
They don't have
much responsibilities,
at least they should be afraid.
I am afraid that you will scold me,
forgetting that I am MD.
Not at all.
So, what's up?
What is your mom saying.
Same old thing.
She is going out to meet them
because I am scolding her
if she brings anyone at home.
Why don't you adjust
yourself because of her, then?
If I want to stay
together for lifetime,
first I should connect to him.
I hope you find your
connection very soon.
Hi. - Hi.
You told me to come urgently
from Paris. What's the matter?
I want to go to India.
Why do you want to go there?
- You know,
wherever you look, you just
see black coats and white beards.
Even if you come out, you
just see tall buildings and cars.
It's been so many days,
I am missing those trees,
fields and traditional attires.
Now, what do you say?
You were saying, there's
some project in India, right? - Yes.
Tell them,
we are ready to take the project.
I need a break from here.
You are thinking about taking break?
Hi, sir.
- Let me break some news to you.
Have a seat, sir.
Thank you.
When I saw you on the dais
you looked like upcoming
billionaire. When I see you here,
you look like a college student.
Okay, I will come to the point.
Sure, sir. - I will give you a deal
which will increase your
bank balance to 200 crores.
200 crores?
If you are okay, I will
make the papers ready by tomorrow.
Thank you.
But no thanks, sir.
I am not interested.
Did you listen the numbers
correctly? It's 200 crores.
After 2, there are nine zeroes.
I already told you,
I am not interested.
I thought, you only looked
like a college student.
Even your thinking is the same.
I know, money is very necessary.
But that is not the only
thing that is necessary.
Nice meeting you.
Hey, 200 crores?
I am just speechless
after telling that.
How can you reject that so simply.
You forget about that 200 crores
and get two tickets to India.
What Madam, didn't you
like the guy you met that day?
No.
The boy said okay
after seeing the photo
but my daughter said no
without even seeing the photo.
Leave it, Madam.
He was a bit average.
Was he? - Yes.
Just see this once.
- Shall I tell the truth?
That last guy was better.
- Shut up.
You will tell
something to everybody.
Shall I bring you coffee?
Go, bring it. - Okay.
If I won't purchase anything you
people will tell me not to sit here.
You are good looking
in person than the photo.
Whom are you searching?
Are you waiting for somebody?
- Where is your daughter?
She won't come.
- Oh, she won't like coffee?
She won't like the concept
of this kind of meetings.
Then, why did you call me?
- Talk to me, son.
If I like you,
then I will talk to her.
I thought, meeting in the
coffee shop is like a new trend.
People will be open minded.
But, she is not even present here.
I can imagine,
how my future will be with her.
Son...
Hi, Daddy. - Hey.
Why is this house so silent.
Where is Prabhavati?
She is not here.
She went to the temple.
Oh, she is not back yet? - No.
She went to circumambulate
700 times for your wedding.
She went to pray to God.
Hail Lord Venkatesh.
- I am not so sure.
Oh, she is already here.
Give me that phone. I will call her.
Where will she go?
She will be back soon.
There she is.
Oh, God.
Oh!
You look tired.
Oh, God.
My legs are paining. - Oh, God.
I am tired.
Where did you go? - Can't you see.
I went to Venkateshwara temple.
Take the offering.
New sari,
offering, flowers, leg pains.
You are managing it all very nicely.
But, if someone goes to
temple they will crush the coconut
not bring the coconut to the house.
Won't you change? - I won't change.
Mom, marriages won't
happen like this.
Then tell me, how marriages happen?
I will do it like that.
Just making me sit like a doll,
or scanning me if
I they like me or not.
I can't do those.
Who rejected you?
You are only rejecting them, saying
you are not connecting with them.
Should I connect with
whoever you show me?
If you want to connect with
somebody, you should see him first.
Women of your age are having
babies and sending them to school.
And here I am, searching
a husband for you like a mad woman.
I am very unlucky.
I can't tolerate all this.
Will you say something...
- Sachin.
Satyam.
Hello, Satyam.
Good morning, ma'am.
Ma'am, after thinking
deeply I made another design.
If you see this,
your mind will be blown. Trust me.
How much will you take?
Thank you.
I know, you will like this for sure.
Also, I am comfortable
for any negotiations between us.
Just give me whatever you like.
- Not for this design.
I asked as you had to do it again.
Thank you, ma'am. Sarla,
please think about your likes.
Please, don't say
anything about my sketch.
We are about to start
a new manufacturing unit.
Once we start it, I will inform you.
You can visit that day.
Madam.
What are you seeing? - Madam.
Give me the phone. Give me.
Here!
What is this?
I try to hide it inside, ma'am.
But, it comes out bursting.
What is that? - Talent, ma'am.
Next time, if I see something
like this you will loose.
What will I loose, ma'am?
- Your job.
Monster.
Why did you shout at that architect?
Our company's concept and the
design he made is totally different.
He should've at least
used his common sense.
Correct,
but don't be too strict, Bhumi.
Even our office staff
is afraid of you.
No student likes
to go to school, uncle.
Everybody just wants to play.
But, when they study
their future will be bright.
I am not talking about them.
You are being too
strict for yourself.
When I was not strict,
nobody took me serious.
Now, when I am being strict
nobody wants me to be with them.
If I tell you the truth
I don't even remember,
how I was back then.
I don't even know, how should I be.
Hello, Akash.
- Hello, Uncle, How are you?
I am good.
How was your travelling?
Gautam said, you are coming here.
If you are free tomorrow, I will
come and meet you in the office.
You are not some outsider.
Come home.
Sure, uncle.
Do you know how he is?
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, you said you wanted
to see sari and skirt.
Here, size of buildings
are increasing
and size of clothes are decreasing.
- Stop it.
This is the problem with you.
You don't see them and
you won't allow us to see.
Hi, uncle. - Hi, Akash.
You reminded me of my son,
I am so happy that you came.
Do you remember him? Akash.
Hi, aunty. - How are you, son.
Yes, I am good. - How is my son.
He is fine, aunty.
Tell him to come and meet us
at least once a year.
Okay, I'll bring you some coffee.
- Okay, aunty.
I saw your interview on CNN.
I felt very proud. - Thanks, uncle.
You will leave early or
will you be here for some days?
Actually,
I have some important work here.
Okay. - Yes, uncle.
Come Bhumi.
Why did you stop there?
He is Akash.
He is a friend of Gautam. - Hi.
She is... - Bhumi.
You people know each other? - Yes.
Yes, uncle. We were in
same batch in the college.
Oh...
One minute.
You guys sit down. - Okay, uncle.
I will be right back. Hello.
It's been many days, right? - Yes.
You look very different.
What are you doing now?
- Nothing, just small business.
You? - Akash.
You said something about a project.
Did it started?
It's almost getting started. - Okay.
Bhumi, you know he
is very famous architect.
Oh!
I just remembered.
We have a small project.
If you are free
just look at it once...
- We don't need
so big architect, uncle.
You are afraid, he will charge more?
Bhumi is afraid that
it will be out of budget.
Nothing like that, uncle.
One second.
Hello.
You are informing me now
that raw materials didn't arrive.
If you can't do the work.
Go home. Bloody morons.
Need to go, uncle. Sorry. -Okay.
Bye, Akash. - Bye.
What happen, Akash?
Are you confused?
She might be a bit angry,
but she has a very good heart.
Hi, ma'am. How can I help you?
Please give me some time.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I should ask that. I stay here.
I came here for a business deal.
Oh, okay.
I will accompany you till then.
You know what.
You are in sari when everyone
around you are in middies and jeans.
You know,
you are very beautiful in sari.
Don't make silly compliments
like a college student.
There is nothing wrong giving
complements. Age doesn't matter.
But seriously,
you look so beautiful in sari.
Did you do any course in flirting?
Hey, I am telling you the
fact and you think I am flirting.
I don't like all these.
If you are this beautiful
then you can't miss all these.
What's up? How's business going?
Yeah, fine. - Great.
Uncle said something
about a project.
Do you want me to look into that?
No, no. Not necessary.
It's a small project.
Hey, don't worry. I'll help you out.
No need Akash. It's not your range.
Okay, I'll leave now. What?
You are here to meet someone, right?
How can I do business
those who don't respect time?
In business people go
through finances, not time.
Money is necessary.
Just money is not necessary.
Bye.
She is interesting now.
Why didn't I knew it then?
I didn't observe her before?
Or I never knew about it.
- Hey, is that you, Akash.
Many girls have proposed you.
Did you even care for anyone?
She is new and different.
So, I must closely observe her.
For that, you must go nearer to her.
Yes, I know a way to do that. - Oh!
Whom are you calling?
He will take me closer to her.
Hello, Akash. - Hi, uncle.
Hi, Bhumi. He's Raghu.
He is my friend/PA. - Hello.
Hi.
So, you are doing our project then?
Yeah. Mr. Bhupati asked
me and I can't say no to him.
He said, you called
him and you want to do it.
Oh, that's what he said?
That's how you did.
I told you, this is a small project.
- I will do it.
I don't like everything that easily.
Later, you will only be in trouble.
What? There's no chance
you won't like it.
This is not a big matter to him.
He makes it look very simple.
Let's see.
Sir, tea.
Sir.
Sorry. Sorry, ma'am. - Idiot.
Can't you see? - Sorry, ma'am.
Clean it. - Okay, ma'am.
Hey, you said she is interesting.
She is totally different.
Don't judge her.
Hey, she is not your range, Akash.
She is not your match.
If you want to be near to home,
you must decrease your imagination.
Okay.
Kishore, come to my cabin.
This is our site layout.
May I come in, ma'am? - Yes.
He's Akash, architect from Paris.
This is Kishore.
If you have any doubts,
he'll clear it. - Sure.
Hello.
For just a small sketch,
you came from Paris.
Do you think,
we don't know how to sketch?
You are hear to clarify our doubts.
Not your doubts.
Wow. You are so handsome.
One selfie, please. - Sure.
Selfie Sarla?
Do you know me?
Your tiktok videos are
so famous even in Paris.
They removed Tiktok and
kicked talented people like me.
Thank God. - You guys just gossip
or do any work?
She saw her while saying
it but I think, that was for us.
Do you doubt that?
Where is the site?
What is the plot size?
What are GHMC norms?
Who is present at the site?
How much paper work is done?
If I get the details
what I just asked in two days.
We will start the work.
Let's go. - Two days.
Sarla, come with the sales register.
Why is she telling
me to bring the selfie?
She didn't say selfie.
She told you to come
with the sales register.
There are many unique people's here.
Hey, you are in India
but you won't come home?
I will come.
I just have a small work.
When it's finished I'll be there.
It's been two years
since you were home.
I just look at you
in the mobile screen.
Hey, someone catch him.
Hey, hey.
Oye.
I will call you again, mom. - Hey.
Wait.
Hey.
Thank you, son.
It's okay. Just check whether
everything is there or not?
I came to the cafe to
meet a guy for my daughter.
When I came out, he stole the bag.
You are meeting a guy for
your daughter in a cafe? - Yes.
Please tell me more
details about it.
It seems little different.
Yes, I know. - You must be careful.
What if something happens to you?
Nothing happened to me.
You were here to help
me in the correct time.
Okay, I'll leave now.
I will drop you. - No.
No need. I will go in the auto.
Okay.
Auto.
Will you drop me
to Jubilee Hills? - Yes.
Bye, son. - Bye, madam.
This is our proposed
site in Shad Nagar, sir.
If we stay here,
even if we are so talented
they will see us as
locals and as a cheap.
If you come from abroad,
they are imported and
they will be respected more.
Don't feel bad, Kishore. Thank you.
If you come from Paris or Parel,
you will be the same.
#joke
They are NRI's so, #moz.
No issues, sir. - Inform Bhumi also.
I already informed her.
She said to tell you.
Brother. Genuine question.
Is he understanding anything
or is he just acting?
Bring another one.
- One second, sir.
Bindu. Marker. - Okay.
She is bringing.
- Bring an imported marker.
Do you like her?
She worked hard to give him that,
that means, she likes him too.
Excuse me, sir.
Follow.
Their love story is so complicated.
Like in films, this girl
comes from a poor background.
And the boy's family is very rich.
This whole complicated love story
is directed by our big man.
Who? Mr. Bhupati?
Yes. There he is.
Speak of the devil.
He will definitely hit a century.
Now see,
she will go and talk to him.
Hi, sir. How are you?
- He will reply her casually.
She will laugh,
as if he said a big joke.
Okay, okay.
But, there's no big joke in there.
He pays her, that's why.
Whatever he says, she will laugh.
This recipe is only
known to Indian people.
Then, why don't you do it?
I tried,
but I never understand,
when to laugh or when not to.
When I try to laugh,
he will leave till that time.
Did you get it?
Even this small thing is an art.
Please, don't judge an artist.
Oh, God!
When are you going to see the site?
We were just leaving. - Good.
Kishore. - Ma'am.
Show them the site. - Ma'am.
You also go, Bhumi.
Uncle, if I go then who
will take care of the office?
This is not a border of India.
Nobody will come and destroy
if you are not here for sometime.
Superb. Good one, sir.
Good one. Superb.
Oh. He is more bigger
artist than everybody here.
We'll go in my car.
There's no problem going
in their respective cars.
I don't know the address.
Kishore. - Ma'am.
You come with him. - Yes, ma'am.
Brother, looks like
your madam is too strict.
Just be frank about it.
She is always angry.
If there was any
premier league in anger,
in every season she
would've been the winner.
I think she is not married yet.
- Who will marry a girl like her.
We can adjust if
woman are not beautiful
but we can't if they are angry.
Bhumi.
Nice sari. - Let's look at the site.
Nice sari?
Your boss is trying
to make an ice in the desert.
Yes.
Hello.
Bhumi, what's this eco friendly?
You alone will change the world?
Why? Do you have any problem?
Ah! No.
Why so serious? I am just kidding.
Men and architects
are born to be rejected.
Did you see any batsmen who can
hit sixes every ball. There he is.
Did you see any umpire who
gives no-ball for every delivery.
There she is.
Mom, what did you
prepare for breakfast?
What was that suppose to mean?
What happen to your mouth?
She vowed that she won't talk.
Vow of silence? But why?
My mom just talks about my marks
and your mom just talks
about your marriage. Right?
If she vows, will I be married?
My mom is praying for my marks,
but am I getting it?
Leave them, it's their belief.
Okay, tell them to do this everyday.
We will have some peace of mind.
But I won't make
my mom suffer like you.
Whoever gives me the first
love letter I will marry him.
First stop wetting the bed,
then think about marrying.
Who are these guys?
- Boys keep photos of heroines
and your house is
filled with boys' photos.
Who is this guy? Look so good.
Let me see. - Really!!
Let me see. - Let me see.
Did you like him?
Should I talk to them?
What about your vow of silence?
Don't act those vows
and homage in front of me.
Bhumi, it's cheating.
What happened? Who is cheating.
Yes. - What happened?
She broke Prabhavati's vow.
Monster. - Hey.
What is this? - That's
Sreedhar's daughter's marriage
who stays in house number 12.
During her function
you made a plait of it.
That is an invitation card.
Don't cry while reading.
What is left except
crying in my life?
If you are so sad,
then don't go to the marriage.
Don't link everything
to my marriage.
When people ask me
about your marriage,
I am just speechless, and
I even stopped going to marriages.
Hey, did you just born
me only for marriage?
Why are you hiding
as if it is a crime.
You broke my vow and made me speak.
Also go and shut their mouths.
Hey, do breakfast...
Are you satisfied?
Even in AC you are making me sweat.
Tell me what you
are here for? - Yes.
What is today's date?
- You came here to ask that?
You told you will
deliver my order on 18th.
Today is 19th.
There is no stock nor any
phone call that it will be late.
Then, how can this continue?
Kartik. Come to my cabin.
You guys didn't deliver him yet?
Production has been delayed, ma'am.
It's only been completed 70%.
Why didn't you inform them?
How can you be so irresponsible?
What's the matter?
- Let's do one thing.
Like old ways,
I have materials which
are ready to be delivered.
I will sell it to you.
If you use it and
mix it with your material
we can earn much more.
I won't use such cheap
materials for our work.
Oh, you got angry.
Your madam didn't read
the agreement properly, I guess.
If you don't deliver the
material in the mentioned date,
you will need to pay back double.
I am doing what I like.
I won't leave it,
even if I have to bear some losses.
Check the background before
accepting the deal from next time.
If you think, they are
not appropriate throw them out.
If you want to impress
this kind of girl
you must be with them for some time.
Ma'am, raw material file.
Is the plan ready?
It's being ready.
- Why are you taking so long?
You won't like anything
very easily, right?
I must think out of box.
Actually, out of the galaxy...
What brother? Did he make it?
No, brother.
I would've been
done ten times by now.
Shaving your beard? - Sketch.
There is a difference
between LKG student's
drawing and Engineer's drawing.
Akash. - Tell me, Sarla.
I made a new video.
Do you want to see it?
If I say no, will you leave me?
Give it here.
How is it?
Mind blowing, Sarla.
What happen? - I cut my finger.
Give me that first-aid kit. - Yes.
What happen? - Nothing.
Does it pain?
Don't worry. It's just a small cut.
What is happening?
Sorry, ma'am.
Kartik was hurt, so I lost focus.
If you worry, did the pain stop?
If you cry did the bleeding stop?
It's not wrong liking some one
but don't make others
suffer because of it.
Without showing any concern,
she is getting angry.
Even getting angry is one type
of concern. Only if you understand.
Now-a-days, I can't understand you.
It's difficult to understand you.
Hello, son.
What?
- Tomorrow's prospective...
Hi.
Hey, the same lady.
Come, let's meet her.
Keep it.
I was just seeing whether you were
the same guy or not. How are you?
Yes, I am good.
How come you are here?
She must be here to meet
again someone for her daughter.
Hey. - Yes, son.
You are saying it so nervously,
that means...
Nobody will like it,
if the mother comes with the girl.
Correct.
Who is he, madam? In one day,
you arranged two meetings?
No. I know these people.
Do you want some coffee?
- We just had it.
Why are you trying so hard, aunty?
You can tell your daughter, right?
If she listens, I can shout at her.
She is not afraid of anybody.
I must not say this but,
she is a monster.
Even her daughter is like our madam.
Are you married?
No, aunty.
But I am in love with someone.
Oh, good, good, good.
There's nothing good.
Everything's bad.
Why are you saying that?
I can't explain it to you.
Almost, she is similar
like your daughter.
I don't understand
this generation girls.
Even if Lord Ram comes,
they will make excuses.
Oh, time's up.
She might be home soon.
Okay, I'll leave now. - Okay, aunty.
Son...
Take my phone number.
If you know any nice guy,
please tell me. - Sure, aunty.
Bye, bye. - Okay, aunty.
They don't care,
if someone loves them,
they won't listen to their
mother if they like someone.
What do these women want?
Your problem is that
she is not caring me, right?
We'll show the sketch
tomorrow. - Okay.
That's it?
You came all the
way here just for this?
Impressive.
Will this be enough?
If I take something,
I'll make the job done.
I have that confidence on my work.
For the first time,
I was afraid that you would reject.
You made me look into myself.
This calls for a celebration.
Shall we go out for coffee?
I don't have a habit of that.
Even if it's late,
we can change few habits.
I don't like new habits.
Shall we show this
presentation to Uncle?
Can we go in my car?
- We will go in my car.
Chocolate?
No.
Why?
I don't like chocolates.
I gave you back your money.
Then what is this?
I am fine with the money.
What about my ego?
First of all,
I am very short tempered
also, I am aged now.
From the day you insulted me
my blood is boiling like anything.
If I leave you thinking
you are a girl...
but when people come
to know about this
next time someone comes and
throws slipper instead of cheque.
I am a person
when a branch comes in the middle,
I'll cut the whole tree.
And now,
you have dared to confront me!
Just being elder is not enough.
You should know to respect ladies.
Akash.
Weather is hot outside.
Go and sit in the car.
What did you say?
If branches come in the middle,
you will cut down the whole tree.
Celebrities are challenging
each other for growing trees.
And you are saying
you will cut the trees?
I just said it for a punch.
I have many plants in my house.
If you want you can come and see.
You must return the extra money,
wastage costs and everything, okay?
Okay, I'll give it back.
If you come in her way again
thinking your ego is
hurt and that bullshit.
My name is Akash.
I am everywhere above the ground.
Why did you hit him?
Did I tell you to hit him?
You came from somewhere, you will
leave after you finish your work.
After that,
if they come and make brawl?
Who will take the responsibility
for my staff safety?
You don't need to
hit anyone for my sake.
I know how to deal with everybody.
Just do your work.
Are you satisfied?
You won't get hug
even if you help her
or fought bad guys.
Because she is not
any cinema heroine.
Hey, if girls would
be impressed for fighting
then, only rowdies
will be having girlfriends.
And if you think I beat
those guys to impress Bhumi,
He was talking rubbish. It didn't
seem right, so I thrashed him.
She didn't like it.
And now she is angry.
If someone helps, they should
be thankful, not scold them.
Shall we go?
Okay.
What are you doing here?
- I came here to talk to sir.
About what? Go now.
It's urgent, ma'am.
It is more important
than 100 crores building?
You can talk later. Now leave.
I told you to leave.
Hi. When did you guys come?
Just now.
Where is Bindu?
I sent her back.
I came here to discuss the plan
and she was saying something stupid.
We can talk about the
plan tomorrow in the office?
She is in a life
and death situation.
What happened, Uncle?
Kartik's marriage is fixed.
That boy in the office
who is fair and has spectacles.
They like each other.
He is afraid of his family.
She is tensed
that he will get married
because of pressure of his family.
I told her I will solve that.
Sorry, uncle. - What sorry.
If you don't have any feelings
you think, nobody has feelings.
I will talk to them.
Kartik is with
his family in village.
I will go and talk to her.
She is an orphan.
They might ask her dowry.
I will give that and talk to them.
Kartik's family is so big.
They might not accept.
I will try to convince them.
Okay.
I will also come.
Bye, uncle. - Bye.
Don't think me as a villain
who is separating them.
I don't intend to hurt them.
But, he is the only
heir to our family.
And there is nothing wrong
if we have some expectations
for his marriage.
It is not correct
to make everyone suffer
by only choosing his choice.
He doesn't want you all to suffer.
That's the main reason
we are sitting here.
Family should support
their child to go ahead.
Sir, you shouldn't be
a hurdle to anyone's progress.
She is all alone.
I have no objection
against this girl.
At least there should be someone
who can say something
good or bad about her.
When she will come to your home
why do you need someone
who can say about that.
You all guys will be there.
For every girl, marriage
will make her leave her home.
But, for this marriage
she will get a family.
Don't say dialogues
as if you are in a cinema.
This love and all is bullshit
and this meeting is useless.
Yes, love is just four words.
But, it can separate two lives.
Love is just loving
and forgetting about it.
For loving someone,
it takes just one minute.
But for forgetting them,
whole life can't be enough.
I am much younger than you, sir.
It is up to you,
that you break their heart,
or make them marry each other.
I always thought girls family
should also be as big as ours.
If she thinks this
family as her own family
then why will I not accept her?
Thank you, sir.
You will never come to know,
that there is no one for her.
Bindu's marriage
responsibility is on us.
What do you say, Bhumi? - Yes.
Okay, then. Let's do their
marriage on the same date.
You talked to Mr. Naidu very nicely.
Thank you.
Apart from this architect job,
do you also lecture like this?
Or did you copy it from any book?
You can't even give a compliment.
What happened in last meeting?
Is it done?
If it was okay,
then why will I be in the temple.
I will be in search
for a good marriage marquee.
So, even your matter
is going slow like mine.
You also didn't tell
her that you love her?
No, aunty. If she is in front of
me I can talk to her about anything.
But expressing about my love,
I am a little bit scared.
But why should I
care about all that?
Do you want to see
my daughter's photo?
No, aunty. I love someone.
I also love my daughter.
I wonder when will your daughter
and my beloved understand our love.
What is this, aunty?
I am writing Ram's names
for a million times,
so that my daughter
gets married early.
If this work out, please tell me.
I will also write 10 million times.
Do you like her so much?
Is she beautiful?
She is so beautiful
and always proud.
How can I say you about her?
She is so perfect.
Does she like you?
I think, she also likes me.
But, she is not
expressing it outside.
These girls are all the same.
They wait until you leave.
If they have doubt that they'll
miss then they will express it.
I didn't get you.
Idea is so good. Will it workout?
Try it.
What if it fails?
Then you also write a
Ram's name a million times.
Prabha. - Yes.
What are you doing?
I am writing Ram's names
for a million times,
so that you get married early.
Looks like Lord Ram listened to you.
Now, stop writing it.
What are you saying?
Okay, now you don't
need to visit coffee shops
or any wedding websites.
Why?
Did you decide be a hermit?
Mom. -Then what?
I got whom I was searching for.
And from now on, you leave this pen
and start planning about marriage.
What are you saying?
Are you serious?
Bhumi.
Bhumi,
I don't know,
what is happening to me.
I don't know, what to do?
Should I talk to the priest?
Should I call them
to make the marquee.
Or should I first pray God.
- Prabha. Prabha.
First be calm.
You do everything later.
I must tell him first.
What? You didn't say him yet?
I will tell him tomorrow.
- Why delay doing good things?
Call him right now.
Sure? - First call him.
Okay.
Bhumi... He likes you, right?
He didn't say me directly,
but I understood.
It will rain tonight.
Why?
You called me and asked me out.
Nothing. I didn't have
any work in my house.
I think you are
here to say something,
but you are not saying it.
- Nothing like that.
I just wanted to meet you casually.
Really? - Why are you
asking the same thing?
There is nothing to hide.
Are you hiding anything?
Nothing.
I am going to village tomorrow.
Oh, when will you be back?
After attending few programs,
I will be back once I finish it.
What programs?
What can I expect, when people my
age go home after these many years?
I am going to meet some girl.
I am almost 30.
My mother keeps yelling
me if I don't marry now,
I won't get any girl.
At least I must go
and see the girl, right?
If you like her, then?
You are okay to marry her. - Yes.
Aunt's idea is
working out actually.
Let me try a little bit.
Why didn't you marry yet?
You didn't get who you wanted,
or nobody liked you?
Do you think, it's a joke?
I am a joke to you, right?
What did you ask?
Why didn't I marry?
It feels nice while tying the knot.
If feels nice while holding hands,
with closed eyes.
I didn't understand all that.
That's why I didn't get married.
And I was never in love with anyone.
I didn't want to marry
someone else leaving you.
Bhumi... - Let me talk, Akash.
Let me talk.
How many times should I be a fool?
How many more times I should
be wrong in front of you?
It's my mistake.
It's all my mistake.
I made a mistake falling
in love with you before.
And I made a mistake again
falling in love with you.
I shouldn't have done this.
Anyway, this isn't called
falling in love again.
Because I didn't forget you.
I thought, I forgot everything
that happened before
but once I met you
again I know I was wrong.
But once I saw you again,
I knew I didn't forget anything.
That's why,
I couldn't connect to anyone.
You said once that
I look great in sari.
And I couldn't see
myself in another thing.
You look great in Sari.
You ran a campaign in
college based on save nature.
I started a company on that basis.
"Save the nature"
I came to know that,
whatever I do, whatever I wear,
you are there in part of my life.
I see you everywhere.
I realised it when I met you.
You know, what is most
painful thing in girls life?
That, they couldn't express
their love to someone they love.
To forget the love
and see the world.
If you dial a wrong number,
it doesn't go to right person
even if you redial it again.
Bhumi.
It's over, Akash. It's over.
There is nothing to talk now.
I think,
we are not meant for each other.
Though Bhumi (Land) and
Akash (sky) are facing each other,
they couldn't meet ever.
You and I are the same.
Good Bye.
If you dial a wrong number,
it doesn't go to right person
even if you redial it again.
I remember the day I met him.
In fact I remember every
moment when I was with him.
Akash, it's three words.
Six feet of form,
seven years of memories.
Even here the same books. You
should listen lessons in the class.
Here you should learn
what are not in the lessons.
I will help you practice that.
These engineering girls
have the same problem.
They see biology
as something different.
My guys worked very hard
and cleared the traffic.
If you won't give at least one kiss
they will feel very bad.
Just one kiss, okay?
Kiss me.
I searched everything, but
I didn't find the author you said.
Just check this. It looks fine?
Who are these guys? Your classmates?
Where is Shiva?
Shiva.
I am right here.
Where did you go?
I told you to be with her.
I went there to
prepare for supplies.
What are you guys doing here?
I was waiting in the canteen.
What will someone do in the library?
We were searching books.
Where is the librarian?
Here. - There he is.
Good morning, sir.
I told you to clear everything.
Bye.
You were alone here
surrounded by ten idiots.
I understood the situation. So...
New admission?
Looks like CSE.
We build the buildings
and they arrange the computers.
Time's up. Let's go to the class.
I had heard of love at first sight
but it happened
to me when I saw him.
I felt instant connection with him.
I felt like we know
each other by ages.
I wanted to be with him.
Who was the guy that helped you.
I don't know. I think
he is from some other branch.
At least he was there
to help you in correct time.
I didn't even say thanks to him.
He is from the same campus, right?
You can say him some other time.
Where did I lost the watch?
Don't worry, you will find it.
Have you lost something?
Yes, something very important.
Is this what you were searching for?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
You were in the library...
My name is Akash.
Bhumi. Bhumika.
This is my friend, Anjali.
Hi. - Hi.
I thought I lost it.
I am very happy that I got it.
Why are you so excited?
Nobody will take it even
if you give it for free. - Hey...
Thank you. - You already said that.
This is for helping
me in the library.
It's okay.
'I didn't even know
him until yesterday.'
'Now wherever I look,
I only see him.'
"Save the nature"
'I am feeling like the whole world'
'is bringing me closer to him.'
He even found my favourite watch.
Give me the ball.
Wonderful!
What did we discuss yesterday?
- Don't you remember?
I want to know,
you remember it or not?
Who was that? Stand up.
Let everybody see
who that great person is?
I thought it,
when I heard the voice. Idiot.
Tell me,
what did we discuss yesterday.
I am like Gajini, sir.
I forget things very easily.
Radha, you tell me.
- Her name is Swathi, sir.
Gajini can remember these things?
Shameless fellow. Sit down.
I won't care about the attendance,
I will miss his class.
Did you enjoy it?
- Keep quiet! - Hold on.
Oh, Akash is appointed
as head of the cultural fest.
Wow.
Congrats, man.
Thanks. - Superb.
Let's go, come on.
- Wait for one minute.
Who will help Akash as
a volunteer from this class?
I will help him.
- Come on, let's go.
What is your name? - Naya.
What can you do? - Dance.
Will you dance with me? - No.
Give this paper to him. - Okay.
Hey, you are here for? - Volunteers.
Hey, watch. Learn something
from them. - Okay, okay.
Write their names too. - Okay.
What? Swathi won't dance?
Rahul don't like dancing
her on the stage.
He don't want boys
teasing her from the crowd.
Who is he to control her?
- He is his boyfriend, so.
So, he won't respect his girlfriend?
If you are in his place,
you will do the same.
If I was in his place
and if my girlfriend
would like to dance
I would've enjoyed cheering
her from the crowd.
Okay, come.
Now what? If that dance is
cancelled, our program will be flop.
I will do it.
Are you sure? - Yeah.
I should go and practice. - Bye.
All the best.
Will she able to do it?
- Do we have any other option?
You danced very beautifully.
Hello, I was the best
dancer in my school.
Is it?
Then why didn't you say that first.
We were so tensed
till the last minute.
I didn't want to participate.
I did it for you.
I didn't want the
program to be flop.
Oh!
Anyway, I don't know whether
you heard the claps or not,
but I can still hear them.
'I felt like I was on cloud
nine when he was praising me.
'I felt like kissing
my mom because she forced me'
'to go to dance
school in childhood.'
Here, here.
Lift it. Lift it.
Hey. Throw it this side.
- Very good.
This way. Come on.
- Very good. That side.
Madam, dance was so nice.
Thank you. - What do you say guys?
If audience say once more,
artist will do it again, right?
Just do it once more for us.
Just one step.
We just get to see it once,
and practice and all only with him?
Let's go.
Madam, if you get bore with him,
my door is always open.
You are sad because you
lost the quiz competition?
Hey.
Cheer up, Bhumi.
It was just a small thing.
That was not a small thing.
I never failed in anything.
If you win always,
it won't be thrilling.
You must lose sometimes
to enjoy the thrill of the win.
Chocolate.
Thank you.
- You can say it by smiling.
Think that was the first
prize in the quiz competition.
Bhumi.
You look beautiful when you smile.
'You look beautiful when you smile.'
You are doing the
same thing from evening.
Stop seeing yourself in the mirror.
Many people said that
my smile is beautiful.
But I never felt
this special about it.
See, he gave me this chocolate.
Will you frame it or what?
He gave my favourite things.
I think, he likes me.
There is a big difference
between liking and recognising it.
You think he doesn't know,
but I think he does.
If you switch off the light,
I will go to sleep.
You guys here to beat me?
I don't think it is nice
to fight inside the college.
Bhumi.
Why are so tensed? What happened?
In the ground,
Dhanush's gang and Akash...
Comment him again?
Our boy walked away calmly, right?
Back in the day,
Dhanush was talking rubbish
and Akash didn't even dare to fight
them. He didn't even looked angry.
Hello, first listen to me.
Did he beat them so bad?
- Not just a little...
...but very badly.
Why do you think he beat them?
I too don't know.
What are you thinking,
please tell me?
He beat them because Dhanush
was commenting on me, right?
It doesn't matter, what I think.
What he thinks matters.
What is this? - Shivaratri.
Do you know any temple nearby?
I have it in a cupboard in my room.
You are looking beautiful.
You are so beautiful in sari.
Cinema heroes and college
guys have the same reaction
when they see a girl in sari.
Nothing like that.
I saw many girls in sari
but I never told this to anyone.
Today is a holiday.
What are your plans?
Nothing.
My friends just went to the match.
- You are not going?
One second. Hello.
Yeah.
Okay.
Will you say it?
Girlfriend?
Just like her.
Mother.
Seriously,
do you have any girlfriend?
No. - Sure?
Why are you asking that?
You look handsome, talk nicely.
Even you fight when it's necessary.
In simple words,
you look like a hero.
Oh, is it? Nobody else
felt it that way I guess.
Nobody is there in my heart.
It's true.
Hello, paper?
Sorry, sir. - Okay.
What if, Akash is also
confused to ask me out?
I will ask him whether
he likes me or not.
Don't think, just ask him.
Can girls take the first step?
Do you want to wait for few years?
Hey, are you able to
understand what am I saying?
Just think about your parents.
Remember, how many hopes
your parents must have on you.
You didn't study
all this for her, right?
You are a lucky fellow.
Don't feel bad,
because she rejected you.
Be happy.
If I was in your place,
I would've been so happy.
I would've partied all night
thinking my future didn't stop here.
You would've known if
you fall in love with someone.
Yes. I never loved anyone
nor I will love anyone.
What is there in this love.
Just giving flowers and talk
with each other the whole night.
You can get girlfriend
anytime in your life.
But think about your goal,
if you miss now, you can't reach it.
Whatever is lost,
we can get it later.
But if you waste your time,
it won't come back.
I never wasted time till now,
also I will never waste my time
in this useless things like love.
Bhumi.
You are leaving?
Yes.
Even I have a flight in the evening.
What else?
- Nothing. I came here to say, bye.
Yeah, yeah. Bye, Bhumi.
Don't know, when we will meet again.
Okay, be in touch.
Bye.
'I felt like he was
directly saying to me.'
'Whatever he said to him,
I felt it was just for me.'
'Few questions are answered
without even finding the answer.'
'Now I know,
what Akash has in his heart.'
'I felt happy before when
he said no one is in his heart.'
'But I understood that,
even I am not there in his heart.'
'If we read the
book again and again'
'will the story change in the end?'
'If you think it will change,
then you are a fool.'
What happened? Did you tell him?
What did he say?
Did he say yes?
No, mom.
He is not correct for me.
- What happened?
Didn't he like you?
Leave him.
Just say one word, I will bring more
handsome and nice guys then him.
Just leave it, mom.
This marriage and
all is not my thing.
What do you mean?
You won't marry?
I believed you and
I stopped praying.
So now, pray to get rid of me.
I am so unfortunate.
You are like a burden on my heart.
Prabha. What are you saying?
Go out of here.
Go.
Responsibilities are
same for mother and father
over their children.
But, in this house
it is not the same.
Here, nobody cares.
Even if you are not interested
in marrying your daughter,
at least did you think about it?
I am neither worries nor thoughts.
nor I take the responsibility,
okay?
Do we just make children
just to marry them, Prabha?
You are right.
Marriage is necessary, but that is
not the only thing that's important.
We have children with high hopes.
We work hard to raise them,
and educate them beyond our means.
And give them whatever they need.
Just to marry them with someone?
We do all this because
we want to see them live happily.
Why can't we wait,
till they search for themselves?
Why can't we know
their choices, Prabha?
Why can't we give the
same amount of time to a girl
like we give to a boy.
Why do we hurry only
for girls marriages?
If we ask them,
people say, what will society think.
If we marry her in some
place where she is not happy
who will suffer in the end?
When a girl turns 13,
you should sanction her.
If she turns 25, just marry her
with someone and loose the burden.
I can't think like
an outmoded father.
In my eyes,
I am not a failure,
if I don't do her marriage.
I can't make her marry
where she doesn't want to marry.
Not until, if there's
a situation where I am ashamed
let anybody think
whatever they want.
I really don't care and I mean it.
Morning, Daddy. - Hey, morning.
Daddy, I am going to Alak
for one week for Bindu's marriage.
We are organising it.
Good, good. Enjoy.
She is helping in everybody's
marriage, but she won't do it.
We can argue and can
even change the judgement
but we can't change
your mother's heart.
It's really impossible.
Mom, I am leaving in the evening.
If I say no, will you stop?
You never listen to me.
Now, what?
I should get married, right?
Mom, who can think that
I should be good more than you.
You see, whoever you like.
Huh, really?
Yes.
Just see,
how nice guy I will search for you.
I will kill the guy who rejects you.
What is that look?
Give me that phone.
Give me.
Why are you guys so serious? Laugh.
What happened to you, ma'am?
You changed your
dressing and your style.
What is the fun
being the same person
in the marriage and in office?
There should be some entertainment
in one's life, right?
You are giving us
some shocking news.
This look suits
you very much, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am. Looks like your
age has been decreased five years.
So, is it fine if I have
still five years left to marry?
Look, they all are here.
- Hey, Bhumi.
Uncle.
All your friends came?
If you have any problem, just ask.
Sure, uncle.
Where is Akash?
He is.. - There he is.
Come.
I was talking about you.
How was your travelling?
- It was nice.
Okay.
I thought you went to your village.
How can I leave you all?
Did you see the location?
It is so good.
If you are okay,
we will make a nice couple video.
Do with me, Sarla.
I will also become famous.
For a couple video we need a hero,
not comedian.
Hey, don't you know how
to talk in front of everybody?
They arrived just now,
let them take rest.
Don't feel bad.
Hari.
Come here. Show them their room.
I should only do all the work.
Come fast.
I am coming, what's the hurry?
He is like that. He is little slow.
It doesn't matter,
but the work should be done.
Take that. Go to your room.
Hey, listen! Find out
why are decorators aren't here.
Who is he? Looks like he
is a brand ambassador for laziness.
I don't know.
- Walk little fast.
If I go fast will
I get any prize? - Oh...
Okay, you come late but
tell us where our room is.
Climb the stairs and turn left.
Take left after the stairs. Okay.
We will go,
you can bring this by noon.
Don't mock me!
Did you see Bhumi.
She changed her style.
She is beautiful even like this.
- Are you feeling happy?
She changed her style because
she doesn't like you.
That is a bad sign.
Don't get excited.
You should be alert.
Take this.
Use it.
If I want to save
it I need to go to bank,
if I want to use it,
I need to go to shop.
I don't have that much patience.
Keep it, yourself.
Hey.
It was really fun. Did you see?
Once.
One more time.
Tiktok batch, I guess.
Hi, Pooja.
Akash. - Akash.
I took that social media reel
but you look like a cinema hero.
Come.
Weather is so good, right?
I like this kind of weather.
What a change, ma'am.
All this because of this place?
If there is no pressure in here,
then you can be happy
wherever you want.
Hi, Bhumi.
Sir, location is so good, right?
Come we'll take a selfie.
- Come, we'll take one.
Why are you leaving?
This is a group selfie?
I am bored here.
I'm going to my room.
Hello, is this Birju?
- Don't you know, who you called?
What's the matter?
The girl you saw
yesterday accepted you.
I saw her yesterday,
and she accepted me today?
So soon? Say no.
Are you driving this car or pushing?
How much time will it take?
Is this car or bullock cart?
Already, I am driving at 100 kmph.
- Drive at 200 kmph.
If I drive it at that speed,
you won't go to marriage
you will go and meet God.
Do you want to go?
Get down.
Bloody old ladies.
Can't get down and can't climb up.
Why did you sit in the middle?
I sat first. Then they came in.
I don't have change.
Just wait here for five minutes.
What did you say? I won't even
wait for any girl for that time.
You think,
I'll wait for your change?
Bring the change and take the money.
Or else leave.
Everywhere there is lag.
- Hey, Birju, how are you?
Yesterday lorry hit him.
This is his soul.
You ask stupid questions.
- He won't reform.
Oh, God!
I am the only active person
amongst these lazy people.
Hey, man.
Just bring me that water bottle.
I sat just now,
and you already gave me other work.
Oh, God!
He is so slow,
looks like even lag is lagging.
Please wait.
Don't work hard.
I will go and get it.
Oh, God! When will go there?
It will take ten days
to you to reach there?
You and your slow motion!
Thank God, one work is done.
He is too slow man.
Hi, how are you?
Hey, Birju.
Why did you come this late?
Normally I will go to
weddings at the last moment,
but this is our Kartik's wedding,
so I came very early.
Okay, wash your legs.
I will make you breakfast.
Oh, when I eat with
hand why should I wash legs?
Time waste.
I will eat it now, itself.
Oh, is this idly or bricks?
He is brainless.
What? - That's what I am asking you?
You blocked my number.
If I come and talk to you,
you are just leaving.
You are not even
giving me time to speak.
I need to talk to you.
- Akash, please.
I have nothing to talk.
Just listen what I am saying.
- I said, no.
Actually, that day...
I am trying very
hard to forget that.
Please don't remind me.
- Just listen what I am saying once.
I am begging you.
What else do you want me to do?
Should I catch your legs?
Oh, oh.
You slow coach! Where are you from?
Hey, brother. Won't you
introduce me to your friend?
He is not my friend. He is my sir.
Oh, sir! Which soap do you use?
Who invented this marriages.
Brother, you have so much height
between your feet and your head.
And she doesn't
even have any height.
What is this?
Rose. - Why?
For love.
I liked you at the first sight.
You also should tell
your heart to love me.
Go ahead! There is lots
of food for all. Please go ahead.
Eat to your heart's content,
and praise the Lord. Okay?
Aunty, is everybody good?
- Hey, Mr Birju.
You reserved first seat for food.
Brother, you are the
only person who understood me.
Thank you.
- Do you want to sit beside me?
No, I will sit somewhere else.
- Come, let's go.
He is a different type.
I will be the very first one
who will be served.
Hey, start serving from this corner.
Oh, my God!
What? You guys are
serving from that side?
For just pickle it
took fifteen minutes.
Just ask whatever you want.
- Oh, my God!
Uncle, I can't wait for
every item to come from that side.
I can't control the hunger.
Don't be angry, Mr Birju.
- What do I do?
I will send a guy who
won't lag and will serve you.
Thank you, brother.
Hey.
Oh, this guy!
I think, I am not lucky today.
Bhumi, why do you keep
your face always angry?
You know, how cute you look
while you sleep like this.
Oh!
Why didn't I observe
you like this back then?
I want to say one thing,
if I get any chance
to rewind my life again.
I will go back to our college days
and I will start living again,
but this time with you.
But now, there is no chance of that
I want to continue
my life being with you.
I want to experience your love.
When will you show me?
I have many things to say you.
Not like this,
I want you to hear me.
While seeing in your eyes.
Good night.
You should've told me first.
Why did you make it so complicated?
If she is angry,
she won't listen to anyone.
I am the reason,
why is she like that.
She loved me so much, that
she couldn't find any other person.
These days, people are
marrying after calculations
but she stayed single for her love.
Nobody loves anyone
else so much, uncle.
Without knowing I made
her suffer very much.
I will wait for years
till she knows my love.
Okay, then.
Pack this. - Hey.
Come here.
Keep it there.
See there.
Hello. - How is the guy?
Did you like him?
Tell something.
Did you change your heart again?
Remember, you gave me your word.
Yes, he is nice.
- Should I arrange the meeting.
It's up to you.
Bye.
Sister, they are waiting
for you in the bride's room.
Come. Let's go.
Hello. - How are you?
How is the wedding going?
All good, daddy. How are you?
I am good.
Your mom is so excited
for your engagement.
Hey,
did you like him for real
or you just said okay
because of your mother.
If you don't like him, tell me.
Don't think about her.
Nothing like that, Daddy.
I am okay.
Okay, take care.
Bye, daddy. - Bye.
"The groom and the bride are ready,
to be for each other."
Bhumi, you will come soon, right?
Tomorrow is the engagement.
If you come home and take rest,
you will be fresh in the morning.
Okay, I'll come.
Bhumi, I want to talk to you.
Congrats.
We did it.
We wanted to do their
marriage together. We did it.
Now we don't have to act.
You think, this is all just an act?
Isn't it?
I think, you are still angry on me.
I am not upset with you,
but I don't like you.
Please, don't trouble me.
What did I do?
Time's up. I need to go.
Why are you in hurry?
Tomorrow is my engagement.
This made me closer to you.
If I give it back to you?
I am afraid you will
never meet me again.
Nice.
If I don't want to remember you
I should not keep anything
that reminds me of you.
Wait, Bhumi.
What? What is your problem?
I need to talk to you.
Just give five minutes.
I don't want to talk to you.
- You loved me so much.
You can't give me five minutes?
Just wait.
Why are you leaving
when I am talking to you?
Won't you listen what I want to say?
I didn't say it
when I should've said.
I didn't listen when
I should've listened.
You loved me, you felt it,
you are breaking up,
and you are leaving.
Then who will think about me?
Only you have feelings?
I don't have it or what?
Do you know, why I came
here after all these years?
Why am I roaming around you?
Did you think about it even once?
I didn't come here for any project,
or any marriage function.
I came here only for you.
When I knew that you loved me,
I couldn't stay there and
I searched for you and came here.
Hi, how are you?
Yes, I have reached.
I am so sorry.
Akash.
Anjali. What are you doing here?
How is your friend, Bhumi?
After college, we didn't meet. - Oh!
She didn't tell
you but she loved you.
She just used to think about you.
She always tried to talk to you.
At that moment
I saw it from your view.
I didn't want to participate.
I did for you.
Seriously,
you don't have any girlfriend?
No.
After knowing that,
I didn't like what I was doing?
I didn't know where to find you.
I didn't know what were you doing?
I searched for you.
I called everybody whoever I knew.
I searched you in social media.
You were nowhere.
Where are you?
You are still in love with me?
Or did you forget me?
Gautam. - Yes.
She is in Hyderabad.
She is running a startup company.
Guess what?
My father is funding the company.
Hey, Akash. One more thing.
She is not married yet.
I don't know why,
after hearing that,
I couldn't control my happiness.
I couldn't stay there any longer.
I thought you will
be excited when you see me.
But, when I saw you
behaving so casually
I didn't know how to react.
I thought you moved on.
I wanted to observe
you very closely,
so I took up this project.
I felt very attractive
when I saw you changed totally.
So, I loved you,
when you made me recognise myself.
I just wanted to know
what you think about me,
so I lied about the bridesmaids.
I listened that you loved me.
But that was first time I saw,
how you felt about me.
I didn't know your love.
I made you feel very sad.
You left that night,
I thought you were angry on me.
I was waiting that
you will come back.
But,
you are leaving this watch...
now I can understand,
you left me on that day itself.
I thought I understood
your love very late,
but now I get that,
it is very late.
This is a small project.
- I am saying I'll do it.
I need to talk to you.
Akash, please.
I don't want to talk to you.
Sister, everyone is leaving.
Call Akash.
Mom is waiting, uncle.
I need to go.
Sarla, bring the bag.
You already came? Come here.
Let's go.
Bhumi. They will
arrive anytime soon.
Get ready.
Go Bhumi.
Please smile, Madam.
You look beautiful when you smile.
Did you connect at first sight?
If you love someone, let them know.
You should know,
what he thinks about it.
You didn't even question
and you are waiting for an answer.
How will you know?
Go. Already you guys
waited for so long.
What is all this, Prabha?
Hello, aunty.
- Son. The girl you love...
Is her name Bhumi?
Yes, aunty.
Did you guys study
in the same college?
How do you know?
Her love is very pure.
That made Akash come here.
I just helped them be together.
At last, you daughter is
marrying and you are sending her.
I am not sending
her after the marriage.
She must need someone to guide her.
You gave me the watch and you left?
You decided you wanted to leave me.
No chance.
However you cut me.
I was about to go
and meet your parents.
In the mean time aunty
called me and asked about us.
So, now we are here after that.
When you came here,
why didn't you meet me directly?
Why do you think your client
kept the meeting in
the hotel where I stay?
She told she will be coming
but she was not there. Why?
So, that was all your plan?
You look innocent but you are not.
What can I do?
I couldn't see your love.
I had to put up an act for that.
You waited for me this long.
I should at least fight this, right?
Hello, I didn't wait for you.
Just, I didn't connect to anybody.
Why are you laughing?
You didn't have this ego in college.
You made me like this.
You didn't even say it yet. - What?
That you like me. - Wait for that.
How long?
Till that 'Bhumi' (sky)
meets the 'Akash' (land).
I will tell your mom,
she will do it easily.