the most important thing is take care of
your family take care of your parents
the strength lies in your family your
family is your first priority
this is what i believe and i have always
done it and i would suggest you your
family is your first priority
i write about startups and i write about
entrepreneurs and they have perhaps some
of the toughest times when they build
their businesses you've done the same
grind too as an actor so you know you
started your life from ground zero and
today i mean i was reading architectural
digest and they said you've got the most
beautiful home in mumbai today so what's
it been like
to go from ground zero to right up there
where it matters
yes it's been a
hard journey and it's been
um
a different kind of experience
i don't know from where to start from to
answer your questions
it's going to take a lot a lot of time
to talk about it
my formula has been a very different
kind of formula i'll tell you something
i
yes my hard work is a lot in my film
industry i've been working hard since
last 28 years now i finished about i've
finished about
130 films
and
i've now become a producer since last 10
years i've been producing films
like bhakt
airlift baby
special chabis
and stone and even padman also
i always
wanted to bring you know the most
important thing of my life has been that
i wanted a change every time anybody
tries to put an image on me
i have always jumped to some other image
i never wanted to be in one track
because i always think a change is the
most important thing in anybody's life
because if the person can change himself
he
he can do many different things like i
started doing romantic films i started
doing
i've done
villains role i've done so many kind of
different kind of roles i didn't i
didn't care about it i just went and
then changes so i just would like to say
the changes is the most important thing
but on top of that
i would
uh bring one thing
whether you believe it or not
but this i will share it with you guys
that
my success
lies
a lot
and my parents feet i'll tell you why
my
whenever in the morning whenever i go to
work
i always touch my mother's feet and go
ahead
trust me
it is
it has made so much difference in my
career in my life i have been saved by
so many people who are
like a lot of negative energies i've
been saved from
but that is the fact
yes obviously the hard work is the most
important thing change is another thing
but to have a positive aura around you
and that only your parents can bring you
not even god it's only your parents who
will bring your positive aura around you
and and care for you
i like to deconstruct when i construct
myself completely then i look at myself
i want to break it
i want to break this whole image i want
to start another construction and build
another one
this is
uh
i would say it is in my mindset this is
what i have followed i never stick to
one particular image
i just want to just keep on innovating
myself
undergoing i know i miss i can be
comfortable by just doing
commercial cinemas like a rowdy rathor
or a house full or this kind of films
but i just want to deconstruct myself
even when i did 2.0 with rajnee khan sir
i'm playing a villain's role a lot of
people ask me why do you need to play a
villain's role why not
what is wrong so i just need to d i i'll
i love to deconstruct myself that is it
ma'am sure
um
so you know i also see that you probably
the complete man of the industry you
know you're so busy you do four movies
as you said and yet you make sure that
you always spend time with your family
and you always have time for holidays
and i see startups who just get so
engrossed with their work that they
completely forget that they have
families back there they have parents
their children their bi
sister
you know how do you make sure that you
balance it out see i'll tell you that is
why the first thing when i started
talking about it i said the most
important thing is take care of your
family take care of your parents that is
the most important thing the strength
lies in your family
the positiveness lies in your family
i
i work a lot i work
hell of a lot but it is nothing i divide
my work nothing i all i always take
whatever in my life i want to do i do it
with maths
i calculate it
i'm doing four films a year
i'm doing about four movies a year
one movie takes about 35 to 40 days
i don't work
i saturday i work only seven to two
two o'clock in the afternoon i'm off
saturday two o'clock onwards i don't
work
sunday i don't work
monday i start working
i work eight hours a day
but in that eight hours i am on the set
i don't move away from the set i don't
go sit in my vanity van
i tell my producer my director that i am
here
you make me work
eight hours is good enough
because because after eight hours you
know because i have to be in front of
the camera i have to look good i take
one and a half month of holiday with my
family every year
i just put the globe in front of my wife
and ask her i worked a lot you tell me
where you want to go
i do that
i
so basically what i'm trying to say is
all you have to do
you have to look at your
family you have to look at your priority
your family is your first priority
this is what i believe and i have always
done it and i would suggest you your
family is your first priority
once the priority is set properly once
they also know you okay my husband or my
father or my or my brother will after
working he will come and he'll spend all
his time here perfectly fine nothing can
go wrong with you guys nothing can go
it's a tried and tested thing which i
have done it i have even told a lot of
people
in my
in my colleagues i have told them and i
have seen changes coming to them
i love the fact that you said that you
have some extreme discipline and that
you follow it and it's worked for you
bollywood is known to party it's known
it's about fun it's about excitement so
how do you make sure that your entire
teams your your producers your directors
go actors everybody is in tune with you
they're insane because when they are
working with me the agreement is so
strong
that
they have to come early morning properly
time otherwise the agreement will get
you know
that's a good thing to be in a position
where everybody sort of no it is not
even a small producer can do it it is
not that amazing because if you are
taking a chance and if you i always
believe i i always tell everybody
i am an actor
who's a producers actor
i believe what the producer says i have
to do it
and it is important he is my boss but
yeah some of the cases i myself am the
boss of myself you know one thing i like
about the bollywood industry and i think
which all industries need to learn
is that money cannot be tapping you know
money cannot be taboo you cannot grow
your business or yourself without money
having your businesses your products
making money so you know what i would
want you to message out to startups here
today is that making money is really
important i see money is become somehow
a third or a four year plan after they
start a business you know making money
is important
i was working i did films for 50 000
rupees
but for i think a long time i must say
for 10 years i worked
not more than about
10 12 lakh rupees uh a movie
so you're the 10th highest paid star in
the world
so uh
so now
but then
i worked hard for it
and it is not necessary i mean you don't
have to run behind money first you have
to run behind your product first you
have to run behind the quality first and
after that things will change you will
realize it
and i think that i i have done that like
that so i cannot tell them anywhere in
any other way
[Music]
you