1otha
Subscribe to Technical Guruji channel and press bell icon
to see latest technology videos first.
Friends, Samsung has brought in the market new in Samsung Galaxy line up
the latest phone which is with me the Samsung Galaxy J8.
So keep watching this video today I'm going to talk about this brand new phone
Here we are going to do it's unboxing and see some
new features of this phone
and here talking about special, here is something special for all of you
here you will get J8 to any 8 lucky winners
keep watching this video and I'm going to give all the information
Namashkar(Hello)! Friends myself Gaurav you are watching Technical Guruji
"Chaliyee Shuru Karte Hain"
(Come on Let's Begin)
[Intro Music Rolling] Captions by Facebook.com/Knowledge To World
Friends, here we have the box of Samsung Galaxy J8
and this box is similar to Samsung Galaxy J6
where in the front there is the mention of Infinity
which shows that the display of this is phone is 18.5:9 aspect ratio
on the back some features are been mentioned of this phone
tells us about its display, along with it has dual rear
it has 4 GB RAM, 64 GB storage you will get
and the screen is 6 inch 720p+ display which is a Super Amoled Screen
along with that the combination of the
rear camera
is 16 MP + 5MP for deepth sensing
the front camera is a 16 MP and the processor is a
Qualcomm Snapdragon 450
3500 mAh battery, fingerprint scanner,
option of face unlock is also available
and here other branding is also there
Make for India, Samsung Duos, and Nor Security.
Here on the box, the price mentioned is Rs.19,990
but the official pricing is Rs.18,990
and you can get a cashback of Rs.2000 if you pay using
PayTm or by using ICICI Bank Credit, Debit Card
which makes its price down to Rs.16,990.
Here friends if you get this phone before 31 July
then you will get one-time screen replacement.
Other than that some basic info is mentioned on the box
and here a very important thing here is written
"Indian Sim Card Only" which means you can only use this in India and not outside India
so first you user get an Indian Sim card and activate it
So without wasting any time lets unbox this phone
however I don't have a good knife
but I think this can break the seal see what is inside it.