'Madhupur, Uttar Pradesh.'
No...
'It's my wedding today.'
'I will have to part'
from my fields, my land!
'No! That's not possible.'
"Nandini, the child of the soil."
Nobody can take me away from you.
I shall never leave you.
Mother Earth, you need water.
I'll bring it right away.
Nandu, you're here?
It's your wedding today
and you're toiling in the fields!
You're a bride-to-be
yet you can't leave the fields alone.
Uncle, this soil is worth gold.
Every girl dreams of marriage.
Likewise
farmers live for their lands.
When we touch this soil
let alone me
but the whole world benefits from it.
Do you get me?
Need I say more?
I'll leave now.
Listen up, everybody
be there on time for my wedding.
Yes, dear, we'll be there.
Mother Earth, I need your blessings
so that I won't forget my village
once I leave for my marital home.
Let's go home, Shera.
Stop!
Why are you blocking my way?
Nandu, get down.
Your grandpa hasn't repaid
the loan he borrowed from me.
From now on
this tractor is mine.
My grandpa and I never break promises.
We'll clear your dues.
Don't you dare!
Don't your dare touch Shera!
I told you, we'll clear your dues.
Do I look like a fool?
You'll get married and leave.
How will you repay my loan?
So what?
I'm getting married, not dying!
I'll come here every day
after getting married.
My marital home isn't far.
It's close by
in Ayodhya, the land of Lord Ram.
'Ayodhya.'
'Hail Goddess Sita and Lord Ram.'
[Devotional Song]
Lord Ram, when You returned to Ayodhya
I'm sure, Your mother, Kaushalya
was as anxious
as I am today.
My grandson, Akash
my dear boy
is returning from New York.
I am brimming with joy
and endless hopes.
Dear Lord
shower us with Your blessings.
Give the holy offering to everyone.
Pack some for Akash.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, Mr Dubey.
Everything should be well organised.
I'm leaving it to you.
A new chapter of Bharadwaj Industries
begins tomorrow.
New chapter?
What is she planning for tomorrow?
I've invited eminent people
from across the city.
In their presence
I shall announce the successor
of Bharadwaj Industries.
Things better go well, Mr Dubey.
Poor Aunt!
She's planning a coronation of sorts
in Ayodhya tomorrow!
She has no clue
how I'll throttle her plans.
Sorry, Aunt.
It was a huge mistake
that Kamya overheard you.
Kamya won't sit still.
That's great!
You'll look better than your
sister-in-law, Imarti Bharadwaj.
By God
I'll look stylish!
You'll look super glamorous.
My beloved Mother-in-law.
As pretty as you are, you're naive too.
You're always in the dark.
You're always putting up with things
but I won't.
My dear Kamya, are you done
creating suspense?
If yes
just be out with
the news that's troubling you.
It's a scintillating piece of news!
Do you know what your sister-in-law
is planning tomorrow?
Without seeking your approval
she has chosen the successor
of the Bharadwaj family.
- What are you saying?
- It's true.
How could Sumitra take that decision
without consulting with me?
I am the eldest daughter-in-law
of this family.
I'm her senior.
I call the shots here.
'Be ready for the blast!'
Driver, get the car.
Grandaunt
how do I look?
Are you coming like this to the airport?
I told her
it's not a wedding!
Exactly!
Sister-in-law Jyoti, look at me.
This is called the airport look.
Suraj couldn't take his eyes off me.
Of course, Tanya, you look gorgeous.
You're too good.
Wait till you see my mother-in-law.
That's grandma for you.
I call the shots here.
What say, Sumitra?
No doubt about it.
The Bharadwaj family will take the airport
by a storm
only if it makes it there!
Please spare Akash!
He has landed
and left from the airport.
[Sanskrit chant]
Left? Where did he go?
I know where.
I'll bring him home.
[Sanskrit chant]
Stop right there.
I'm the seniormost member of this family.
Did you forget that?
You decided to
declare the successor
of the Bharadwaj family
without consulting with me!
First and foremost
who's the successor that you've chosen?
You'll know tomorrow along
with the others.
Have patience.
[Devotional Song]
Hail Goddess Sita and Lord Ram.
'Soon, you'll know'
'what fate has in store for you.'
'I've aimed my gun at Sumitra Devi.'
'I'll shoot her.'
'I missed the oldie!'
[Sanskrit chant]
Grandma, how do you always find me here?
That's how love works.
Welcome to Ayodhya, kid.
I'm pleased to no end.
You studied abroad
yet you didn't forsake your culture.
How could I, Grandma?
I've learned this from you.
You know what
I've earned my masters
and I'm the gold medallist.
- Wow! That's befitting for a Bharadwaj!
- Yes.
Now, I'll find you a suitable bride.
No, Grandma.
I won't marry yet.
I've some research to do.
I don't think
I'll marry a girl from Ayodhya.
Our feelings won't match.
Do you get me?
I'm sure, such a girl doesn't exist
in Ayodhya.
Why not?
There's an Eve for every Adam.
I'm sure, your partner awaits you.
Nandu, you argued
with the moneylender again!
You know it's your wedding today.
What if things had gotten out of hand?
When you were little, your parents died
and left you in my care.
I raised you
so you'd marry in a good family
and I'd rest in peace.
Grandpa, it's live in peace.
Yes, whatever.
I just want to see you dressed as a bride
and get you married off.
You can't bear to part from me
yet you want me to marry.
- Why so?
- My child, I want you
to live a happy married life.
But, Grandpa,
this village is akin to heaven.
What heaven?
Farmers live terrible lives.
We're called
sons of the soil
who feed the world
yet we die of hunger!
We're either beseeching heavens for rains
or begging money lenders
to give us grace period for loans.
I don't want you to
ruin your life in this soil.
So, just get married
and live in the city.
Grandpa, I've made a decision.
I won't give up my duties here
after getting married.
After getting married
I'll serve my in-laws
and fulfil my duties here as well.
Understood? Need I say more?
Grandma!
- I am ready.
- Oh, wow.
Come.
Grandma, now that I'm here
I'll be at your service.
- Is it?
- You just take rest, okay?
- Okay.
- No more work.
I've to attend a friend's wedding
in the evening.
May I?
Of course, you may go.
For all you know
you might find your love there.
I don't think so, Grandma.
I feel
I won't marry a local girl
but a foreigner.
No, Akash.
Things will go as per Lord Ram's wish.
You'll see
how His plans unfold.
- Come.
- Let's go.
'The oldie's here.'
'I won't miss this time around.'
What are you doing?
Give me the key, I'll drive.
Hello.
- Greetings.
- Just make sure
nothing's lacking in catering
to our guests.
Nothing will lack.
I'm just waiting for the groom
so that we can perform
the welcoming ceremony.
That will happen pretty soon.
Just come with me.
Please call the groom.
As soon as you grease my palm as decided.
200,000 rupees!
I see, hold on.
You never have money to repay my loan
but you have loads for this wedding.
Sir, this is for Nandini's wedding.
I will repay your loan gradually.
Mr. Ram, try saying that
to Nandini's in-laws!
This amount
pays off your tractor debt.
I'll recover the rest eventually.
Thank you, Akash.
I didn't think, you'd make it.
Oh, come on! We're school buddies.
How could I miss it?
- Let's go in.
- Wait.
Yes, Dad. I'm about to enter.
Don't come in until I say so.
'Guess he didn't get paid yet.'
What's wrong? Let's go.
No
I can't go in until dad says so.
Why not?
Guess the girl's family
hasn't fulfilled our condition.
Look, conditions are meant
for business, not marriage.
Be a man, bro. Your bride awaits you.
Let's go in.
Mr. Ram
you lost the money.
No money, no marriage.
Money is more important than the bride.
I beg your pardon
my grandpa has taught me
not to speak unless spoken to.
But you compelled me
to speak up.
You're particular about accounts.
So am I.
To give you 200,000 rupees
my grandpa sacrificed
his hunger and sleep
to organise that amount.
He didn't keeps tabs of that
but I did.
He wept a million tears worrying
about his granddaughter
at the cost of his well-being.
His eyesight weakened
yet he didn't stop dreaming
of my marriage.
You said, nothing should be lacking
in catering to the guests.
He broke his back
tending to your demands.
What for?
Simply because
he's the bride's grandfather?
And you...
The groom's father won't compromise.
Why so? Why won't you compromise?
You have a mighty sharp tongue.
I should've demanded for 5,00,000
instead of 200,000.
- 5,00,000?
- Yes.
Is that all your son is worth?
My grandpa says, I am invaluable.
Thus, this isn't a match between equals.
We will neither pay you
nor beg your son to marry me.
Go away.
Nandu, don't say that.
Why not? You taught me how Lord Ram
was a man of principles.
But if demons cross their limits
they should be annihilated.
Understood?
Need I say more?
I think
I should set your spineless son right too.
[Sanskrit chant]
Is that your bride?
Let's settle your account.
How much are you worth?
2,00,000?
I'd like to see what
I am paying Rs. 2,00,000 for?
Dowry?
Vikas
what nonsense is this?
I mean, how can you demand dowry?
So? What's wrong in that?
It's a custom here.
I've to get my sisters married eventually.
I, too, will have to pay dowry then.
I'll need money for that.
Fine, here you go.
Stop it.
I'll talk to him.
Vikas, this is really wrong.
If you really need money, I'll give you.
Two lakh, three lakh,
whatever amount you want.
What are you saying?
You're asking him to demand
for more dowry!
Claim any amount you want!
What nonsense!
I didn't ask him to demand for dowry.
Dear God! You just said that.
Guess I should hand you
to the police as well
for demanding dowry.
Have you lost your mind?
Enough with the English.
Don't try to intimidate me.
What's with this
brazen negotiations?
Making demands!
Two lakh rupees for a railway employee
three lakh for a policeman
and five lakh for a doctor or an engineer!
Hey, English hero, what's your amount?
How much are you worth?
Way beyond your imagination!
He has studied abroad.
Oh!
So a million to say the least.
Will that do or...
- Listen...
- Is this a market
where educated suitors
get auctioned?
I didn't ask for dowry.
Why are you targeting me?
Ma'am
since you don't speak English,
I'll explain in Hindi.
I am against the dowry system.
Understood?
I say this to all of you.
You should neither give dowry
nor marry suitors asking for dowry.
Understood?
What do we do then?
This girl should call off this wedding.
Listen up, lad.
Such things happen abroad.
In our society, if a bride
is abandoned at the wedding
nobody marries her.
She remains unmarried for life.
What rubbish!
Why won't anyone marry her?
Anybody will.
Will you marry her?
Answer me, will you?
Why drag me into this?
Why would I marry her?
He'll marry the one
who pays him the most.
No, not for money.
I'll marry the one who wins my heart.
A girl who can be a worthy companion.
A life partner due to whom
my head would be held high.
Not someone I can't even talk to.
Oh, forget it,
I can't tolerate your presence.
I can't tolerate you either.
Understood?
- Let's go, this wedding is called off.
- Mr. Jeevan.
Look, if you leave like this
we'll be humiliated.
Move!
Grandpa!
Let's go. This wedding is cancelled.
Grandpa, you...
'I'll make sure that him and his son'
'fall at grandpa's feet and apologise.'
Sumitra!
Sumitra! Sumitra!
What's the matter, Mother-in-law?
Is that a new chant?
You're chanting Sumitra
instead of the lord's name!
What?
I was chanting Sumitra's name?
Sumitra has ruined my life!
She has messed with my mind.
What do I tell you, Kamya?
I was the elder daughter-in-law
in this family.
But the day Sumitra
got married into this family
my in-laws entrusted her
with the household and business too.
She has seized all the power
and orders us around.
Then, you should find
a way to overpower her.
I'll help you.
'Kamya is right.'
'I have to get Sumitra under my control'
'by finding Akash a suitable bride.'
'If he marries a cunning lass'
'Sumitra will rule this house'
'not me!'
'I can't let that happen.'
What's wrong, English hero?
All alone?
Where's your friend?
At the police station.
I handed him to the cops
for demanding dowry.
I see. I threatened you both.
Hence, you left him alone
at the police station
so that you can be the good guy.
This is why I want to marry a foreigner
and not the likes of you.
Girls like you
just don't understand anything.
Foolish!
What? I'm foolish?
Because I hail from a village?
What did you say back there?
I am not a worthy companion?
Why? Because I am a villager!
Yes, I am a villager.
But don't underestimate me.
Girls from villages aren't always docile.
We're well bred
capable of raising a family
and if need be
they can fiercely protect their family.
I don't speak English
but that doesn't mean that I'm no good.
I'm a farmer, adept at ploughing
and driving a tractor too.
Can you drive a tractor?
No!
What was that you said?
You want a life partner
due to whom your head will be held high.
When I'll drive my tractor, you'll have to
hold your head high to see me.
Understood?
Need I say more?