God has written so much travel in my life.
We didn't even reach home
properly from Hong Kong.
That we had to leave for
Mumbai again tomorrow morning.
Yes, brother.
Put on your shoes quickly.
Hurry up, we have to go pick up sister.
Pihu and I are going to pick up Rashi Didi.
Ritu and Preetu are
going for something else.
Hurry up.
Don't know what happened
to Pihu today at 1 o'clock,
Sister, Sister, Sister
How does she know that it's
time for elder sister to came.
Today we made Pihu wear other shoes.
Today shoes won't drop,
Who gave you this gift today?
This is our house's gift
Is this your house's gift?
Yes
Yes Let's go.
I don't want to go home.
She is having fun, she
doesn't want to go home
Pihu, do you want to go home or not?
Finally, our Lala ji move ahead.
Hurry up, let's go home.
I have brought a very
nice gift for both of you
Let's go, let's go
Didn't you get chocolate from school today?
No one had a birthday.
It's 6.30 in the evening, I
have taken a bath and got ready
So now we are going to worship God.
Today is Monday.
So we are going to worship, I
said let's keep Lord Shiva's fast.
Let's worship God and then
we will start eating.
After that, we will go to the gym.
Rashi's class is going on.
Welcome back to the vlog
We have just left for Mumbai.
And there is so much travel in life
I don't feel like it, but if there is
work then it has to be done, bro.
We have reached Mumbai airport.
In Delhi in the morning,
everyone travels by DIGI Yatra.
So in DIGI Yatra, I scanned by
outside the airport automatically.
They don't check the
ID, it's already checked.
So there was no crowd outside the airport.
As soon as I went inside,
the security belt DIGI yatra didn't work.
It was empty outside and crowded inside.
Anyway, we are not going by taxi today.
We will take an auto.
Because the taxi will take me
to where i want to go in an hour.
From here the auto will take
me in 15 minutes.
The metro will take 15
minutes more ahead from there.
It's raining here, I bring
an umbrella from Delhi.
Ritu says i am crazy,
but it from Mumbai itself.
I didn't an umbrella from Mumbai.
When it doesn't rain, I think
if I leave it now, it will stop.
I will take it later.
Then it starts raining, I
think how can I take it now
It's raining now, I can't even
go out to buy an umbrella.
So I get stuck in that loop.
That's why I wanted to
take an umbrella from Delhi.
You have to come here to get an
auto, you don't get an auto from above.
We have reached Airport
Road Metro, This is the right thing here.
Oh, I left this.
This is such a nice bag.
This was sent by YouTube,
I made an unboxing of it.
Dude, YouTube used to
send a lot of stuff before.
There used to be YouTube
FanFest, Creators Meet.
Meta used to do it, but I
don't know about YouTube.
I mean, since Covid happened,
YouTube is like.
Literally, do you see how
empty Mumbai Metro is.
This is a culture habit
for the people of Delhi.
I can't even think of
traveling in Delhi Metro.
I know some people will say
that there is no time, it's 11 o'clock
Dude, there is no time for Delhi
Metro, there are crowds everywhere.
This is the ticket counter,
omly two girls are waiting.
Bro, there is not a single
person on the metro.
Look at this.
It's 11.30 am, we have
reached our destination.
We will work here till
10 pm and then go home.
If you come to Mumbai, do
bring this, otherwise don't come.
The work is done, we took
an auto and went home.
My house is a little far
from here,
but I told the auto driver to drop me here
Because it's impossible to
live in Mumbai without eating Pani Puri.
We have reached home, it's 10 pm.
Where did my bag go?
I did bring my bag.
I have ordered food,
the food is almost here.
Let's take this bag out, it work is here.
Let's take this inside.
Welcome back, it's 3.30 pm
I have been working since
morning,
I am getting up a little
late I took a little chill.
This is my breakfast, lunch and everything.
I have done one job,
now I have to do the other.
But bro, I have to praise the city.
It rains so much here, but
still work doesn't stop.
Everyone does their work.
But here people have learned
how to work even in the rain.
I mean, if you are ordering
food, it is also coming on time.
If you are ordering groceries
from any app, it is also coming on time.
Everyone has learned how to live.
We still have problems.
It rains so much that
we are sitting at home
Making tea, fritters, holiday, rainy day.
But it's not like that here
Bro, so much time is
wasted in ordering food.
I am still watching, I don't
understand what to eat.
I think I praised too much.
My order was an hour ago,
now my order is canceled.
I am starving to death.
Bro, it's been raining since morning.
Let's go out and see if we
can find something to eat.
If we get tea and biscuits, it will be fun.
Finally, the food has
arrived, let's eat a little.
I have ordered simple
food, I have ordered Khichdi.
We are editing something and
shooting something at the same time,
This is the condition of the room.
Bro, it's 11 o'clock in the night.
It's still raining.
I couldn't even go to the gym.
I mean, I could go, but I
couldn't, take an umbrella this far.
It's not like that, it's
an excuse of the rain.
But it's amazing, bro, it's raining.
Bro, at 2 o'clock in the
morning, finally work is over.
But I am very hungry right now
No delivery will come at this time.
But for the betterment of
man, man is useful to man.
This is Airbnb, I mean, it's an apartment.
The people who were living
before me must have bought Maggi
But they couldn't eat it,
they left it.
Good luck to that person.
Bro, I am eating Maggi after so many years.
Maybe I ate it in the lockdown
After that,
how small will the Maggi packets be.
Bro, the packet in which the
Maggi was in, look at the insect in it.
Should I eat it or not, I
don't understand, man.
I am very hungry.
Isn't there any insect in it?
I can't see it in it, then it's okay.
We make Maggi and it is made in 2 minutes.
I said, we have 2 minutes left
Let's fix the face of the room, bro.
What I am doing, you guys don't do it.
Don't eat Maggi at night.
Now people will say that
you are eating brother, you don't do it.
Bro, you watch my vlog and tell me.
When did I eat Maggi last time?
The person who told
me, showed it in the vlog.
I will give him a reward.
Welcome back, day number 3
We are leaving for work in Mumbai.
Yesterday, I had a holiday in a way
I didn't do anything yesterday.
I mean, I did it at
home, I didn't go there.
Today I am going from here.
Today is the day to go out.
It's still raining, I have an umbrella.
That's why we are leaving.
I am getting my Uber
booked quickly, auto.
When you book an auto,
it shows in 1 minute away.
And it's been 10 minutes now,
he hasn't booked anything yet
Bro, my auto is here.
I have come back to the same metro
from where I started in the morning.
It's 10 o'clock at night, I
just need to get the auto.
Auto! It stopped.
That's it, get me off.
Thank you.
The tiredness of the
whole day vanishes.
When we come here, we eat our Sev Puri.
Today, brother will make
something different and feed us.
He is making Bhel Puri instead of Sev Puri.
Today we will eat Bhel Puri.
Bro, there has been a huge loss.
The auto in which we came,
the umbrella got left in that auto.
In a city like Mumbai, living without
an umbrella It's impossible, bro.
bro, I will have to order
a new one tomorrow.
Now, what's the point
of buying an umbrella?
I will go in the morning,
it will be raining at that time.
God should stop the rain for
those who want to buy an umbrella.
Once you buy an umbrella,
let it rain again, God.
But no.
Welcome back home.
No matter what I say,
it's fun to come home.
Hey guys, welcome back
to the vlog It's morning now.
I am telling you, last night
I slept after drinking tea.
So here is a cup of tea.
There was no tea in it.
There was only a tea bag.
There was a little tea in the tea bag.
I woke up in the morning
and there were insects here.
When it rains, the sun doesn't come out.
Insects terrorize people, bro.
There was no food, there was nothing
There was only tea in the tea bag.
There was a light tea in the
cup, there were two drops,
It was left in the tea bag.
There were insects in it.
The sun doesn't come out.
I don't know how long it's been.
Even if the sun doesn't come out.
Bro, there are insects here.
So I have made coffee now.
Let's enjoy coffee with Mop.
Cheers Mop.
I ordered a new umbrella today.
New Hey New Umbrella.
The Uber driver went ahead.
I thought he left today.
It's raining heavily, bro
This is normal for people.
I have reached the metro station.
My whole life has been like this.
Home, auto, metro, work
Without a metro, auto, home.
But I can't go to gym, don't know why.
I have become used to it,
I don't know what will happen to me.
But there is a big
advantage of doing a job.
That you will never waste your time
Because you have to
go to the office every day.
So if you are going to the office.
Then the boss will give you some work.
So when you work for yourself.
Sometimes it happens I
haven't done anything in the day.
It's a non-productive day.
When you do a job,
So there is no non-productive day.
Which is what I like about when i go.
When I come to work,
I have to go to the office If
I have to do work, then it's fun.
But yes, I have the
liberty to set my own time.
I will have so much fun today.
I have that.
Let's drink tea.
Bad luck, didn't get the tea.
I mean they didn't have without sugar.
He was making it.
I said I'll come later.
But the biscuits in the tea stall.
They are so crunchy, it's so good.
I enjoy in eating them.
Just stop it here.
Thank you
Back from work
Same old place
Today i don't forget the umbrella.
Let's get up.
Let's start the work.
What's up guys
Welcome back
Today is our last day in Mumbai.
Let's start the morning routine.
Let's heat the water and drink.
This is my third trip to Mumbai
in the last month and a half.
But the same condition I was in on day 1.
The same condition I am
in on day 5.
Non-stop rain.
Brother, I drank water.
Let's do our morning routine.
I have been doing in my morning
routine one thing for 3-4 days.
Because if you do it
too it will help you a lot.
Brother, there is nothing much to break.
Like what you have to do is,
You have to sit, Full squat down.
Indian style.
In the Shit position,
Like this.
Everywhere in our house has become western.
I forgot to sit in this position.
There is a lot of benefit
in sitting in this position.
Your digestive tract will be fine.
Your pancreas will work well.
But why do I sit?
I sit in the lower back
When I wake up in the
morning my waist is stiff.
This disgestive system will be fine.
This will be fine.
You will get to know the effects slowly.
But the stiffness of the lower back.
Sit for 5 minutes
You will get to know at that time.
So what happens
What I do is
I round my spine.
Because your spine is round,
So I do this.
And I do this
So my whole spine is decompressed.
So your spine is like this
So even I sleep wrongly.
And my weakness is that
I sleep on my stomach,
You shouldn't sleep like that
You should sleep sideways or frontways.
But i turn myself in the night.
My spine is completely compressed
I sit all day.
There is work on the table.
The spine is compressed
So you must have seen.
Some people hang upside
down and some do Pilates.
To decompress the spine.
So this is a good position
To decompress the spine
You sit in this position for 5 minutes
That's it
I have massaged a lot.
Mama Earth has launched new
Rose merry, Now let's go for a bath.
And leave
Today I have a check out from this house.
Bye bye
Time to say bye bye to this house.
- Bye Aftab
- Bye
Day number 5,
Same place,
Same metro.
Today I am going to work a little early.
Because I will leave early
in the evening from the office.
The aim is to take this umbrella to Delhi.
I don't want to lose it I have tug it here.
The day I was last in Mumbai.
I have a slight cold
I have a sore throat it happens.
Means going to Delhi i will
take a sore throat from here.
I have lost my ticket.
Thank you sir.
We spent 110 rupees.
Let's go.
Came back here.
Mumbai trip is over.
We are going back.
We are going by metro and
take the auto to the airport.
Thankfully, it's not raining this time.
- Should i get down here
- Yes sir
After spending 5 days in Mumbai,
it's time for me to go back home.
I was very late.
I'm tired. I landed to Delhi late at night.
But I'm happy that I'll go
home and see my kids.
[ Subtitles by Mohit ]