Hello, friends!
On 1st January 2024,
when the world was celebrating
the beginning of a new year,
Japan was hit by a terrible 7.6-magnitude earthquake.
"In Western Japan, scenes of devastation
are emerging after a 7.6-magnitude earthquake
shook the country
k!lling dozens of people."
This earthquake was not alone.
Numerous earthquakes, small and big, followed this.
In total, more than 155 earthquakes
occurred in just one day.
Because of this, sea waves about 1 meter high
hit the west coast of Japan.
Japan's meteorological agency
had also issued a major tsunami alert.
Although this warning was downgraded later,
but the earthquake itself
caused substantial damage.
Dozens of buildings were completely destroyed.
Electricity was cut off for thousands of houses.
Some places were engulfed in flames.
And as of 2nd January,
55 people have been declared d3ad.
Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida says that
this situation is a battle against time.
Rescue operations are underway
and efforts are being made
to save the trapped people.
But on 2nd January,
another unfortunate incident
took place in this country.
A Japan Airlines airplane
crashed with a Japan Coast
Guard aircraft in Tokyo airport.
Thereafter, both planes caught on fire.
"Japan Airlines plane has caught fire
at Tokyo's Hanida Airport.
And all runways,
at the airport, have been closed."
This Japan Coast Guard aircraft
was getting ready to help
people affected by the earthquake.
Fortunately, all the people in the other plane
were evacuated safely.
But 5 out of 6 crew members in
the Coast Guard aircraft lost their lives.
The 29-year-old plane captain
was the only one who could survive.
Two big questions arise here.
First, why are there so many
earthquakes and tsunamis in Japan?
Second, how does Japan
deal with these disasters?
Because if an earthquake of the same
magnitude had hit any other country,
perhaps, thousands of people
would have lost their lives.
The d3ath toll in Japan is
below 100 as of now.
How does Japan protect itself against such circumstances?
Let's understand this in this video.
The earthquake that just hit Japan
is named the 2024 Sea of Japan earthquake
or the Noto Peninsula earthquake.
You can see its exact location
on this map on the screen.
There's a region called the Noto Peninsula in Japan.
You have read about peninsulas in school.
It is a piece of land
surrounded by water on three sides.
The epicentre of this earthquake was located here.
The Sea of Japan,
in the west of the country.
It is 500 km away from Tokyo, Japan's capital.
But even so,
this earthquake was felt in Tokyo.
Now, our first question is,
why do so many earthquakes take place in Japan?
The answer to this
is hidden in the map.
Look at this map.
This is the map of the Earth's
16 major tectonic plates.
Tectonic plates are the outer-most layer of the Earth,
made up of the Earth's crust
and the upper part of the mantle.
The heat that is generated in Earth's core,
releases convection currents
which causes the tectonic plates to move slowly.
These are the 16 main tectonic plates
that move slowly year after year.
When they collide with each other,
earthquakes happen.
So, the countries and the areas
that lie on the boundaries of the tectonic plates
are prone to earthquakes the most.
And the thing about Japan is that
it is situated at a place where
four tectonic plates come together.
The Pacific plate, the Philippine plate,
the Eurasian plate, and
the North American plate.
This is the biggest reason why
so many earthquakes are seen in Japan.
Among them, the Pacific plate stands out a bit.
Since it has the highest amount of tectonic activity.
So, the boundary of the Pacific plate
is known as the Pacific Ring of Fire.
Because this causes the highest
number of earthquakes in the world.
As well as the highest number of volcanoes.
To some extent, this is true for the other plates as well.
And the countries located on their boundaries
witness a higher frequency of earthquakes.
For example, if you see India's northern boundary,
the boundary between the Indian and Eurasian plates,
that passes through Nepal,
amidst the Himalayan mountains,
this causes devastating earthquakes in Nepal.
The earthquakes in North India,
in Delhi and its surrounding regions,
in most cases, their epicentre
lies between these two plates.
Compare this with regions like
Australia, Russia or Europe,
where you rarely see any earthquakes.
When was the last time you heard about
a terrible earthquake in Australia?
It's not like there have been
no earthquakes in Australia at all.
But the regions that lie in
the middle of the tectonic plates,
get earthquakes at a lower frequency.
And when earthquakes do occur,
they are not as devastating.
And the reason behind this is that
these major tectonic plates are
made up of minor tectonic plates.
And, at times, the collision
between the major tectonic plates
can be felt even in the middle of the plate.
But depending on the way
that these main tectonic plates
collide with each other,
various types of boundaries can be formed.
Such as the Convergent boundary,
when one plate collides and slips under the other.
Or Divergent boundary,
where both plates move away from each other.
Or Transform boundary,
when both plates move parallel against each other.
Among these, the most dangerous earthquakes
occur when convergent or
transform boundaries are formed.
And the boundary of the Pacific plate
is a convergent boundary.
It has a specific sub-type
known as the Subduction Zone.
In the Subduction Zone,
causes the most powerful earthquakes
because in this type of collision,
when one plate collides with another,
it goes right under the other
submerging into the mantle.
And when this happens,
as you can see in the diagram,
a deep cavity or hole is formed under the sea
on the boundaries of the two plates,
which is called a Trench.
These underwater trenches are
often the deepest point in the ocean.
They can be 3 to 4 kilometres
deeper than the surrounding seabed.
The deepest point on Earth in underwater
known as the Mariana Trench.
This trench is 10.9 kilometres deep.
In Mariana Trench, the point Challenger Deep
is the deepest point in any ocean and on Earth.
You would have heard about it a lot.
But perhaps, you might not know that
There is a deep trench in the East of Japan,
known as the Japan Trench.
The depth of this trench is 8.4 km.
There are very few countries in the world
that are located so close to such deep sea.
Look at this map.
This map shows you
the depth of the sea in
different parts of the world.
The lighter the colour,
the shallower the ocean.
And the darker the colour,
the deeper the ocean.
Look around most of the countries.
Indian coastlines,
African coastlines,
South American coastlines
they are shown in a light colour.
But zoom in and look at Japan.
On the right side of Japan,
there is a massive dark area.
This is the Japan Trench.
And through it crosses,
our imaginary Ring of Fire.
The Pacific Ring of Fire.
Due to the movement of the tectonic plate,
such horrific earthquakes are caused,
the sea is so deep here,
most number of volcanoes are found here,
and due to this,
the area that gets the most
number of tsunamis,
is the country of Japan.
Japan's coastline is very close to this trench,
which means that the tsunami waves
have to travel only a short distance
and there isn't sufficient time for issue warning.
For this reason,
Japan is at the highest risk from tsunamis.
In fact, the word tsunami
is derived from Japanese.
Tsu-Nami
is made up of Tsu and Nami.
Tsu means harbour
and Nami means wave,
meaning harbour-wave.
Harbour is also known as a seaport.
Since there were so many tsunamis in Japan,
when the news of the Japanese
tsunamis spread all over the world,
the word tsunami became popular
and people started using it since then.
Approximately 90% of the world's earthquakes
take place in this Pacific Ring of Fire.
And approximately 75% of active volcanoes
are also found here.
Since the geography of this area is such,
historically, Japan has always been
in a danger zone.
But perhaps this is why Japan
has been at the forefront
at controlling the damage caused
by earthquakes and tsunamis.
What does Japan do exactly?
Before talking about it, I'd like to tell you that
if you want to learn more about Japan's history,
there are amazing audiobooks on KUKU FM,
such as this one talking about Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
It is a 1.5 hour long audiobook,
that tells you the story of
the nuclear bombing of the two cities.
Apart from this, there is an audiobook on
Oppenheimer: The Father of The Atom Bomb.
There are numerous audiobooks
on KUKU FM across various topics.
Whether it is fiction, history, geography or politics.
Overall, it is an amazing audio-learning platform
where you can listen to books.
In case you haven't already,
do check it out,
there's a link with a big discount in the description.
And now let's get back to the topic.
The buildings built in Japan have to
meet strict earthquake-proof standards.
There are three standards.
The lowest is the Taishin standard.
The requirement mandates the
minimum thickness of the pillars,
walls, and beams of the buildings.
So that if an earthquake shakes the building,
the building can resist it.
Second is the Seishin standard
which is recommended for tall buildings
where they are required to
install dampers to absorb the earthquake's energy.
They need to put large, thick rubber mats
under the foundation of the building.
These rubber mats absorb the
vibrations of earthquakes very well.
But there is a third standard,
which is even more strict,
the most advanced standard,
the Menshin Standard.
In this, the entire structure of the
building is isolated from the ground.
Layers of lead, steel, and rubber are installed
so that the building moves independently of the ground.
Even if the ground shakes,
the building can remain stable.
This iconic Skytree tower in Tokyo city,
was built using the same standard.
This is one of the most earthquake-resistant buildings in the city.
When the horrific Tohoku earthquake hit Japan in 2011,
the magnitude of that earthquake was 9.0.
This building did not even get a scratch.
On the other hand,
Japan has adopted many strategies
to protect itself against tsunamis,
although they haven't been as successful
as those protecting Japan against earthquakes.
They have built tsunami-controlled forests.
Planting a large number of trees
to stop the force of tsunamis.
They have built coastal dikes,
which look like this.
These are long structures built of stones.
These dikes are very expensive to build,
but they can successfully reduce the impact of tsunamis.
Apart from these, tsunami evacuation towers are built.
In areas with a high-risk of tsunami
and a significant population,
since people do not get a lot of time for evacuation,
they are told to take shelter in these towers,
located at a high point,
to be protected from the tsunamis.
They have improved their warning systems.
Evacuation drills are regularly conducted,
to help the locals understand
what they need to do in case of a tsunami.
And how to prepare for rescue operations.
And finally, they have built walls near the sea.
Sea walls.
Japan has a 22,000-mile-long coastline
40% of which is surrounded
by these concrete sea walls.
But, unfortunately, these walls
are not always effective.
As it happened in 2011.
Watch this video.
The earthquake that caused this tsunami
was the most powerful earthquake in Japan's history.
This tsunami caused the
Fukushima nuclear disaster too.
Nuclear reactors were damaged,
leading to radiation leaks
that spread over the Pacific Ocean.
The 2011 earthquake and tsunami
was the most devastating in Japan's history.
Around 20,000 people lost their lives in it.
After this, their government made their standards stricter.
Thankfully, this year's disaster
did not turn out to be as dangerous and fatal.
If you found this video informative,
click here to watch the video on
Chernobyl nuclear disaster.
The most dangerous nuclear disaster in the world.
It is explained in this video.
Thank you very much!