Hello, friends!
Last month more than 30,000 people
gathered in Ladakh to protest.
Watch these videos.
It may not seem like a huge number.
But here, 30,000 means
more than 10% of the population of this Union territory.
Everyone was gathered at one place
to protest for their rights.
On 6th March,
when the discussions with the government did not yield any result,
the famous educator, innovator, and activist
Sonam Wangchuk decided to go on an indefinite fast.
"I'm going on an indefinite fast
until Ladakh's voice is heard.
Until the government pays attention to Ladakh."
A 21-day fast,
which can become a fast till de@th.
Think about it, if in any state in our country,
10% of the population takes to the streets protesting,
will it not be a huge news?
But the way this news is being
suppressed by the news channels,
it is very shocking to see.
We will talk about the demands
of the protesters later in the video,
but, in the video, I would also like to show you
that story isn't unique to Ladakh.
This story is playing out in
every corner of the country today.
The political corporate mafia
that is putting Ladakh in danger today,
is the same mafia that
destroyed the forests of Hasdeo,
set fire to the hills of Manipur,
and is bent on destroying Buxwaha.
The same mafia that is causing Joshimath to sink,
that caused the tunnel collapse in Uttarkashi,
and put Lakshadweep in danger.
If this mafia is not stopped,
it will slowly devour the country like a termite.
It will make it hollow from within.
Let's understand this in today's video.
Friends, if you don't know Sonam Wangchuk,
then it is important to tell you that
he is the person who inspired
the character of Rancho in the film 3 Idiots.
The innovations made by Rancho in the film,
Sonam Wangchuk made similar
innovations and more in real life.
In 2021, he built these environment-friendly
solar heated tents for the Indian Army.
With these tents, our soldiers
were able to stay comfortably
even in the freezing cold of Ladakh.
Apart from this, Sonam Wangchuk
has also designed many carbon
neutral solar buildings in Ladakh.
He was the one to introduce the concept of Ice Stupas.
To deal with the water shortage in Ladakh,
he introduced this concept
of building these artificial glaciers.
Throughout the years, he has been
awarded many awards for his innovations.
Be it the Ramon Magsaysay Award,
the Green Teacher Award,
or an award by the UNESCO.
So today when this Sonam Wangchuk
is sitting on an indefinite fast,
it must be because of a serious problem.
The problem is the democracy in Ladakh,
the environment of Ladakh,
and the rights of the people of Ladakh.
The people of Ladakh have four main demands.
First, including Ladakh in the
6th Schedule of the Constitution.
Second, giving full statehood to Ladakh.
Third, electing 2 MPs from Ladakh.
Currently, there's only 1 MP
is from Ladakh in the Lok Sabha,
and 0 MPs in the Rajya Sabha.
And fourth, establishing a Public Service
Commission to provide secure jobs in Ladakh.
Let's understand each of them in detail.
First, what is this 6th Schedule?
This is the part of the Constitution
that protects the tribal population in the country.
According to this, in tribal areas,
to promote democracy, the tribal people
can form their own Autonomous District Councils
and Autonomous Regional Councils.
Also known as ADCs and ARCs.
They are basically elected bodies
that have the power to administer tribal areas.
So that on a local level, the tribal people
make their rules about their land,
forest, and socio-cultural customs.
So that people from outside
cannot exploit their land and resources.
Today, this 6th Schedule is applicable
in the tribal areas of Assam,
Meghalaya, Tripura, and Mizoram.
Now you might think,
since there are no forests in Ladakh,
why are the people of Ladakh demanding it?
There are three main reasons for this.
First, it is true that there aren't forests in Ladakh,
but every area has its natural biodiversity.
And Sonam Wangchuk has explained this many times
that the area of Ladakh
is very vulnerable, considering climate change.
"The mountains are facing the wrath of nature
in the face of climate change."
If the resources are allowed to be exploited in this area,
it will be largely dangerous for Ladakh.
The frequency of natural disasters,
flash floods, and landslides will increase.
Second, the majority population of Ladakh
falls in the Scheduled Tribes category.
According to NCST,
66.8% of the population of Leh is Scheduled Tribe.
83% in Kargil,
and in some areas it is as high as 99%.
The third and the biggest reason,
the 6th Schedule will give the people
of Ladakh their democratic rights.
Today, what do the people of
Ladakh have in terms of democracy?
Think about it yourself.
Since the abrogation of Article 370 in August 2019,
Ladakh and Jammu and Kashmir were
divided into a separate Union Territories.
People didn't have any issues
with the abrogation of Article 370,
rather, their issues are with the actions
of the government after the abrogation.
J&K used to be a full state.
After 2019, it was downgraded
and divided into two separate Union Territories.
This is what J&K's former
Governor Satyapal Malik had said.
"More than the abrogation of Article 370,
they feel bad about this."
"Absolutely, so why did you do this?"
"I didn't play any part in this.
Had they asked, I would
have warned them against it."
J&K's Union Territory did get its Legislative Assembly.
But Ladakh wasn't given that right.
Before 2019, when J&K used to be a full state,
there were 4 MLAs from Ladakh.
But today, this number has come down to zero.
Delhi is also a Union Territory,
but there exists a state level government.
You can vote for them,
you can elect them.
Now, it's a different issue that
the Central Government has tried
its best to take away powers from the Delhi Government,
over the last few years.
But Ladakh wasn't given this right at all.
There are no offices at the state level,
that you can elect by voting.
At the next level,
people of Ladakh can vote for the Lok Sabha elections only,
but even there,
they have been given only 1 MP.
This is the reason behind all these demands.
On a local level, they want to be included in the 6th Schedule,
so that they can elect their ADCs and ARCs,
and can protect their land.
On a state level, they want full statehood.
But if that isn't possible,
they want at least a Legislative Assembly
so that they can elect their government.
And on a central level,
they want to have 2 MPs.
Otherwise, this is only a shell of democracy?
Friends, the most interesting thing is that
it doesn't matter whether
you agree with my reasoning or not.
Because 4 years ago,
BJP was the one to demand
that Ladakh be included in the 6th Schedule.
What could be the reason
that BJP doesn't want to fulfil this demand now?
It's an interesting reason
and quite predictable
if you understand BJP's politics.
I will talk about this reason in a while,
but before that, if you want to
understand the Indian Constitution properly,
then I would like to recommend
this audiobook on Kuku FM.
Bhartiya Samvidhan: Ankahi Kahani
It explains in detail how our country's
great Constitution was actually drafted.
The history behind it.
If you don't know Kuku FM,
it is an audio learning platform
on which you can find many such audiobooks
on almost all kinds of topics.
Whether it is history, politics, fiction or self-help.
Download it and try it yourself.
The link is in the description below.
Using that link, you will get
a whopping 70% discount!
Now let's get back to the topic.
In fact, not only a demand,
right at the top of BJP's manifesto,
they mentioned including Ladakh in the 6th Schedule.
You can read what they've
clearly written in their manifesto.
"I have shown this earlier,
today I will show it again,
in 2019, during the Lok Sabha elections,
in the third bullet point of you manifesto,
you had promised to safeguard
Ladakh in the 6th Schedule."
September 2019 was the first time that
the National Commission for
Scheduled Tribes had recommended
the inclusion of Ladakh in the 6th Schedule.
But the government did not take any action.
In August 2020, the people of Ladakh
put their demands in front
of the government for the first time.
In September 2020,
the first mass protest took
place in Ladakh regarding this.
In 2020, the Autonomous Hill District
Council was to be elected in Ladakh.
And before the elections,
Home Minister Amit Shah promised that
within 15 days of the election,
they would fulfil these demands.
After this, the protests were called off
and BJP won the elections with 15 seats.
But after that, no action was taken.
During December 2021 and November 2022,
there were two more protests.
For a while, there were discussions with the government
but despite writing in on the manifesto,
the government kept refusing to give in to their demand.
This is the reason for this indefinite fast today.
It didn't escalate all of a sudden.
As you can see, over the last few years,
people have been raising their demands repeatedly.
But the biggest question here is,
What is Modi government's problem
with fulfilling this demand?
Adding the people of Ladakh to the 6th Schedule,
will not bring the nation crumbling down.
It's a simple demand.
And there won't be any backlash for the
Modi government or BJP if they do this.
After all, they were the ones to include this in their manifesto.
What could be the reason behind this refusal?
I would like you to read a line
about the functions of ADCs.
Look at the screen.
"The district and regional councils
administer the areas under their jurisdiction.
They can make laws on certain specified matters
like land, forests, canal water, shifting cultivation..."
Did you notice it?
Lands, Forests.
This means that if Ladakh is added to the 6th Schedule,
then the Modi government won't have power
over the Ladakh's land.
This means that Ladakh's land and forests,
cannot be sold be PM Modi to his friend.
"They wanted every valley here
to be mined and have industries set up,
but Ladakh's people are wary of this."
Sonam Wangchuk and Ladakh's people don't want
their lands to be opened up for corporate exploitation.
Doing this will not mean taking away
the rights of the people living there,
but it will also be very dangerous
for our country's environment.
Ladakh is a beautiful and
ecologically sensitive part of our country.
The mountains and valleys here are so unique that
you can't find such features
anywhere else in the world.
The world's rarest and most
endangered animal species are found here.
Like the snow leopards or the Tibetan antelopes.
The water of the lakes here is so crystal clear,
you won't even believe that
such clarity can be found anywhere.
And if you have ever been to Ladakh,
then you must know how innocent
and pure-hearted these people are.
Their culture and tradition,
these monasteries and festivals
are so amazing that
people from all over the world come to see them.
I believe that it is every Indian's duty
to protect the environment and
cultural diversity of a place like Ladakh.
Places like these are like precious gems in our country.
But the way our government is
treating these precious gems today,
tells you a lot about the government's intention.
How long has it been since Manipur is on fire?
It's in a state of civil war
and PM Modi is not willing to even visit that state.
And the reason for Manipur's terrible situation
is corporate exploitation.
I explained it in this video.
There's deforestation of the Hasdeo jungle in Chhattisgarh.
People made countless reels
to protect the forest.
But the government opened it up for mining.
Who is benefiting from this?
The people?
Or Prime Minister's friends at the top?
This story isn't about Ladakh, Manipur or Hasdeo only.
On a large scale, they are trying to
sell the forests of the country.
To sell our mountains,
and to sell our land.
And the benefit from the corporate exploitation,
goes to a select few at the top of hierarchy.
If you still can't see the connection,
click here to watch this video.
You'll understand this funda thoroughly.
Thank you very much!