What is its maximum speed?
If you want to check its maximum speed, come.
Oh!
I will move the steering left, the light focus has already turned.
I feel like its eyes are moving.
The reverse parking camera is hidden.
Come and find out where is it.
The ground clearance of the car.
When we were coming, the car touched the ground.
What if someone tears the fabric of it?
We will talk about its advantages and its disadvantages too.
Hi friends.
After researching for two days,
I have learned so many features of this car.
We will tell you about these features now.
Let's start the video.
Yes. Ok.
So... But first of all, I want to tell you something
What?
Aayu and Pihu read the comments, and I also saw it,
Some friends have commented that we are showing off.
We are showing off an expensive car.
I read some comments like this.
Ok, friends, we were not showing off.
If you buy a new house.
So, you throw a party for that.
You have a housewarming ceremony.
And you invite your friends to your home.
We also bought something new.
You are also like our friends and family.
That's why, we are showing you.
We share all our things with you.
So we will share it too.
Yes.
So, what is the first feature? Convertible. Yes.
Remove the rooftop of our car.
Yes.
This will go up.
And that will go down. Then everything will go in the trunk of the car.
A small trunk. It will close.
OK, friends, so it is open now.
It has one more amazing feature.
What?
All four windows go down one by one.
Yes. But it has one button for these.
Let me tell you. Ok.
Oh, wow!
All four windows went down together.
When we go on the highway at high speed and
We opened the window that time,
Then the wind comes very forcefully.
So, for that, it also has an air cap.
This car has an air cap. Look at this friends.
Its air cap is being opened.
Can you see the air cap?
It has opened. This is for safety.
Yes. The air pressure won't directly affect us.
It will pass over us. Yes.
Its 4th feature is the seat.
Oh, this one. Look from here, this one.
We don't need to push it.
Like, if I want to adjust the seat backwards. It's an electric seat.
I want to press the button to adjust the seat backwards.
Ok.
Friends, it also has a memory function. Yes.
1 2 3.
Pihu has set the feature for reclining in this.
At sleeping mode.
Done.
This feature is for Mom, very advanced, very straight.
Look, it's moving forward. Yes.
How much have you moved it forward?
Friends, its seat becomes a bit longer.
I'm pressing the button from here. See, this seat will move outward. now.
Oh!
So that the legs get a bit of support. Yes.
It is called under-thigh support.
Pihu, do it. See, your seat is also moving outward.
Yes. Press M and then press 1.
Yes. The beeping sound you heard has been stored in its memory.
Now, whenever Mom presses the 1 button for the seating position.
The seat will adjust according to Mom.
It will move outward.
I haven't learnt Kia's function yet.
When will I learn its functions?
Friends, we will tell you its positive features which are almost 10.
However, we will also tell you its negative features.
Ok. He will tell you all the features. Yes.
Why did we buy this car?
We will tell you that too.
The next feature is the music system.
It has 15 speakers.
15 speakers?
Where are those hidden?
They are hidden.
Two here, two there, two and two. We can see 8.
Yes. This car's seats also have speakers installed. One is there.
One is in the centre. 9.
Some speakers must be installed below as well as above.
It must be installed indoors towards the leg.
Wait, I'm sitting inside.
Ok.
Aayu, don't start the car, sit carefully.
It's not on, if it would be on, don't worry, it is in the parking gear.
Yes.
That's why Aayu has understood it's on parking gear.
Increase the volume.
Role it.
It's real audio.
Lower it down.
It is open now.
Yes. Even with the car open, the sound is so good.
This sound is enough to party.
Right, we can have a party around with music playing.
Yes, but the neighbors will come outside that's why no.
Yes, we can't do this. Ok.
Pause it.
Now one more feature. What?
When we sit inside it.
After sitting in it.
Oh!
The seat belt will automatically come forward.
It will remind you to fasten your seatbelt.
And move into position automatically.
When the car starts, the seat belt automatically tightens securely.
It hugs you.
Dad. Yes.
Then we can't play the radio in this. Why?
Because it has no antenna. We have closed the rooftop.
It means we can't play FM.
The radio option is available.
Yes, but we can't play. Where is the antenna?
Every car has an antenna.
The antenna looks like a stick or it is fish-shaped.
Yes. Where is its antenna?
Its antenna is printed on the glass. What?
Here, there are very fine lines in groups of three. Yes.
Yes. These lines.
It has been printed up to this point. Sister, see.
Do antennas like this also exist?
Yes. Printed?
There was no space left, that's why they printed it on the glass.
They have stuck a sticker on it. Wow! what a technology.
We can't recognize it. Dad
Yes. What is its maximum speed?
If you want to check its maximum speed, come.
Look at this.
Open its menu then set.
Then Vehicle.
Its maximum speed is 160.
But 260 is written here. Is this a lie?
No, we can increase it.
You can set its maximum speed limit.
They have given a maximum speed limit.
If you set the speed limit to 160, the car will stay within that.
No matter how much you accelerate.
You can set it to 240.
Yes. We can set it to a maximum of 240.
Ok, I got it. Wow!
Anyway, we are not going to drive the car at such high speeds.
Because there are no roads for that.
Yes. There should be roads like that for driving a car.
We have set it to 120.
120 is the maximum speed limit in India.
That is allowed only on the expressway. Yes.
On other normal highways, a speed of 80 or 100 is allowed.
Or 60.
Yes, 60 is also allowed. Even in the city, speeds as low as 20 are common.
I drive the car at a speed of 20 only.
Mom!
Now, I'll tell you one more feature. Ok.
This is its trunk.
What is this?
If you want make trunk space.
Or if you need to take something out of the trunk?
So, this seat goes completely down.
If two members are travelling, we can set this up like this.
If you have locked someone in the trunk,
They can get out by pressing the button from inside.
That's it, Dad?
Is that all the features it has?
These are the features that are not available in normal cars.
Besides these, there are other features in it as well.
What? Show us.
It has a separate AC.
What do you mean?
Mom has a separate AC.
This is my AC.
It's a very good thing.
Because I feel cold.
And Dad feels hot.
He always sets the AC temperature so low.
That I feel cold.
Not high, low. I mean low.
It's showing 25. Mom will set it at 22.
And Dad will set it at 18.
17 16. Wow, Dad!
OK, friends, let me tell you more features about this car.
If the key fob battery has run out.
You have to take out the start and stop buttons?
Insert the key fob and turn it.
And the car will start.
Friends, this is its touchpad.
With this, I can easily browse through all the features.
If I need to call someone, I can dial here.
9.
8.
And you can call.
7.
It has a safety feature, friends.
It has such a big door and there is a light.
So that if a car comes from behind, they can see that the door is open.
This lights up too.
This will focus the light on the ground as well.
Friends, I hope, you can see it
As soon as I turn the steering wheel slightly,
The light turns in that direction.
You will see, when I turn the steering wheel, the light will turn along.
Just like eyes. Yes.
See, now I turned the steering straight, the light turned straight.
Yes. See.
The light dances here and there.
It will be very beneficial on corners or turns, especially in the dark.
And on the highway also.
Yes, you will find it in driving, right?
I just feel like its eyes are spinning.
The best thing I like about this open roof is,
We can open it at night and see the moon and stars.
I love watching it.
There is one more good feature. Get down, you have already seen it.
Let me tell to friends, get down, as if Aayu has to go behind.
So he will rotate this handle from here,
And will leave the seat forward.
This seat moves forward automatically.
Oh...
It also gets up and moves forward automatically.
Go inside, take your seat.
Ok? And here we sat.
As soon as you sit, the seat will back to its original position.
The headrest also came up, as was set.
It will take its original position automatically.
The seat was a bit over relaxed now Pihu cannot fit properly.
Look, when Pihu touched the seat, it moved forward back.
Pihu was saying that Mom had moved the seat very far forward.
The reason for adjusting the seat forward was so
That you could sit comfortably.
Yes, OK.
The reverse parking camera is hidden in it.
Come and find it.
We can't see it.
Search.
Come. The camera is certainly installed at the back.
It is in the back. The reverse camera will be in the back only.
Mom can say anything.
The back camera is in the back only.
Who knows, a camera may fly in and come at the back.
These should be its two eyes.
No. Yes, these are its eyes.
I know, it's inside the lights.
Like its antenna. No. No, I know.
There is a camera installed inside the exhaust.
Wow! The camera will burn inside the exhaust.
Or maybe the camera is installed at the bottom? Here?
I know. Here...
No, that is the reverse parking sensor.
It shows me in the rear view mirror how close the car has come.
So it is here.
Let me show you, you found it, right?
Yes. Okay, I'll show you.
This camera will appear when we put it in reverse gear.
It's not somewhere down here, isn't it?
You could see, but you can't see.
Show us?
It would come from here.
Back off, Dad will reverse it.
Oh!
Here is it.
We saw it.
Hello. Hello.
Can you see us?
Hello...
But I did not understand. It's cheating.
Why have you kept it hidden?
Is it to avoid the evil eye?
Yes.
This is cool.
This saves the camera from dust.
Otherwise, if we go somewhere in the dust,
Dust sticks to the camera and we have to clean it again and again.
Yes. The high-end cars...
Like a windscreen washer from which water comes out.
There is also a washer for such cameras, a small one in those cars.
But you did the cheating.
What? When we came to see it, you had not even opened it.
You should have put it in reverse gear first. Yes.
Okay, so now let us also tell its negative points.
Yes, tell us that too.
Keep listening one by one.
There are many.
But? Yes,
It is not like that you show us negative points,
And say that we will send the car back.
No, it has come now. We won't send it back.
We will tell you in the end why we have bought the car, okay?
Before the negative point, we could not decide its name.
We can ask friends to suggest the name for this car.
Good! You will comment and tell us,
The most common comments,
Or whatever name we all like, we will name it.
Of course and we will tell who told its name,
Ok.
Okay, tell us good names like what is the name of our KIA, Miss Kerry.
So the name of this car is Mercedes-Benz,
The model is C300.
Its style is called Cabriolet.
Cabriolet?
Miss Cabri.
Miss Cabri!
Miss Kerry and Miss Cabri.
Friends, you have to suggest to us.
Yes, you will tell us.
Let's move on to the first negative point.
Ground clearance.
We have to pass through the breaker very slowly,
Otherwise, the car gets stuck at the bottom.
And if all four of us are seated,
Friends, when we were coming, the car had touched the ground.
Yes, the car got stuck in one place.
Or when I am sitting alone, then there is no problem.
I'm not that fat.
You are the fattest among us.
Of course one person weighs less than four.
Yes.
Reduce your waist a little.
Yes, second now?
Second, you will tell.
Let me tell you.
Yes. There is no trunk, it has no space for keeping luggage.
If the four of us are going somewhere,
Can't go at all.
This car is not suitable for the highway.
But now we can drive this car on the highway.
So the biggest problem is when to go on the highway.
We can drive it at speed on the highway.
To drive, we will have to go to the highway.
Yes. If we go, we will have to stay overnight,
But where will we keep our luggage?
Let's do one thing, Dad, Aayu and I will sit in this Mercedes.
Mom in KIA.
Ok, it's done, tell me more negative points.
Two negative points are done. Yes.
Now whoever tells will get chocolate.
What is this?
The third negative point is its seat space.
There is very little space inside the car.
The front seats are super comfortable.
But the rear seat is straight.
Sister will sit, after 2 years I will not be able to sit.
There is no charger at the back either.
Aayu Pihu were saying the same, there is no charger.
Now how will they charge the phone?
Yes. It is in front, isn't it?
Yes. Look, this type of car is considered a 2 seater.
What? What?
And yes Dad, one more negative point. Come.
This is fine, leg space is still fine but...
There is no seperate door to enter. Where do we enter from?
First, we must get out of the car, then they can sit back.
Otherwise, they can't sit.
Yes, if the roof is open, then jump and sit.
Yes, now give me the chocolate.
Let me tell you, there is no night lamp behind, give me the chocolate.
Let me tell you, there is no safety, give me the chocolate.
How is there no safety? Tell us how is there no safety?
Well, the roof is open. Yes...
The roof is open, there is no safety.
This car is not safe. Yes.
And the biggest point...
We cannot drive the car with the roof open in the rain.
We can't drive in storms, extreme heat and sunlight.
And even if we did,
So pollution, dust, everything will come.
And stink.
We can smell everything if we drive with open roof.
Yes.
We can't open it and leave it.
Yes. And even if we close it and leave it,
What if someone cuts this fabric and goes away?
No, it is strong in this thing.
Good.
The cloth on it, the hooded cloth on top.
It is made of bulletproof jacket cloth.
Good. So it won't even cut normally.
One positive. Ok.
Well, there are a lot of positive points.
We are happy with you.
Our last point is why we have bought this car.
The convertible looks good, and everyone likes it.
And the hard work done by Aayu-Pihu for 7 years,
in making 500 videos,
Because of this, both of them have received this gift.
Because they wanted a convertible car.
Because we have to consider their wishes.
They have done a lot of efforts since childhood.
Thank you, Dad, and thank you, Mom.
Thank you to all of you too.
Because of your support, we were able to get this car.
Tell us by commenting what should we name this car.
Yes, please name it.
Bye.