'On one hand is your hatred, Vinayak'
'which I could never see
in your eyes or heart.'
'You hated me to the extent
where you tried to kill me.'
'And then there is me.'
'I want revenge.'
'But I still love you just as much. '
'I feel like giving you
a tight hug right now.'
Only Siddhi would arrange
things properly for me like that.
No. No. How is this possible?
Dadiya.
Dadiya, Maya, was Siddhi here?
Did you see her?
What's wrong? Why are you shouting?
Dadiya. Maya. Just come with me.
Please come.
Come.
See. Siddhi would do this.
Good Lord.
How can Siddhi come here?
What are you saying?
Listen to me.
Vinayak, Siddhi is no more.
She left us two months ago.
I wish what you said comes true.
That she comes back here to us.
But this is not possible.
If that's not possible
then who did this?
Only Siddhi would arrange
my things alphabetically like that.
No one else can do it.
Hey...
Why the heck are you shouting, mister?
What happened? Huh?
Okay. Tell me honestly.
What kind of a relationship
did you share with your wife?
Did you harass her?
Shut up.
Look, I will not beat around the bush.
I'll explain to you in short.
Look, when we torture
or harass someone when he is alive
his soul isn't at rest after death.
It comes back to seek revenge.
And tortures us the way we tortured it.
I mean, was it your wife's spirit?
Look, if you have wronged your wife
then atone for your sins
and apologise to her.
Or glory be to the Lord.
Shut your mouth.
I don't believe in these things.
Vinayak...
How can you talk rubbish about
my sister without knowing her?
She never believed in revenge.
Vinayak.
[Sanskrit chants]
Siddhi!
I was sure
you'd come back to me one day.
Do you remember our last night together?
We had such a hearty chat.
Every moment was full of love.
But despite it, you...
I know, Siddhi.
I scolded you a little too harshly.
I shouldn't have done that.
I am sorry.
Do not try to beguile me.
You know very well
what I am trying to say.
What you did to me at the cliff...
The cliff? What are you trying to say?
Vinayak?
Maya.
Vinayak, what happened?
Who were you talking to?
Maya, I was talking to Siddhi.
She is back.
Look...
Siddhi.
Maya, Siddhi was right here.
I wonder where she went.
Where is Siddhi?
I don't see anyone.
Trust me. She was right here.
I wonder where she went.
Vinu. What are you guys
doing here so late?
Why haven't you slept yet?
Is everything all right?
Nothing, Aunt.
Vinayak claims he saw Siddhi.
That she was here.
Siddhi? What rubbish!
How can she come here?
She is dead.
Wait a second.
Did you see her ghost?
Like the say.
When someone dies young,
he comes back as a spirit
to fulfil his unfulfilled desires.
Is Siddhi's spirit here to seek revenge?
Mom was also saying that
she was in your room.
What was she saying?
I am terrified.
I don't believe in these things.
'You killed your wife'
'only because she was dark-skinned.'
'You will have to confess
this crime in front of everyone, Vinayak.'
Vinayak.
[Sanskrit chants]
Destiny gives everyone a chance.
In the past, it gave you the chance
to commit a crime.
And today, it is giving me
the chance to punish.
I am Siddhi.
And I have come back
to seek revenge from you.
You remember your sin, right?
You tried to kill me
by pushing me off the cliff.
Only because I am dark-skinned
and not pretty.
You tried to kill me
because you desired my pretty sister.
You were my husband.
But you discriminated against me
because of my skin colour.
You disrespected
the sacred bond of marriage.
[Sanskrit chants]
Snap out. Have you lost it?
Was Siddhi here?
Tell me, Tanmay.
Is Vinayak speaking the truth?
I told you to wear
Vinayak's mask again to find that out.
Tell me. Did you see her?
Tell me. Tanmay?
Why can't I remember anything?
You can't remember?
- Tell me.
- I don't know
whether Siddhi was here or not.
I am not sure.
Today, you got away
because of Maya, Vinayak.
But I am going to expose you very soon.
But what got into you when you saw me?
Why did you start dancing
as if you were drugged?
Today I'll make a joke out of Rangeeli
by making her eat the cannabis 'Laddu'.
She acts so smart.
She insults me in front of my...
Where did the cannabis 'Laddus' go?
I wanted to teach her a lesson
by making her eat them.
She was acting smart in front
of my mother. Where are they?
I got them thrown away.
What?
You got them thrown away?
For God's sake please ask me once
before you act smart again.
Ask before touching any of my things.
You ruined my plan.
Now I understand.
It means Tanmay ate
the cannabis 'Laddus' made by Aunt Sushma.
Hence, he was acting weird.
Thank God, I sent him away before
he could spill something
that would put me in trouble.
But Rangeeli is surely here with a motive.
I won't be at peace until I find out
what her motive is
or who she is.
I am going to make you confess
your crime very soon, Vinayak.
I will find out with whose help did you
try to kill me
by pushing me off the cliff.
I won't be at peace
until I do that.
You have to come back, Siddhi.
If my love is true, you will come back.
The police have still not found
your body.
It means you are alive.
The love between Siddhi and Vinayak
is immortal.
It will always be immortal.
Always.
I have tried everything.
But I have failed to find out the truth.
I don't know what to do.
What more can I do?
'I sense Siddhi is around me.'
I must find out the truth
because not only did Vinayak
try to kill me deceitfully
he is also responsible for the death
of my unborn child.
Because the fall from the cliff
killed my innocent baby too.
Oh, God.
Who has got into our house this late?
Stop.
Who are you?
And what are you doing here?
Speak up. Who are you?
Speak up.
Siddhi!
'I wonder what's going to happen.'
'Aunt has seen me
and she thinks I am a ghost.'
'I must do something in the morning.'
Siddhi darling.
O' spirit of Siddhi, I am sorry...
I mean I beg your pardon.
Forgive me.
I am stupid and ignorant.
And you are great.
And I promise to venerate
you every day, Siddhi darling.
Glory to Siddhi.
Aunt,
what are you doing?
And what's all this?
Siddhi's ghost is back
to seek revenge from me.
I harassed her so much.
So she is not going to spare me.
Aunt, what rubbish!
Stop it.
Like I said. Siddhi is alive. She is fine.
She will come back to me one day.
Say what you want.
But the fact is that
Siddhi's spirit is here in this house.
I am sure she has come to fulfil
her unfulfilled desire.
Glory to Siddhi.
No. Siddhi cannot die.
She is alive.
Let them say what they want.
I refuse to believe them.
Siddhi is alive.
She will come back to me one day.
Ma'am, does he believe it?
Now what do I say?
He is not ready to believe it.
I tried all I could
to make him believe that Siddhi
is no more.
Whatever it is
but I am so scared.
She is stubborn as hell. I mean by Siddhi.
She will not spare me.
She will take her revenge.
I don't know.
How do I save myself?
Something similar happened
at my village too.
A woman died with an unfulfilled desire.
And then the entire family would see her.
And then...
Ma'am, she would try to seek revenge
by attacking the entire family.
The spirit was really dangerous.
Is it that the girl...
- What's her name?
- Siddhi.
Is Siddhi's spirit also...
No. Siddhi was not like that.
She was very noble and nice.
She can never do that to me.
I agree
I have made some mistakes.
A few mistakes.
- Right.
- And that's why she is haunting me.
I am so scared.
How do I save myself?
There is a way.
The person who loves Siddhi the most
in this house
can tell you what her last wish was.
Yes. There is. Vinayak.
He loves her the most.
He must be knowing
what Siddhi's last wish was.
I will try to find out.
Vinu must be knowing.
'Aunt, you are wrong in thinking
that Vinayak loves me the most.'
'The truth is something else.'
'A truth that shook me up completely.'
What's going on in this house?
Everyone is seeing Siddhi everywhere.
Tanmay, are you sure she is dead?
No one can survive
after falling from such a great height.
'Maya should be in her room.'
'I'll go give her some hot milk.'
The vultures must have
devoured her body by now.
Don't worry.
Your darling sister must be dead by now.
Do you remember
how I pushed her off the cliff
so dramatically?
I slept soundly that night
after a long time.
Siddhi is dead.
And Vinayak is listless.
And you are the mastermind behind it.
I was just following your orders.
You should get the credit
for killing Siddhi.
Pretty madam, what happened?
What were you muttering to yourself?
I don't see anyone here.
Hmm?
Actually, I am missing my sister terribly.
She was my protector.
She was my world.
Never mind.
'I feel like embracing you
and telling you the truth'
'that your Siddhi is back.'
'But I cannot tell you or anyone'
'about myself until I expose Vinayak.'
'I am going to expose
Vinayak very soon.'
'I promise you.'
He is here.
'Maya is so treacherous.'
'First, she kills her sister.'
'And now she is shedding
crocodile tears before this maid.'
'One should learn from her
how to deceive your own.'
Grab him. Hold his hand.
Who is this?
Leave me.
Why have you caught me?
Let me go.
You will have to tell the truth, Vinayak.
You will have to tell everyone
why you did that to me.
And on whose orders.
What are you doing?
And why have you got me here?
If we let you go, how will we find out
what we want to know.
The truth.
What do you want to know?
Siddhi's last wish.
- Tell me quickly.
- How would I know?
Please let me go.
To lie is a sin. Beware of your sins.
My efforts are on.
It's time for the doctor now.
Glory to the Lord.
Come. Show some magic.
Hope you remember
the chat we had on the phone.
Open your pandora's box
and get cracking.
Doctor, you have to help me.
Otherwise, I will never be able
to expose him.
He took away my family
my right of being a wife
my child,
my joy, my hope,
he took everything from me.
I want to expose my husband at any cost.
Tell me.
Will you help me?
- Will you come with me?
- Yes.
'Today with this doctor's help,
I'll give you a medicine'
'which will make you confess your crime'
'and also confess
on whose orders you did that.'