'My story begins in Lahore.'
'No..
Not the Lahore'
'which is a part of
another country now.'
'But the Lahore,
which was before the partition'
'not just the heart, but also
the crown jewel of India.'
'The city, where people
of different religions'
'lived together in
peace and harmony.'
'Neither the river Ravi
was partitioned'
'nor the country and not
even the hearts of people.'
'Even today,
when 'Dhol' is being played'
'at the Wagah border'
'it can be heard in Lahore,
20 miles away.'
'And Englishman named Radcliffe'
'drew a line between us
in such a cruel way'
'that Lahore feels so far away
despite being so near.'
'Where I was born
in a large mansion.'
'Where I lived for 16 years.'
'Made real friendship.'
'Where I dreamt of
the freedom of girls'
'along with the freedom
of the country.'
'And where I fell in love
for the first time.'
'27 January, 1947.'
'We were celebrating
'Basant Panchami'
'with a lot of happiness
and enthusiasm.'
'Unaware of the fact'
'that it will be'
'the last 'Basant Panchami'
'at our home,
'Om Niwas', in Lahore.'
'After this day'
'I will never be able
to see my house'
'my neighbourhood,
or the sunrise'
'from the roof of our house.'
'Take a look.'
'My father,
Lala Ratan Kishore Sahni'
'the famous rich man in Lahore'
'the owner of 'Lala Di Hatti'.
'The king of 'Masala Mewa'.'
'He is so happy to embrace'
'his best friend and neighbour'
'Dr. Baig.'
Come here, buddy!
Wish you a very happy
'Basant Panchami'.
To you too, buddy.
Have a seat..
You tell me,
you came here alone?
Do I have to send a car
to the opposite house
to bring your wife here?
No, Zayeda has been
here since morning.
She and your wife are cooking
some 'Khichdi'.
Not 'Khichdi'.
We were cooking yellow rice.
Come, Zayeda, they've been
waiting since morning.
Come on..
Here you go..
There you go.
All right, let's start eating.
Well, you've waited for so long.
Wait for a bit longer.
Have patience.
Before eating this sweet rice
you both will have
to give a test.
Yes.
You will have to tell
which were cooked
by Lala's wife
and which were cooked by
Dr. Iqbal Baig's wife.
Yes.
Lala, we will have
to give the test
of our love in the
pretext of rice.
I'm not afraid of it.
Let's give the test.
- Wait, Lala..
Why do you want to embarrass
yourself at this age by failing?
Well, why don't you call
the apple of your eye?
She will take your test.
Where is she?
She must be here somewhere
with your daughter.
Where else will she be!
Where is our dear daughter?
Amrut!
"Beloved!"
"Oh, sweet beloved!"
"Oh charmer!"
"Oh, sweet beloved.."
Amrit.
"Oh charmer!"
"Oh, sweet beloved.."
Vashma!
Greetings to the heart
of Lahore
from Vashma.
Vashma, you're too much.
Let's talk about
the prettiest girl
in all of Lahore, Ms. Amrit.
What are you doing, Vashma?
She likes to dream
with her eyes closed
as well as with her eyes open.
And she believes in dreaming
of doing those things
she is restricted to
and be content with it.
But what do I tell her
about the beauty of dreams?
They come in a second,
and break the next second.
Vashma, you're..
Let's talk about her
latest dream.
Which just broke from
the sound of my footsteps.
Get lost.
In your dream,
you saw yourself
in the middle of the street
playing the drums.
Which included all your friends,
including me.
Such lovely dance moves.
Hey!
Tell me I'm lying?
Shut up.
- Oh, my!
Look at your red cheeks,
from blushing
all the handsome, young
fellows
are looking at you from
their windows
and opened the window
to their hearts
waiting for you.
- Vashma..
And were your parents,
as well as mine
clapping hard?
- Stop it.
By the way,
the dream wasn't bad.
But aren't you dreaming
a little too soon?
Yes.
- Oh, my!
And between all
the song and dance
your heart throb must have
walked up to you and said..
Your dad is calling for you.
There goes my dream.
- Wake up!
Let's go.
Amrit, keep your
father's dignity.
And your uncle's too.
- Yes.
Your mom and your aunt
are testing us.
Hey..
- Wait, let her.
Now, tell me,
who cooked which one?
It's a difficult one
to answer, right?
No, Dad.
It's not a difficult question,
it's the wrong question.
Look at this.
Both the rice grains from
Om Nivas and Baig Manzil
have come together in this bowl
and can't be called apart.
Until they can't be told apart
they'll taste good.
The day you can tell
them apart
they'll become tasteless.
Wow!
Well said!
You've made me happy.
Here, you can have
whatever I've got in my pocket.
No, Dad.
I don't need anything.
Dear, you don't need anything,
by I do.
Go on, take it.
Sons gets everything
with their right.
But daughters refuse even when
you try to give them something.
Oh, my God!
It's the ancestral bracelet,
isn't it? - Yes.
Are you going to give
all the treasure to her?
Shall I..
- Listen..
You do not gift
the golden bracelets
to such a lovely daughter.
Instead, you put them
on her wrist.
Look.
Stay blessed.
But..
- When you go in
keep this in the kitchen.
- Turn on the radio.
I haven't heard the news today.
Take Zara with you and bring
breakfast for everyone.
You should make the 'Lassi'.
Otherwise, he won't drink it.
Go.
- You are so lucky, darling!
I will bring 'Lassi'.
What a lovely day?
Praise the lord.
This is your worth
in this family.
I am not expected to do anything
other than serving them.
He wants me to make
'Lassi' for him.
Yet he is giving
the bangle to her.
Amrit, let everyone hear
what you said to me
about Delhi and Bombay.
Delhi, Bombay,
Kolkata, Karachi..
The 'Masala', 'Mewa',
and 'Larchi' from Lala's shop
are famous everywhere.
'Attacks in various places
in Kolkata'
'took the lives
of more than 12 people'
'and around 50 people
got severely injured.'
'On account of these
religious riots'
'the leaders of both
the political parties'
'have asked the people
to maintain peace.'
'People are now worried that'
'the freedom received after
200 years of oppression'
'will be followed by division
of the country.'
'Considering the current
situation in the country'
'the famous cartoonist
Ullu Lal's question'
'to the foreigners.'
'Will they ruin the communal
harmony in the country?'
Abdul, stop this nonsense.
There are riots in the nation
and Ullu Lal finds it funny.
No matter how hard
the foreigners try
they won't be able to divide us.
Because, the freedom
was not a dream
exclusive to one community.
Instead, the entire nation
dreamed about it.
When the sound of the bell
from temples
and prayer from the mosque can
be heard together in the morning
how can they divide it?
Go and alert them.
Tell them that
those who celebrate
Diwali and Eid together..
Will celebrate freedom as well.
Whatever pleases the God,
Lala.
Whatever pleases the God.
What do we say on
every 'Basant Panchami'?'
The spring is here,
and the winter is gone.
On the next 'Basant Panchami'
all of us will say together..
The spring is here..
The Englishmen..
- Are gone!
Just watch..
As soon as we become free
Lala, Ratan,
Kishore, and Sahwney
will adorn the entire Lahore
as if it is Diwali!
As if it is Eid!
And then..
You and I will remain
together such that
the entire Punjab
will be ecstatic.
I agree, Lala.
God, please protect
father's faith.
It's enough.
Why are you bothering the God.
There will be no partition.
I wish the same.
But the news says..
- Forget about the news.
Look at this.
- What is it?
Finally, it's here.
The letter?
- Yes.
The day when your lover..
Be quiet.
- The day when
the lover's story is printed,
that's when you get the letter.
In the post box number 111.
Shall we go and get it?
- Yes!
But how can we go today?
It's a holiday today.
I cannot think of an excuse.
Why should you make an excuse?
We have a someone in this house
who can help us.
Wow!
This is known
as dedication.
Mr. Dhyanchand, listen to what
I'm going to say very carefully.
The way Ekalavya considered
Dronacharya as his teacher
Uday Kishore Sehmi is
considering you as his teacher.
And with your blessings
he wants to join the Indian team
and want to make India win
a gold medal.
So, Mr. Uday Kishore
don't you think
your dreams are too big?
Hey, those who have
an ugly face
should talk
in a pleasing manner at least.
Hey!
Do you think
that only you can have
ambitions?
Look into my eyes.
I've millions of dreams.
I can see that
you have millions
of ambitions.
Ambitions of Surayah
and Noorjahan
Ambition to own jewels
and get married.
Girls like you have
no other ambitions.
Hey!
- Ma'am
One having ambitions
doesn't depend on their sex.
Male and females
both have ambitions.
The only difference
is that women doesn't get
any support
to fulfil their dreams.
They struggle all their lives
because of that.
Ignore that.
- Ignore that.
We want to go somewhere.
What do you mean?
It's a very important work.
- It's a very important work.
What's wrong with you?
Just a minute.
I can't help you.
Don't think
that I'll help you.
Also, Mr. Bhanuveer
and our aunt
are at home today.
If they..
That's why we need
your help.
We will finish our work
and return soon.
Where do you want
to go?
Both of you tell me something.
Let go of me.
- I helped you few times.
So, now you both started
asking for help every day.
Let go of me. - Mr. Bhanuveer
and aunt is at home.
If they come to know
about our conspiracy
I don't know
what they will do to you both
but they will teach me
a lesson for sure.
Do you get it?
- Amrit
what's the use of tying rakhi
around your brother's wrist?
He doesn't even help you
when you need help.
Don't tie next time.
Hey
don't change the topic.
Do you get it?
Where do you both
want to go?
We can't reveal that.
We also have ambitions
and secrets.
We need only a small help
from you.
We will return soon, Veer.
Please handle the situation.
We'll return soon.
We are leaving.
- Listen to me.
Hey, Amrit.
Hey, Vashma, listen to me.
Also
don't let the goal happen.
Vashma, listen to me.
- Let's go, Amrit.
Vashma
come fast.
They will put me in trouble.
Uday.
Yes, Dad.
I'm coming.
Come.
Where is Ms. Saira?
- Where is she?
Ms. Saira.
- I'm coming.
Come fast.
- Okay.
Give it fast.
Take this.
We will return soon.
Handle the situation.
Okay?
Go.
Sir, greetings.
- Greetings.
Post box number..
- 111.
She meant, letter from 111.
Give me.
- Vashma.
Come.
- Thank you..
Vashma.
- Hey!
What happened?
Look at that.
Stay away and watch.
No one should touch him.
Leave..
Move back..
What are you doing?
Move back.
Kid, move back.
Stay away and watch.
That is Ullu lal's statue
the cartoon character
of Randhir Raizada.
Yes!
But why and who has
someone kept this statue
in the middle of the market?
Look, something is
written there.
What is written?
'When the country gets freedom'
'will the girls also
get freedom'
'to play the drums
and perform 'bhangra'?'
I dream about this.
Where are you lost?
Hurry up. If we get late,
Uday won't be able to handle it.
It will be a problem.
Let's go.
Come, let's go. We'll get late.
- Vashma!
Letter!
Where are you lost, Uday?
I have told you several times.
Come quickly
whenever I call you.
You should not be late.
But no!
I am calling you.
Let me keep calling you.
How does it make a difference?
I am already ill-fated.
My son is also useless.
Hey, your love for hockey
has driven you crazy.
I have told you several times.
Forget hockey and help
your father and uncle out.
People believe that a young son
is a father's strength.
Here, my father is useless
and my son too.
What are you doing?
Dad, I'm sorry.
- Do it properly.
Amrit, Vashma, where are you?
Don't you want to fly kites?
Kiran, go and see
where they are.
Call them, dear.
I had gone to Amrit's room.
She is not there.
Where could she go?
I'll go and inform mom.
The security person
is not letting us go in front.
How do we go there?
Wait, I'll do something.
Amrit!
The kites of Lahore
are touching the sky.
And the one who will hold
the thread of my brother's kite
is sitting inside.
- Aunt!
Are you trying to scare me?
Where are you going?
Go to the mansion and fly kites.
I'll bring them. You go.
You think my niece is a kid?
You move aside.
Look at this.
Look, I've got a special thread
fixed
for the kite.
Nobody listens to me.
You are here?
- Yes.
Aunt, that's what
I am telling you.
Go to the mansion and fly kites.
I'll bring both of them.
- Really?
Will you tell me what to do?
I too want to see
what the two of them
are doing inside.
Move aside.
- I'll tell you.
Listen to me, Aunt.
Aunt, they..
They are doing something
special inside.
Oh, my God!
They must be doing
something really special.
That's why they've asked you
to guard their room.
Guard!
Come on, move aside.
- I'll bring them.
I said, move aside.
- Aunt.
Move aside.
- Aunt, I'll bring them. You go.
I'll bring them. - Move aside.
- Why are you arguing?
Don't we have to go to
the mansion to fly kites?
What happened to both of you?
Tell me, what is happening here?
Brother, Amrit is not opening
the door
and he is saying
that she is doing
something special inside.
That's what I'm saying.
You guys go.
Amrit is doing
something special inside.
She's doing something special
for uncle. - Really?
Brother, do you know
what is she doing inside?
Yes, I know.
I know everything.
Tell us if you know.
Uncle, she's making
a waistcoat for you.
Brother Uday had told me.
Am I right?
- Yes, actually..
Waistcoat..
Amrit is preparing
the same inside
for uncle.
- Yes, but..
That was kept
in the drawing room.
Here it is.
"Oh, Lord.."
Oh, God..
This means..
Udit, you are lying!
How come he will speak the truth
who himself is a liar?
Dad!
Because of hockey
you are going
beyond our control.
Dad, please spare it.
Because of hockey..
- Dad!
To heck with this..
Because of hockey..
Uncle, what are you doing?
You should thank God
that I have just broken
the hockey stick.
I didn't thrash his face.
Open the door!
- Brij.
Amrit, you got the letter?
- Yes.
Vashma.
It is not a statue.
He is a human being.
What!
He is deceiving people
by posing as a statue!
I will tell everyone.
- Fashma!
Lower your voice.
And he is not deceiving people.
Whoever he may be
it's possible
even he has a dream like me.
And we shouldn't
shatter someone's dream.
Amrit, he is Ullu Laal
built by Randhir Raizada.
He is not Randhir.
Let's go quickly now.
Uday shouldn't be in trouble
because of us.
Come on.
Let's go quickly.
"Why did I leave
my heart behind?"
Amrit.
Amrit!
Brother, let me check.
Amrit.
Oh, God..
Brother, Amrit is not here.
Whoever he may be
who was he?
And why was he standing
in the middle of the market?
Because if you want to touch
people's heart
your message should be
conveyed in a unique style.
Then people like your message.
And they remember that too.
I have learned this new
style of marketing in London.
Who has taught Amrit
how to lie?
Oh, God!
What will she do?
Will she die?
May I be disgraced
all my life.
I am not saying this.
People say this.
People say that when a young
girl lies to go out of the house
this means,
something is fishy for sure.
I know she is an apple
of your eye.
But one shouldn't be
so lenient to his child
that she becomes audacious.
Oh, God..
I swear on Kiranbala.
I can still read your mind.
I was 14 years old
when you fixed my marriage.
Why?
You feared
that your love and affection
may spoil me.
How old is Amrit?
Sixteen?
This is the age
when people make mistakes.
Think about it, Brother.
Oh dear Lord!
"Dear Lord!"
Imagine..
What if Ullulaal
was Mr. Randhir?
When this letter flew
in the air and reached him..
What if he came to know
about Ranjhan?
Sooner or later, I will find
out information about Ranjhan.
Of course, sir.
After all you are Randhir Ray.
Sir, tea.
Thank you.
Well, Mr. Sharfu..
There was something special
about the lady in burqa too.
'If I could see the moon
hidden in the clouds..'
'...then my sky would have
also been filled with light.'
'Looking into her eyes
has started something..'
Maybe I would have fallen
in love if I had seen her face.
Come, hurry up..
Where have you been?
You know, everything
is messed up.
Your dad came to your room
and opened the door.
He knows everything.
And Kiranbala has made the mess.
Now?
Hey, listen. Shut up!
Oh! Brother..
She is the young girl
from our family.
If she gets into a love affair
then can you stop the people
of Lahore from making gossip?
Dear Lord!
I can't help it.
My worry is killing me.
Where did you go
without informing
or telling anyone?
Where did you go?
Look.. Look at your father.
Just look at him.
Where did you..
Answer me, Amrit.
I was proud of the way
I raised you.
I trusted you more than myself.
Swear on me and tell me..
Swear and tell..
Do you.. Do you have a love..
- No.
No, Father.
I swear on you.
There's nothing like that.
Then..
Why did you lie and go out?
Amrit, tell everyone
that where we went.
Uncle asked you something.
You have to tell everyone.
Uncle..
We went to bring
something for you.
Here it is.
Your hookah-pot was broken.
So, Amrit said that when
you will ask for hookah
in the evening then
we will be in trouble.
So, we went to buy this.
Hookah's pot?
Thank God!
There is no confusion now.
It was dragged too much
for nothing.
Sister-in-law is right.
Both of you have done
a good job.
You bought this for brother.
But why did you go alone?
It is a festive day.
We saw you smoking the hookah.
- There are others in the house.
Why did you lie and go out?
- Shall I tell everyone?
Yes, Aunt.
You are absolutely right.
But to save Kiranbala
from getting scolded..
We went alone.
- Hey..
Why are you dragging
my daughter in this?
Dear Lord!
Yes, Uncle.
She was playing with your hookah
last night.
And she broke it.
Amrit made me and Uday swear
so that we don't tell
this to anyone.
And that we should get
a hookah-pot quickly.
She said that she will feel bad
if Kiranbala is scolded.
Am I right, Kiranbala?
Say something.
Kiranbala..
Y-Yes.
Actually, I broke it by mistake.
So, I told Amrit
not to tell anyone.
This is not a toy.
You are not a kid anymore.
Even you listen..
From today
never lie
and go out of the house.
If a lie brushes past the truth
the truth loses its colour.
Sir, our accountant is here.
Make him feel comfortable,
we'll be there. - Okay.
Kiranbala..
Come downstairs. I need to have
a word with you.
Okay, Mother.
Come downstairs!
Kiran..
The tree at our backyard
which has a beehive..
From which honey drips..
I hope you saw it.
Try putting your hand inside
that beehive for no reason.
The stings will be so painful,
you'll not be able to bear it.
I gave you the hint.
I hope you're intelligent
to understand it.
Step aside! - Hey!
Vashma.
Let us see it.
- Of course!
Apologise! Come on!
- Stop it.
Sir, had I known, I'd to face
embarrassment for her
I would've throttled her before
she was born! - Accountant!
Get up.
- Calm down.
Stop getting violent.
- I've no options, sir.
I searched
a suitable boy for her.
Even the wedding date
was finalised
but she is adamant
to see the boy
before she marries him.
She has been guiled
by someone named Raanjhan.
Raanjhan? Who is that person?
No idea.. Whose love stories
have brainwashed my daughter!
Amrit.. Amrit, show it to me.
Let me read it.
- Hey!
'Raanjhan..'
'I saw London, Paris, Prague,
Austria..'
'I'm yearning to see you.'
- Oh, my!
'My newspaper publishes
your stories..'
'And believe me, you never
made me wait for the stories.'
'Your stories come in time
every month.'
'Then, why make me wait
for your letters, Raanjhan?'
It's my turn to read it.
- Let me read it.
I was reading it..
- It's my turn.
Okay. Read it.
'I don't know if you did it,
but I've counted it.'
'I've written 11 letters
but never received any reply.'
'Do you like to take time?'
'Are you a coward?'
Even he says that.
'Whose stories are always
about unbridled love..'
'Love knows no guilt.'
'An inspiration
for the young girls..'
'It is showing them
a new direction.'
'It is making them feel
their rights and freedom'
'why has he himself
hiding his identity?'
'Not Crime but Love.'
'Love Knows No Shame.'
And now, his new love story..
'Vibrant Love'.
Sir, the female character
of this story is so shameless
she tells her father, she'll not
marry until she sees the boy.
She says, she has to lead
her life with him.
What if she's a daughter..
She says, she has her
views and desires.
Sir, there is so much
to tell you..
This story also has the lines..
We will actually be free
when girls are free to take
decisions for themselves.
Well, when girls
read such stories,
they will be misled.
She is my daughter.
Not any foreigner.
'You should read your
stories out on radio'
'so that these stories can
inspire more and more people.'
'I have talked
to Radio Lahore in this regard.'
'I am waiting for your consent.'
'Be it from the lover
or the beloved'
'rejection hurts alike.'
'But making someone wait
impatiently'
'is something that
damsels do, not writers.'
'Awaiting a positive reply.'
'Randhir Raizada.'
Oh my..
If someone had said
such lovely words to me
I would have agreed in no time.
So my dear Amrit aka Ranjhan..
I suggest you accept his offer.
Really? Should I meet him?
Shall I tell him I am Ranjhan?
Of course!
Meet him and tell your
stories on the radio.
Tell him that the Ranjhan
who writes love stories
is none other than Amrit Sahni.
It's not so easy, pal.
Work a way out.
The Randhir Raizada who girls
of Punjab are eager to meet..
The one whose mention brings
a smile on your face..
This is the 11th letter
he has written to you.
And you say it is not easy.
What are your feelings?
I feel like writing
all my stories
under the name Amrit Sahni.
I don't want to hide
behind any aliases.
I want this city
to know me as a good writer.
I want dad to be proud of me.
I want him to be proud
of me as a writer.
I will tell him the truth.
I want to tell my family that
the famous writer
Ranjhan is none other than
their daughter Amrit.
What if dad doesn't like it?
Dear, this shameless Ranjhan..
Don't read the nonsense
stories by this writer.
They will mislead you.
Decisions of women's rights..
..can be taken their father
brothers or sons.
By only these people..
Women can get respect
and love.
But they do not have
the right make decisions.
Do you understand?
Accountant, take her home.
Do not scold her.
I have convinced her.
Go on now, dear.
Anu.
- Yes.
He might feel a little bad
but it is 'Vasant Panchmi'
today, Amrit.
Your father is so happy.
Go on and tell him.
I am with you and we will
talk to him.
And we will show him
the letter of Randhir.
He is no simpleton.
He is from a prominent family.
He has praised you so well.
Let us see this through.
Tell your father
that you are Ranjhan.
By the Gods, if I ever found
this Ranjhan
I'll thrash him so badly
in the city square
that he will forget his own name
let alone writing these
foul stories!
Shame on such writers!
One who spreads vile filth
in the name of change.
And he poisons of minds
of our women
leading them to become
shameless!
Please listen to me.
Just listen to me once.
'If I ever find this Ranjhan..'
'Shame on such writers!'
'I will thrash him so badly!'
'He poisons the mind
of our women..'
My dreams are shattered
yet again.
I would rather die
but never let father know
that I am Ranjhan.
No.