This school in Cameroon has
extremely dilapidated
and hazardous classrooms.
No running
water or electricity
and only a single toilet
shared by over 3000 kids
and staff daily.
And what's even worse
is despite the school's
mission
to empower young girls
and provide them a safe
haven from domestic abuse
and other challenging
conditions,
many children cannot enroll
because of overcrowding and
deteriorating conditions.
So in this video,
we're going
to rebuild the school
from this to this,
this to this
and this to this
to give these kids a better
opportunity at life.
We started out by sending
Dan and Darren
there a few months ago
to see how we could help.
Upon their arrival,
they met with Francis,
an extraordinary man
who has dedicated his life
to combat inequality
and suffering in Cameroon.
He is the founder of CDVTA,
an organization
that helps build wells
facilities and solar power
installations and aids
The development of education
throughout Cameroon.
When we
first visited the school.
What we saw of those
children
were actually
on the conditions
of lack of sanitation.
Some of them were abused.
They had no right
to raise their voice.
They could not speak
for themselves.
These conditions
had no dignity.
These conditions would not
make your child believe that
the future is bright
The kids that are in the
school,
are sitting in classrooms
that are literally made
out of scrap wood.
I've been shooting
in one of these classrooms
for 5 minutes
and my face is literally
dripping with sweat.
I can't imagine what it must
be like to sit in here
for an hour long lesson and learn.
The environment
is, first of all dirty.
That is dust all over.
We don't have ceiling boards.
The state of these classrooms
is tragic for many reasons,
but mainly because this
school is on the border
of the English and French
parts of Cameroon,
making it a rare junction
point
between two populations
in ongoing conflict.
This school could help unite
these communities.
Many people have moved
from the English part
and is settled in this area.
This school became a safe
place for them to come and
get educated here.
But because of the poorly
built
infrastructure, rain leaks
through the roof in winter.
There is no electricity
and the school was beyond
maximum capacity.
Once we saw this, we knew
we had to do something.
- So almost immediately...
- The team quickly
got to work to completely
transform the school
and surprise the kids
before they got
back from their school break.
And before the kids returned
from their holidays,
Darren and Dan went to visit
their brand new classrooms.
Darren and I looked
at the new structures
which have airflow.
They have
lights of electricity.
Let there be light!
I can't wait to see
the look on the kids faces.
The teachers faces
when they get to see
the new classrooms,
also the new bathrooms.
The school
is going to transform
thousands
and thousands of lives
in the future.
The next day,
it was finally time
to surprise the kids.
There's a whole bunch of
people outside the school.
This is really exciting.
The school was the busiest
it had ever been, with kids
beyond excited
to get a glimpse
of the brand new classrooms.
I just got out of the car.
There's
a whole bunch of people
over here to welcome me.
This is a little bit crazy.
The headmaster, Dillon,
turned to the new classrooms
where he would
officially cut the ribbon
and declare
the new school open.
When the environment is
beautiful,
academics moves positively
just the happiness,
motivates them psychologically
to study and study well
When interacting
with these kids over here.
I realized that
these are children
that have a thirst to learn.
And providing them
the opportunity to realize
that is
probably the best legacy
that we'll leave behind
in this community.
I can't imagine the impact
this will have on the lives
of children in this school.
Thank you.
And thank you very much
indeed.
Before I show you
an unexpected surprise
the community
had for Darren,
I want to tell you
about the amazing sponsor
of this video,
Lectric E-Bikes
They're back on board
and supporting our mission
with their affordable,
eco friendly and fun to ride
bikes.
Time and time again,
they've
shown their dedication
to a global impact
by helping us
rebuild an orphanage,
donating thousands of shoes
to kids in South Africa
and distributing
millions of clothes
worldwide.
Additionally,
they helped us power
an island in Colombia,
a children's sanctuary
in Zambia, and give away
hundreds of electric bikes
all across the globe.
And now, for the eighth time
this year, they stepped up
and helped us build
this school in Cameroon.
So I just want to
give a heartfelt
thank you to Lectric E-Bikes
for their continuous
support.
Let's get back to the video.
Now it is
time for Darren's surprise.
So the village leaders
took him to a ceremonial hut
and dressed him up
in local attire.
He then took part
in a traditional Cameroonian
induction
as a village elder.
What?!
Forefathers.
Hold it now.
Hold it...
Yeah!
I've just been honored
as a chief in the village.
Now that Darren
had finally become a chief,
it was time to say goodbye
to Cameroon and these kids.
We can't wait
to come back soon to visit.
By watching this video,
you helped us
generate some ad revenue
so we can continue
to do philanthropic projects
all around the world.
And you've told the YouTube
algorithm
you like the video,
so they'll recommend it
to more people.
And for that,
we are very grateful.
And if you want to continue
to support
Francis
and the many communities
he helps throughout
Cameroon,
you can donate directly
to his charity
using the donate button
or the link to description.
All the proceeds
will go to Francis and CDVTA
so they can continue to help
build
a better future
for these children.
Thank you so
much for watching. Subscribe