So doctor..
how is the 106 dialysis
patient doing?
How's the creatinine level?
Still not the best and..
she's responding to the EPO injections pretty well.
Hi Doctor!
Hey hi!
How's dad doing?
His blood pressure is pretty high and uh..
even the ECG levels are not normal.
uhhh..Next 24 hours is pretty critical for him.
Okay.
We are monitoring him.
If his body is stable and if everything goes well,
we'll schedule the surgery for the 24th.
Let's hope for the best.
We'll do our best! You take care okay.
mm Yeah!! The EPO injections...
huh..she's responding to the EPO Injections pretty well.
Well! Good let's maintain the dosage
for the next 48 hours.
Farhaan..
Farhaan: Hey Nidhi..hey hey.. hey hey..
What's going on?
Are you ok?
What happened?
Are you at the hospital?
Yeah
I am at hospital only.
My dad I feel, I don't think so he'll make it.
Farhaan: Hey Nidhi.. hold on, hold on..
I am here with you. OK..
Tell me what is the doctor have to..
Nothing makes sense to me Farhaan..
I don't know..
Farhaan: Nidhi.. look. look listen..
Listen to me..
We will get through this together...
Calm down ok! ok?
Yeah..yeah...
Farhaan: Just, just.. just be strong for your Dad, Nidhi. Ok...
I am sure he will respond to the medicines.
I am with you...
I have to leave..See you tomorow..
Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow...
Seriously?!! You came at this hour?
It's okay..
I just called you because I was feeling helpless.
You didn't need to come..
It's okay.. mmm
What does the doctor advise..
as the treatment plan?
The doctors are saying, they have to wait and see
how he's responding to the medicines after the surgery.
and then decide the treatment plan.
You know what?
He is.. he's not responding to the medicines.
His BP is still high.
It's okay.
I don't know.. I don't know! I really don't know..
Clearly..
Things are so uncertain.
You should be going, it's getting late...
It's okay. Fine, chill.
hmm..
After 16 years...
So Maya, mmm... 32 people, awesome number no?
Not bad at all for a reunion after 16 years!
I am so excited!
Yeah man, tell me about it! I just can't wait!
By the way umm...
Are you planning to call him, Nidhi?
Who?
Oh! You know who..
Farhaan !?
Ah ha!
No Maya, there is is no way I'm going to call him.
I mean- it's been such a long time...
Sixteen years! It's not a joke.
No, I'm not gonna call him.
You have no clue where he is?
No n..no clue where he is..
and I don't think so anybody knows either.
I looked him up everywhere ...
Uh huh.
He is not on social media.
Yeah..
No ya, let's just forget it.
OK,
never mind..hmmm
You know, I just thought it would be fun!
Actually..
It will be a nice idea to call him!
What you think?
Ahh.. Nidhi! You are unbelievable!
Seriously..
Man...
I'll tell you something..
You know, you do one thing..
Watch 96.
96, It's a movie?
Ha, a movie.
I don't know if I will have time. I'll see.
But why do you want to me to watch?
You know for everything Nidhi,
You have a why...
Gosh, my goodness!
Just go watch it ya!
Yeah it's a movie
See it's actually two friends okay,
who were close in college.
And they meet after 21 years or so..
It's really nice!
Ok, I'll see.
Alright ya..Bye.. ok!
OK Maya, bye..see you
Ace, let's go buddy. C'mon..
BGM of movie 96
So! Let's invite him Nidhi..
No no! Leave it.
Forget what I wrote no, Maya.
Oh ya!
Oh, It's ok ya Nidhi.
You should call him!
See, Worst case- what will happen?
Either he will come, or he wont come.
Big deal.
What difference does it make?
Hmm.
But I don't have his contact ya.
How will I find him?
hmm..wait a minute hmm..
what-hold on guys let
me put on speaker..
Alright, so wait a minute.
What, what was his last name again?
Farhaan what?
Ashraf. Farhaan Ashraf.
Hmm..
I see five Farhaan Ashrafs.
5 Farhaan Ashrafs?
Yeah I think it's him ya!
It says he studied in our college.
Did he do Masters at Boulder?
Yes.
Then it's him! I am sure!
What?
Oh! Oh wow! Really?
How did you find him?
My 6th sense!
Linked in ya, how else?
Linked in? Seriously? Even I searched..
I never found him! How come?
Because my dear Nidhi! It's an art!
You want more details or no?
Where is he?
Where does he work?
Wait man!
Let me look ok..
hmmm
OK, this says its close to our reunion venue ya-
In Glendale!!
No way! Are you sure Maya?
Check the address properly, no!
Hey!
Why don't you look him
up in...huh
people finder or something
get his number?
What the heck ya, Anu?
Are you out of your mind?
It's like as if I'm gonna stalk him!
hmm..
Did you hear that Maya?
As if searching in Linked in wasn't stalking!
How else will you find him girl?
I know its insane, but whatever! Who cares?
hmm..
Exactly!!
and if at all we find out that he is near Glendale..
let's go ahead and invite him for the re- reunion.
That's all!
Yeah thats true, Thats all! What say girls?
yeah let me do that and I will
keep you guys posted okay!
OK all the best! Bye..
Yeah yeah okay bye.
"What is this selfishness of yours!"
"It's neither light nor shade"
"What is this selfishness of yours?"
"You don't feel settled at any place?"
Nidhi..
Nidhi!!..
What is the status with Farhaan?
Found him!
What?
Anu! Focus!
"You have become your own God"
"You swam all the seven oceans"
"Still you are dry inside your heart"
"Why do you remain so?"
"O great one, heed to this"
"O great thinker, heed to this"
"Come, your shadows are calling you"
""O great one, heed to this"
"O great thinker, heed to this"
"Come, your shadows are calling you"
What huh?
You are not going without
telling me!
Please tell!
Airport!
Nidhi!!
Hey Nidhi.. are you kidding me?
Byeee..
What?!
Hi!
Mayaa.
So good to see you..
Man its been so long!
How are you?
Doing good! How are you guys?
Its ok ya! Not great
Man it was tiring..
You want some help?
Its 221..
haa, this one.
Who has the keys?
Uhh, I have the key..
haa..
Shh..
Shhh..
Hmm?
ehh?
Sheeeh.. huh..
hmm..
Nidhi..
What happened?
What is going on with you?
Maya..
I am like super worried ya!
So.. nervous!
I don't know why I got into this.
All because of you only!
You and your out of the world plan!
Oyee! Now you blame me?
As always?
Nonsense..
Of course!
How many times I told you?
No need!
You and your that movie 96
Ah so?
So do one thing
Don't go!
Simple!
What?
What? "What?!"
You know what? Give me your phone
Give.. I'll text him
No no no.. its ok it's okay
I should be professional right?
Yeah right!
The professional you!
Ughhh!! Shhhh..
What's this gals?
Why are you guys sitting and yelling at each other
in the middle of the night?
Anu, you'll understand me!
You will understand my state of mind better, OK!
See my life right?
Was all perfect!
Until this thing happened..
and suddenly I feel my life is all upside down.
I don't know what to do!
About what?!
Oh!! oh oh.. Farhaan?
Oh dear, chill no!
You're just meeting him only right?
That too in a restaurant..
It's going to be casual and nice! Trust me!
You think so?
Absolutely and..
No! This is NOT going to turn your life upside down..ok?
Both of you have your separate lives. Right?
I know, I know, I know it will be all ok..
But Anu! I have this weird feeling
as if butterflies are churning inside..
See that's exactly why I said, don't go!
Keep quiet, right Maya!
Leave her alone please..
As it is she is confused..
Listen.
You go.. ok?
Go meet him..ok?
It's going be casual and nice- right!
You'll enjoy this
okay
Ok, let's go to sleep..
But guys my biggest worry is none of this..
What if after all this drama..
he doesn't show up only?
That will be epic, no!?
No change! Still the same!
You as well..
Straight out of college..
Absolutely no change huh!
Really? Thank you..!
Seems like you brought the rains from Seattle huh?
Was hoping to see the sun for sure..
but,  you know what?
The rains do make me feel at home..
Okay..
So tell me why now?
How did you find me?
Uhhhh..
So, I used to google you..
and uhh..
Maya found you on Linked in recently
and that's how I got your number.
Simple na?
Uhhh..
My phone number is not on Linked In
and I'm actually not friends with Maya either..
Soo...
You know the problem is you know me too well..
and I simply cannot lie to you..
OK! I'll tell you..
uhhh..
Maya found your Linked in
and that's how we got to know your work place..
And uhh..
I got onto people finder..
Wait.. wait..what?
And...uhh
I got 3 numbers from there.
Wait people finder?
Which means, you subscribed?
Yeah! How else?
No way!
So, for someone who is totally cut out from this world..
What other way to contact?
Okay go on..
Yeah so.. hmm
I had three numbers..
And I randomly picked a number and texted.
It ended up being a wrong guy!!
Can you imagine?
I texted a complete random stranger
Oh man!
You texted a random person,
and you didn't know it wasn't me?
Yeah!! how am I supposed to know?!
Oh come on! That's ridiculous huh..
Well! To start with..
You were not the most receptive person..
Were you?
Oh!
Then the 2nd number..
had the picture of your daughters..
The older one-
looks ditto like you..
and that's how I confirmed..
Amazing na?!
Nidhi..
Why after all these years?
I don't know..
Hmm..
Farhaan..
This..
this meaning you and me..
uh.. what do I say?
There is this box of memories which I hold on to..
and I completely own it!
Way...
Just way too special to me!
This is .. just a way..
of re visiting something
that was long left behind..
uhh.. I don't know.
I wish I knew..
It's okay..
You don't have to tell me..
It's ok..
No..
I seriously don't know..
Even.. even I..
You know, even I have been thinking about this why part.
It's like..
How do I put it..
You finish reading this book and,
there is this one page
which you really like.
And you go back to fetch that page
and relive it once more..
That's what I guess..
I agree and no umm..
I don't really want to know the reason..
it's okay..
OK!
Tell me
how have you been
doing this past 16 years?
How's your family?
Been in Seattle..  pretty much..
Yeah pretty much in Seattle..uhh..
Working for Expedia.
Two sons..
and husband is a cardiologist..
Oh nice!
Yeah let me show you their pic..
Oh wow!!
How about you?
Let me show you this pic..
Ah.. beautiful family!
I told you no,
the older one looks ditto like you!
Thanks
So tell me..
So why..
Why aren't you coming for the reunion boss?
I.. I have a friend's wedding to attend..
Sooo..I cant skip that.
Oh!
Otherwise you would have come no?
See, I knew..
Some things just don't change..
Tell me how's your Mom doing?
Mom's okay.
It's been 16 years since Dad left us.
She is managing..
I know..
Those hospital days were a struggle- I know.
Totally remember that
Yeah..
Do you remember the night when..
when you came to the hospital?
and we spoke until dawn?
Yeah.. You were..
really amazing.
You handled it very well..
Thanks to you!
I think it's time for you to leave.
Time to pick up kids right?
Yeah..
Nidhi ya..
It's been too short uh..
One hour after 16 years..
right?
I know..
Time was always short for us, no Farhaan?
It was never enough..
Anyways..
We still made it!
So what time do you have to pick them?
In half an hour..
Okay there is still time.
Yes..
Man.. it is cold in here!
Take my jacket..
Thanks! But no thanks..
Okay, freeze then..
Oh. How will I return your jacket if I
take it?
In your next visit right?
Excuse me!
Yeah, of course..
Don't think too much okay...
Just take it.
Listen to me for a change, OK.
Thanks! But I'm good.
Listen I got to book my ride..
Nidhi...
Thanks for all this craziness..
It was worth it..
Stay in touch okay?
Yeah..
I will..
Looks like..
My car is parked there..
I guess this is it..
time to go..
bye.