I can feel the sunlight,
Touching on my skin
Boy I feel you eyes
Pierce me deep within
I feel your eyes
They bring desire, ohhh ohhh
Everytime you are next to me
You look like trouble
Dangerous lover
Get on the dance floor
Show me what you came for
Babe when you touching me
I'm loosing my control
Don't leave me here
Dancing on my own...
You feel like summer
Yeah, i got summer on My mind
From Barcelona to Dubai
You feel like summer
Yeah, i got summer on my mind
From Barcelona to Dubai
I can feel your sunshine
Shining on my sky
Boy I feel your light
Always on my mind
I feel your touch
It brings desire, oh, oh
Everytime you look at me
You look like trouble
Dangerous lover
Get on the dance floor
Show me what you came for
Babe when you touching me
I'm loosing my control
Don't leave me here
Dancing on my own...
You feel like summer
Yeah, i got summer on My mind
From Barcelona to Dubai
You feel like summer
Yeah, i got summer on my mind
From Barcelona to Dubai
You feel like summer
Yeah, i got summer on my mind
From Barcelona to Dubai
You feel like summer
Yeah, i got summer on my mind
From Barcelona to Dubai
You feel like summer