I found the most expensive fails on the
internet from causing hundreds of
thousands of dollars in Damages to
millions of dollars in Damages to
billions of dollars in Damages billions
is that even possible we'll see punching
a hole in the wall it's a spider
I don't blame them that hole is gonna
cost a hundred dollars to fix thanks a
lot Rachel this bird steals a pair of
airpods why is he doing a report also
are we going to talk about those fake
airpods that guy's rocking the bird's
taking it to the lab to see if they're
real assuming they're real he just lost
two hundred dollars and as this video
goes on the damages will be higher and
higher a pigeon walks on wet cement
that's pretty cute actually oh wait I
think there's a pigeon in this room good
thing there's no cement in this room I
love how he just won't stop and that is
250 in damage that pigeon in this in the
room
oh oh that was RC first of all I need
that RC helicopter if you look in the
top right you'll see that as a thousand
dollars in damage can someone buy me
that it's so cheap what's this plumber
doing
oh that sucks what do you because like
the water's just gushing out now what
you do is you hire a better plumber and
also don't hire a cleaning lady to be
there the same day she's like ah man how
much supposed to clean all the water
1300 I think 1300 damages is a little
modest you're gonna have to replace that
subfloor the joints you know the
and building top as a manly man I know a
lot about these things you know a lot
about Hydro drifting and MacBook Pro I
actually love hydro dipping wait a
MacBook Pro you can't put it in water
okay number one don't turn it on hold on
future of vegetable
versus Lambo door look at this little
scruff of hair oh he's like oh crap I
don't have insurance I'm sorry that bear
destroyed the Lamborghini easier than
our hydraulic press did it's only four
thousand dollars to replace a Lambo door
I might trade out my front door with
that imagine if your front door was a
lava door that you had to like crawl
into imagine what that bear bit the
Apple it actually bit his hand imagine
the dragons robot falls down escalator
that's the future oh those people oh
hi robot it's already starting how much
did that say that was five thousand
dollars I mean that's a new knee way
more because I'm suing I'm suing the
mall I'm suing the escalator I'm suing
the robot yeah if I'm that robot dude
I'm suing these people marriage proposal
goes wrong they're in love are they
gonna fall through
oh he's so defeated all this that he's
gonna
he's confounded she's like just keep it
and walk away seven and a half Grand
down the drain suitcase cart goes wild
whoa gonna go somebody get on that thing
we need Bronco Bill hit the plane would
they still fly it you can never fly this
there's a suitcase cart one of my
flights got delayed because A bird hit
the plane really yeah
yeah
he got it I picture USPS does that
driving whenever they deliver packages
no whenever they deliver a fragile
packages they're like you got a vase
the truck's empty you don't have to
shove it in there like that it's got to
fit forklift Falls in water it sure is I
don't know if that's falling in water I
think it was already in the water we
skipped a couple of steps oh he was
probably one of those boat Fort lifts
how much you pay for the for the new guy
how would you pay for the luga this guy
doesn't spend a lot of time on Tick Tock
that's just a tick tock audio dog what
an idiot was forty three thousand
dollars
oh
well he made it held him like a orange
if you freeze it at the right time it
looks like the car is going for takeoff
and then it looks sad when it hits the
ground because it's like oh maybe next
time car falls down the lift that means
the elevator in British people
geez that's a lot of money I don't know
what I'd do if that happened to me
honestly I'd probably have to sell
everything that I own if you are gonna
sell everything you own you should do it
online and if you're gonna sell things
online you should use the sponsor this
video Shopify let's go let's go you're
told me if I were to sell everything on
Shopify then people would even buy maybe
this sweatshirt that I'm wearing right
now I don't really think he meant like
that Carl no I didn't mean that and
Shopify offers an easy to use Commerce
platform where you can set up a store
and instantly start selling to people
all around the world
and the best part is you can sell
anything on Shopify even pictures of
Carl's feet
sure they're perfect for your first sale
and once you scale up to become like a
major business they'll have all the
tools you'll need any of you can start a
business with the help of Shopify just
click the link description or go to
shopify.com mrbeast and start an online
business right now do it click it click
it now tow truck drags cards oh my
goodness it's his last day okay give him
a break hey that's not how you do it
that's got to be a world record for how
many car accidents in a minute I like
the idea that he was just listening to a
podcast unaware he's like
you might be experiencing some bumps on
the road of life and he's like yeah he's
like you know what I am
yes keep going while valve fixes it
train Tin Roof gets ripped off oh
I open it like a can of beans that's so
satisfying yeah it really is it's just
peeling it back when does the train come
to a hole when it stops I didn't think
of that apparently a plane got stuck
under a bridge let's see how that's a
big plane that is that's a small Bridge
do they call that a plane crash yeah
does that qualify as a plane crash I
don't want to fly on that plane truck
crashes into highway signs you're gonna
want to watch out watch it oh
how's our truck being destroyed more
damage than a plane well it was only
like a scrape to the top of it you know
those signs on the highway are like a
hundred thousand dollars each government
is inefficient camera equipment gets
destroyed uh Tariq don't watch this
video if you're Tariq oh oh oh
it's bouncing I got some air 150 000
camera hard to be a gimbal when you're
rolling on the ground Dingus I wonder
what those shots look like they don't
look like much because the second it
hits the ground the lens starts yeah
usually that makes the shot look
terrible a truck driver spilled a bunch
of yellow paint well now people are
going to be really confused if they're
supposed to oh oh no he made himself a
Simpsons character that looks like me
when you guys drop mustard on me yes
that was the worst flying a helicopter
indoors this is whistling diesel I hate
being that guy he deserves to get that
thing to crash that looks safe
you know Jimmy I picked the wrong crazy
person on YouTube to hang out with you
made me successful when I could have
been launching helicopters indoors I
agree this is your dream Channel why are
you here whistling diesel whistle my way
this looks like us in 2018 if we had
today's budget yeah that's literally
what he is fishing boat Falls over oh no
don't they understand boats are supposed
to go in water yeah that's probably the
problem
POV the other side of the boat
officially
yeah we're all upset about this but
there's a bunch of fish really happy
right now house Falls in River well that
was bound to happen come on now whoa
houseboat this is just a boat now this
is a better boat than that fishing boat
we're going on a ride I believe that any
house near water is going to be very
expensive if anything this is an upgrade
yeah if you're on the second floor you
were fine the kid don't even notice he's
on the second floor over there playing
fortnite wine tank leaks what look at
this this tank is no need to whine about
it
I'm leaking they call the wambulance
shut up 1.5 million dollars in one I
wonder if that happens and you're an
employee there who's going to stop you
from just running over there and just
it's going to waste anyway because
you're getting fired you're getting
fired might as well go out with a bang
how can you think that you could be on
this list if you don't drive a Bugatti
that's an aquatic car maybe he thought
he was paying two million dollars for an
amphibious car these fish are looking
out they're getting houses Bugattis
boats Fish are winning this video racing
pileup
that's a massive question oh no he's
going the wrong way entirely you have to
imagine when your car is facing the
exact opposite direction in a race
what's going through your head oh my God
I hope I face the other way please train
Falls and drops Bridge wait when do they
make cranes that big cranes can get
humongous but that bridge must be giant
oh yeah it is oh my God look at everyone
running it's like in slo-mo it's like
when giant Fallen like video games and
you're like something big wouldn't fall
in slow-mo like that it does apparently
honestly I didn't know how Jets land but
I didn't expect it to look like that
this is a special type of Jet and it
costs a lot of money to get it that was
basically 500 million dollars down the
drain oh he just gosh thank you that
took him a second oh he's like at least
I got to use the ejector seat oh that
hurt he was not high enough to use the
ejector seat why did he eject the jet
was right there that was a person that
was Panic panicking that's a very
expensive jet there's only a couple of
those and he just broke it and he was
like I just gotta get out of this wait
that actually looks awesome oh less
awesome a little less even less
oh I did not think all that would happen
well that would explain the 20 million
was that like a natural disaster yeah
called stupidity you don't know that
football stadium roof collapses from
snow this was during the Vikings Giants
game yeah during the game in the middle
of the game okay it was right before
dude I would pay everything to be
standing on that field when that
happened yeah right that would be so
sick to just get blasted by cold air for
2010 why is a little black and white
film get a better camera Viking but
crane drops a plane bro cranes are just
taking else don't be a crane operator
guys that must be why they get paid a
lot of money because if you're an idiot
you could mess a lot of stuff up oh
that's not the crane operator's fault
the crane gave out it's someone's fault
this is a crane Builder's fault not the
operator actually it's the crane
inspector the crane Builder built it
then the crane inspector inspected in
the crane operator operator what about
the crane inspectors inspector what
about would I inspect your mom oh that's
up to you and her SpaceX rocket explodes
wait guys I think this rocket is it's
not going to land properly it looks like
it's going to land very it landed what
are the damage oh
look into the space was there anybody in
that nah it's just a test rocket and
that was 200 million dollars in Damages
subscribe or I'll see you for that much
bye