the mi 24
is one of the most admired and feared
attack helicopters
with its impressive appearance and high
weapon carrying capacity
this flying beast whose nato reporting
name is hind
has proven itself in major battles in
many parts of the world
the helicopter which can still find new
users with its new models
left its mark on half a century both
militarily
and culturally now we're investigating
the mi24
a true attack helicopter legend please
don't forget subscribe to our channel
before we start
and give us a thumbs up if you like our
video to be notified of our new video
please click the bell button
[Music]
preferred by more than 60 countries the
mi 24
is the most widely used helicopter and
has fought
in many parts of the world it has been
an important system
that couldn't be ignored not only by
western military planners
but also by hollywood don't you think a
puma that resembles the mi 24
deserved the award for the best
supporting actor and made ramba 2 and
rambo 3
a part of the list of legendary movies
too
and isn't it possible to see its impact
even in the struggle for life and death
between jedi and sit in a galaxy far
far away although it has become a legend
today
in the beginning the faith of soviet
military planners about the mi 24
was very low in the early 1960s
the soviet mill company started to work
on an innovative system
which was basically a flying infantry
fighting vehicle
it meant that the new helicopter should
be able to perform
both fire support and infantry transport
duties
in 1966 mill unveiled a mock-up to
demonstrate its new concept
the value of this new concept was
immediately apparent to some
but many were skeptical of it yet
the us army's successful use of gunship
helicopters in vietnam
ended the debate between these two
groups in a short time
thus mill presented two conceptual
designs
one was the comparatively small and
single engine
and the other was the heavy and twin
engine
kamov also offered a version of the
ka-25 naval helicopter
as a low-cost solution for this
requirement
after extensive consideration in 1968
the soviet army's preference was mel's
heavy helicopter concept
flight test of mills helicopter
prototype began one year later
in simple term it was a highly modified
mi-8
whose nato reporting name is hip for
gunship helicopter world
many airframe components and
sub-component came from mi-8
and its naval variant mi14 whose nato
reporting name
is haze in 1970
acceptance tests started after 18 months
of trials
many changes were required for example
the fuselage was
strengthened to solve fatigue problems
and vibration levels
the position of anti-tank missile pylons
was moved from the fuselage to the
wingtips
after these changes the mass production
of the helicopter
now called mi24a started in 1970.
it became operational in 1972.
however the mi 24a was more like a test
platform
than a real gunship helicopter while
mass production of this model continued
the mill engineers had to deal with many
design flaws
for example the three blade tail rotor
which was on the starboard in the first
production versions of the mi 24a
had been repositioned to the port site
to increase efficiency in later models
also the design of the cockpit was
causing an inadequate view for the pilot
the mi 24d whose mass production began
in 1973
has ended these problems unlike its
predecessor
this model has a tandem cockpit with a
double bubble canopy
the rear seat is 30 centimeters higher
than the front
all later versions of the helicopter
have this configuration
the pilot and the gunner seat inside the
titanium armored tub
in the cockpit their windscreens are
bulletproof
in an emergency the gunner can also fly
the helicopter
thanks to the over pressurized cockpit
and troop compartment
the helicopter can be operated in an nbc
environment
the armored fuselush and the titanium
rotor blades are resistant against
12.7 millimeter rounds there are three
pylons on the mid mounted stop wings
at high speed they provide considerable
lift
the design of airframe has high
aerodynamic efficiency
also the mi 24 fitted with retractable
landing gear to reduce track
these futures make the helicopter fast
unlike other attack helicopters the mi
is capable of carrying eight infantry
however experiences during the soviet
invasion of afghanistan
showed that this capability didn't work
as expected
for the soviet mi24 crew members
fighting in afghanistan
both engaging on targets and thinking
about the safety of the transported
soldiers
had been too much of a burden besides
carrying eight soldiers and the armor
plates in the troop compartment
decreased the performance of the
helicopter as it increased the weight
to overcome these problems the soviet
army started to use mi-24s in fire
support missions
and the mi-8s in troop transport
missions
it has been observed that carrying a
technician with additional fuel and
ammunition in this compartment
allows the mi 24s to be used longer and
more effectively
also carrying a technician who handles
the light machine gun in a window port
was providing the mi24 the ability to
watch its back
while leaving a target area depending on
its model
the mi 24 is equipped with different
weapons
the mi 24a had a one-man operated
machine
gun on its nose the mi 24d
version has a four-barrel 12.7
millimeter machine gun
mounted for the turret while the mi 24p
model has a 30 millimeter twin barrelled
cannon in a fixed position on its right
the mi 24 vp has a 23 millimeter twin
barrel gun
in the beginning the soviet army planned
to use the 9k 114
term anti-tank missiles whose nato
reporting name
is at6 spiral with the mi 24s
however due to the delay in the
development of this missile
the helicopter was first equipped with
the three m11 phalanga
yet this missile whose nato reporting
name was
at2 swatter was obsolete in those years
for this reason many users have equipped
their mi24s with the 9m14 malutka
whose nato reporting name is at3 sagar
in the following period the helicopter
has gained the capability of firing the
9k 114 today
modernized mi24s can use high capability
anti-tank missiles
such as the 9m120 attacker whose nato
reporting name
is at9 spiral 2. the helicopter has a
two-man crew
many countries have also added a
technician to the crew
the mi 24 can carry eight infantries
the fuselage has a length of 17.51
meters
and the total length of the helicopter
is 19.79 meters
its rotor diameter is 17.3 meters
while its height is about 5.47 meters
with an empty weight of 7580 kilograms
the maximum takeoff weight is 11 500
kilogram
two 600 kilowatt tv3 117v
turboshaft engines provide a maximum
speed of 310 kilometers per hour
the cruising speed of the helicopter is
270 kilometers per hour
the mi 24 which has a range of 450
kilometers
can reach a range of 1000 kilometers
with external fuel tanks
its service ceiling is 4950 meters
while its power ceiling is 1400 meters
as we mentioned earlier the weapons of
the mi 24
differs depending on its models the
helicopter has many production
and modernized variants since it will
take a lot of time to talk about all of
them
we will focus on some major versions
export models of the mi24s are called
mi35
the mi 25 is the simplified and low cost
version
specifically for third world use
the mi 24 super hind mark 3 is the
modernized version of the helicopter
by paramount advanced technologies of
south africa
this variant has a 20 millimeter vector
f2 gun in a new chin turret
with an external ammunition storage the
helicopter can fire the long-range
laser guided zt3 ingui anti-tank missile
the super hind mark iv model is equipped
with the ukrainian barrier
anti-tank missile the mi-24vm
has non-retractable landing gear and
shortened wings
there are two pylons under the wings
instead of three
this variant has elastomeric bearings
composite main rotor blades and x-shaped
tail rotor
same as mi-28 the helicopter
uses a kilimo vk-2502
turboshaft engines which provide better
high altitude performance
the avionics and electro-optic
surveillance systems
are also modernized even though the ussr
planned to replace the mi24s with a new
attack helicopter in the 1970s
due to its low anti-tank capacity it
proved itself
as indispensable in many battles
the mi-24 was used in combat for the
first time
by ethiopia during the organ war the
helicopters were one of the key weapon
systems for ethiopian victory
over somalia but the mi 24
gained its real reputation during the
soviet invasion of afghanistan
in the early stages of the war it was a
weapon of terror
for the mujahideen one ceremony 24
scared a group of mujahideen away by
just maneuvering aggressively
to rescue a company of infantry however
the helicopter had been out of
ammunition
besides escorting troop helicopters and
providing air support for ground forces
the mi24s were protecting land convoys
against ambushes the soviet army was
additional using them for hunter killer
operations
the mi 24 hunter kilo groups were
consisting of a minimum of two
helicopters
more often the soviet army preferred the
groups of four
or eight mi24s to provide mutual fire
support
the majority could occasionally counter
the mi24s with rpg type weapons
and machine guns heavier than 12.7
millimeter
however these efforts were rare and
unproductive
after a while the balances changed with
the stinger and red-eye missiles
that came with the u.s assistance now
it was time for the mi24s to be scared
according to russian sources 27 mi24s
were shut down by these missiles in
afghanistan
but western sources estimate that this
number is much higher
although they were the nightmare of the
iranian infantry during the iran-iraq
war
the iraqi mi25s were quite insufficient
for anti-attack missions to overcome
this problem
the iraqis started to use them in hunter
killer groups
together with the gazelle carrying the
hot missiles
while the mi25s were dealing with the
infantry and air defense troops
the gazelles were attacking two tanks
during this war
the iraqi mi-25s conducted many
air-to-air helicopter combats
according to some sources during the war
the heinz claimed 10 victories
against ah ones in exchange of six lost
even once an iraqi mi-24d
managed to shut down an iranian f4
phantom 2
using s5 unguided rockets iraqi mi25s
also claimed 43 kills against other
iranian helicopters
such as uh-ones it is claimed that in
a russian mi24 vp shot down a georgian
su-25 using a 9k 114
anti-tank missile while in the 1980s
many analysts thought that the modern
attack helicopters overshadowed the
mi-24
it has shined brighter once again after
1990s
after the end of the first cold war many
african countries
that needed an aircraft for
counter-insurgency missions
began to acquire the surplus heinz the
mi 24s
have played important roles in all
corners of this continent
the mi 24 is still successfully fighting
in africa
as well as afghanistan iraq and syria
it is an indispensable helicopter in
fact
russia which announced that it would
replace the hind fleet with the mi-28s
and k-52s by 2015
changed this decision the russian mi24s
are being modernized
and will continue to instill fear in
their enemies
for many years to come the helicopter
is continuing to add new pages to its
saga
the combat proven impressive beast mi24
deserves to be called a true legend
thanks for watching our video and please
don't forget to subscribe to our channel
and give us a thumbs up if you like our
video to be notified of our new video
please click the bell button