I have to leave for my
solo trip in the morning.
I am going on a solo
trip after so many years.
I have a lot of work to do.
And I am busy in seeing partnership
between Kohli and Dhoni.
Packing?
I have just started charging my gadgets.
I have set an alarm for 4.30am.
And now the time is,
1:16 am.
- The number you have
dialed is not responding.
- Please try again later.
I will miss my flight after some time.
Driver on the way. Please don't be late.
Your driver is late.
Saved
My boarding pass was fallen.
Let me tell you one thing.
If you are not feeling well.
Especially if you have a cold.
Don't travel in an aircraft.
There is a pressure difference.
Your ears will hurt a lot.
I have a lot of friends like this.
Their ears saved from burst.
I am also not feeling well.
And today is Monday
and today i have a fast.
But I have to eat something,
I have to take medicine.
I am missing only one
thing on this highway.
When I cycled.
I used to cycle along the side of the road.
From morning to evening.
I used to cycle for 14 hours a day.
Let's have tea and take medicine.
Then move ahead.
The place where I have
to go is 280 km from here.
I have come to
Chhattisgarh for the first time.
I have heard that Chhattisgarh
is a good place for tourism.
But it is unexplored.
And the resort where I
am staying is amazing.
Let's check out.
Let's have tea first.
Give me tea.
Are you making hot samosas?
Make two cups, okay.
Samosas are being
made early in the morning.
- Does samosas serves for breakfast here?
- Samosa, Puri, Sabji
Let's go.
Now, i am leaveing for..
When I used to do vlogging
before the lockdown.
I used to travel solo.
You guys gave me a lot of love.
We went to Meghalaya.
You bumper loved the Meghalaya series.
And when you go alone.
You are stopping somewhere,
to set up the camera.
You have to shoot according to yourself.
When you go with your family.
You can't do those things.
There is a lot of
restriction with the family.
There are kids.
When I was in college.
I was not interested in traveling.
From our college in Kharagpur.
Freinds used to go to the beach.
I said I won't go.
But then I started traveling actively.
Because of vlogging.
I said let's travel to make
good content for the vlog.
But it happened like this.
I went to the start for that reason.
But while traveling.
I fell in love with traveling.
Then Ritu and I started traveling together.
To make a vlog together.
After traveling, Ritu said
I won't travel anymore.
But I wanted to travel more.
Because I was getting
addicted to traveling.
But then Rashi grewed up.
Slowly more work increased.
More responsibilities increased.
Lockdown started.
Then solo traveling stopped suddenly.
Then I had to take the
kids with me anywhere i go.
After so many years.
I am on solo travel.
Maybe that passion will leave
inside from you very soon.
That passion will not remain a passion.
There is a very fine line.
That's why I said to
Ritu that I will go alone.
Because I really
like this thing.
Solo travel vlogs.
If you like it too.
Please appreciate it.
It was so nice to leave this highway.
Greenery everywhere.
Such a beautiful highway.
Greenery is everywhere.
In rainy season.
Everything is green.
And our country is so beautiful.
This is the country where
you will find Himalayas,
Ganga,
Desert,
Beautiful beaches.
Hill station.
And in Kashmir.
In Gulmarg.
You will find snowy valleys.
There are so many Kawadiya.
You will find them on this road.
Our traditions, customs.
The villages of india,
People who is living
there have kept them alive.
If someone works in a
multinational company.
Lives in Delhi, Mumbai, Bangalore.
Whoever has to go to take
Kawad, then there is no time.
They are overburdened with
work, they are busy with work.
We they get a day off.
then there is work at home too.
Are you planting rice?
Planting?
Can I come and see?
Let's see.
Wow.
- Does it implement
like this? Wow, just throw it
It hit my foot.
How long does it take
to plant a whole field?
I have listen that, does
snake come in planting rice?
- Yes
Oh it comes?
So, is a snake non-poisonous
or is it poisonous?
- Poisonous one
What are you saying, really ?
Have you ever been bitten?
- A man passed away?
Yes.
While planting rice?
- Yes
- Ohh sister
So do you keep the medicines?
- No medicines, goes
straight to the hospital.
If they have luck then they will
survive, otherwise they don't.
Don't you feel scared?
?
So sister why don't you feel scared?
- No we don't feel scared
Don't feel scared?
- This is our job, so what fear?
This is also true.
We are farmers, so who fears?
- Now may be snake sitting in the water,
What can we do, if i see the snake.
Is there always this much
water in the rice fields?
Always ?
The best thing i like is,
They have practice of it like they
are throwing it and it get settled.
Look at this.
It was nice meeting them.
But it was bit surprising that,
They have threat that
snake comes and bite them.
But still they are planting rice.
If they don't sow, we won't get food.
Planting rice means risking the life.
3-4 people says,
They run to towards the hospital,
3-4 people have died here.
It's a very difficult
work, sometimes i think.
So much risk of life in this work.
But they will hardly make any
money, hardly they will make.
There are so many crops in the
middle man, they don't get anything.
When we went to Ritu's
village, they had such a big field.
They said they will plant the whole
field, whatever crops they plant.
Finally, they earned
40-45 thousand in this much.
- Kawad is going?
I got real fun of travel is when
you stop and talk to people.
They don't say yes, they
have learned a new thing.
They say, How, How.
Is there tea here? Yes
Earlier, I was very shy
when I didn't start vlogging.
So I couldn't talk to anyone.
But the benefit of vlogging
is that I have opened up a lot.
I can talk to people, talk to them.
And you will see, when you
have your own inhibition, y
our own shame, I talk to them
and they are so welcoming.
The real fun of travel is not in
the destination, but on the way.
There is life with family too,
but this is my therapy that I travel.
It's a lot of fun.
But the problem with me is
that I have to go 250 kilometers.
GPS is showing, it's a 5-hour journey.
But it will take me 7-8 hours.
And what I go to explore,
it happened many times.
It happened on my last trip too.
The place where I am
going is closed at 5 o'clock.
I am reaching at 6 o'clock.
The roads are so much
fun, what you are seeing.
But where we are going, they
are saying that it has rained.
Maybe the place is closed.
Look at Gau Mata.
Gau Mata got no chill on the way.
It's 12.15 pm.
There is a 4-hour long way left from here.
Now we have come to the old highway.
I can't stop myself after seeing tea.
You put such a big board for tea.
Without sugar.
And I need that stuff at any cost.
I can't complete the trip without it.
It's near the bank.
Yes, it's here.
When I was packing
for this trip last night,
I had a problem.
Because my travel is so back-to-back.
I just come home for
a day and then I leave.
When I sat down to pack,
I realized.
Ritu.
Hey Ritu.
Where are you?
Here.
I don't have any underwear
what should I do pack?
Why?
Not a single underwear.
What I wore today's was the last one.
what dream did you have?
Am I asking for a underwear in your dream?
- Yes
Wow.
We had to do this shopping.
It was very important.
It's good that main highway was closed.
So, we entered the city a little.
Now we will live freely for 4 days.
Otherwise, it feels like 4
days in one underwear.
How bro?
There are some things in
life that you do only by feeling.
When you play cricket, no matter
how many techniques you have,
you always play with
the feel of the pitch.
When I used to do landing in the aircraft,
No matter how many techniques
you learn, but every landing is a feel.
Similarly, a car.
You are driving a car with
a manual transmission gear.
The technique is the same.
But still, in every car, you will take
10 minutes in the beginning to feel.
How big is the car?
What is the size of the car?
But especially this gear transmission.
The combination of gear and clutch.
To feel it.
It will take you 10 minutes.
No matter how many techniques you have.
And in life it is very important to
know when to change the gear.
If you go whole life in the same gear.
Then you won't have fun in life.
You should know when
your time is not right.
So drive in 1st gear.
And when your time is right and
the wind is blowing towards you.
Then drive in 5th gear
- You will get to see the
whole of Chhattisgarh.
It is being broadcasted on
the radio that Lord Ram,
Had passed by Raipur somewhere.
There is a tree planting on the road
going on and school kids are doing it.
- How much for the banana?
Rs. 50?
It will cost you Rs.130
Give it to me.
- Dantewada
While driving, I was very sleepy.
Let's take a break.
When I leave the house in the morning,
There were a milk truck
overturned on the road.
I am thinking of getting a Red Bull.
It is difficult to get a Red Bull here.
Bro, a lot of difference is
made by stay for a while and eating here.
I lost all sleep.
The mountain road has started.
And it is very beautiful.
Green belts on both sides
Chhattisgarh Valleys.
We are passing by a place called Kesh Kaal.
From Kesh Kaal we are
going to Chitrakoot Waterfall.
It is almost 2 hours away
Whole city has been left and
again highway has started.
I had left the hope
That I would get food today.
I have ordered food.
The food was very good.
We also had coffee.
It was fun.
But the bad news is that the place
where are we going closes at 6 pm.
And it is 5.20 now
So we are going to Chitrakoot Waterfall.
Which is India's Niagara fall.
When I went to Canada
I started vlogging on Fit Muscle.
No one knows that.
I have never shared it
I started vlogging on Fit Muscle
Then,
I went to Canada and started there.
The work that I do
The work that I believe in
I don't do it slowly
I do it very blasting.
I bought expensive cameras, drones.
At that time, no one knew me for vlogging.
Mom-Dad told me to start it slowly,
When you grew up, everybody know you.
Then you can buy it.
I said no
I want a drone.
Because I have the
confidence that I will do it.
So now  don't know, where
I have reached from there.
We made a vlog then at that time.
It became famous as Niagara Falls.
It was a vlog on  Fit Muscle
I started vlogging on Fit Muscle TV.
We are already late
And we came back
I am so unlucky today
I don't know what to say
Chitrakoot Road
When I was passing from here
I saw such a beautiful road
Such beautiful fields
Chhattisgarh is so beautiful,
I didn't know until today.
But it was very beautiful.
So I thought
We are not going to reach anyway
Why not stop and fly the drone.
Bro, Is Chitrakoot is straight from here?
Finally reached the room.
I got a little more bad news.
There is no boating here at the moment.
Because there is a lot
of water in the waterfall.
Don't worry, Keep your courage high.
This is the best waterfall in India.
And it looks like this from the balcony
I will show you in the morning.
Very amazing
The day was very long
We were very tired
Now
Bye Bye
Let's sleep.
They have put something.
Welcome Flying Beast
Not a bad day.
They have put something.
Thank you so much.
To make this bad day a little better.
It's down too.
But dirty...
This
Who put this here.
Closed it from outside.
Who was here?
Don't be seen.
SEH LENGE THODA