subscribe to this channel
and click on the Bell icon
to see the latest Technology videos first...
Friends, May be you all are enjoying free data
but in today's date, you may have fgvhv
if you see, free of charge is no more free
and
in such a case that if you are in a rural area
and if you don't have sufficient internet speed
then probably you might not be able to see this video properly
for that YouTube has developed a new superb app for India which is called as
YouTube Go
and today I am going to talk with you about that
because here we say
Maje Udao, Data Nhi
Hello Friends,
My name is Gaurav
and you are watching
Technical Guruji
So Let's Begin
Friend's I had already made another video on YouTube Go somedays before
but that time it was only announced
But now it is available in play store in the BETA format
and more updates are comming soon
so lets see how much awesome youtube go is
and whether it will let you download videos on slow net speed
and though this you can share the videos too
now let see youtube go
this is youtube go application on play store
download are still little because it is released recently
and if you read it benefits and details by going into its Readmore option
and here you will it is a normal application
which works like youtube
but here you will have many data benefits and the size of the app is low
instead of that you can control data, share videos after downloading
and this app is going to be fast and will work on old phones too
so here are many benefits of youtube go
and if you need I will give the link to this app in the description
so from there you can install this app
after installing this, you will be asked to verify your mobile no. which is linked to your google account
doing all this and you will get the app home screen
here you will get videos depending on your search history or standard trending videos
and here you will get another tab for saved videos
where you can see your saved video collection
and if you want you can send or receive them too
which is the most important feature of this app
and you also get some basic setting where you can change your language kinds of stuff
you will get this basic layout where you can search videos
and if you click them you will see the preview of the where you can see
what content is inside that video because this happens often mostly
where video content other than video title and your data get wasted
so here you will not let your data get wasted and
you also get some options for video quality
a basic quality which will be around 144p
and
and a standard one having like 360p
you will also see the size of video according to the quality for letting you play or save
for a sample, I will save this video on basic quality
I clicked on save
here the video is saving
and after completion it came in my saved videos
now let I want to share this with my friends
you can do it too if you and your friends use YouTube go app
although you may not get the option for subscription, like/dislike you can't comment in this app
but even at least you can see the youtube in less data
so if I want to send
which video I want to send
I will click on this video to send
then it will try to make a local wifi hotspot
clicked on allow once
It will make wifi and scan nearby
and now at that time I have to pick the other phone where you want to get video
and click on receive video
after that, they will make the connection and will show the name,
when clicked it will show confirmation message on the phone wether you want to send it or not
afterward the video will be transferred between the phones in less instance of time
and after receiving video, you can see the same video
it is an excellent option by the way
but as I said you will not get any other option on the video you can only watch it
you can neither like nor comment on the video
but you can search and play many videos like if you want to see Technical Guruji
when you will search that you will find many videos which you can see
that is a good point
beacuse you want to save data
because you know the free is no more freer
so in case you can use, this YouTube Go app which will save your precious data
I am giving the link in the description
Go install it
and Save your data because, we want fun without using data
So thats all for in this video
Thanks for watching
If you have any suggestion then don't forget to comment if haven't liked and shared this video so far
then like it and share it and don't forget to subscribe to the channel.
Because I bring such videos on the daily basis
Thats all for the moment friends
"Jai Hind"
"Vande Matram"