Hi Friends, today we are going to do the 'English Vinglish' challenge.
Wait a minute, I have heard English but what's Vinglish?
I am already weak in English.
And you are doing this challenge so I'm out.
Look at your side. Are you forgetting me? I am at your side.
Oh right, I have him at my side.
She always makes me lose and yet I am at her side. Very nice.
Alright! Now let's start the game. OK.
In today's game, there are 4 rounds with 10 questions in each round.
You can play with us as well.
And there is no compulsion for English like she said.
If you are not good at English still you can play. It will be fun.
And the first round is here on the screen.
What's this? Aayu and few show. Aayu and Pihu show.
Right. Oh, this is how the challenge will be.
We have to make a guess by rhyming the words.
Yes, like this you have to guess. This is "English Vinglish".
Read and guess the word.
So, there will not be any point in this one.
Why? Because this was the trial question. Alright!
And here goes round 1. Food. First round is on food.
Will there be letters or sentences? You'll see.
1st question of 1st round is here.
You pressed too soon. Okay, answer quickly.
Blue? No. Boe? Day.
Time up! Potato chips. You will be given 10 secs only.
Why did you buzz first? You want to join Mom's team.
They lost a point. No, no.
Minus 1. No! Why, why didn't you answer?
You didn't answer you were only reading.
From now, if someone buzzed, they have to answer or minus one point.
So, friends are you getting the game?
Boe day tote ships become potato chips.
This is really fun. OK now, the next question.
Oh no, who buzzed first. I did. It's a cheeseburger. Cheeseburger.
Okay now, next.
Ice cream cone.
Oh wow. See, I told you I am good at English.
Today is my day, and I chose the right team.
What will happen to your team, Aayu Pihu? Don't know.
Next.
"Peanut butter". Oh, very nice.
You have to answer before secs or it will not count.
Now, their brain has started working. Yes, you are right.
Pihu Di's not mine. Yes, mine & Aayu's brain is yet to start.
Don't forget to like the video.
OK, next question.
Chocolate brownies
I buzzed first. No, I buzzed first.
OK, Aayu got a point too. Chocolate brownies.
Friends, Are you getting it? Keep noting down your scores.
And share with us in the end by commenting. Alright.
OK, next.
He buzzed. Apple Juice.
Is it apple juice?
What's this? There are three words. Apple juice.
It can be like this also. It could be anything.
You have to guess by speaking the words.
This is why it's called Vinglish. It's Vinglish, not English.
OK, next.
Cheese pizza. It's already done.
Not pizza it was a cheese burger.
Mom, at least get us one point. My brain is not working in this game.
I am weak in English and you added Vinglish too.
Oreo cookie.
I was thinking of winning in Dad's team.
You can change teams if you want.
No. It's not worth I will make them lose. They'll not agree.
OK now, next.
Right now, I feel like I'm good for nothing.
Focus.
Old Bud, old butter. Old butter.
Aayu got this. Chole bhature. Old butter.
How is this chole bhature?
Last time it was in peanut butter.
Don't get confused with the last time, it can be anything.
Chole bhature reminded me of the north vs south food video.
Relax, relax. We will have chole bhature too don't worry.
OK, next.
Paneer tikka. Oh, we got it later.
I was guessing burger tikka.
What burger tikka? There is no burger tikka. Thanks for being quiet.
I mean you can speak but first, make sure you are right.
Got it. We have to get points.
Round two is here. Countries.
Countries' names are not very familiar.
I only know a few countries' names, if it comes then good or else.
You didn't study G.K. ? I did but I forgot most of it.
Now, let's move on. But I do know G.K.
It's a part of their syllabus what's the big deal. OK
OK now, next.
I buzzed first. South Korea. I got it too.
I challenge you both in this round. Relax Dad.
There's going to be a challenge within the challenge. Yes.
Next.
Australia.
Friends from Australia will let us know that they are watching.
Friends from respective countries, please do comment.
OK, next.
Thailand. Why are you so slow, be quick.
A tube light takes time to start.
I haven't answered a single question.
Friends, it's a record.
I didn't answer even a single question.
And she is holding the buzzer like this.
Feel like you are alone in this team, I am out.
OK, next.
Bangladesh. I buzzed first. This time I got it.
Aayu also said bang. Bangladesh.
We receive a lot of comments from friends in Bangladesh.
There will be a lot of comments from Bangladesh.
Indonesia. This time we buzzed first. OK, they did it first.
It means Mom got it too. Now she can keep her hand on the buzzer.
I miss it when I try to buzz.
But what's the point in that you are only telling them the answer.
I believe we have friends in Indonesia as well.
There is a yeah in every country. Yeah. Yeah.
OK, next question.
South Korea, Africa. South Africa. I said, South Africa.
Mom said south Africa.
Thank god, I got us a point.
Friends from south Africa don't forget to like.
The jungles in South Africa are amazing. We will visit there sometime.
I thought she'll complain about not taking her there.
OK now, next.
Ukraine.
You car rain.
OK next.
Zimbabwe. You got me scared by buzzing too soon.
This one was cool, Zimbabwe
OK, next.
Saudi Arabia.
You are going to break that buzzer you were so loud. Sorry!
Now, they are in the mood to win, why did dad challenge them?
It's always that people who try to be over-smart end up losing.
We take back our challenge. No, we accept it again.
West Indies.
I pressed the buzzer too.
I didn't even understand.
This is a fun challenge. Isn't it friends?
Don't say any thing rubbish. The next round is sports. I am ready.
What?
We had a team meeting. We want to do it too.
Do it. Include us in it too. Yes, after the round.
Alright, we played half of the game and mom took one point.
She scored 2 points. There will be comments that I scored 1 point. 2!
Cricket, we pressed the buzzer.
We buzzed first. Let me keep my hand here.
Table Tennis! Oh, man! Table Tennis.
We buzzed first. No, we buzzed first.
You try buzzing first. OK, next.
Basketball.
What happened to Mom?
I am active now.  Mom told me a trick before.
Mom is using that trick. I know it's guesswork.
No, no. We won't tell you. We will tell you after this round.
Alright, next.
Volleyball!
You're thinking after pressing the buzzer. No. No.
We are not even taking time to think, we are giving answers quickly.
We buzzed and answered. Yes. Next.
We buzzed first. Alright, now answer.
They are trapped. Archery.
Don't use your brain much. They planned to buzz first.
Not us, him. Yes. It's your team don't point fingers.
Make your team understand.
If you wouldn't answer, your point would have been deducted.
Now Aayu is not saying anything, he is quiet because he been caught.
That's the face of one who is caught, he is covering his face.
He is not even showing his face, show your face, don't be shy.
He is not even showing me.
Let's move on with the game. We won't till I say so.
Computer Sir, continue. Yes.
Wrestling. Wrestling.
What are you doing? Why are you blaming me?
What did I do? Aayu takes 4-5 points in every round like this.
Just press the buzzer. Yes, so you can say anything.
Answer now. We buzzed.
Did you buzz? Yes, should I answer? Yes. Kabbadi.
Don't buzz if you don't know the answer.
Its challenge is like we are saying something fast.
We're going, the proper way is we are going.
We speak in short form. Yes, I had a t-shirt earlier.
It was written on it 'What are you saying?'
If you read it together it might sound weird.
But it meant What are you saying?
But it was written 'What are you saying?'
It looks like they know English really well which is not true.
If it wasn't a sports category, what would we have said.
Scrape dealer. Next.
Hide and Seek.
What's the trick I don't get it.
Guess from the initials. Use your brain.
Timing is crucial, you can see we are answering so quickly.
Alright, next.
Karate. Yes. None of you got it, still, you pressed the buzzer.
Not all three, it's just him.
This mother-son duo are alike.
Aayu and I buzzed, we both didn't know, I thought Piyush will answer.
Look at them, they both are alike.
He takes after me.
Their faces match too.
Mine and Pihu's face match as well, tell us in the comment.
Whose face matches whom.
He has a dimple like Mom. I have a dimple too.
You have it too. Only I don't have it.
She had it but she lost it somewhere. She ate it, alright next.
Gymnastics.
Oh, man!
This was good.
Now it's Round 4 Fruits.
We did a fruit challenge and we ate so many fruits.
There's no way there could any fruit beside them.
We ate almost every fruit. Let's watch that Fruit challenge once.
Alright, I will tell you the trick. What?
I won't, I will tell after the challenge. Tell us!
Mom recalled all the sports names before the round began. Yes.
So while playing it immediately clicks.
Give us 10 seconds. We'll also recall all the fruits. Yes.
Orange. Apple, Kiwi, Sapodilla. Avocados.
Did I pronounce it right? Yes. What? Avocados.
Avocado. Mom said anaconda earlier. Anaconda. Yes!
First round fruits, here it is.
Watermelon! We said it first. It was very easy.
Alright next.
Custard Apple, mom buzzed but she didn't know the answer.
I buzzed first. We did it. You're buzzing it so quickly.
I am not doing it, mom is doing it. Don't do it, Mom, let us play too.
If I know then I will buzz. Yes.
What is this? He was checking the buzzer. Alright next.
Dragon Fruit.
What? It's there.  Something. Next.
Say it. Say it quickly. Pineapple.
He thought and answered he buzzed without knowing. Don't do it.
You saw what happened right, next.
Guava.
The computer is also calling us to let's go to Goa. What?
Let's visit Goa on the computer only, come on.
Take us for a trip. We will, but on the computer. Stingy!
Every time you say it, why are you playing with me, alright next.
Pomegranate.
I won't leave it. Obviously. He will buzz, alright next.
Strawberry, We buzzed first.
I can see it they both are cheating. Not both. Not Cheating.
It's not cheating, we are answering. You do it. Yes!
Dad does that every time. I will, I will change the game next time.
What? Next.
Muskmelon. Mom buzzed first. I did it.
She banged it. We have to win.
Yes. My reputation is on the line, and my English is well.
You laughed as well, alright, next. Yes.
I was just... It wasn't here. It won't count.
Minus 1. No! You buzzed too, both will get minus one.
There are tears in my eyes.
I didn't buzz, my hand wasn't even there.
In this respect also Pihu and Dad are alike.
They both get tears while laughing.
Alright next.
Who buzzed? We both buzzed, we don't know the answer.
Aayu buzzed. But I buzzed too.
Avocados. I said it at the start. It's an anaconda.
Did you get it? No.
No, I didn't get it, we still buzzed.
It happened two times that we are caught cheating.
Next time, no buzzer, these are pointless.
Say it. Capricorn.  What is Capricorn?
Which fruit is that? I will tell Capricot! Capricot.
What is capricot? Apricot.
Apricot. You said capricot.
Challenge over, It's finished. Capsicum.
There's a special round.
The one who wins the special round is the final winner.
Subscribe. Like Share. No. subscribe.
Subscribe to my channel. Do it quickly.
This was good.
We won! You just won by one point.
This mother-son duo cheated a lot, so we don't know.
I hope you enjoyed the video and laughed.
You can also play this challenge with your friends.
If not on a laptop, you can play it on paper with your friends.
See you in the next episode till then. Bye!