If I gave you the choice to either buy
30 Lamborghinis or help save
the lives of 10,000 people in one year,
which would you choose?
We decided to do this.
Cue the epic highlight reel of the year.
We started this mission in Khayelitsha,
South Africa,
where we found an orphanage
that was in desperate
need of our help because it was at risk
of being closed down.
I started back then, I saved more than
5330 children.
Those children would be dead.
But we keep on opening the doors,
knowing that maybe someone
will come to our rescue.
Like Beast Philanthropy.
So we spent the next
six months working
tirelessly by rebuilding 12 new homes
with an ongoing supply of fresh food,
as well as a brand new playground.
While the orphanage was being built,
we begin our next project,
where we gave away
20,000 pairs of shoes to kids in Africa.
Beast Philanthropy,
what you have done here at my school
is absolutely amazing.
Thank you Mr Beast!
Darren then flew to the Hopi Reservation
in Arizona,
where he met with Wendy.
There are over
10,000 members of the Hopi tribe.
These people don't have very much,
but they are
some of the most generous people
you'll ever meet.
The Hopi tribe is situated
hundreds of miles away from the closest
quality clothing and food stores,
which is bad because the winters here
get freezing cold
and they need all the help they can get
to stay warm and put food on the table.
When we realized just how difficult it was
for them to get access to these basic
neccessities, we decided to donate over
$2.7 million of clothing.
It was amazing.
Our kids, our people are just so happy.
Thank you, MrBeast.
We then found out that there is
an abnormally high number of amputees
throughout Cambodia,
so we partnered with Exceed Worldwide
to give away 2000 prosthetic limbs.
What we've experienced
is that it's so much more than a limb.
We're giving back people
their independence.
But most important,
I realized that we we're giving them back
their dignity and their self-esteem.
I’m so excited.
and I really thank you!
Darren and Dan
then flew to a remote island in Colombia
where they capsized a boat
and fell in a river filled with
crocodiles!
While they were there,
they built a solar grid
which gave the island electricity
and WiFi for the first time,
which will give the kids on the island
the ability to access education online.
We also built a bakery to empower
the woman in this community, which
from day one was a hit.
We then travelled to Kenya, where fresh
drinking water is extremely scarce.
I am a father of six children
and I want to be the best father of all.
That's why I work so
hard to maintain my bread.
My bicycle,
it has no gears.
One of the pedals is not there,
the brakes are not 100% working,
Sometimes I think,
if I could take a motorbike engine
and put it on my bicycle,
my life would be easier.
So with the help of Lectric E Bikes,
we were able to provide
Mr Barasa and 1000
other people with free electric bicycles.
You have made work easier!
It’s so easy to ride!
Darren and Dan then travelled to the Cure
Children's Hospital in the Philippines,
where we were able to provide
160 kids with life changing surgeries.
This little girl has just got her cast off
and she's learning to walk
for the first time
ever with her straight legs.
The magnitude of the surgeries
that these kids are getting from Cure
for free, will change their lives.
And the fact that Beast Philanthropy
can come in here and help Cure
provide care to some of these kids
is something that's going to affect me
and stay with me for the rest of my life.
The construction of the orphanage
in South Africa was now complete,
and it was time to surprise
Mama Rosie and the kids.
No!
Mama Rosie also told us about a boy
named Yamkela, who left the orphanage
14 years ago with
the dreams of becoming a musician.
However, he was struggling to make money
and practice his craft,
working full time at the airport.
It kills me
knowing that I'm doing something
that I'm not into,
and there is something that
I want to do that
I really love, but I cannot do it.
So we decided to surprise Yamkela
with a brand new top of the range
acoustic guitar as well as award him
a full scholarship to the best
music school in the country.
See you in a year.
The team then flew to Thailand,
a country with over 2 million
stray and disabled dogs,
to meet with Michael and help him rescue
as many dogs as possible.
Where we help thousands of dogs run
for the very first time,
As well as give Michael
a brand new rescue van,
state of the art gas machine
and a brand new ambulance.
Really happy.
Thank you very much.
Darren then received this video from a
TikToker named Dora moono.
Beast Philanthropy,
please please help me save our village,
our kids need you.
So Darren immediately
flew to Dora’s sanctuary in Zambia,
which had absolutely no electricity
and is located in a dangerous area
with high rates of domestic violence.
It became evident
that the lack of electricity
was holding them back
and severely curtailing Dora’s ability
to help develop this village
to what its potential could be.
Having to wake up thinking,
what will these kids eat?
That is still very difficult
to do each and every day.
So we came up with a plan
to use the direct sunlight
and scorching heat to our advantage
by installing a massive solar grid
that will provide electricity
to the entire village.
It was then time to turn on the lights
and the kids
couldn't contain their excitement.
Mateo, turn on the lights!
And we have lights!
We then found out about a college kid
in Philadelphia that is rescuing
thousands of pounds of food every month
because of his school meal swipes.
I originally started
just as a student with
leftover meal swipes
in my dining account,
and I realized as I was getting close
to the end of the term,
I have 50 meals left that I know
I'm not going to be able to use, and
I just had a pit in my stomach thinking
about all those meals going to waste.
So Darren flew there to meet him
and help expand his operation
to a national scale.
After witnessing everything
that Evan had done to help this community,
it didn't take but
an hour to know that we had committed
to partnering with Sharing Excess,
to help them achieve their goal of feeding
as many people as possible.
And with our help, Sharing Excess
were able to open an operation at
Hunts Point Produce
Market, the largest
produce market in the
world in New York City.
And that operation
is going to be three times larger
than the one that we have in Philly.
Next, Darren and Dan
travelled to the heart of Cameroon,
where thousands of children at this school
have to share a single toilet
and have lessons in these derelict
and dilapidated classrooms.
These conditions had no dignity.
These conditions would not make a child
believe that the future is bright.
Once we saw this,
we knew we had to do something.
So almost immediately
we started drawing up plans to begin
construction, and a few months later,
the brand new classrooms were built.
Just in time to surprise the kids
before they return from their holidays.
Lastly, we flew to Nepal
for a secret project
that will be revealed next year.
But on that mission, Dan and Darren
went to 21,000 feet high to Mount Everest,
to sign out this video where the altitude
made Dan very loopy.
Darren and I,
are at the highest point
we've ever been together.
It's been one hell of a year.
You know, we've been working together
just one year and look where we are
on top of the world,
literally and figuratively.
And I wouldn’t share this experience
with anybody else man.
Send this to any billionaires you know,
and tell them to stop buying
cars and instead help people.
IT'S BEEN SUCH AN
INCREDIBLE YEAR,
AND WE'VE HELPED SO MANY
PEOPLE AROUND THE WORLD
BUT NONE OF THIS WOULD HAVE BEEN POSSIBLE
WITHOUT YOU.
YOU ARE THE HEART AND
SOUL OF BEAST PHILANTHROPY
AND WE ARE BEYOND GRATEFUL
FOR ALL YOUR SUPPORT.
HUGE LOVE, BEAST PHILANTHROPY.