Friends lot of viewers keep asking me, how to hack someone Facebook account and Gmail account.
that also in just one click!
So today please keep watching this video
I will explain how to do it...
There is a little twist in it....
that how can hacking be done in just one click...
So keep watching this videos I will talk more about it..
and I hope..
I can clear some of your confusions that your have in your head.
about one click hacking.
lets hope I will clear these confusions.
and things will be clearer later.
Hello Friends, My name is Gaurav and you are watching Technical Guruji.
Lets gets started!
Friends I can't understand why....
Hacking is so popular?
if I talked to you about Ethical hacking..
that is totally different..
But I get  messages, emails about
How can I hack Facebook?
or (hack) Gmail?
means the attack is at the personal level..
...that I want to hack particular persons Facebook account....
...that also in just one click....
If you will Google how to do it....
You will get thousands of these websites
where..
You will see a lot of softwares
that will tell you that it is possible in one click.
If you search YouTube...
...you will get a lot of videos where they show you that download one software...
Put your ID and password and some of your details....
and put ID details of the person who you want to hack
and just press a button...
..and you get their password. You revealed their password!!!
Means there are so many websites that
We think that it is possible to hack in one click!
When we go ahead....
and download those softwares...
Then we get these surveys...
and you can not bypass these surveys..
Even if you managed to do it....
and you get the file (if it exist)
If software like this actually exist on a website....
..you download it..
..but what happens after you download it?
Can you hack in just one click?
Friends the Reality is this that in one click
..Maybe your own account can get hacked.
Friends...
Its not a joke...
that at the Facebook or Gmail where...
..there are a lot of of experts are working
means their expertise is waste?
People think that they have made a one click software to hack and it should work!!
I mean...One should have some sense..
But still lot of people keep on thinking about various ways of
hacking in one click....that...
They can hack Facebook,  Gmail or Yahoo.
It is not possible my friends.
On the contrary, there are chances....
....that your own account will get hacked.
Either you may keep on going through Surveys....
That is also one way
to cheat....and to steal your personal details
and you won't get any thing....
I agree that you can..
...bypass some of these surveys by using no script....
or by using survey bypass tool...
Those are separate tools..lets not talk about it...
But even if you got a website....
they use...
Several weird ways like...
enter your ID and password
enter your details....email..
Tell about the person being hacked, attach their photo...
There are various options provided there....
All in all....
They just extract your personal information....
You won't even realise...
You just keep on thinking you will keep on clicking and you will get....
....the password of that person.
In this "one click" Please don't get hacked yourself.
friends all these softwares...
all these websites are fake...
There is no such way ....
that works...
There has not been.... and there won't be any either.....
One click and done....Its just a useless idea....
friends I am not saying that
....hacking is impossible...
There are ways...You can hack accounts...
There are several options available..
for example: Phishing, cookie stealing....
But there is no such way that can let you....
...hack in just "One Click"
Please keep this fact in your head..so.
You won't waste your time in future....
and also you won't get your account hacked in one click.
I hope you liked this video my friends...
I hope you understood that it is not possible to hack in one click..
Please protect yourself....
Don't waste your time in stuff like this...
and also...
It is possible that if you try to do " one click hacking"  You will get hacked yourself and then ...
(laughing.....)..and then commenting that your ID has been hacked...
Thats all in this video. Thank you so much for watching.
If you have suggestion please don't forget to comment below.
if you have not liked or shared this video
then please share it
so others can also stay away from "One Click Hack"
If you have other suggestion
please don't forget to comment below
if you have not subscribe it yet then please subscribe.
because I bring you videos like this everyday.
Thats all for now friends.
Jai Hind!! Vande Mataram   (Long Live Mother land.