How is it going Prerna, Harsh, and Asher?
I have a challenge for all 3 of you, okay?
I want you to pick any fast food location of your choice
and spent 24 hours in it without being kicked out.
Good luck!
What to do?
It's from Mr. Beast and not
an ordinary challenge.
We are in the McDonald's and I
am going to be here for 24 hours.
We searched for the biggest and most empty McDonald's.
It's highly rated.
It has two floors.
It was very crowded so we
sneaked to the first floor.
We are now sitting in the corner.
So Harsh, we now have to order
And how will we pass the time?
I have thought of ordering the full menu.
It will take time for us to eat and
they won't rush us out.
You have become as cunning as me in my company.
And your son will be the most cunning.
He is saying that he will eat fries.
Go to the floor below and order the full menu.
It's 10:00 am.
Go order fast.
Hand me your parcel.
Don't take him with you.
yes. Keep it with you.
Mr. Beast's channel is in Hindi so let's see some videos.
I opened his channel.
First, go to Settings, then Audio, and select Hindi.
In this video, we are going to rescue 100 street dogs.
Isn't it awesome?
Since we have to pass the time, let's change seats.
- Prerna, Asher wants to sit in this one.
- Jumping from here to there.
The way he is
I wanna do a trampoline and drive the jeep.
Asher, let's do this after we are
done with the challenge.
Please, mom!
It's been 15 minutes and it was the best decision.
I mean what would happen in 15 minutes?
We have to spend so much time here.
Our order is here and I was hungry also.
So I am gonna eat so much.
The full McDonald's menu is here.
Kartik Aaryan meal!
When did this start coming?
Asher, do you wanna have the Kartik Aryan meal?
He wants to eat Asher's meal.
He wants to be popular so
that his photo is on it.
So I am gonna take an
hour to eat all this.
It's a big day and we have a lot of time.
But I don't know how will I settle Asher.
Because he has to play around.
Should I let him down?
The first item is the Butter Paneer Grilled Burger.
Then we have McVeggie.
Then we have Maharaja McVeg.
- Give me this one.
- Eat all of them.
Kartik Aryan Meal Burger.
Spicy Wrap Paneer.
McPuff.
I have all types of fries - small, medium, and large.
And there are more burgers.
Excuse me Harsh.
There also is McSpicy Paneer Burger.
Okay!
McSurprise Whole Wheat Burger.
Ice Teas, Large Coke!
And that's coffee for me! Cold Coffee.
Coffee.
That's total Rs. 1500.
That's a very affordable price for Mc Meal.
We have to pass the time and not rush it.
They must have it limited.
Let's start with iced tea.
I'll eat fries then.
What's special in the Kartik Aryan Burger?
It's McAloo Tikki Burger.
It is the same.
They keep checking on us.
It's the start, no one will object to anything.
2-3 hours are pretty easy to spend here.
Let's start with the big burgers, McMaharja.
It's very tasty.
What have you done to McMaharaja?
It's a Zoom burger.
One bite challenge.
He is snatching the burgers from me.
You are not of age. Well, here eat some.
Don't eat.
Feeding a baby is so tough.
They won't eat what they are
supposed to but paper only.
Have you ever tried
fries dipped in Ice Tea?
That's a weird combination.
You just ruined them.
Who does eat like this?
I eat without tomatoes.
Do tell me in the comments how
do you eat your burger?
Also, tell me what's your
favourite burger from these?
If you want to be in top subscribers
of the next week.
This week's top subscribers are
Somint
Tansi
Aadhira
and Hina!
The moment you take your eyes off,
you meet with a situation.
He has eaten a full tissue.
Handle him. Look at
what he is doing!
He can do anything.
He is eating Ketch Up!
Oh, it's not opened yet.
Asher, you didn't like the fries?
Now you would have to mop.
- Hello!
Do you watch our videos?
Thank You!
We met with a subscriber
while doing this video.
You know we are doing a challenge?
That you will get to know
after watching this video.
It will be out the next week.
Tell us your name.
- My name is Sanket.
- Mine is Vansh.
Vansh, Sanket, Kunj!
Such good names!
If you watch our videos, tell us
which is your favourite?
The 'Our Home is Haunted' one.
This is cheating!
- It was so nice to meet you all.
- Thank You.
- You didn't eat the fries?
- You ruined my challenge.
I wanted to count how many fries are
there in small, medium and large.
There are 150, 200, and 250 fries in those.
Don't tell me rubbish.
I wanted to calculate.
Go, get them for me again.
Now she will count the fries.
I will get to know how many fries
are there in small, medium and large.
We have so much time.
I will get them. Don't worry.
Harsh is going to get us fries meanwhile
I will change Asher's diaper.
It's been so much time.
let's clean him and I will touch up my face.
let's go to the washroom, Asher.
We are in the washroom but
there is no changing station.
There should be one
diaper changing station.
Where should I change it now?
Look at how he is looking at it.
So focused.
So we will do the changing here.
I waiting for Harsh to come here.
Here he is!
He is here with all preparation.
Asher, this is your bed.
The diaper has been changed now.
But he isn't lying on his back.
He created a ruckus.
Sometimes he feels hot and cold.
It was so easy on the bed.
Should we go home?
You ate the meal it was the challenge.
- Give him the lipstick.
- No. He has already broken one.
- Is that so?
- Yes
- Harsh!
- What happened?
- You said you got a full meal?
- Yes obviously
- There were hot beverages. You didn't get them.
I want free coffee with them.
- You want coffee?
- Yes.
Harsh is going to get me the coffee and
I am gonna decide in which corner I can hide.
I have to spend the night here.
This table? I will get caught.
- Under this table?
- yes.
Yeah, I can hide here.
Asher is looking at the rides outside.
Can I take him outside for the rides?
No.
It's Asher's first challenge that too by Mr. Beast.
He called out his name.
Harshi!
Harshi and Asher.
It's Mr. Beast's challenge and
we have to complete it.
Guys I am jumping from one seat to another.
We have changed so many seats
and spent so much time here.
it seems like it's my second home.
But I am very tired and I
don't know what to do.
I am thinking of getting a nap right here.
There is no other option.
You can handle Asher?
Definitely. You go to sleep.
It's been evening from the morning.
We are tired of watching this view.
The staff is also bored of seeing us here.
Asher is feeling sleepy and hungry.
It's milk time for Asher.
I found a baby chair.
Let's give Asher milk in this chair.
And here is my coffee.
Where is the coffee?
- See what I got?
- I already saw it and thought of making him sit in that.
- Where?
- Anywhere!
it's our home now. Anywhere!
Your coffee. Where is his milk?
- That's what I am making!
- Wow Prerna
It's almost evening.
Eat play and be happy.
It's the best spot.
It's all empty.
This is your milk.
Make it in a good quantity.
I will make it so much.
Here have the milk.
As you can see Mr. Beast. how good Asher is doing the challenge.
He is the best challenger in the world.
Guys spam 'Asher OG challenger' in the comments.
Now Prerna has started dancing with Asher.
To make him asleep.
First Asher will sleep then I will.
We will sleep and then it will soon be dark.
And we will hide and that's how we will complete our challenge.
They will kick us out.
Let's keep ordering.
get me an ice cream.
McFloaty.
It feels like heaven in the lap of Dad.
I have to sleep sleep sleep.
Harsh how to pass the time?
it's been evening from day and I thought to touch up a little.
It's more red.
Harsh is still walking with Asher.
- Aren't you tired?
- Very
- Thank You!
- Thank You.
He didn't seem happy to me.
We are bothering him with orders.
This is my fourth coffee.
To accompany me Harsh has ordered hot chocolate.
This is already my fourth coffee.
I ordered only because of the cookie.
It's the best chocolate.
And it was a good cookie so I ordered coffee 4times.
I have had four cookies.
They have been pissed off a little by us.
They weren't coming for the coffee I ordered 30 minutes ago.
They said we should take out the order by ourselves.
I was eavesdropping.
The kid behind us is also named Asher.
You only do this, don't you?
I have to pass the time.
What else to do?
She gets super attentive while she is sitting somewhere.
The lights are turned on outside.
It's evening now.
I feel sleepy.
I am trying again and finally, he is drinking the milk.
Let's order him a hot chocolate.
He is not of age.
It's like a house now.
He is again taking him to walk around.
While exploring the M McDonald's menu.
We found a goggle for Asher.
It's a little big for his face.
These were the only ones in the kid's section.
- I am not interested.
- Try it on once.
You will see double momies and daddies.
He wants to eat that too.
no, I  am not giving it to you.
Play with this.
He likes McD.
Just we couldn't.
What happened?
He is slapping me.
He wants to ride in the car.
- It's a challenge.
- He wants to go to trampoline.
He wants to go with them.
He got bored here.
Your fries are here.
Count them.
It's a happy meal.
He cried seeing the happy meal.
Thank You!
Now I am going to tell you
what's in a happy meal.
We have a Kartik Aryan burger, fries, coke and
it's a book inside the Pokemon Pikachu's box.
And pineapple juice.
What happened? Your neck got stuck?
Let's go home.
He got me upset.
He is slapping me.
Now I am going to count how many fries
are there in small, medium, and large.
First, let's start with small.
19...20...I won't be able to fill them back in...
21...22
- 41
- Small has 41 fries.
Now medium.
Guess how many would be in this?
- I guess 70
- Don't confuse me.
67 fries.
I guessed 70.
I was close.
- NOw large.
- First guess.
Around 60. Medium is similar to large.
It would be a fraud then.
- We will get to know soon.
- I am guessing 85.
I feel it has the least fries.
large fries are a myth.
Never order large fries from now on.
Medium is good enough.
I will say order small.
They robbed us. I used to think how
many would be there in large.
He comes for cleaning again and again.
Thank You!
He is very helpful.
Let's give him a meal.
Call him over.
It was good until we hadn't calculated.
It's a shock.
Medium and large are the same.
I was getting bored so we will now do a Happy Meal challenge.
We will do an epic Happy Meal challenge.
This is the fastest eating challenge.
Let's see who finishes the happy meal between me and Dhruv.
1...2...3...start.
Jump right in.
Don't eat in such a bad way.
- Dhruv you couldn't even eat it.
Come on do it one bite.
Go for a single bite.
I would eat fires.
Look at how badly they are eating.
I think he will win.
- My fries are finished.
- Finished?
So fast!
There are no tomatoes.
You are behind.
Come on.
Don't you want to win?
Dhruv has lost
In how many bites are you gonna finish it?
3 bites.
Let's ee.
The end.
He hasn't even finished the fries.
he is way behind.
No, the Pepsi.
Dhruv lost and harshly ate the meal in 20 seconds
The world is moving but she isn't.
Because Asher is asleep and now
I have to keep sitting like this.
Asher liked McD.
Sorry!
They have got very comfortable here.
We have to be here so we had to make it comfortable.
They have been standing right
here for the last 15 minutes.
What are you looking at?
Asher is looking at the car and trampoline.
He wants to go there. He is stuck here.
He is saying he can do it tomorrow.
Today he feels good here.
We want to go there. he is getting sad.
We will go after the challenge.
- We will circle back here
- No the challenge will end.
- It won't.
- It will.
So Harsh and Asher left.
I thought of taking him on this car ride.
He is enjoying it so much.
Should I leave Asher?
He isn't seeing me.
Look up your mother is doing the challenge.
He isn't sitting but standing.
After spending the day, the evening,
the night in the McDonald's
Harsh and Asher got soft over a car.
A battery car.
We got Asher to the trampoline.
Asher go fetch the ball once.
Come back after getting the ball.
We are waiting for Prerna.
When she will be content?
Otherwise, we will wait
here but not go up.
It's the McDonald's where we are doing our challenge.
Prerna is sitting up there somewhere.
- Do you wanna order anything last?
- Last, means?
- It's gonna close at 11 PM.
- Isn't this 24/7?
- No. It's not 24/7
- Can't I stay here?
You can stay here but you
would have to do the dishes.
Just give me 5 minutes to think.
Is this gonna close?
Do you want to eat anything?
Okay.
What? I mean I thought it was 24/7.
It closes at 11 PM.
What to do now?
Should I try to hide?
Will I fit here?
Won't someone catch me here?
What are you doing mam?
I was trying to hide in here.
Okay. I am going.
Sorry Mr Beast! I have to leave now.
I have to leave.
Bye!