hi how are you i'm great what about you
i'm too thank you for asking um can you
stay and hear me all right yes yes i can totally
okay i had some trouble just with like my internet
so if you can't see or hear me at any
point just let me know and we can fix it
um but aside from that um this is our first chat
so it's so nice to meet you um normally i like
to just ask some questions about you um and like
how old you've been learning english give you some
information about me during these first lessons um
so we just know a little bit more about each other
but um let me get this pulled up okay so can
you pronounce your name for me um it's adrija
adrija yes okay and um where are you from
um i'm from india okay what part of india
um i live in the east side well um kolkata
okay so i actually have never heard of the city
until today i talked to somebody earlier in
india from the same place really i think so yeah
because he was talking about how it was eastern
india and i'm almost certain that it was the same
city um so what's your what's your native language
like living there i know that there are a bunch
of different languages in india um i my native
language is bengali but the main language in
india is hindi like we all know hindi um but you
know everyone has different native languages like
yes in the south there are other languages like
you said that you can like you know hindi as well
yes yes do you know any of the other languages or
just like hindi and bengali yeah no hindi bengali
and english these are the three languages that's
a good mix um and you can communicate with a lot
it's like good news that's so cool though so um
okay okay he also spoke moving goalie so now
i really think that he was from the same place
but uh how long have you
been learning english then
um i'm learning english from my childhood
like from i don't know three years old maybe
okay so you've been learning english for a while
do you speak english at home like with your family
um no not really uh but i do speak english with
my friends at my school okay so that is very
like some practice yes yes yes um that's cool and
then do you how long have you been using gambling
um not not for a long time i would say uh maybe
for one month one or two months oh okay okay so
it's still new here and then i'm assuming like are
you using it just to practice your conversation
yes just to practice okay well you sound
great so far so really thank you yeah
um and so i had another question for you
oh you're yes yes i'm in school right now
um i'm in class eight
okay can you hear me if those are the
same hello i can hear you can you hear me
um yes yes i can hear you now okay
can you hear me okay yes i can
yes okay so can you tell me where are
you from yeah so i'm um my name is tori
and i'm 22 yeah um i'm from the united states
so i am from tennessee which is like the
southeast of the us and i was born there raised
there and i stayed there all the way up until
um i graduated college so lived in nashville i
lived in one city for my whole life and then for
college i moved to another city in the same state
and went to college there um so i studied spanish
and education so i can speak spanish as well um
and i let's say oh i graduated last april and then
i worked in the us kind of as like a spanish
teacher for a little while and in september
i moved to spain so i live in spain now so right
now you're a spain yes yes that's nice it's cool
it's really cool i grew up somewhere really really
small i grew up in a super like super tiny town
and then i moved to madrid which is the capital of
spain and it is like a huge city by comparison and
so it's been really amazing for me i feel like
there's like so much to do and so much to see
all the time um so i really like living here and
here i work as an english it's i work as like a
language assistant um teaching english and i work
with like really really really young children
so i work with four-year-olds and
i don't like colors and letters and
how to write their names um all of that
different stuff and then i'm studying
my master's degree here as well
so busy busy busy yeah i like um
are an inspiration to me because i also
live in a really really small town and yes
i have to go to a huge city after you know
i graduate maybe or i have to move to some
huge city afterwards so yes i'm also a little bit
scared about what is going to happen over there
yeah well i was so scared about moving here
because i had never visited spain before
but it's been fun it's it's a good
experience to like be away from my
family and like have to be independent and so
if you're thinking about like studying abroad
or just like going and traveling for a
little while um i would definitely recommend
do you know so i know that you said that you're
only uh in eighth grade but um do you have idea
what you might want to do when you're older um
well not really i say um i would go in the path
of science because i really really love science
um but after that i don't know what i'm going to
become whether in the research line or medical
line or i have i will think that in the future
oh yes you have a lot of time you have a lot of
time but you said that you like science so do
you like like biology or like chemistry um biology
biology is my favorite subject ever that's so fun
i am horrible at science so i really respect
that because whenever i'm trying to think about
how old i was when i had to take biology for the
first time i think i was 15 and i've always been
like really good with the rest of my classes and
i remember i think i made like a c in my biology
class or something and i was so upset about it
because i i just like could not my brain could not
understand some of the stuff that i was learning
um now i think it's like a little bit more
interesting um my like partner he works in the
sciences and he'll like explain things to me some
yeah well you know if you have
a little interest in it then
yes yes right totally
yes i can hear you i cannot hear you can you
hear me oh no i can hear you yes what about now
hello hear me
oh no yes yes can you hear me now
okay okay yes yes okay it's fine now
what were you saying just like being
interested in it do you feel like it
makes it easier for you to like learn
some of the stuff because you like it
yes yes of course because you know when
you're interested in a subject you automa
automatically get addicted to it and yes it
works because like uh that's me in history
that you said you are in biology because like
in history like i don't understand that even
a little bit of it what is happening so well
yeah you know sometimes i do get a little bit
of interest and i love to read it but most of
the time it is like just memorizing the stuffs
yes history is also really hard for me because of
the like memorization for us like we would have to
memorize all sorts of like years and oops dates
that stuff happened and i okay i could not tell
you now anything that i learned like in history
class um but that's cool that's cool that you at
least like have an idea and you know what you like
and that kind of thing um because i think whenever
i was in school like when i was your age i had no
idea what i wanted to do when i was older so if
you have an idea it like helps kind of guide your
path um and you were saying you wanted to move
have you thought about like studying abroad um can
you do that in like high school there um no not
really i have not really thought about it right
now um i would see where my destiny takes me but
um well let's see what happens because you know
if i get some you know there are some scholarships
and all that so if i get that maybe i will move
there but maybe after graduation just not afraid
i understand and do you think um what was i gonna
ask oh have you ever traveled outside of india
yes yes a lot of places like um china and then
europe i have traveled a lot of places in europe
then dubai maldives um then bali singapore yes is
awesome that's so fun you traveled to many more
places than i have have you ever visited the us no
i haven't but i'm eagerly looking forward to visit
it because you know i've heard a lot about it and
i also know a lot geography about it so where are
these popular places and all those so yes i am
really looking forward to visit it someday yes
yes no have you ever um visited spain too have
you ever visited spain at all no i haven't oh
it's okay it's okay spain's a really cool place to
visit um i think even after i move away from here
i'll probably come back and visit like just like
a tourist because it's a super super cool country
um that's really cool that you've been to all
of those places and i think that like the next
i'm a teacher i don't think i'm ever gonna
get rich but whenever i save up some money
i would really like to travel to asia um because
i are like southeast asia because i talk to so
many people all the time from like japan vietnam
like thailand all these different places and for
people in other parts of the world it's like super
cheap to travel to somewhere like thailand and so
um i need to save up some money and go because in
the culture i mean even where you're at in india
it's so different than like the culture that i
grew up with and it really interests me and um
like being here in spain even it's still very
westernized so it's honestly like some things are
different than they are in the us but some things
are and so i would like to visit somewhere that's
like really different you know yes because
in india everything is different from the us
like you know the culture is totally different
over here our eating styles everything is
different our clothing habits everything asian
countries have a lot in common i would say
like you know japan um then thailand india
china and all of these they have a little common
but um well i'd not say that they have a
lot of common with the western countries
yes exactly exactly and that's the thing like
europe and the us kind of have together but
anyways we only have like 40 seconds but it
was so nice to meet you and to talk to you
um yes i hope that you have a
wonderful rest of your night
yes you do awesome thank you bye bye