Greetings to all of you.
You must be wondering
what I am doing here.
I'm neither the protagonist
nor the antagonist.
The story of the film takes us to
London, Turkey, Pakistan..
..and many other countries.
So, you may not be able to understand
the languages..
..spoken by different nationalities.
We could've provided subtitles, but
visuals and audio have different impact.
So, we've made the characters
speak in Hindi language..
..so that you can enjoy
each and every scene in the film..
..and understand it well.
Don't move from your seats as you're
going to watch a sensational movie.
Enjoy. Thank you.
Send this file to the Crime Branch.
- Okay, sir.
Hello.
They are the two Algonia murder suspects.
The Istanbul police headquarters
has announced..
..a reward of 50,000 lira to the person
who can share their information.
Look for them in that direction.
- Okay, sir.
Come with us quietly. Come on.
Get in the car.
Okay, I'll handle everything.
Don't worry.
We've got the girl.
We'll find the man too.
I'll call you as soon as we get him.
Okay, sir.
C'mon speak up. Where is he?
You've so many sidekicks.
Tell them to find him.
- Shut up!
How dare you argue with me?
You've two options.
First, you call him here
and we'll set you free or..
..I'll kill both of you here.
Anything else?
When he'll come you won't be left with
any option as it'll be time for action.
Shut up!
I've easily caught you.
Now you know how powerful I am.
I caught you. It's his turn now.
What did you say?
You think you found me?
It's completely opposite of
what you think.
He sent me here to find you.
Call him. Let's see how powerful he is.
He has travelled a distance of
6000 km to find the truth.
He can definitely travel
one kilometer to get to you.
Your boss is here.
C'mon tell me who you work for
and who is the mastermind.
Speak up or you'll die.
You won't be spared.
C'mon speak up.
If I don't tell you then you'll kill me
and if I tell you then you'll be killed.
It's your turn to die now.
Hello. Greetings.
- How are you?
Hello. Hello.
- We haven't seen you for a long time.
I was busy.
Hello.
- Hello.
Offer them tea.
Please attend the other guests too.
- Okay.
Hello. How are you?
- Hello.
He'll soon be here.
Hello.
- Hello. How are you?
Please remain seated.
Hello.
- Brother, why are you waiting here?
I'm not Shravan's friend right now.
I've come to meet the Deputy CM
to discuss business.
Doesn't matter if it's business
or personal matter. Come inside.
Come on.
- Okay, let's go.
Tie it properly.
Tie the laces properly, dad.
How will I tie the laces
if you move so much, son?
You're the Deputy CM
but at home you're attending your son.
Take it. - Auntie, he didn't do
my homework properly.
The teacher scolded me because of him.
This is his punishment.
Are you going to expose me
before everybody? - Look there.
Hi Deepak!
- Hello.
Bye, my child.
- Bye, dad.
Come.
- Guddu, take your bag.
Dad loved your solar project.
It'll get approved today.
Shravan, I incurred a lot of loss
in business.
I would've gone bankrupt.
But, you helped me as a true friend.
You've done a favour by giving me
this project worth 4000 crores.
Thanks for being a true friend.
Deepak, my dad is the CM
but I neither took any favour from him..
..nor did he do any favour to me.
I'm breaking the rule for the first time.
I know it very well.
The big players of the business
were after this project.
But, you helped me bag the project.
Thank you, bro.
That's okay.
Work with diligence and honesty.
After all it's a matter of my reputation.
- Of course.
Come and meet my dad.
- Yes.
Come in, son.
I'm signing your file.
This is going to be
my last signature as the CM.
Why are you saying so, uncle?
Didn't you friend tell you anything?
- No.
I'm planning to put forward my son
as the CM candidate in the next election..
..and retire from politics.
How long will old people like us
hamper the career of young people?
Only young people can bring
about significant changes.
Take this.
The government has given you this project.
You'll be responsible
for the success of this project.
I won't disappoint you.
Deepak, you're really lucky for me.
- Why? What happened?
The IDM party is ready for an alliance
with our party in the next election.
National leader Mr. Indra Gupta
will come to our state on..
..the 10th of next month for
the joint conference of both the parties.
Is that true?
- Yes, dad.
We've only twelve days
to prepare for the meeting.
We must start the preparations
in full swing.
Hand over all the responsibilities to me.
I'll bear all the expenses.
That's great. Are you bribing us
for giving you the tender?
Oh God! What are you saying?
- What else?
Deepak, dishonest people
will try to buy your honesty.
A weak person will sell himself.
One party will offer bribe
and the other one will accept it.
Ignore all this
and focus on the project.
We'll handle the conference. Got it?
Uncle.. uncle.. I didn't mean this.
Politics and government are
two different things.
Bro, I've started
a new ac manufacturing unit.
If you've no objection then I would
arrange the ac for the conference hall.
I've no problem in buying AC from you.
Send your invoice and take the payment.
- Okay.
Hello.
What did you say?
Parade about turn.
- Right. Left. Right.
I'm Lieutenant General MJ Rehman.
I'm the chief of Subhash.
She's Diya.
She's was Subhash's partner
in the operation led by him.
Please come in. Subhash is inside.
What happened to him?
Two days back he made a plan
to wipe out..
..a terrorist gang positioned
in the borders.
The operation was successful but
on his way back he got shot in the leg.
Subhash.. Subhash..
what has happened to you?
What has happened to you, my son?
- Subhash.
He's in induced coma
for the last two days.
Don't worry.
- Don't worry, dad.
Nothing will happen to brother.
Oh God! What has happened to him?
Who shot my brother-in-law?
I hope you got the answer.
Did you think that
I've come here as I'm concerned?
I've come to India
only to dance in your funeral.
Sister, did you see how much
your husband loves Subhash?
Why won't he love him?
They're good friends
since their college days.
My brother-in-law,
if I find the man who shot you..
..I'll treat him as God
and worship him lifelong.
My life is in mess
and you've a rocking life. Huh?
Sister, please don't marry him.
You'll be ruined.
Subhash, don't give unwanted advice
since you didn't get leave.
Please keep quiet. It's better to be
a spinster than to marry this fellow.
He's a duffer.
He was my senior in college.
But, he failed and became my junior.
How can you think of keeping
such a beautiful girl unmarried?
Her smile can kill anybody.
I don't go to the borders
to fight like you.
I'm in a MBC, ac office,
posh house, posh cars.
Sister, can't you see his buckteeth?
Why? Do you want me
to peel carrots for you?
Your sister fell in love with
my talent and not teeth.
Isn't it?
- Please keep quiet.
She's willingly marrying him.
- No!
Priest, carry on with the rituals.
Sister, don't let him tie
the marital chain.
I won't spare him.
Sister, don't do this. Stop!
Sister, please stop.
Don't let him tie the marital chain.
Mission accomplished.
Mission over and not accomplished.
To hell with him.
People spend their wedding night
with their wife..
..but I spent it in a dental hospital.
What has happened to
my dear brother-in-law?
Excuse me. The patent needs rest.
- Okay.
Let Subhash take rest.
Please take him out.
Brother-in-law, you've gone into coma.
I'll go and meet the doctor.
Get well soon.
I've got the holy vermilion from
the temple of the Goddess.
I promise that
I won't let anything happen to you.
I saw how crazy you
were to save your sister's life.
Since then I went crazy for you.
But, I never had the courage
to express my feelings to you.
I forget to breathe when I see you.
Do you know three months back
on your birthday I went to your room?
I had decided to express my love for you.
But, you were in deep sleep.
I was confused
and didn't know if I should wake you.
I mustered a lot of courage
and kissed you.
I also said 'I love you'.
But, you didn't feel anything.
I'm going to repeat the same thing
as I say 'get well soon'.
And this time too you won't find out.
Madam, please don't disturb the patient.
What's this, nurse? Why didn't you come
after a couple of seconds?
I missed a kiss from her.
I had to give in to
all of Subhash' demands.
He didn't leave me with any option.
I'm really sorry.
Subhash, what kind of
immature behavior is this?
There were 45 terrorists
in the terrorist camp.
I've wiped them out
with zero casualties.
I'm going to get the gallantry award
Keerti Chakra for it after two days.
When I was in school
dad never saw me getting any award.
So, I had to stage this drama.
This will help him attend the function
and also take a break from his busy life.
That's good. But, you scared us.
It has helped me.
Now I know how much you all love me.
I was joking in the hospital.
- Hey you..
I swear on your uncle.
- Was it a joke?
Yes. Of course.
A terrorist like Syed Ibrahim Malik
has no right to live in Pakistan.
He's a stigma for our nation.
Terrorists like him defame
the entire community.
Brother..
- Yes, tell me.
My father is inside.
I'm from Karachi.
'What's the problem of
the ruling party that..'
What do you want from me?
- He's member of this party.
Brother, the meeting is soon
going to get over. Where were you?
We'll protest.
I request all of you not to spare
terrorists like him.
Hey stop! Who are you?
From where have you come?
- Over there..
Stop! Hey stop! Catch him!
Hey, catch him!
- Stop him!
Hey stop!
- This nation is ours..
Hey, catch him!
Who is he?
- Back off.
Catch him!
He has shot him.
Run!
- What's going on?
Run! Run!
Greetings!
- Greetings!
Malik!
You dared to plan
an explosion in our country.
We've given you shelter
but the Pakistan government..
..doesn't allow you to
do whatever you wish.
If we remove the security cover
from here for a moment..
..the Indian government
will trace you and kill you.
He's the fake one.
The one with squint eyes.
Where 's the real Malik?
Taheer!
Don't you apply kohl in your eyes?
You can't even distinguish between
the real and the fake one.
Malik, stop this.
Have you forgotten your limitations?
Taheer..
Taheer, I despise
if anybody challenges me..
..or speaks to me in loud voice.
You've killed the opposition leader
and landed us in trouble.
You all made me carry out
seventeen blasts in my country.
Can't I plan one explosion
in your country?
Neither you nor your government
is looking after me as a favour.
I help you earn crores
and so you look after me.
You're a watchman and do your job.
Out.
Taheer, don't forget that I'm an NRI.
Non-reliable Indian.
Goodbye.
My dear sisters and brothers,
I'm very glad to see all of you here.
Sir, Malik used to work for us.
Now he has gone out of control.
We need to tame him with force.
We'll do that very soon.
- But when, sir?
The election in India
will take place soon.
The leader of IPTP is Indra Gupta.
As per the latest exit polls
he may be the next PM of India.
If that happens then Malik
will be traced and killed even..
..if he's in Pakistan
or in any other part of the world.
I promise all of you that India's
most wanted criminal Syed Ibrahim Malik..
..will be brought back to India
in thirty days.
If anybody else tries to spread
terrorism in India again..
Yes, tell me.
- The speech is awesome, Mr. Varma.
It means you're watching the television.
But, don't pay heed to his words.
Concentrate on the party alliance.
Don't worry,
the conference is going to be great.
But Mr. Varma, there are two areas
in your list where we can face problems.
I'll speak with Mr. Gupta about it.
You plan the conference.
Okay, sir. Jai Hind.
Thanks, Subhash.
Political stress had robbed your dad
and brother of their peace of mind.
Look how relaxed
they are because of you.
Coffee?
Sister-in-law, didn't you tell your sister
that I prefer tea to coffee?
Go and get tea for me.
Why are you standing so far?
Do you want me to drink it with a straw?
Come close to me.
Hey shy lady, your mission
in the hospital was incomplete.
Complete it now.
- Only after marriage.
Will your husband allow all this?
It is a joke.
Enough of all this.
It's just a kiss. C'mon kiss me.
Kiss?
The soldier is getting ready
to kiss. Wait.
Then why were you trying to kiss me
the other day?
That's because you were in deep sleep.
I was sleeping that day.
But, today I'm awake.
The mark of the kiss
I gave that day is still there.
Find it and then
I'll do whatever you say.
How can the mark of the kiss
be still there after three months?
Hey! I've overheard everything.
What's this kiss story?
Is he disturbing you?
I was watching something. Tik Tok.
- Tik Tok?
Yes, Tik Tok.
- That's a banned app.
Which movie is going on here?
Why are you looking here and there?
Which film is it?
- Blue Lagoon.
But, it was not remade in Hindi.
It was something else. Right?
- Hold this.
C'mon tell me.
How dare you interfere
in somebody's privacy?
I can see that you've started speaking
a lot these days.
If you speak again
then I'll dance of your funeral. Got it?
What's wrong?
So, you'll worship the man who shot me?
- Friend!
Keep your mouth shut as long as I'm here.
- Don't hit me.
Get lost.
I still have a doubt.
Say it.
How can the kiss mark be still intact
after three months
Hey you!
- Don't get angry.
Have a cold drink.
- Get lost.
He uses his hands a lot.
Did she kiss with lipstick on her lips or
did she use the indelible electoral ink?
You're a strange man.
Why do you always argue with my brother
and then keep running from him?
Darling, I never hide after an argument.
I stay away from him so that
we don't get into another argument.
He has been harassing me
for the last ten years.
He's the youngest
and the most pampered one.
Always accept his point of view.
- What?
Give him whatever he wants. Now go.
My shy girl, the indelible electoral ink
doesn't last this long..
..how will the lipstick mark stay?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Trying to harass me?
Not at all.
Look for it properly.
- You're very stubborn.
Okay, c'mon kiss me quickly
and I'll check later. - No.
If you don't then I'll kiss you.
If I kiss you I'll kiss anywhere.
Feeling shy?
Okay, I'll close my eyes.
C'mon kiss me quickly.
You want me to kiss you?
If you don't kiss still I count three
then I'll kill you.
Pervert army-man. He's a lustful man.
One.
Give him whatever he wants.
Two. Three.
Hey you! You kissed me?
Your sister told me
to give you whatever you want.
Do you've common sense?
Will you jump into the fire
if she says you to do so?
Are you an idiot?
Does a man kiss another man?
I need to take bath now.
What do I do?
Can you hear me now?
Mr. Varma's call.
Hello.
Shravan, cancel the conference.
What happened, sir?
What's the problem?
We've report from
the intelligence department..
..that Mr. Gupta's life is in danger.
That's the reason.
There'll be commotion within the party
if this meeting doesn't take place.
The media will make our life hell.
Don't worry.
Our state is absolutely safe.
He'll be safe here. Okay?
Sir, please don't cancel the conference
under any circumstance.
If you take the responsibility,
I've no problem. Okay?
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
And now Mr. Jagdish Shukla of
2012 batch Dehradun regiment..
Hello.
- Hello. welcome, sir.
..will receive the gallantry award
from the honourable minister.
Take a seat.
I'm very happy.
It's going to be great fun.
Hey Diya!
- Yes.
Have you got it?
Give it to me.
..Dehradun regiment..
..will receive the gallantry award
from the honourable minister.
For whom did you get this?
- It's a secret.
Wait for few minutes.
What's the need for this suspense?
We're in the same regiment
for the last three years.
I'm aware of your feelings.
Why are you being so formal
with the proposal?
You can say it here.
She's cooking her love story.
I wish I had worked on my body.
Now I call Colonel Subhash,
2013 batch Ooty regiment..
..to receive the gallantry award
Keerti Chakra.
Go.
- Kiss me first.
Col. Subhash. Col. Subhash.
What's wrong with him?
- Where is he?
Please go.
Col. Subhash.
Where is he? Where did he disappear?
- Col. Subhash, please come on the stage.
Brother..
- Yes.
..clean your cheek, there's lipstick on it.
- Sorry.
I won't spare you.
Subhash is coming.
Absolutely fine.
Congratulations.
Hello. How are you?
- Many congratulations.
Everything is fine.
Good morning, sir.
I've an important information.
- Okay.
Your friend Deepak Mehta
left the country last night and escaped.
What are you saying?
Where did he escape?
He took a loan of 4000 crores
for the government tender.
As soon as he got the money
he left the country.
Are you sure? Is the news confirmed?
- Yes, I'm sure. It's confirmed.
Brother, any problem?
- Yes? No.
Commissioner, don't worry.
- Yes.
I'll look into this matter.
We'll discuss about this
after the conference. - Okay, sir.
Do something.
Try to contact Deepak.
- Hello.
Madam, this way. Come this way.
The arrangements are quite grand.
- Yes, it's impressive.
Hi! I've found it.
I've found it.
Sir, CM sir has arrived.
- Okay. He has arrived.
Brother, please take care of things here.
I'll be back. - Okay.
C'mon hurry up. CM sir is here.
Glory to our CM.
Glory to Mr. Gupta.
Thank you.
- Welcome sir.
Welcome, sir.
Hail Mr. Gupta.
Glory to our CM.
- Glory to Mr. Gupta.
Sir, the phone of Deepak sir
is switched off.
Keep trying. It's important.
- Okay, sir.
Welcome everybody.
Politicians have the bad reputation
of misusing their power..
..to amass huge wealth.
Once they are in power they misuse
the black money to stay in power.
My motto is to serve
my country selflessly.
When I'll retire from politics in future
I won't have a house of my own.
I'll shift to a small government quarter.
I'm sure that my son, my successor
will walk on the path of truth.
With your permission I would
request him to take the administrative..
..responsibility of this state.
Congratulation.
All the best.
Greetings. Thanks to all of you.
I'm here only because of the principles
and teachings of my father.
I'll be dedicated to the service of the
people of my state till my last breath.
Mira..
Hey listen to me..
I'll hit you.
- Please.
What is it?
- Mira, Subhash is calling you.
Check your message.
Son..
- Yes, father.
Today is a very important day for us.
What happened?
- I've forgotten my phone in the car.
I'll get it.
Hurry up. Sir's speech has started.
- Yes.
It's going to be a great one.
We're going to enjoy it. Hurry up.
Madam, you?
- Actually I forgot my phone in the car.
Okay, I'll get it for you.
- No.
I know that you're very eager
to hear brother's speech.
I'll get it.
- Okay, madam.
Let's go.
- They won't let me romance properly.
Everybody should get their due respect.
This is what we aim to achieve.
Where is Mira?
She went to the parking to get her phone.
We aspire for the
development of our society.
Where are you going?
- To make a call. - Okay.
Sorry, madam. Is he blind? Idiot!
Hey!
Why are you late?
There's police everywhere.
Okay, give me the phone.
How come someone is calling on
this number?
Oh no! I'm in trouble.
I banged with a girl on the way
and our phones got exchanged.
Do you think this is a joke?
The number that'll cause a blast
on the stage is in that phone.
How will the explosion take place
without the phone?
Go and get the phone
before the speech ends.
Look there. She's the girl.
Give my phone. My phone.
Hey you!
The police are coming.
Excuse me. What are you doing here?
We're from the catering service.
Nobody is allowed to stay here.
- Okay, sir.
Get in the car and leave immediately.
- okay, I'll leave.
What happened? Where is she?
- She hit me and escaped.
You go in that direction and
I'll go in this direction. - Okay.
Madam, what's wrong with you?
What do you want to say?
Who is there?
Now, I request respected Mr. Gupta
to come on stage and speak few words.
Greetings to everybody.
Respected Mr. KRK..
Where did she disappear?
- I don't know.
Yes, sister.
- Where are you?
Dad is looking for you.
Come here immediately.
Did Mira reach there?
Hello. Hello.
Madam, our phone is with her.
Don't let her go.
Our government will give
equal facilities to all states.
We'll try to solve the water problems
that's been going on for years.
We've planned to set up
a new medical college here.
Deepak, hello..
Shravan, listen to me.
Where are you?
- Stop asking about me.
Get out of there immediately. Come on.
People are speaking ill things about you.
Shravan, please try to understand.
Your life is in danger.
What nonsense?
We'll finish the terrorists.
You don't have time.
Get out of there. Get out.
Look what has happened to Mr. Gupta.
He showed faith in us.
We were responsible for his safety.
Look what has happened?
Mr. Gupta! Mr. Gupta!
Brother..
Subhash..
No!
It's believed that politicians and not
terrorists are involved in this mishap.
Stay connected.
Hello. Hello. Yes, it's confirmed.
We've got the medical report.
He died on the spot.
No.. no.. they used hydro-med.
It was fitted in the ac
and it caused the explosion.
Okay, I'll do it.
This incident has caused
an uproar in the entire nation.
We've orders from the high command
that his body be taken to Delhi,.
How can we do that?
- Shut up.
He died in our state.
- I said, shut up.
Sir, please listen to me.
Damodar, arrange a private jet
at the airport.
Please listen to me.
- Please take him out.
This is an insult to our state.
- Sir, please come with us.
Please come.
What's our fault?
Please go from here, sir.
- What happened?
The circumstances are not favourable.
Your safety is very important.
Get out of here immediately.
- Okay.
What's going on?
Subhash, the circumstances
are very critical.
Your safety is my duty.
Please don't act stubborn.
Please go from here.
Is my safety more important
than his life?
Are my party workers safe?
Ten people died in the bomb blast.
Besides that fifteen people
were killed in the stampede.
Where are their bodies?
In the next block of this hospital.
Sir, we'll handle it.
- Forget it.
Sir..
- Sir..
What's going on?
Sister-in-law..
- Subhash, Mira hasn't reached home.
I failed to connect her on phone.
Is she with you?
- No. She is not with me.
She must be stuck somewhere.
I'll wait for her.
We couldn't identify the deceased yet.
The officers are busy
trying to identify them.
What happened to my husband?
I'm ruined.
How will I live?
Look what happened.
Brother!
She was his fiancée.
Look what has happened.
How did this happen?
We found her body behind the stage.
She went to the parking lot
to get her phone.
She got killed in the stampede.
As per postmortem report
she died of choking and strangulation.
Down with him. Down.
What's happening, son?
I don't know.
Sir, we've deployed
two more units of police force.
Please stay here with your family
till the matter settles.
Forget it. first tell me
what's going on outside.
Nobody has the courage
to tell you directly.
You watch it on the television.
As per our reports the death of Mr.
Indra Gupta has led to riots everywhere.
It's being suspected that the Deputy CM
is involved in the blasts.
It's not an assumption, it's the fact.
Deepak Mehta
and the Deputy CM are close friends.
He helped Deepak get a loan of
4000 crores to plan this attack.
If Deepak hadn't left the country
then he would've exposed..
..the opposition and shut the case.
But, what will the deputy CM gain
by killing a politician?
Death of a national leader
will garner sympathy votes for him.
The CM doesn't want to take any risk in
the first election his son will contest.
Do you know that m Shravan got
a call just before the blast?
The call was from nobody else
but Deepak Mehta.
It's a confirmed information.
The CBI should be handed over
the investigation of this case.
I've proof of my innocence.
Shravan, get out of there quickly.
Come on.
What nonsense are you speaking?
Shravan, your life is in danger.
Santram, arrange a press conference
in our house in the evening.
What are you saying?
We haven't bid farewell to
our deceased daughter yet.
Why do you want to call for a press
conference under these circumstances?
It's useless to douse the fire after
everything has turned into ashes.
Sir, I'm here.
The meeting hasn't started yet.
Subhash, your brother went to his room
after announcing the press meet.
All the reporters are here.
We've been continuously
knocking on his door..
..but he isn't answering.
I'm feeling sacred.
Sir.. sir, please open the door.
Please open the door.
- Sir, open the door. - Step back.
What happened, sister-in-law?
He isn't opening the door.
- Brother... brother...
Brother!
The deputy CM committed suicide
in his house today.
As per our sources the deputy CM
was involved in Mr. Gupta's murder.
We haven't been able to solve
the conspiracy yet.
The mystery is getting deeper with time.
The police is trying to
calm down the crowd.
After this incident
all the party offices of MSC party..
Dad..
A son carries the bier of his father.
But today a father will carry
the bier of his son.
Subhash, the crowd
is getting out of control.
They can do anything.
Please take the body
from here immediately.
I've a request.
It's going to be risky to go
from the front gate..
..so I suggest you go
through the back gate.
What nonsense, Bharadwaj!
Repeat it again.
I'm saying this for your safety.
The situation is critical.
Please try to understand.
Is my son a thief?
Is he a terrorist? Or is he an orphan?
Why should we take the back door?
- Please try to understand, sir.
They think you're the culprit.
There are thousands of people
waiting outside.
Many of them have weapons.
We're helpless.
People are going out of control.
To hell with you.
You're useless.
I'll call the higher authorities.
No, sister-in-law.
They're taking my son's dead body
as if he's an orphan.
He was going to begin his career.
Bye, brother-in-law.
Subhash, sister-in-law didn't eat anything
since the last two days.
She's sitting quietly.
I'm worried.
Please go and talk to her.
He was a virtuous and an honest man.
He never wished ill for anybody.
He was innocent like a child.
But, the people who considered him God
started hating him in a day.
They're cursing him.
Life has become meaningless.
Don't spare the people who killed my dad.
Please make him cry
the way we're crying.
Yes, tell me.
Subhash, do you remember the number that
Mira wrote on her hand before she died?
We've found that car.
We've also found the place from
where the car was bought.
Come fast here.
Punish him, uncle.
Two days back a lay and two men
bought a van from here.
The documents provided by them are fake.
None of the CCTV cameras
installed here is working.
We've got a small footage of the exit.
But, their faces are not clear.
Sir, pause and rewind.
Stop. Zoom the image.
I've seen this somewhere.
Bharat, I've seen her at home
on the day brother died.
Who can she be?
Besides your relatives
the party workers were present there.
The only unknown people present there
were from media and press.
As far as I remember
everybody signed before entry.
Look there. Look carefully.
She's the one.
She came inside,
but didn't sit with the other journalists.
After brother committed suicide
everybody left.
She came out from inside
and merged with the crowd.
She came with everybody
and left with them.
But, she was missing
for around fifteen minutes..
..exactly at the same time
when my brother died.
This girl is the common factor in the
deaths of Mr. Gupta, Mira and brother.
She came in as a part time
photographer with Malti..
..a top news channel reporter.
If we get Malti we'll get her too.
Sir, we went to the news channel's office
and enquired about Malti.
Malti hasn't come to office
since the past two days.
She is not going to office. But why?
We haven't found the reason yet, sir.
She went to attend your
brother's press conference.
But, it was her dead body
that came home.
Her scooter was knocked down by a truck.
Did we raise her for this day?
Brother, does she have a friend
who has a tattoo on her neck?
The girl with a tattoo on her neck?
- Yes.
She befriended her
a couple of days back.
She was very sweet.
She went as a photographer
with Malti the day your brother died.
But, she never came back after that day.
Brother, can we get your daughter's
diary and phone?
Malti didn't write diary.
Her phone broke
the day she met with the accident.
Subhash, this phone is
our last hope in this investigation.
She's very smart.
She has already formatted the phone.
There's no information in it.
I knew it.
There's always backup in Google drive.
Try from her email.
- Okay.
Yes! We've got the backup files.
- Copy them.
What?
Oh no! This girl is very smart.
She's a step ahead of us.
She's hacking all the data.
She deleted the later files at first.
It'll be difficult to trace her.
- But, we'll definitely find her.
Try to trace her user location.
- Sure.
Mexico. It means she's there.
Iran.
Indonesia.
London.
Sri Lanka.
Five locations at the same time.
She's brilliant.
She's using a proxy server to confuse us.
Only one out of these five locations
is the correct one.
But, it's difficult to say
which one is her actual location.
London.
How do you know?
Do you remember the footage
on which she was signing the register?
I saw her phone in the footage.
There were two time zones on that phone.
The time difference
was of four and half hours.
Among all these five locations
the location which has a time difference..
..of four and half hours is London.
Check the lists and find all
the passengers who travelled to London..
..on the day my brother died.
We'll find her on the list.
Sir, the girl left for London that day
on British Airways.
All her details are here in this file.
Her name is Kayra.
She's a professional killer.
The most wanted criminal by the Interpol.
As per our information
she's based in London.
But, we've neither found her address
nor her next target.
Now she's my target.
How will you find her without any clue?
Her passport is also fake.
It's obvious that the address mentioned
in it is also fake.
How will you trace her?
I've no option.
The absconding can escape
anywhere in the world..
..but the person chasing
has only one way.
Move.
You've arrived at your destination.
Who placed the electric pole here?
He looks like a human.
Yes? What do you want?
- Kayra?
18-12-79, Down Street. Correct?
The address is right but the girl
you're looking for doesn't reside here.
Are you an Indian?
- Why?
Didn't you hear the language
I just spoke in?
I'm a pure Indian. From Mumbai.
What's the problem?
- Somebody gave me this address.
Don't look at her, she's an old lady.
Close the door, old man.
Please listen to me.
Can you help me find her?
I swear on God that
I don't know the girl.
Four people had come before you
to enquire about the girl.
But, I don't know what went wrong.
All four of them died.
But, you seem to be from a decent family.
I suggest that
you book your return tickets and leave.
If you jump you'll reach India.
You're an Indian.
Wouldn't you like to help me?
Do you want me to leave my job
for the girl?
I can offer you coffee on the way.
But, you've to pay the bill.
There's nothing in the bedroom.
Let's go.
Let me introduce myself. I'm Subhash.
- I know.
You're a colonel in the Indian army.
2013 batch. Ooty regiment.
Your phone number is 9444131157.
You've an account in Dehradun's
Kendriya bank. You're from Valli.
Your dad is the CM of Tamil Nadu.
Is that enough or shall I tell you
what's in your horoscope?
How do you know so much?
- It's my job to find details of people.
I'm a professional hacker.
You don't look like one.
- Why? Does a hacker look special?
You look like a comedian.
This is the reason
why I don't help people.
The doorbell of my house
has a fingerprint scanner.
As soon as you rang the bell
I got your history.
Do you get it now?
So, it must be very easy
for you to trace a girl.
It's not as easy as you think it to be.
If you want to catch a shark
then you need bait.
We need data. Got it?
There's a flight to India in the evening.
Leave.
What happened? Got fever?
Do you remember the old couple
who lives next to your flat?
They're my landlords.
What do you want from them?
I need their phone number.
So, your preferences
have changed drastically. Huh?
When I rang your doorbell its
they who opened the door before you.
They're an old couple.
If they were based in India
they would be busy watching TV soaps.
They don't get that here,
so they were looking for gossip material.
I saw a tattoo design
which was also on the girl's neck.
Kayra killed many people.
I'm sure the old couple
has links with her.
What can I do?
If we get their phone number
then you can trace the calls..
..made by them in the last half an hour.
It's a small job but
I need good payment for it. Okay?
Don't stare at me.
If you pay then I'll switch on my laptop
or I've lot of work.
Done. Just do it.
Soldier, they made only one outgoing call
in the last half an hour.
I've messaged you the number.
Check it.
I got a message that 50,000
has been debited from my account.
Don't worry, I took the money.
It's my fees
which I've already taken from you.
What if you betray me later?
You've got the message
with the phone number.
I've got a call from that same number.
Hello.
Listen to me. Give him the phone.
Why? Don't you like my voice?
Idiot, just give it to him.
Brainless loser. Do as I say.
She wants to talk to you.
Speak with her.
Hello Kayra.
You've come to London to avenge
the deaths in your family. Huh?
Political power. Police power.
You had everything..
..yet I easily went there
and killed them.
This is my area.
Killing you'll be a cakewalk for me.
Stop acting smart and leave.
Where will I get Deepak Mehta?
Deepak Mehta betrayed you
but I won't betray him.
I've already traced your number.
So, it won't be difficult to trace you.
You mean call tracking. Idiot!
I'll take out the sim card and destroy it.
Who will you follow after that?
If you want you can search every lane and
alley in London for the next ten years.
It's impossible to trace me.
You can destroy your sim card and
escape anywhere as you're scared of me.
But, I'm not scared.
9444131157. This is my number.
I'll wait for you at
the Trafalgar Square tomorrow.
I'll be in a red t-shirt. Spot me.
I've no power except will power.
You're confident that
you're in your territory now.
Come and meet me.
Okay. Let's see.
What did she say?
She threatened that
she'll kill all my team members.
I'm the one in your team.
This is a serious punishment
for hacking an old woman's number.
Brother, it's your responsibility
to save my life.
There's only one solution.
- Share it quickly.
I haven't got the idea yet.
You've landed me in trouble
and you don't even have an idea.
I was spanked by lady teachers
in childhood.
And even now a woman is after my life.
Take it, bro. You too.
Take it.
Listen! I remember all your faces.
Wear them and stay here.
Anybody who doesn't wear
this will be thrashed badly.
Take it. Take it quickly.
This is only for men.
I request the women not to crowd here.
Subhash, I've distributed
the t-shirts to everybody.
I always thought that Indians are greedy
for free goodies..
..but, these foreigners
are smarter than us.
They snatched away the t-shirts from me.
Stop discussing these foreigners now.
Quietly donate the two t-shirts
you've kept for yourself.
How did he know?
This is the advantage of being tall.
I've taken out the two t-shirts.
What do I do now?
Give it to somebody and wait there.
I'll go there.
Go.
Red t-shirt.
Chief, many people are in red t-shirts.
But, I can't spot him.
You fool, he is around.
Keep everybody in conference mode.
I'll track him and then
I'll connect with you and guide you.
Yes, chief. Move it. Move it.
Okay.
- Copy.
Jack..
- Yes.
I knew that she wouldn't come.
What do I do?
Many people here are using
their cell phones.
Can you find out the source of
their conference call?
Hello I'm one and only Jack.
I'm an expert at cracking server codes.
This is the reason why
my friends call me Crack Jack.
How can you doubt my ability?
I'll find everything in two minutes.
Just wait and watch.
On your right.
200 meters away from you.
Okay. Guys, right.
Hello Subhash, four conference calls
are active here.
One is a service provider
and ten people are connected to it.
It seems to be some company meeting.
Next.
Oh God! A woman is playing with three men.
Share the location with me.
It's right in front of me.
But it's useless for you.
Shall I try to mingle with them?
- What?
I'll try to gel in with the three guys.
We're in a serious matter.
This isn't the tome to joke.
- You're so selfish.
Please think about this poor fellow.
You didn't get one girl
but I never got any girl in my life.
You're near him.
Go 70 meters to your right.
This way. Move.
Done?
- Just a second.
These people are on the call
for a long time.
One number is quite familiar.
Who are you busy talking
to instead of working?
I'll slap you hard, fatso.
- Sorry, bro. It's a mistake.
You're very close to him. 40 meters.
One more conference call is on.
I think it's an important.
It would've been great
if I could hear them.
Six men are talking to one woman.
Five of them are close to us.
Only one is in some other corner.
That's her. She's the one.
Share her location.
Wait, give me a couple of minutes.
You're only 20 meters from him.
Go straight.
Have you fallen asleep?
10 seconds more.
Let the internet do its work.
C'mon hurry up.
Why are you shouting at me?
Let Google do its job.
Found her.
There's a famous Victoria Hall
200 meters to your right.
She's over there.
Do what you want to.
Thanks, Jack.
- Where is he going?
Hey Tall fellow!
Is it a cheap phone that he left it here?
Chief, we didn't find him.
Three meters to your left.
We've found the target.
Yes, friend.
Why are you hacking the numbers?
Idiot! I'm doing my job.
- Hey you!
What are you doing?
Why are you hitting me?
Don't hit me.
- Yes, Chief.
Idiots, you got the wrong man.
He's here.
Come here quickly.
Guys, let's go.
You've turned a hacker into a joker.
Mr. Subhash, well-done.
This is a great way to express gratitude.
I'm so glad.
Chief, catch.
He won't come to save you.
So, you too don't try to save him.
C'mon tell me where Deepak is.
You can torture me and even kill me
but I'm not going to share anything.
I also follow certain principles.
- Principles?
How can a contract killer
talk about principles?
I will..
There's a message from your bank.
You're going to die in five
minutes and somebody has paid you..
..5 million dollars for your next target.
It's not for anybody else,
it's my advance payment to kill you.
It's a huge network.
If I fail to kill you there are
other people who'll be hired to kill you.
Its better you go back.
You may not get this chance again.
I'll definitely go back
but after I find Deepak.
This is not a game.
How will you find him without my help?
- I don't need your help.
Your phone is sufficient.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Subhash, please help me.
Please help me.
- Follow your principles.
I know where you'll find him.
Please save me.
Listen. Stamp her and kill her.
It should appear that she got killed
in the stampede after the blast.
Note down my order.
A scorpion soup with a snake rice.
Pack the food.
I'll send somebody
to hell and come to get it.
Why didn't you come inside to receive me?
I've come to see you
off and not receive you.
Are you joking?
- What else?
Mira and elder brother
died because of you.
You've come here to take revenge.
I'm not going to accompany you. Get lost.
Please listen..
- Subhash..
Hi Subhash!
Did she come here for vacation?
- She refused her promotion offer.
She applied for a post in
foreign affairs and came to Turkey.
I don't know why she did this.
- But, I know.
Forget all this.
I needed a break and so I came here.
But, he was saying something.
- Nothing.
When a person makes castles in the air
and thinks it's not nice..
..it causes heartbreak
and to mend the heart..
So, what's your plan?
- I'll tell you.
Has he come here to
take revenge or to romance.
Brother-in-law, listen to me.
The bank which transferred money
to Kayra to kill me is in Istanbul.
Do you know whose account it is?
- No idea.
Deepak Mehta's account.
What?
- Yeah.
We need to find his address
from his bank account details.
Brother-in-law, you'll turn into a turkey
looking for a address in Turkey.
You won't get any
address from the account.
No chance. Enjoy your vacation
and go back to your country.
Hey! You always talk shit. I will..
- He's gone crazy.
Our work will become easier
if we seek the government's help.
We can't trust anybody right now.
I tried to hack his
account to get the details.
But, I failed.
The bank's system is protected
with a strong firewall.
The passwords automatically keep changing.
The security is tight.
It's impossible to infiltrate.
Awesome! My account is in the same bank.
It means my money and I are safe.
Coffee for you.
I told you to keep your mouth shut.
Brother-in-law, why do you always hit me?
I was praising the bank's system.
Is this the way you behave
with your sister's husband?
Can you do anything just
because you're in the army?
Here's the bank's blue print.
- Okay.
What are you going to do in Turkey?
How will you get the address?
Customer details are encrypted
in the bank's main server.
We can copy them only
from the server room.
As per the bank's blue print..
..there's a basement to the left
of the bank's basement.
Is the server room located there?
I surveyed the bank.
It's a highly secured bank.
Especially the server room.
Only the security head
has the access to the room.
You can't enter without an access card.
Entry is very strict.
You can chop off his hands
but won't get the card.
The lunch time is from 1- 1:30.
He goes to the same restaurant every day.
This means that his lunch
time and venue is fixed.
It's a confirmed information.
So, we can go to the server room
when the security head goes for lunch.
Don't get so excited.
The account we want to access
should be active or it won't help.
There's one more option.
Let's call Deepak Mehta.
We'll tell him to keep his account
active and we'll access the detail.
Do you understand now that
there are loopholes in your plan?
We're planning to take
out the details from a bank.
This is not a child's play.
Keep that in mind.
He finds all our ideas useless.
You suggest something.
I'm a talkative fellow.
I can't help with any idea.
Very good idea.
The manager has a special
password for every account.
Use your talkative nature
to keep the bank manager busy..
..and make him blurt out
the password of Deepak Mehta.
I'll handle the rest.
- You'll handle it?
If I make any mistake then
remember that it's not India..
..that you bribe anybody
and get your job done.
This is Istanbul, you'll go missing.
To hell with your idea.
- Stop!
You're ruining my reputation here.
- Listen to me.
My sister told me that my brother-in-law
is brave and intelligent.
She also said that he's
the only one who could help me.
Did she really say so?
You heard it right.
My wife is devoted to her husband.
I won't spare him.
Now that your sister has said
it there's no question of going back.
Let's go and handle the bank manager.
- Let's go.
Wait and watch what I do.
Soldier, if you hear any mishap
happening inside you'll know that it's me.
Tell your sister that
I'm on a mission today. Jai Hind.
What happened? Are you okay?
Excuse me, sir. Rajesh Malhotra.
Are you an Indian?
Yes. I've been working here
for the last ten years.
I'll soon find out if you've
been here for ten days or ten years.
I need your help.
I need to confirm a payment transfer.
Why did you come to me?
You could've done it online.
I know, sir.
Did you see the speed of the internet?
You've to wait whenever
you need to download anything.
Last night I saw 'Gulabi Jawani'.
A plumber comes to repair the taps and the
auntie at home takes him to the bathroom.
That's all I saw.
The film stopped at the climax.
- Okay. Okay.
Tell me the account number.
- 75432257.
Subhash, tell him to hurry up.
I don't like the orders.
- When did I order you?
I'm not talking to you.
Has the money come to the account?
There has been no transaction
in this account recently.
Sir, please check it properly.
The person who sent the money
is from India. - So?
Does anybody lie in India?
Stop your nonsense.
It's not time for patriotism.
Concentrate on your job.
Make him open Deepak Mehta's account.
Sir, please don't mind my words.
I can tell you his account number.
Please check if he
has transferred the amount.
We can't share any details without
the permission of the account holder.
Would Dharmendra become a super-star if
he sought permission before he left home?
Would Vijay Kali be involved in a scam
if he took the bank's permission?
Who's Vijay Kali?
- He's Mallya now.
Oh please! Give me his number.
- 79573299
I've got access.
No amount was transferred
from this account recently.
Keep the account window open.
Do anything you can, but he shouldn't
log out before ten minutes. Idiot.
What? Whom did you call an idiot?
What?
- I'm the idiot. It's me.
This is going to happen
if I trust somebody.
Subhash, how long will it take?
Ten minutes.
Okay.
This is a high value account.
The account holder is an important person.
Are you sure that you were going
to get your payment from this account?
He's a strange man.
In the past he used to borrow money
from me to buy snacks.
What are you doing?
Ten minutes is enough
to make a short film.
Talking isn't as easy as hacking.
Please hurry up.
Subhash, please tell him to hurry up.
Why? What happened?
He has found out that he
doesn't have the access card.
Subhash, he's going to the bank.
Please hurry up.
I've got the access just now.
The files are getting copied.
Please try to keep him back by any means.
Impossible.
Impossible? Then I'm leaving.
- Okay.
I'll kill you. I've finished only 30%.
Manage it anyhow.
I'm not on a talk show.
Sir, you were born on 30th February. Right?
- No.
Then you were born on 29th.
C'mon show me your hand.
Diya , do something.
Sure, I'll try.
You're married yet you've
extra-marital affairs.
You're a characterless man.
How did you find out?
- I've ten years of experience.
Your wife watches the
family drama every day.
So, you go home late. Right?
Hey! Hey stop! Stop!
Stop right there.
I need to go. Leave me.
How much work is left?
40%.
What kind of misbehavior is this?
What's this?
- I didn't take this.
Your sister goes around with old men.
- Leave my hand.
Keep the money. Please let me go.
- Stop! Hey!
Your stars are in unfavorable position.
- Enough of your nonsense.
Leave my hand.
How much money was he going to give you?
- 400 dollars.
Take the money from me.
Oh my God!
Isn't there any money in the bank?
- Somebody has hacked the password.
All his money is getting transferred.
It's getting transferred
in some other account. Darn it.
What? Transfer my 400 dollars also.
- Get out.
You idiot!
- You fool!
What's going on?
- I don't know how this happened, sir.
I lost the access card.
- Where is Subhash.
Let's go.
- He hasn't come out yet.
Let's get out of here.
- Yes, let's go.
He'll get caught.
He'll be in deep trouble.
The police here are very efficient.
They'll thrash him so badly that
he won't be able to walk for months.
The culprits never repeat their mistake.
Really?
- Yes.
Walk more slowly and the
police will easily nab you.
I'm hungry. Let's eat something.
- Got it.
You'll send him to
jail and make me bankrupt.
After that you'll enjoy in Istanbul.
I had doubts on you.
You've a gang. Will you tell me..
Brother-in-law..
Could you decode it?
- I could de-code 70%
I'm tired of looking for you.
How come you are here?
Did you know that he is here?
- Of course.
This was the plan.
Everybody should be aware of the plan.
Both of you're not aware
of the actual matter.
Somebody stole 4000 crore rupees
from Deepak Mehta's account.
Do you know that?
- I know.
You know?
- I stole the money.
Did you think I took this
risk only to find an address?
Give people some money and
they'll get the address for you.
It's a matter of 4000 crores.
It's our country's money.
The amount was sanctioned by my dad.
He thought he would escape
with the money and I'll keep quiet.
I've taken the money from
Deepak Mehta's main account..
..and all the proxy
accounts linked with it.
I've returned the money to
the original bank with interest.
It means you fooled me.
You are a born fool.
I've also found his location.
Algornia.
It's not only time to
lose my job but also my life.
Why?
That territory is under
the control of the mafia, right?
Yes, brother-in-law. Neither the police
nor the army can enter that area.
It's under the mafia.
There's only one way to enter that place.
You can go there only if
a mafia personally invites you.
Diya, do you've contacts there?
No way.
Ask her. I'm living here for the
last four years and you don't even ask me.
Idiot, I'm talking about
mafia and not a vegetable vendor.
I don't know mafia but I know Sofia.
- Sofia? Who is she?
My girlfriend. She stays there.
Is it paining?
- Yes, it is.
Bloody fool. I need to maintain
safe distance from him.
Brother-in-law,
please think from my point of view.
Your sister stays in India
for eleven months in a year.
The population has increased in India.
Just imagine the extra heat
we need in cold place.
You...
- Don't hit me.
I flirt with her only virtually.
No physical. No practical.
We talk only on phone.
Tomorrow is her birthday.
She has invited me.
If you want to enjoy the
cake I'll take you there tomorrow.
I can't wait so long.
I need to go there today.
The news that his account
has been hacked must've reached him.
He must've become alert.
Before he takes his next
step we need to catch him.
Brother-in-law,
please don't tell your sister about this.
You've already thrashed me
but she'll thrash me before everybody.
My BP has shot up, my sugar levels
have increased, my hands are shivering.
Oh God! Please save me.
Soldier, you can see that mansion there.
It's the entry point of the mafia's den.
The security is very tight here.
A rose comes with thorns.
Similarly my Sofia is surrounded
by huge cactus plants.
What nonsense!
I want to meet Sofia.
Wait here.
Call Sofia and tell her that
someone has come to meet her.
He has come to meet Sofia.
- Are you going to wrestle?
Put your biceps and chest inside.
Do you know what will happen if you don't?
We'll be killed.
He's my man. Send him in.
I'm waiting for him.
- She's Sofia.
This is the voice that has made me crazy.
You've only ten minutes.
We've only ten minutes.
Follow me quietly.
Where's Sofia's house?
- It's over there.
I'm sure that Sofia will help us.
Sophie!
- Yes, please.
Hello.
Sofia.
- No, I'm her maid.
If her maid is so beautiful then
her mistress will be paragon of beauty.
Brother-in-law, where did you go?
There's trouble if he's
with me and even if he's not.
As per the map let's go to the left.
Where's Sofia?
- Wait, she's coming.
Yes! She'll come.
Are you Sofia?
Yes darling, I'm your Sofia.
Darling!
Darling, stop.
- Stop!
It's good that brother-in-law
and his girlfriend didn't see her.
We've reached.
Where is it?
Second on the left.
Wait here.
- Okay.
Deepak..
Abort.
Catch her.
Break the door.
That way.
Hold this.
Sit behind me quickly.
Go. Go fast.
Fast. Let's get out of here quickly.
Hey you!
What's going on?
You've landed me in trouble.
The police has reached my house.
- Keep quiet. Check with the card.
What are you doing?
At first they robbed the bank
and then they killed a gangster.
Oh God! Save me.
Got it.
Our guess is wrong, he's not a criminal.
He's the city commissioner of Istanbul.
What's going on?
Please tell me.
He was pretending to be blind.
He killed Deepak.
He tried to trap us first
and now he's trying to arrest us.
Why would he kill Deepak?
- I'm also thinking about the same.
I thought that Deepak
was the real culprit.
But, he was just a pawn.
If we can catch him we'll know the truth.
He's a policeman.
How will we catch him?
He'll come after us.
Hello.
The person you're looking
for is in Argu market.
C'mon tell us who you work for.
Whose plan is it?
If you don't tell us you'll die.
C'mon tell us.
If I don't tell you then you'll kill me
and if I tell you then you'll be killed.
It's your turn to die now.
No! No! I'll tell you.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
- C'mon tell me.
Malik!
Syed Ibrahim Malik.
Syed Ibrahim Malik is the
mastermind behind the attacks.
Syed Ibrahim Malik has been traced.
He's in Dubai.
Syed Ibrahim Malik is the
mastermind of Hyderabad attacks.
The number of deceased
in the blasts is over sixty now.
According to sources Ibrahim Malik
has shifted to Pakistan from Dubai.
The Pakistan government has
denied giving shelter to Malik.
After repeated pressures from India,
UN has declared Syed Malik a terrorist.
Syed Ibrahim Malik has been traced.
He's in Pakistan right now.
This is his location.
The other name for terrorism
is Syed Ibrahim Malik.
India's most wanted terrorist.
Syed Ibrahim Malik.
The search is still on.
This is totally unbelievable.
How can Malik be involved in this?
Sir, I've got this information just now.
Mr. Gupta was expected to be the
Prime Minister after the next election.
Malik knew that he
could be a threat to him.
If he had killed him in north India
then he would've been the prime suspect.
In order to avoid it
he cleverly chose our city.
The alliance meeting
gave him an opportunity.
He used both bankrupt Deepak
and professional killer Kayra..
..to kill Mr. Gupta.
He spread the rumor that my
brother was behind the conspiracy..
..so that he could win the election.
He killed my brother to prove it.
I'll accept what you
say but where's the proof.
Both Kayra and Deepak are dead.
But what about Malik? He's still alive.
What do you mean?
- I'll rest only after I catch him.
Are you joking?
We don't even know where he is.
Pakistan.
That's what we think.
Pakistan government
has denied that he's there.
They had said the same
about Osama Bin Laden.
What happened after that?
He was killed.
C'mon Subhash. That was America.
Their policy is different from ours.
I know it, sir.
I'll not go there as an army-man Subhash.
I'll go there as an ordinary man.
Our agents are posted
there for the last ten years.
But, we haven't got any
information about him till date.
Police, CD, CID, CBI,
RAW, military, intelligence, customs..
..there are several departments
and thousands of officers.
While he's just one man.
Yet we don't get any information
about him or any glimpse about him.
We always get the same
answer that he can't be traced.
Enough of this.
This is not only about
my brother or Mr. Gupta.
240 people died in the Mumbai blasts.
120 people died in Hyderabad.
Seventeen terrorist attacks were
executed in the last twenty six years.
More than seven thousand
people were killed.
Do you've an answer to anything?
Don't talk like a mad man?
If you go there then.. - I'll die. Right?
It's okay.
I'm ready to die for my country.
I understand your emotions.
But, I can't help you officially.
It's okay, sir. I can manage.
I'll go there today.
Are you sure that you want to go?
Do you think that's easy?
You're a criminal here.
It's impossible for
you to step out of Istanbul.
If you take the road then you'll
have to cross Syria, Iran, Afghanistan..
..and that too without visa.
Yes, that's what we're
exactly going to do.
I can unofficially cross that route.
As soon as you reach Pakistan
contact our agent Imran.
But, on one condition.
Our country has issues with this country.
God forbids if you get caught then..
Got it, sir.
I'll never mention your name. Thank you.
Subhash, I'll also come with you.
No. I'll do it.
This is my personal matter.
This is the reason why I'll go with you.
You didn't get her.
She's seeking your permission.
Take her with you.
How long can a honeybee
stay without a flower?
How long will you be alone?
Stop the car.
She's pregnant.
Where's the hospital?
- To the left.
Thanks, bro.
Excuse me brother,
is Nawaz road on that side?
No, it's in this direction.
- Okay. Thank you.
This way.
I want to meet Imran.
Brother is inside.
Brother, somebody has come to meet you.
Please come.
- Go in.
It's my brother-in-law's wedding in Delhi.
I want you to stitch an attire for him.
Collect it from this
address after two days.
So, you want to secretly
take Malik to India?
That's impossible.
Do you think it's as easy
as taking a parcel of food home?
Do you know that Malik
is under the control of ISIS?
Nobody except them can go near him.
I've been working here under
cover for the last ten years.
Rehman sir had given me the
assignment to prove that he lives here.
But, I got no evidence.
I've gone crazy stitching dresses
for women for the last few years.
Forget about any evidence I
couldn't even see his face till date.
Fifteen years back RAW
went to Dubai to catch him.
Later on it was found that
the person they caught wasn't Malik..
..but his lookalike.
That was it and Malik escaped
from there and came to Pakistan.
The government takes money
from him and treats him like a king.
The military provides him with security.
He's living a grand life here.
Can you show me his house?
Why is the place decked up?
Any special occasion?
I've heard that it's his daughter's
wedding after three days.
I'm sure he'll come out
during the wedding. - No.
Due to security reasons the wedding
will take place inside the house.
What are you doing here? Get out of here.
Nothing. The car broke down.
C'mon get out of here.
- Okay, sir. we're leaving.
Let's go, brother.
He's Taheer Iqbal,
Pakistan's military general.
He's in-charge of Malik's security.
The security system of this
house is divided in three layers.
The first layer is that
of the Pakistan police.
Second layer has trained
commandos from Pakistan's army.
The inner circle has the tightest
security for Malik's safety.
He's not an ordinary officer.
He's SWAT trained.
He's the one who plan
the attacks of ISIS.
He's expert in brainwashing youngsters
and making them terrorists.
It's impossible to get through
his security and meet Malik.
Everything here belongs
to my granddaughter.
Brother Taheer,
you're still in your uniform.
Come with your wife and children tomorrow.
- Yes.
Salma, keep it.
Malik, you need to postpone
the wedding for the time being.
Why? Is it for the Indian agent who has
crossed the borders and come here?
Do you think I'm a coward like you?
So, you know about him.
I get all the information
at lightning speed.
His name is Col. Subhash.
SEAT training,
19th battalion, Madras regiment.
Look at his photo carefully. Get him.
- Okay, I will.
I suggest that you shift to a
safer place before this issue is resolved.
Entire India is scared of me.
It's strange that I need to
be scared of this petty fellow now.
Your safety is my duty.
I request you shift
to the military safe-house.
Do you think you can protect me?
I've faced thousands absolutely alone.
I never sought any help.
It's my daughter's
wedding and I'm very happy.
If you spoil my mood I'll kill you.
You asked for the blue print of his house.
This is it.
The right time to kidnap
him is the wedding night.
Impossible!
Limited guests will attend the wedding.
You can't enter without an invitation.
Even if we manage to enter
how will we fool the police..
..military and personal
security and reach him.
We can shoot him from a distance
and then get killed for it.
But even that will be difficult.
It's impossible to kidnap him.
It's possible.
I've a plan.
I want to know who gave the permission
to go ahead with this mission.
Our soldier has risked his life.
He's asking for a small favour in return.
Mr. Rehman, the relation between
the two countries is already strained.
If our officer gets caught
not only the UN but the entire world..
..will support Pakistan.
We can't ruin the goodwill
of our country. No way.
Call him back right now or
I'll have to give the statement that..
..he trespassed the borders
without required permissions.
We'll be forced to give the
detail to the Pakistan embassy.
Sir, don't rush into any decision.
According to the information
we got from Subhash..
..Mr. Gupta was killed by Malik.
That's not all. A VVIP from India
is also involved with him.
But, it's very important that
we bring Malik here to prove it.
What's the plan? Share it with me.
Okay, I'll speak with the high command.
Please keep your mission on hold till then.
- Okay, sir.
Sir..
We've to keep the mission on hold until
we get permission from the government.
The mission has started.
Subhash.. Subhash..
Isn't this design nice?
Do you want to apply it?
Subhash, Malik knows that you're here.
The police is searching you madly.
The situation is getting more complicated.
The chances of the mission's
success are very less.
If we make any mistake tomorrow
none of us will be alive.
So, I can't involve you in this mission.
Diya, this is my battle.
I'll fight it alone.
You can leave.
- Doesn't matter. We'll fight together.
We may win or lose
but I'll never leave you.
Bye.
- Bye.
Who are you?
Sir.
Subhash, we've got permission
from the high command.
Thank you, sir.
But be careful, if you win it'll be
India's victory and not just yours.
But, a small mistake from your end..
..can spoil the relationship
between the countries further.
All the best, my boy.
Sir.
It's time for action.
"O Lord!"
Isn't this a nice design?
Do you want to apply it?
I'm very happy.
There should be no
loopholes in our security.
"O lord!"
Hey look there. Fire! Fire!
Why's there so much smoke here?
What happened?
The kitchen is on fire, sir.
Go and check quickly what's happening.
Yes, tell me.
Malik, I'm sure that the Indian
agent planned this fire outbreak.
Be alert and careful.
- Shut up. I can take care of myself.
You should've listened to my advice
and this wouldn't have happened.
I've got orders from higher authorities
to shift you to a safer place.
And I'm under pressure.
So, be ready.
Okay.
I'll kill him.
- Don't worry about him.
Think about your safety now.
Don't go out of the main gate.
I'm sure that he has
laid a trap for you there.
Take the rear exit.
Take the Shah Alam market route.
Move. Move. A car is coming. Move.
Step aside. Let the car go.
Close the barricade. Close it.
He's running with my car.
Catch him.
Hey Indian, stop the car.
I'll kill you. Stop the car.
Malik is in the car.
Do you want to go with me or die here?
Don't shoot. You're mistaken.
I'm his lookalike.
The original Malik is downstairs.
If you don't believe me,
I'll call him here.
Hello.
Are you sleeping downstairs?
I've an urgent work.
Come to my room immediately.
You made a mistake in hurry.
You're the original Malik.
If you were the lookalike
you wouldn't have ordered him.
Oh! You scared me.
Where do I have to go?
Taheer will be here in a few
minutes to take me to the safe-house.
If you want to stay alive
then get out of here immediately.
Your lookalike will go with Taheer.
Call him.
Hello.
You'll go with Taheer.
- Sir..
Do as I say.
- Okay.
Now move.
Come on.
You may go.
Next.
What's wrong with him?
Medical visa.
We're taking him out
for kidney transplant surgery.
Don't we get good treatment in our
country? Why do you wish to go to India?
We're getting AB negative donors
only there.
Sir..
- What is it?
This is his medical report.
I think something is wrong.
Please check it.
Hello.
Pakistan immigration.
I want to talk to you about Zaheer Iman.
He's our patient.
He has a surgery scheduled tomorrow.
What's the matter?
It's a routine verification.
Okay.
Send them.
Uncle, how is he?
- Don't worry. Malik is absolutely fine.
Don't worry, the doctors
are taking good care of him.
He's okay. Everything is fine.
Everything is okay.
Malik, are you okay?
Enter runway 25.
- Roger, entering.
We thought that he abducted the lookalike.
But, he has kidnapped the real Malik.
We've been deceived.
He has played his game really well.
He set the wedding venue
on fire to confuse us.
But he forgot that this is Pakistan.
Seal all the check-posts.
Close all possible ways.
- Yes, sir.
Is there any flight to India right now?
Sir, a flight is going to
leave for Delhi in ten minutes.
Yes.
Fax Subhash photo to the airport security.
- Okay, sir.
If they spot any person who resembles him
then he should be detained.
Remember that there should be
no mistakes. Do it fast.
FA908, enter runway.
25 main line up..
..and be ready for immediate take-off.
Roger. Copy.
FA908, you're on line get ready.
Hello.
Sir, the photo sent by you matches
with the passenger of seat number 16..
..on the flight to Delhi.
Call the ATC immediately.
Tell them to abort the flight immediately.
Yes, sir.
Tell ATC to stop the
flight to Delhi immediately.
Roger, waiting.
FA908 enter the runway.
25 main line up.
You're clear for takeoff.
- Roger, clear for takeoff.
Stop the flight to Delhi.
There's a terrorist in it.
Do it right now.
Call the ATC.
Stop the flight to Delhi immediately.
Sir, I'm unable to connect with the ATC.
I'm sure somebody
is carrying a cell-phone.
Sir, cell-phones aren't allowed inside.
Cell-phones aren't allowed.
If cell-phones aren't allowed
then you go inside and inform them.
I'm on the way and will reach there soon.
Turn right at 240 degrees for takeoff.
Fly to 8000 feet.
Roger, copy.
Move. Step aside.
Let me go. Move. Please step aside.
FA908 runway clear. Ready for take-off?
Roger, ready for take-off.
Stop the flight to Delhi immediately.
What's the matter?
- There are terrorists in it.
FA908 reject take-off immediately.
Reject take-off immediately.
Reject take-off.
Roger, why reject take-off?
There are terrorists ion the flight.
- There are terrorists in the flight.
We're stopping the flight.
'The flight has been stopped
due to security reasons.'
'Please bear with us. Thank you.'
Boarding pass.
What's your name?
- Rashid.
Where are you from?
- Karachi.
Sir, your doubt is correct.
Passengers with these names
have left by the flight to Nepal.
Stop the flight by any means.
Ask the flight to return.
Sir, that's impossible.
The flight has taken off.
By the time you complete the formalities
the flight will have crossed our borders.
'Dear passengers, right now we're flying
over the beautiful Himalayan mountains.'
'You've entered Nepal now.'
Sir, call for you.
Hello.
- Sir, our mission is successful.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Superb, uncle
That was a thrilling story.
It must've been so difficult for you.
What happened after that?
- After that?
He was handed over to
the Indian army in Nepal.
Well-done, Subhash.
- Thank you, sir.
What next? - He confessed
everything after some thrashing.
All his partners were also arrested.
Mr. Varma who planned Mr. Gupta's murder
wanted to be the PM.
He was arrested by the police.
Uncle, what was the
punishment given to Malik?
Malik was a dangerous criminal.
He tried to escape on the way to jail.
But, the police shot him dead.
My super uncle!
Grandfather always said that good things
happen to good people..
..and evil people are always punished.
I request our honourable President
to unveil the photograph..
..of Late Mr. Shravan Kumar.
Uncle, put me down.
Hey!
No! Stop!
Don't shoot. Don't kill me.