'Agra (Uttar Pradesh).'
Glory to Lord Krishna.
Wonder if she ever sleeps.
Not a day has gone by
where she hasn't prepared the offerings,
well ahead of the prayers.
Glory to Lord Krishna.
It's not possible for Siddhi
to forget to keep the matchbox.
My daughter never forgets.
I had taken the matchbox
for some other use.
So now, stop blaming my daughter
in front of God, will you?
Siddhi has always been
the light of our lives.
It would've been difficult
to run the house
had she not become a confectioner
after your health issues.
She runs the shop and the house
and also takes care of Maya.
She goes to bed after we sleep
but wakes up earlier than us.
Ever since your medical condition,
I've hardly seen her sleep.
Anyway, it's a special day for her.
She was to wake up at 4 a.m.
and leave for the shop.
Do you think I could pull this off
had I not woken up at 4 a.m.?
All these sweet delicacies
and 'Laddus' made as offerings.
Quickly pack them all
and send them to my house right away.
Your house?
Ma'am, is there a prayer ceremony
at home today?
Not really but God grants this day
only after years of hard penance.
Now hurry up, I'll be back at 9
fire up the oven and prepare the rest
of the sweets as per the order. Come on.
Do you even have a moment to breathe
amid all this hustle and bustle?
You truly are a one-man army.
Whenever I look at you,
only one thing comes to my mind.
"I wonder what this girl is made of!"
Though I'm Siddhi's stepmother
kids of this generation cannot match
the love and respect she has for me.
She loves Maya more than anyone.
She's an ideal sister.
With a sister like her,
do I need to ask more?
On this day, 22 years ago,
God gave me the most precious gift.
Since then, I've treasured her.
It's my Maya's birthday.
She maybe my daughter
but Siddhi loves her immensely.
She has always shielded Maya
right from her childhood.
But where is she?
Glory to lord Krishna.
As it's Maya's birthday,
she must be celebrating it.
I guess, Maya is still asleep.
But I know the trick to wake her up.
"I'll be the shade for you
in the sunlight, a shadow by your side."
"I'll shower you with love,
my heart beats for you."
"My heart beats for you."
"I want you forever."
Happy happy birthday Maya!
It's Maya's birthday today.
I'm going to serve
you all my best desserts.
Come on.
Mr. Sharma's younger daughter
is so pretty.
She'll brighten up her groom's home.
It's Maya's birthday. Let's dance, kids.
I guess, you are new here.
Let me unravel the truth to you.
Someone pushed me. Someone pushed Maya.
Let me go. Who dared to push me?
Who was it? Was it you?
Was it you who pushed Maya?
Was it you?
Was it you? You?
Who pushed Maya?
- You?
- Calm down, Maya.
I won't spare you. Was it you?
This is the true face
of the Sharma family.
One dusky, the other crazy.
Birthday drums resound here
but wedding drums will never roll.
I won't spare anyone.
Calm down.
Who dared to push me?
I won't spare anyone.
I'll shoot you all.
No matter what,
I promise to take care of Maya for life.
As I'm the reason for her childlike state.
Due to me, she met with an accident at
the age of 12, which affected her brain.
And she became mentally challenged.
Siddhi, they pushed me.
They pushed me.
No one will be spared.
- I'll kill everyone.
- Maya. Maya.
- I'll kill them all.
- Maya.
They pushed me.
Maya, I'm here.
Maya is wise and brave.
She fearlessly walks her own way.
But she doesn't get enraged.
Siddhi is her sister.
I will stay with you forever!
Only Siddhi can handle her.
May they always be together.
The groom will arrive with fanfare.
Anyhow, I'll find a perfect match
for Siddhi.
Maya.
Your birthday gift.
Gift! Wow, a gift.
Wow!
A car! Wow.
I'll drive it.
Maya, it will never run out of fuel.
Siddhi.
The last token of your late mother.
Always keep wearing it.
My mom used to wear it?
Dad, then I'll never take it out.
What is it?
A chain?
Why not one for me? Why only for her?
I want a similar one.
I want one right now.
No, don't do that. It's for Siddhi.
Why only for her and not me?
I want to wear one too.
I want one right now.
Okay, fine.
You will get the chain right away.
Wow, it's so pretty.
Siddhi, you are really nice.
You are the best.
But dear, the chain...
Dad, Maya and I are no different.
What belongs to Siddhi
also belongs to Maya.
Siddhi, let's go to the temple.
Let's race till there. Okay?
1, 2, 3. Go!
- Come on. - Dear, listen!
- Be careful. Dad, I'll be back.
Slowly, Maya. Slowly.
Maya, stop.
Easy. Slowly.
Come on.
Siddhi, I'm already tired.
I can't climb all these stairs to pray.
Let's go back.
Maya, don't say that.
God will be offended, if you leave
without His blessings on your birthday.
But why can't God climb down to meet me?
I'm too tired to climb so many stairs.
Maya.
"I'll be the shade for you
in the sunlight, a shadow by your side."
"I'll shower you with love,
my heart beats for you."
"My heart beats for you."
Such a grown-up girl!
Yet she is a burden on her sister!
She isn't a burden
but a blessing from God for me.
Shall we?
You have found the perfect match for her
from a good family.
O' God,
the groom belongs to a respectable family.
I'll offer you 'Laddus' and money.
Don't let this wedding get fixed.
Maya won't survive without Siddhi.
I can't manage her on my own.
Besides, Siddhi earns for the family.
Please help.
Break off the alliance.
The groom's family is coming tomorrow
to meet Siddhi.
May her dusky complexion
not be an obstacle yet again.
A fat dowry can cover up for it.
Don't worry. I'll arrange for it.
No, I can't let him spend on
Siddhi's wedding.
May the groom be rich or poor,
she isn't getting married.
Mr. Gupta, think again.
You're dealing with me
by calling off a contract
with Agra's biggest businessman.
I hope, you won't have
a change of mind later.
Weak people alter their intentions.
Neither do I fear Jaya Creations
nor Mrs. Jaya Pandey.
That mother-son duo is very zealous.
Soon, we'll erase their company's name
from Agra's market.
It's difficult.
My mom says,
"If a trader tries to be dishonest
then he should be prepared to get beaten."
What is this?
A beating.
I've got news for you two.
All shareholders of your companies
have sold their shares to Jaya Creations.
Yes, I did have to pay double the price.
But I had to teach you a lesson.
Please spare us.
We will be doomed. Please forgive us.
The word 'Forgiveness' doesn't exist
in Vinayak Pandey's dictionary.
My company is named after my mom.
Jaya Pandey.
Our friends and foes know
the significance of her name very well.
Letters from a hermitage at Vrindavan.
You may spend
the rest of your lives in peace there.
He is so arrogant!
Watch it, soon someone will
bring him down to his senses.
Love can transform anyone.
This order has to be delivered on time.
As the payment will be made in cash.
I have to buy dad's medicines
and take Maya shopping.
First, the spices,
then onions, next are tomatoes
chilli and then lemon.
Oh, no, Maya has curdled the milk.
Stop crying, Maya. It's okay.
It's okay.
Why yell for a petty thing?
Petty! It's impossible
to find so much of milk before evening.
Are the sweets ready? It should be
delivered within half an hour.
Sweets should be delivered
in half an hour?
Yeah, sure.
Ma'am, you'll have to cancel the order.
Will you really have to cancel the order?
Not at all. I won't do that.
How do you plan to make sweets now?
I may not be able
to make his favourite sweets
but we can surely make Rasgullas
using curdled milk, Jhumki.
I'll make lip-smacking ones for him.
Hold on.
And it's done.
We'll quickly go shopping for Maya.
And be back in a jiffy.
What do you want?
The property deeds.
Why do you want them?
I'll have to arrange money
for Siddhi's wedding.
Mr. Verma has agreed to mortgage
our house at a low interest rate.
What's wrong with you?
You are overlooking
Maya in favour of Siddhi.
This house is all that we have.
If that is mortgaged,
will anything be left for Maya?
Don't worry, I'll manage everything.
Focus on Siddhi's wedding.
No, the wedding can't take place.
I'll put up a big act for Siddhi
to rethink about Maya before marrying.
You bought such nice stuff for me, Siddhi.
You are very nice.
What plans for my birthday?
It will be loads of fun.
Wait.
Hello.
Maya!
Maya, are you okay?
Hope you didn't get hurt.
No.
Does anyone stroll
in the middle of the road?
Maybe you can't see, mister.
It's a no entry lane.
You were driving rashly
in a crowded street!
Don't you feel ashamed?
Well, whoever she is,
was walking in the middle of the road.
She seems to be crazy.
Don't you dare call my sister crazy!
She isn't crazy
but rich boys like you are who don't
follow the rules while driving fancy cars.
What if my sister would have got harmed?
Stop staring,
be decent and apologise to her.
I guess, you don't know who I am.
I'm Vinayak Pandey.
Owner of Jaya Creations.
So? Agra isn't yours alone.
Look, you scared her.
Come on, apologise to her.
Fine, if she is hurt, take some money
and get her treated. Stop this drama
and get out of here.
What the heck!
You must apologise.
Or else, you can't leave from here.
How arrogant can the rich be!
They can't mow down people.
He must apologise.
Yes, he must.
It's the right thing to do.
Yes, he should.
I'm sorry.
Don't you ever do this to anyone else.
Get in.
Mom, don't take her away,
I've got to give her the pills.
Mom!
Mom, what happened? Please tell me.
Where are you taking Maya?
Don't worry, Maya.
Please tell me. What's wrong?
What are you going to do?
- No, Mom!
- Siddhi!
Mom, don't do this.
- Mom, no!
- No!
Reluctantly, I'll have to enact this
to instil fear in Siddhi's mind.
And manipulate her into obeying my wishes.
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill her today.
- No, Mom.
- No!
What are you doing, Mom!
Don't worry, Maya.
How long will you save her?
You will leave after the wedding.
For how long will I take care of her?
It's better to push her in the well
and end the matter.
Save me, sister!
- Maya!
[Sanskrit chant]
My Maya got saved in the nick of time.
Thank God.
What had gotten into you?
Does anyone ever do this to her child?
What else could I do?
Your dad is adamant on marrying you off
and sending you away.
He is thinking of mortgaging the house.
Being homeless, where will I take Maya?
Answer me.
You don't have to worry about Maya.
I've always taken care of her
and will do so in the future too.
But how, Siddhi?
You'll be married and gone.
How will Maya survive then?
Mom, Maya has always been
my responsibility.
And it will be the same
even after I get married.
I'll only marry the one
who accepts this condition.
Otherwise, I'll remain unmarried forever.
I'll never let Maya be sad.
Even if it calls for a sacrifice.