The almighty has blessed us
with a baby boy.
Great! Didn't I tell you?
Priest sir, please prepare the
horoscope of the boy. Note the time.
Surely, I will prepare it properly.
First, tell me the right time.
Let me tell you. Sharp 5:00 am.
How are you so sure?
When our maid, Parvati comes and
knocks the door at 5am sharp.
Look, the bell is ringing.
This girl is never late.
Priest sir, please prepare
the horoscope immediately. - Sure.
Come, Parvati. You have
come at the right time.
What's the matter, ma'am?
All of you are up at 5 am today!
The matter is...
- That she has delivered a baby.
Hey, how did you learn about it?
Last night, when I was leaving
for home, I saw her face.
I saw the shine on her face and I knew
it that she will deliver the baby.
Oh dear! You aren't even married yet.
How did you know of these things?
What are you saying, ma'am?
My mom delivered three kids after
me and we didn't have a nanny.
I was always with her.
My mom has given birth to 8 kids.
She herself says that no nanny
can help the way I did. - I see.
Listen, Parvati, I won't be able to
come to the kitchen for a few days.
You come at 5 am usually.
Tomorrow onwards come by 4 am.
Take care of all the
household chores properly.
Don't worry, ma'am. You take care of
the baby, I'll take care of the house.
Parvati, is all the work done?
- Yes, ma'am.
So many people will
be coming to see the baby.
We'll have to arrange for snacks.
I knew you'd be saying this.
I have already started preparing.
The tea is almost ready.
I have to just pour it in the cups.
Great! You are very smart.
Shall I take your leave?
I have to go to two more houses.
If you need me then send a message
for me home, I'll come. - Alright, dear.
Parvati.
- What is it, sir?
Tell me, sir.
It's nothing. My room is very
dirty since so many days.
The dust is getting accumulated.
No one is bothered.
Won't you clean it?
Alright. I'll do it.
Parvati.
Tell me. - It's been so many days
since you have been working here.
But you never talk to me.
If I keep talking
then who will work?
Work goes on, Parvati.
But if you need anything..
..then don't you think you
have the right to ask me?
Me? I work here and I take my
salary from ma'am for that.
I know you do. But you can take
something from the owner as well.
You can money, saris,
clothes, jewellery.
Hey! Listen!
What were you telling Parvati?
I was saying... I...
- Go ahead. Why are you fumbling?
It's nothing, ma'am. Sir is
suddenly worried about me.
He was asking me why I didn't
get married as of yet.
Yes. That's what I was asking.
Yes, Parvati. I, too wanted to ask you.
When will you get married?
This is the right age.
What can I do, ma'am? Destiny can
do nothing in front of poverty.
We are 8 kids in the house.
I am the eldest.
You tell me, how can I think about
getting married in such a situation?
Dad didn't leave us any money.
He just increased the number
of family members and died.
And my mom is there but
she can't do anything.
I have six younger sisters.
And one of them is dumb.
What can I do, ma'am?
I just have one brother.
I am funding his MBBS education
with great difficulty.
"Aa O Meena, Super Seena."
"Big Boys, Lazy girls..."
- Enough, stop shouting.
Come here. Can't you see
Suresh is studying?
I have told you so many times, when
he is studying, don't make noise.
C'mon! Go out and play.
Kamla, come here.
They are younger to you. Let them
play outside. Why are you going?
Are you a kid to play with them?
Yes, yes... Let it be. Listen,
we need to eat in the afternoon, right?
Then go inside, turn on the
stove and start preparing lunch.
Parvati, you asked her
to turn on the stove.
But is there anything
to eat at home?
Mom, you always say negative
before even checking.
Yesterday, I bought 4 kg rice.
In the second box on the
third shelf in the kitchen..
..I have put all the rice.
Haven't you seen? - No.
Great! Come, I'll show you.
Why, mom? You know Suresh is
sitting there and studying.
I have told you so many
times don't say such things..
..so loudly that Suresh can hear.
Why wouldn't I do that?
If there's no food at home..
..won't I tell you about it?
- Of course you can.
But you can get me in the kitchen
and tell me about it in person.
Suresh is studying. We are funding
his studies with such difficulty.
If he gets worried about
the requirement of food..
..he won't be able to
study at all, mom. You always...
Mom, promise me you won't
say anything to him.
No. No, I won't.
Now tell me. What were you saying?
There are grains at home, right?
- Where?
You just said that you
have a full box of rice.
You expect me to loudly speak in front
of Suresh that there are no grains.
What do we do now?
- Mom, why do you have to cry?
We aren't rich people.
Here, even if people have money
they don't have it for necessities.
Don't worry, mom. The stove is turned on
and rice too will be arranged soon.
Parvati!
- I think it's arranged.
Please come. What is the matter?
Tomorrow, all of us are
going out for a wedding.
Will you be able to stitch four
blouses and petticoat immediately?
Yes. You are leaving tomorrow
morning, right? - Yes.
I will stitch it today
and send it by tonight.
Here you go. Take this money.
Shall I take your leave? - Sure.
Go and get it.
- I was saying...
That's exactly what I am saying.
Go on, mom.
Yes, dear.
Parvati.
Only 15 days are left for
the college to reopen. - Oh yes.
You'll need money, right?
Hey, Suresh. Why are you worried?
I have arranged for it.
That's not the thing, Parvati.
You had said..
..that if there's need
for a large amount..
..then I should remind beforehand.
- I do remember.
Now you go and study.
"Who is this who has
shyed the sun's ray!"
"Who is this whose beauty has
fired up the water's bay!"
"Who is this because of whom this
gush of breeze has come our way!"
"Who is this whose songs have
made the waves to stay!"
"Who is this whose intoxicating
tresses have shadowed the waves!"
"There are no clouds in the sky,
they are all lying on the rivers!"
"Who is this standing with a
storm of desires in him!"
"I feel so shy, God knows who is
this whom I have come across."
"Who is this whose beauty has
fired up the water's bay!"
"Who is this whose songs have
made the waves to stay!"
"Who is this who has
shyed the sun's ray!"
Parvati, you were praying
so much concentration.
What did you ask from God?
My brother, Suresh.
In spite of so many problems..
..he has been scoring every year.
I was praying..
..that he scores well in
his final year as well..
..and becomes a doctor.
- So that means..
Everything depends on
he becoming a doctor.
Our marriage too. Right.
Isn't it.
Tell me Parvati.
So, it means..
..we will have to wait
for another year.
May be more than that.
If you pray to God
the way I ask you to..
..then we can get married
within months.
How is that? - You want
your brother to become a doctor.
You want him to take up
all the responsibilities.
After that you will marry me.
While I think that I want to win
the court case of my wealth.
And then I will marry you.
That's why, pray to the almighty
that I win the case faster.
What if you win?
- I will get wealth of Rs 4,00,000.
After that I will take
care of you, your brother..
..and all the responsibilities
of your family.
I hope you trust me.
Why do you ask that?
- I meant, I hope you don't think..
..that when I get the wealth,
I might change my mind.
You aren't the kinds whose mind
changes when wealth comes to them.
Parvati.
Hey, what is all this?
You had said that you want
to get married again..
..and that I must get an
eligible girl for you.
I have got these photos and now...
- Rubbish!
Is this all you have? They are all
illiterate girls from the village.
They are beautiful.
- You will find everyone beautiful.
I hope you haven't clicked these
photos by wearing the saris yourself.
Why do you think I thought of
getting married again at this age?
I am doubtful about it.
Why? My hairs are white.
Is that the reason?
I might be 55 but my heart
is still as young as 25.
Sir, I know that but...
- What?
I am not getting married for her
to cook for me or get kids.
I am tired of having 6 kids already.
Then why are you getting married?
- Now you are asking!
Let me tell you. The girl who gets
married now, I will get her right here.
I will just stand in front of her
and keep looking at her.
That's it.
I want to keep looking at her
for 24 hours 7 days a week.
How do you think should she be?
- Why don't you tell me?
Useless! You need the eyes for that.
Her face should be like
beauty queen Saira Bano. - Okay.
How should he waist be?
- How?
Crazy fellow, it should be like Helen.
- Helen.
And her walking style...
Just like Vaijanthimala.
I mean to say she should be like..
..Padmini. Go and get her.
But sir, do you think such a
beauty will get married to you?
Do you think she will marry you?
Is there anyone better than me who
can appreciate beauty? - No, sir.
Son!
Where are you?
- I am right here.
But whenever I am doing some work,
why do you come with all of them?
Son, these kids are insisting
on going out for a movie.
These kids want to watch a movie!
Yes, do you think I am insisting?
I understand everything, mom.
At this age, you want to
watch movies and theater..
..and circus.
- You keep yelling at me.
I thought, they are
kids without a mother.
At least they will
go out for a movie.
Well, the idea is good.
Manohar, let them go.
The film is really nice. Its
on Tarzan, they will like it.
Alright. Go and watch it.
You keep bothering me all the time.
Take this. Go.
- Thank you.
Go on, mom. You too go.
Sir.
- Yes?
This girl is your sister, right?
- Yes.
Should I look for a
good boy for her?
What a personality! You won't
let go of a client, will you?
I have asked you to
get a girl not a guy.
Go. Wear a good spectacles and
take a look all around the city.
And get a girl just the
way I explained you. Go.
Alright.
- Listen.
No one should know about my marriage
in this house. Neither my mom, sister..
..and nor my brother.
If my brother Ratanlal learns
about it, he will break it all.
Sir, I have been coming
here since so many days.
I have never seen your brother.
I have a younger brother.
But he is completely opposite
to me in every way possible.
He doesn't wish to stay at home,
so he rides a cab.
"My car is a flying machine."
"Some call it a king's chariot and
some call it a bride's palanquin."
"My car is a flying machine."
"Why should any traveler
be left behind in this world?"
Sir, am I say right?
- You're right.
"Why should any traveler
be left behind in this world?"
"Is someone lucky enough to find love?"
Sorry!
"The mirror of the heart always
reveals the secrets of love."
"My car is a flying machine."
"There are a lot of thieves in this
world, some a big and some small."
"They roam about as gentlemen
but work as thieves." - What?
"That's not for you, sir."
"Their life runs on lies and
they never speak the truth."
"My car is a flying machine."
You are back. I was waiting for you.
Tell me clearly.
How much money do you need?
I have to pay the college fees.
I have buy books as well.
I was thinking of stitching some
clothes as well. - Okay, for all this..
..Rs 770 is enough, right?
Parvati, the college fees
itself is that much.
Rs 1000 would be enough, right?
I will try.
- Listen, I have arranged for the money.
I was just asking that how
much do you need now.
Rs 1000 should be enough, Parvati.
- Okay. I'll go and get the money.
Stay at home. As soon as I come
back, we'll go to the market.
Please come. - You are inviting me!
First, give me my money back.
It's been so many days.
Give it back.
I wanted to give it back myself.
How will you give it back?
All you know is taking.
You don't know how to refund.
When you need, you always come home.
It is so difficult.
Now I am coming to you
to get back my refund.
The Tyre of my car is
messed and so are my shoes.
That's not how it is, Mr. Manoharlal.
I went 5 times to your house.
But your mom said
you aren't at home.
Whatever she said... I don't
have time for nonsense.
I need my money back.
Mr. Manoharlal, as of now I will
only give you the interest.
I will return the entire
amount next month.
That will never happen. I want my
money back right now. - Greetings, sir.
Come, dear.
- I need to talk to you.
Is it?
- Why don't you come in the evening?
You are a strange man!
When the girl has come now then
why call her in the evening?
The poor girl must
be in some trouble.
Ask her what she needs.
- Sit down.
Let me sort your problem first...
- My problem is not a problem.
What's the use if I take
Rs 20,000 from you?
As long as it is with you I
will keep getting my interest.
Ask her what she needs.
Alright then... - First, ask her
why she has come to you.
I won't leave until she leaves.
- Sit down.
Come, dear.
Just what I wanted.
Thanks to you..
..my brother is studying
since so many years.
He is in his final year.
At this point, I need Rs 1000.
I will be grateful.
Why, dear?
As soon as he finishes this year,
will he become a doctor? - Yes.
Oh God!
What is the matter? - What can I say?
I don't have money right now.
What? You don't...
I didn't think of it. I came
here with a lot of expectations.
You have never refused till date.
You used to give it to me
without me asking for it.
I used to, right?
- Yes.
When I had, I used to give it.
Today, I don't have any
then how can I give it?
Sir, why don't you do this?
What? - You used to keep our
house in lease and give me money.
Yes. - Buy that house
and give me the money.
Dear, what do you think I am?
Do you think..
..I gave you money according to the
amount your house is worth of?
You aren't married yet.
You work as a maid in other's house.
You somehow manage to take
care of your mom and sisters.
You are making your
brother study MBBS.
I had helped you because
I saw your qualities.
Listen, do one thing.
You need Rs 1000, right?
- Yes.
I am giving you a
guarantee of Rs 2000.
Try somewhere else.
- What are you saying?
I am telling the right thing.
Nowadays, money is a
huge problem, dear.
What is this, mom?
- Kamla's menstrual cycle has started.
What happened, dear?
- Nothing, mom.
We have faced so many problems.
But I never got scared.
But today after learning about
Kamla's menstrual cycle..
..I don't know why I am getting scared.
What are you saying, dear?
Every girl gets her menstrual
cycle after growing up.
That's true, mom.
Nowadays, a normal girl also
cannot get married easily..
..until a good amount
of dowry is given.
Kamla is poor and dumb as well.
From where will we get dowry
for her, whom will we ask...
Mom, there are 5 more
girls after her.
Every year one of them will
get their menstrual cycle.
From where will we get...
- Parvati.
Shall we go to the market?
- Yes. I was waiting for you. Let's go.
Oh God! The clouds are thundering.
I think it will rain heavily today.
Yes, Parvati.
Look, it's getting darker.
Suresh, you need to buy new
clothes and books, right?
If it starts raining,
everything will be wet.
Yes, that's true.
- Let's go tomorrow.
Okay. We'll go tomorrow.
Parvati, it's you.
I can't believe it.
Come inside, Parvati.
Mom isn't at home.
She has gone to meet her sister.
You are completely drenched.
Here, dry your hair.
What was the need to come alone at
this hour when it's raining outside?
You should've called me,
I would've come.
I don't understand.
What is so important that you
couldn't tell me before?
Or tomorrow morning.
- I was about to come in the evening.
But I was thinking whether
I should come or not.
Then I decided that come what may..
..I must meet you.
That's why I am here.
Anyway, what is the matter?
Tell me.
Don't worry.
Tell me, what is the matter?
Suresh is in his final year.
- Yes.
I was supposed to get
money from somewhere.
But I didn't get anything there.
I need Rs 1000 right now.
Can you give me?
- Parvati.
What happened?
- I am stone-hearted person.
What are you saying?
- Yes, Parvati. Had that not been true..
..then I would've died
by now for not being..
..able to fulfill such a
small demand of yours.
Why are you worried?
It's just me who is asking for it.
No one else.
That's what I feel bad about.
The one who never asked
for anything till date..
..she asked me for something
so small out of helplessness..
..and I couldn't fulfill that.
Listen, I knew that you
wouldn't have money.
Yet, I asked you for it.
Do you know why?
If I am unable to fund
Suresh's studies this year..
..I won't be sad later..
..that I didn't ask
for money from you.
Now I am happy that..
..I tried as much as I could.
That's why I came to you.
Oh my God!
You are suddenly asking
for such a huge amount.
We have a lot of spending ourselves.
You know that ever since a baby is
born, the doctors, the medicines..
..cost so much and people keep coming.
Money is just getting spend.
What do I hide from you?
I was worried as to how to pay
your salary of this month.
Okay, ma'am. I'll take your leave.
I have found such a good groom
that your fate will shine.
His wealth is worth Rs 20,00,000
and hard cash is separate.
I am telling the truth.
The thing is that..
..ever since he has seen your
daughter, he wants to marry her.
That's okay.
But didn't a wealthy groom..
..get a girl from a wealthy family?
- You have asked the right question.
This is his second marriage.
- Second marriage?
Kids?
- He has 6 of them.
What is his age?
- Not much.
He is about 50 years old.
Get up! Get up and leave.
Listen, the person I am
talking to you about..
..at least meet him once.
Enough. I don't want to meet him.
Please leave from here.
- I will ask him to come and meet you.
At least meet him once.
I have told you that
we aren't interested.
Then why are you insisting?
I said, leave right now. Or else...
Alright. As you wish.
Please wait. Please come here.
The person you were talking about..
..can you help us meet?
- Yes, why not?
He is waiting to meet you.
Not to see him.
It is for me to talk to him clearly.
Go and tell him and ask him to come.
Don't send him here.
Ask him to come to the temple at 5pm.
Parvati, why are you calling him?
Why? What's the problem?
- We don't agree to this.
Do you think I do?
- Then why are you calling him?
Am I calling him with
a wedding procession?
First, we'll meet and talk.
I'll talk to him about
whatever possible.
If it works and everyone likes him..
..then we'll think about marriage.
Parvati, there's nothing
to think about in this.
You took the decision!
Please go and ask him to come.
- You won't do that.
I am asking you to do so.
- You go inside.
Parvati.
- Go inside.
Parvati, as long as I am alive...
- Enough...
We are outside the house.
Why are you fighting here?
Let's go inside and talk.
- Parvati, even if I die...
Suresh!
Are you going inside
or should I leave?
What is it, Parvati? What do
you want to talk to him about?
Ask me about it, mom.
I'll tell you what she wants
to talk to him about.
Tell me. - You will be asking
him to help me in my studies.
You will ask him to take care
of your family. Right? - Yes.
That means you are pushing
yourself in to hell.
Am I in heaven living
a peaceful life now?
You are right, dear.
You never got peace in the
house you were born in.
I wish you get peace in your
husband's house at least.
That is what I am saying, mom.
Did you hear?
He is a rich man.
- Whatever it is. I won't let this happen.
Reason?
- What's his age?
What is your age?
Tell me, what is your age?
Had you got married
at the right time..
..then you would've been a
father of three kids.
And I am your elder sister.
Go and get a man of my age.
Alright, I will get.
Why are you yelling
without knowing anything?
I am not yelling. I am telling
the truth. I swear I will do it.
First, do it then I will see.
Stupid. You are studying in college.
Nowadays, when a 40-year old man
looks at a 20-year old girl, he says..
..that she is way too old.
And he thinks he will
get a man of my age.
I am 28 years old right now.
Parvati, I am saying
this out of sadness.
You are trying to shut
me by saying all this.
I beg of you.
This marriage shouldn't happen.
I won't let it happen.
Yes, dear. It would be better to stay
alone then get married like this.
That's right. Suresh?
Mom is right.
- I see.
I'll stay unmarried then.
Let's decide right now.
That means if I get married and go..
..then none of you
will be able to eat.
For your comfort, I should keep
working as a maid all my life.
And then one day I will die.
This is what you want.
Fine, I will do this.
What are you saying, Parvati?
When I said that I should leave
my studies and work somewhere..
..you refused. You asked me
to study and become a doctor.
Now you are accusing me.
- I am making you study. Is it for me?
Then for whom?
Kamla is dumb.
There are more 5 sisters you have.
I am making you study so
that they get married..
..in a better place.
- But Parvati, even you are my sister.
Do you think I won't
take care of you?
God knows whether I
will be alive by then.
What are you saying, Parvati?
- Keep quiet.
You think after your studies, people
will come running to you with money.
After that you will have to work
hard and make a name for yourself.
Only after that will
your earnings begin.
Once you start earning,
God knows if you will
take care of us.
Parvati.
- I know there are barely any brothers..
..who take care of their sisters.
After marriage, they take
care of their wife and kids.
Who takes care of their
parents or sisters?
Parvati, I know there
are brothers like that.
But their sisters are
not goddesses like you.
I just know you and
your sacrifices.
Parvati, after all
I am your brother.
Your feeling of sacrifices
can be in me as well.
I see. That's great. So you are
also ready to make sacrifices.
Why not?
- Do you promise?
I promise. - Then promise me that
unless you get all your sisters married..
..you won't get married.
I won't promise that
I won't get married.
I promise that unless I get
all my sisters married..
..I won't think about getting married.
So, to get these 6 sisters
married in a good family..
..you will have to become a doctor
first. - Yes, Parvati.
Then to make you a doctor,
I will have to get married.
Parvati. Parvati, we will
find another way for that.
I will complete my studies somehow.
You won't be able to do it, Suresh.
You won't be able to.
Let me try it.
Suresh, you don't understand the
world. This is not possible.
Parvati, what are you talking about?
Alright, forget about the world.
Do you know what's the
condition in our house? - What?
The entire house is mortgaged.
Suresh, the day you
started studying MBBS..
..I had to keep this house mortgage.
Did I ever tell you about it?
We have faced so many problems.
But did I ever show it to you?
Today, I am saying it. Why?
Because I have nothing today.
I am completely helpless.
The money lender might
just come someday..
..and throw us out of the house.
I think of it and get so afraid.
I met everyone possible.
I asked for money from
everyone possible.
I begged everyone I could.
But when I saw that there is no other way,
there's nothing we can do..
..that's when I decided to do this.
Go away. Let me be in my situation.
Greetings, sir.
Come. I thought you forgot that
there's a case you are fighting.
Why? I keep coming.
How will that help? Sit down.
Look, your case is very complicated.
Opponent is very strong.
I have left all my work aside and
I am concentrating on your case.
You come every time but you
need to pay the fees as well.
Last week, I had given you Rs 300.
That's it! Is the case over?
Right. I will try to give you more.
But please tell me about
the progress of the case.
I have already told you, the
opponent is very strong.
Your side is weak.
I will make points and
present it in court.
Whether you win or lose,
it is dependent on that.
Go and arrange for the fees.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Sir, is his case really weak?
Who said?
- You said.
Stupid fellow, our case is very strong.
We will surely win.
But after winning the case,
I don't want to file a case
on anyone to get my fees.
Understood?
So, we have been waiting for the girl since
such a long time. Where is the girl?
I had told you that the
girl has called you at 5pm.
But you left home at 3pm
and have been sitting here..
..then what can she do
and what can I do.
When the girl has a house of her own..
..then why did she call
us in the temple?
I think that her brother and mother
don't want this marriage to happen.
Forget about them.
What about the girl?
Sir, had she not been interested
why would she call you?
Yes, that's right.
There she is. She has come.
- Go. Go from here.
Wait a moment.
Let me introduce you.
- Come, dear.
He is the one who
wants to marry you.
I have seen him.
- Right.
We have met each other.
You can leave.
Tell me, what is the matter?
Come. We will speak in
front of God's idol.
Yes, let's go. We will talk here.
What I wish to say is a big thing.
- Surely, tell me.
That's why I wish to keep
someone has witness.
Is it? If you wish, I can get the
richest people of the town here.
That's not needed.
It is better to keep God
as the witness and talk.
Of course it is. I am a huge devotee.
I see God in everything.
In the stone, in the wall,
in the pillar, in you and me.
Anyway, forget that.
Tell me, what were you about to say.
Tell me, what your demands are.
I wish that my brother completes his
final year of studies. - MBBS, right?
Yes. He is in his final year.
No problem. Even he fails, I will
use my contacts and get him passed.
No. That's not needed.
He is very intelligent.
You can just help with money.
He will surely pass.
Alright. I will do it. But he
should be at my house to study.
Demand No. 2.
Until he becomes a doctor
and starts earning..
..the responsibility of my
family will be on you.
This is what I am sad about.
You are still differentiating.
Both of us are one.
They are my family too.
Okay, you will take the
responsibility of our family right?
I swear on God,
on myself and on you.
I will take care of our family.
I too swear on God..
..that I am happily
ready to marry you.
That's great. Take this.
Why do I need so much?
Rs 1000 is enough.
Keep it. Why are you
counting unnecessarily?
All this is yours.
The keys of the house will be with
you then you can do what you want.
One important thing. No one should
know that we are getting married.
Why?
- Well, my mom..
..wants me to get married to someone
else and I don't like those girls.
I really like you. So this
shouldn't be revealed.
If my brother learns about it then..
..he will put a stay
order on the marriage.
We will get married next
Friday here itself.
Okay. I'll take your leave.
- Go on.
Parvati.
Parvati, you have taken
the right decision.
The ones who have a heart..
..will surely appreciate
your decision.
This is a decision which
tells the whole world..
..that a poor person's heart
doesn't belong to him.
But the poverty belongs to them.
Yes, Parvati.
Today, I have come to the temple.
I have heard your conversation.
What do you have to say about it?
What can I say? I am sure..
..that you do love me..
..but you love your family more.
I am telling the truth, Parvati.
I decided yesterday..
..that the two of us can
never get married.
Don't think that I am saying this..
..because you are away from me.
I was expecting that I
will get the wealth back.
Over this expectation I wanted to take
care of you, your family and Suresh.
But yesterday my lawyer told me..
..that my case is very weak.
I feel I will lose this case.
If I get married to you
in such a situation..
..then it will be a disaster.
Parvati, the sacrifice you made
for your brother and sisters..
..it's a huge sacrifice.
I hope this sacrifice of yours
keeps you in peace always.
I'll take your leave.
Listen.
Will you agree to something I say?
Tell me, Parvati. - You want me
to be happy and in peace.
Then do one thing for me.
You should get married..
..and bring your bride
to visit my house.
I will try.
I will try, Parvati.
Alright. I am married now.
Go and inform my family about it.
Give it to him.
- No, I won't.
You won't! You are very stubborn.
Give it!
Take it. Monsters!
- You called me a monster!
Why? Why? Why? Why?
Oh God! The kids are impossible!
Ratan, you are here
at the right time.
Please talk to them.
Mom, kids are mischievous.
Why are you getting mad at them?
Are they kids? Really?
- Of course.
Ma'am, what's going on?
Are you playing with the kids?
I am going crazy and you
think I am playing!
Ma'am, you don't have
to worry at all.
After your daughter-in-law comes,
everything will be fine. - What?
What are you saying?
Ma'am, your son's wife will be
your daughter-in-law, right?
What do you mean?
- Hey!
What are you talking about?
Tell me clearly.
Sir, don't you know.
Today in the morning,
Manoharlal got married again.
What are you saying?
- When did that happen?
What do we do now, Ratan?
He has made such a huge mistake.
- Wait, mom.
Hey, you pigeon.
- I am a man, sir.
I know.
What nonsense is this?
- I am telling the truth.
I had heard that your elder brother got
married in the temple in the morning.
You have heard!
- You heard! What is this?
A sweet! That means you were
a part of this wedding.
Sir, one should be going to
the wedding of the near ones.
So, you got them married.
- Only God takes these decision, sir.
I am just a medium.
- Idiot!
You got the girl.
You got him married.
And now you have come
here to inform us.
Idiot, he is a father of 6 kids.
Why did you have mess his life?
A person like you shouldn't
be allowed here.
C'mon! Move! Out! Out!
Get out! Get out!
- I am going! I am going!
What is all this, Ratan?
- What a mess this is!
Why do you ask me, mom? Has he ever
done anything right till date?
Oh God! What do I do now?
These kids are without a mother.
I took care of them.
I have taken such good care of them.
The witch that comes, God knows
how she will treat them.
Grandma, who is coming?
Your step mother is coming.
Step-mom! How will she be?
She will be like a cat.
She will punish you all.
She will scare all of you.
There he is!
Wait! Where are you going?
Are you deaf? I am talking to you!
Mr. Groom!
- Did you see that? He stopped.
He just got married.
- Hey, cabbie, you shut up.
Why are you shouting at him?
- How dare you get married again?
If you wanted to get married, why
didn't you wait till my death?
Mom, people say that I am
already aged to get married.
Had I waited for you to die,
I would've been more late.
Shameless! It is a sin
to see your face!
We know what is a sin and a deed.
What does he know?
Did you see how my younger
brother talks to me?
The kind of things you do being
the elder brother is worth that.
You are a father to 6 kids
and you got married again!
Yes, I did that. It's my wish.
You shut up or leave from here.
Who wants to come here anyway?
- Why are standing then? Leave!
I am leaving.
I don't live on your money.
I am capable enough to
take care of myself.
Mom, I'll take your leave.
Ratan. Ratan!
- Let him go.
What else can he do?
Who would want to stay
in a sinner's house?
Asha, your sister-in-law is
coming tomorrow morning.
She must be welcomed properly.
Mom. - What are you telling me?
I have heard everything.
Grandma, why have these people come?
Son, your dad has got
married at this age.
Your step-mom is coming.
We have to welcome her properly.
Why, grandma? You were saying
that she will attack us like a cat.
Is she like that?
- Yes.
You said she will scare us out.
Is she like that?
Yes. That's right.
That's how step-mom's are.
Listen kids, if you tried to
do be mischievous with her..
..the way you are with me then she
will throw you out within no time.
Be careful.
Asha, listen to me carefully.
The second wife is always thinking..
..about her targets to
fight and argue with.
Don't give her a chance.
If the two of you have an
argument then you are loss.
I think she has come. Go on.
Be happy.
Parvati, what are you looking at?
I heard he has 6 kids.
I am unable to see any of them.
Greetings. Do you work her as a maid?
- Yes.
These things are in such a mess.
Don't you think we should clear it?
- Yes.
Please keep it there.
Hey.
She is our step-mom.
She will beat us up.
What's so great about it?
She is smiling!
Oh God! These kids!
Oh no!
Oh! That's not the way you should make
a child drink milk, she might choke.
The head should always be up
while making her drink milk.
Here you go. Make her sleep now.
C'mon, let's go and make you sleep.
No. No. Don't cry. Go to sleep.
Sleep. No.
If you make her sleep like this,
she won't sleep.
If you sing a lullaby,
she will sleep quickly.
Parvati, I don't know any lullaby.
Do women need to learn a lullaby?
The life of a woman..
..itself is a lullaby.
"Go to sleep, my dear girl."
"Why sacrifice your sleep?"
"After this phase of childhood
is gone.."
"..a woman doesn't sleep all her life."
"A woman's life is like a swing,
at this end and at that end."
"Sometimes there's smile on her face,
sometimes tears rolling down her eyes."
"A woman's life is like a swing,
at this end and at that end."
"She gives such a lot
of peace to the world."
"She does that being a mother,
a sister and a wife."
"She gives such a lot
of peace to the world."
"She does that being a mother,
a sister and a wife."
"Her life is a difficult one."
"The society has never
understood this."
Parvati.
Look, Grandma said the right thing.
Step-mom is going to
scare us with that.
Oh God! Run! Run!
- Run! Run!
Oh God! What is wrong with you!
All of you are such a mess.
You are always troubling me.
Just wait and watch.
I won't spare you.
They have become very mischievous.
I won't spare them today.
Wait! Where are you going?
C'mon! Come here!
Sit down all of you. Sit down!
Mother! Mother!
What are you doing? Leave it.
What is this?
What if they are hurt with this?
You come here. Come here.
Do you think I will
hurt them with this?
I was just trying to scare them.
With a burning wood stick!
There are other ways to scare also.
You don't know this
mischievous bunch.
They are so stubborn,
they won't listen.
That's alright, mother. But please
don't show them the burning stick.
They are raw mud.
The way we mold them,
they will take that shape.
Is this the right way to scare them?
Well, it isn't right.
Then you take care
of them from now on.
I won't come in between.
I am going.
Go. Go and play.
Munni.
Hey, this step-mom is really nice.
She won't scare us.
Grandma lied to us.
Come. Let's go and ask her.
- Yes, let's go.
Come. Come here.
Why are you standing there?
What do you want?
We'll tell you, step-mom.
Don't call me that. Call me 'mom'.
Mom, will you scare us like a cat?
What?
- No, son, I will never hurt you.
Will you hurt us with
a burning stick?
Why do you say so? When grandma was
showing the stick, I snatched it.
Hey, listen.
Alright. Now go and play. Go.
We hate!
- Grandma!
Dear Lord! What's wrong
with all of you?
Why do you hate me?
Grandma, you lied to us that
mom is hurt us like a cat.
Mom is really nice. She loves us.
You are a witch.
You hurt us like a cat.
You scared us with a burning stick.
Come. Let's beat her up.
Hey! Stop it! - What is all this?
You are beating up your grandma!
This is wrong. Why did you do this?
What happened, mother?
- Parvati, before you came..
..I had told them something about you.
- What did you say?
Usually, step-moms
are bad in nature.
So I told them that you
will hurt them like cats..
..and scare you with a burning stick.
Ever since you have come,
they are observing you.
They love you a lot.
They were saying..
..that you are really
nice and I am witch.
All of them love you a lot, Parvati.
Mom.
- Mom.
Kamla, how are you? Where is mom?
Suresh. Suresh. It's you.
- Mom.
Is Parvati alright?
- Yes, mom. She is absolutely fine.
The kids, her mother-in-law,
all of them love her a lot.
I want to meet Parvati.
Please get her here once.
Yes, mom. I will get her.
She also wants to come.
But Manoharlal's nature
is a bit strange.
He might not like it
if she comes here.
Then let it be, son.
We are happy that
she is happy there.
What about her Asha and Ratanlal?
Asha is good. But I don't
know anything about Ratanlal.
He never comes home and I
haven't seen him either.
Kamla, where are others?
Have they gone to school?
Alright, mom. I'll leave.
I am getting late for college.
- Yes, son.
Go carefully.
- Yes, mom.
I will apply first.
- No, I will.
Enough. Don't fight.
Everyone will take a good bath.
Asha, you continue.
I'll be right back.
Did you call me?
What are you doing?
- Oh c'mon!
Leave me. Didn't you see the
kids are shouting there?
Soap has entered
their eyes and ears.
Let them shout. How are we bothered?
- What is wrong with you?
Your younger sister is
standing there and you...
I won't be able to come tomorrow.
Don't wait for me.
Asha!
- Ratan!
Take a look. I sold that cab and
I have taken a new private cab.
I just have to give Rs 200 every month.
- That's okay, Ratan.
But why don't you come home?
You are having a fight with Manohar.
What have we done?
At least come once in
a week to meet us.
Why should I? First, I saw
Manohar do atrocities.
Now you want me to come and see
our sister-in-law do atrocities.
Atrocities! Who told you so?
What's there to say?
She is step-mom.
She is bound to do so.
You are saying things
without knowing the truth.
Come home and see. I swear, Ratan.
We have got such a good sister-in-law
that no one can imagine.
Really, Asha?
- Yes, Ratan.
Oh! That means I don't
have to worry anymore.
The bell is ringing. You should go.
I will come in meet soon. - Okay.
Parvati, there is a prayer
session in the temple.
Mom is asking me to
go along with her.
Can I go?
- Of course.
Should I take the car? - But the car
is out since morning, Asha.
Alright, no problem. It's nearby.
We'll go walking.
Come back soon.
- Sure, Parvati.
"From the town of sleep, the angels.."
"..have got a bag full of dreams."
"The stars are also feeling sleepy.."
"..when the moon came up the sky."
"As the night has come up.."
"..the entire world is sleeping."
"You too, my dearest daughter.."
"..close your eyes and enter
the land of dreams."
I am asking you to come.
Oh c'mon! Just come.
"How do I come.."
"..unless my dearest daughter.."
"..falls fast asleep."
"Keep patience and don't be wild."
"What is this impatience all about?"
Oh!
What's the hurry? Didn't I tell you,
I am coming after making Munni sleep.
Munni will keep crying all night.
I will go crazy by then.
What?
- What are you doing?
Alright. Go out. Get out.
- No.
Why are you turning the lights off?
Is this important?
- Yes, I am scared.
No.
- Go out! Go!
Alright. Let it be.
Look, Munni is crying.
I think she is coming
upstairs looking for me.
Leave me! Leave me!
- No.
Leave me! Munni might
fall of the stairs. - No!
Let her fall off!
- How can you do that?
Munni! My daughter! Oh dear!
Oh Munni! My dear!
Were you looking for me?
What can we do? Her fate is such!
Oh God! Such a good wife..
..for such a bad man!
Hand over Munni to Asha and come
with me. Did you hear me?
Who is the cab driver here?
Driver!
- Yes?
I need to go to Hotel Grand.
Will you?
C'mon, sit. Hurry up.
Let's go.
C'mon, get off.
- Where have you got me?
Hotel. - What is this? Why would we
leave the house in stay in a hotel?
The kids have irritated
in the house.
Are we able to sit in peace
at home for a while?
Someone asks for food,
someone for milk.
I don't like all this.
Get off.
- What are you saying?
Around those kids, we are able to
see each other, that's enough.
In between their shouts, we are
able to talk to each other.
That's what family is about.
Are you trying to teach
me about family?
Get off right now.
- No. I am scared.
Why are you scared?
Your husband is with you.
That's why I am scared.
When people see us here, will
they think you are my husband?
Why are you talking about others?
I myself considered
you wrong, Parvati.
You know me?
- Yes, Parvati. I am Ratan.
But I am unfortunate to have not
been able to meet you till date.
I am sure you know by now that
my brother is strange man.
He has a great wife like
you yet he hasn't changed.
Hey, shut up!
Don't shout. You are elder
to me that's why I am quiet.
Else, I would've thrown you out
of the cab within no time.
Let's go.
- No, Parvati.
Let's go. - Manohar, if you force her
I will shout and call out to people.
Stay there, Parvati.
Come, Parvati. Go inside.
Manohar, we are lucky to have her.
Make sure she isn't sad.
Go. Go!
- I am going. But I will keep coming.
You will keep coming!
This is such a pain!
Kids irritate me at home
and my brother outside.
Parvati.
- Yes?
Tomorrow morning we will
go to Mussorie - Mussorie?
Yes, be ready.
But...
- I said, be ready
Okay.
Now will you come?
- I am coming, one minute.
If you don't come by
one minute then...
The almighty has granted such a beautiful
face, why do you need make-up?
We have reach Mussorie by night.
But she isn't leaving.
C'mon! Let's go.
- Yes! Yeah! We are going.
All of us are going!
- Yes, all us are going.
Go and sit in the car.
Hey.
Come here.
What did I tell you?
You said, we'll be
going to Mussorie.
What does that mean?
- What does it mean?
I meant, we will be able to
leave peacefully for some days.
So, I had said only the
two of us will be going.
When did I say that the
kids will come along?
Just the two of us?
- Yes.
What is so funny?
- Nothing.
But what so interesting in
Mussorie and Shimla at this age?
Are you coming alone or not?
Listen, it's my mistake that
I asked them to come along.
But now I have told them,
let them come along.
Hey!
- Listen, if we leave them alone now..
..then they will be really sad.
Is that so?
Alright. Then no one will go.
Now no one will go to Mussorie.
I am married to you and
hence I can't do anywhere.
But I will surely go
the cremation ground.- Listen.
I don't want to.
Parvati, please come here.
What is it, Asha?
- Please come.
Parvati, listen to me.
Go with him alone.
What? What are you saying?
I have a reason to say so.
Mom, let's go.
- Let's go!
Wait! I am coming.
Look at them.
How can I go without them?
Parvati, don't get me wrong.
You have come home just now.
Before you came..
..I took care of them.
You don't know how Manohar is.
How will I know?
- I'll tell you.
A sister shouldn't say all
this about her own brother.
But I have to say this
because of these kids.
He is very stubborn, Parvati.
Because of his attitude,
my first sister-in-law died.
A kid every year.
If my brother doesn't get what
he wants at that very moment..
..then he creates a ruckus.
He will start breaking things.
He picks up things and
throws them on the kids.
Do you want him to hit the kids?
- No. I didn't know all this.
I will go right now. But, Asha..
..take care of the kids.
If there's a problem then
call them that very moment. - Okay.
Parvati, go from this side.
Let me make an excuse and
take the kids upstairs.
Go with Manohar.
Listen, I have handled
the situation.
We'll take the kids some other time.
Today, we'll go together.
Had you said this before,
I would've been happier.
It's not too late.
Here, wear your coat.
I asked you to come to Mussorie
with me, there's a reason.
Unless you come along how
will you understand.
Now I am coming. I will understand.
- Let's go.
Yes, Manoharlal speaking.
Hello, Mr. Malhotra here.
Hello, Mr. Malhotra. How are you?
Everyone is waiting
for you at the party.
You haven't come here yet!
Good very good.
I am leaving in 5 minutes.
C'mon! Hurry up!
Parvati, hurry up. Quick.
Let's go.
- How long...
Hey! What is this you are wearing?
Are you feeling cold?
You have covered your
whole body, idiot!
Do you know the kind of
place we are going to?
It is not any ordinary
man who has invited me.
He has a science degree from
England's Oxford University.
He has traveled all over the world.
England, France, America.
He called me as a
gentleman with my wife.
How can you come with these clothes?
You illiterate, woman!
Go and cut grasses in some field.
What can I do? I don't know how to
dress up the way you want me to.
I know you don't know that.
How will you know?
You are always inside the house.
You are always with the kids or
in the kitchen. How will you know..
..about modern fashion like this?
That's why I used to ask you to come
and watch English films with me.
They are such amazing movies.
'Woman By Night', 'Paris By Night',
'World By Night."
The story is just like
the name of the film.
Had you seen one movie, you would've
transformed by now. Shameless
Why did you wear a sari?
Why didn't you wear the
dress I bought for you?
What is this? Is this the
way to do your hair?
I had asked you to dress
your hair properly.
You applied oil in your
hair and combed it.
Modern hair dressing
should be like a bee-hive.
It should be like a Saint Narayana.
Why didn't you do that? Why didn't
you apply nail polish to the nails?
You won't change.
I will dress hence forth.
Let it be.
- No way. People will laugh. Let's go.
Just a minute.
Don't move. Don't move. That's it.
Get up. C'mon. Look at you.
You look like a woman from Paris.
Oh God! What is this nonsense?
What have I done? This looks horrible.
Is it bad? You will have to come
like this.- No. I won't.
Why not?
- Let me wear something over it.
No, no. You won't wear
anything over it.
Then I won't come.
Oh God! This is such a pain!
You are messing with the
beauty of this dress. Take it.
What is this? Is this a cloth?
Why not?
- This is like a net.
Give me something else.
You will have to wear this. Women these
days wear these kind of clothes.
Let's go. And listen.
Do you know what you
have to go there and do?
What?
- We will go there.
Rich people will be around.
- So what?
People from high
societies will be there.
As you reach there shake hands
with them and greet them. - What?
I have to shake hands
with unknown men. No way!
Dear Lord! You are such an illiterate!
If you don't do that
they will laugh at me.
As soon as we reach
there, forget about me.
Don't look at me.
Just greet them and shake hands.
Show it to me.
Hello!
- What is this? Are you crying?
Just say. 'Hello.'
- Hello.
Now let's go.
Be careful.
Nonsense! Get up.
What sort of shoes are these?
Such big heels.
Can I hold them in
my hands and walk?
Why don't you place it on your head?
Walk for a while, you'll get used to it.
Great. C'mon. Good.
Come, Manoharlal, come.
You are so late.
- I am sorry.
That's alright. So you have got your
daughter along. - No. She is my wife.
Second wife.
- Really?
Nice meeting you.
- Shake hands with him.
Hello.
- Waiter!
Take it.
- Thank you.
Please take your seat.
Sit. Sit down.
Hey, what are you doing?
Mr. James, sorry for the delay.
- Oh! Don't worry.
Ladies and gentlemen,
take your partners.
Come, let's dance.
Oh God! What is this?
- Why?
I don't know all this.
- What don't you know?
Just bend a bit and get up.
It's so easy. Everyone is doing it.
I don't know how to dance.
- I will kill you. Just dance.
I beg of you.
No need. Just shake your legs.
C'mon.
"I am in love with you.."
"..but I won't be able to tell you."
"I am in love with you but I
will not be able to tell you."
"There is a smile on my lips.."
"..but I won't be able to tell you."
"I am in love with you but I
will not be able to tell you."
"Sometimes I am happy, I have desires,
my heart beats pace and I am confused."
"My heart is in a strange condition
but I am unable to say it."
"I am in love with you."
"You are waiting to hear about
the condition of my heart."
"I have the time to tell you
everything but I unable to say it."
"I am in love with you."
Mom.
What is it?
Well... Well...
Well... What?
Suresh has gone and sat at the
dining area. Shouldn't you serve him?
Why you asking me? Go and serve him.
No, I am really scared.
You are scared!
You are scared of that boy!
He quietly comes and leave quietly.
He doesn't even look at anyone.
Go on. He might feel bad.
What is this, mom?
- Go. Why are you afraid?
What nonsense? Go on.
She thinks he will eat her up.
Shall I serve you?
It's you.
- Yes.
Can't I serve you?
- No, that's not what I meant.
But your mom always...
Okay. I'll send her then.
No, that's not what I meant.
Little bit rice and a bit of yoghurt.
- Is that it?
That's enough.
- Hey.
If you eat so less, you will become
a patient instead of a doctor.
Pickle.
Why not? I thought I will
give you if you ask for it. - Is it?
Oh God! the lights are out.
So what? I am with you. Don't worry.
Oh God! Asha!
What happened, mom?
- What is this? The lights are out!
Yes, mom. - Be careful.
Don't fall off in the dark.
Oh God! It's so dark.
I am unable to find the matchsticks.
What do I do?
Ask her not to come here.
It's dark, she'll fall off.
Mom, don't come here
else you will fall off.
The lights are back.
Asha.
- What is it?
Come here.
- Asha!
I am coming.
What is it?
This.
- Oh no!
Listen.
Now what is it?
- I'll tell you. See this.
Munni is crying. Please go.
I am coming. Please go. - Alright.
Keep quiet.
No. No. Don't cry, dear.
Quiet. Good kids don't cry.
Mother, why is she crying?
- I don't know, son.
She suddenly woke up
and started crying.
Asha, come fast. What are you doing?
Oh God!
- No, dear Munni. No.
How hit you? No, dear. Don't cry.
Give her to me. Let me try.
No. No.
Quiet, dear. Quiet.
Quiet, dear. C'mon. Quiet.
- Quiet.
Take her. - Mother, I don't know if
her stomach is aching or something.
She is continuously crying.
Should I call the doctor?
- Go, son. Get him.
Get him soon.
- No, dear. No darling. Oh no!
Suresh! Suresh! Come back. Come here.
What happened?
- There's no need to get a doctor.
Look where she is going.
Did you understand
what the matter is?
She is missing her mom.
Oh God! Now we won't be
able to take care of her.
Send a telegram to Parvati
immediately and ask her to come.
Send her a telegram in my name.
- Okay.
Your telegram!
Nonsense! They will never
let us live peacefully.
I threw the telegram.
Why did you pick it up?
Yes, it's my mistake. Now let's go.
Where?
- Home.
Why?
- What's written in the telegram.
That Munni is crying.
- Asha has sent the telegram.
So what?
She has asked us to come.
Had it not been serious, she
wouldn't had sent the telegram.
Let it be. - If something happens
to her if we don't reach on time.
There are doctors there.
They will take care.
I have come to Mussorie,
I won't go back so soon.
You may do as you want. I won't
stay here anymore. I am going.
I see. So, this is the situation.
Listen.
- Yes?
I have a provision.
- Go ahead.
Our luggage will be here.
- It will.
We will go and see.
- Alright.
If Munni is fine...
- If she is fine.
We will come back soon.
- Yes. We will. Hurry up.
We will come back soon or else this
beautiful season will pass off.
God knows what sort of
hill station and what season.
Okay. Have this, dear.
Have it. Good girl.
Hey!
Look at her. She is so irritated.
Driver, hurry up.
God knows if Parvati received the
telegram. She hasn't come back yet.
What do we do? I don't understand.
Keep quiet, dear.
Look, Munni. Your mom has come.
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mom is back. C'mon!
- Mom! Mom!
Mom, you went away without us.
The cycle is stuck. It's stuck.
Help me.
Oh no! Sorry!
"You ignited love in me and fire
in my heart, now don't leave me."
"I am always yours but I was quiet
as I was shy, now tell me."
"You ignited love in me and fire
in my heart, now don't leave me."
"I am always yours but I was quiet
as I was shy, now tell me."
"A lover has come across your way."
"I wish to stay in your
arms all my life."
"A lover has come across your way."
"I wish to stay in your
arms all my life."
"The days are beautiful,
it is a season of love."
"Tell me what is the plan of
his majesty... Of his majesty."
"You ignited love in me and fire
in my heart, now don't leave me."
"I am always yours but I was quiet
as I was shy, now tell me."
"Don't put the pressure
of love on your heart."
"Your youthfulness is cruel,
take care of yourself."
"Don't put the pressure
of love on your heart."
"Your youthfulness is cruel,
take care of yourself."
"All of this is because
of the fun in love."
"You are in my eyes, hence I am not in
my senses. I am not in my senses."
"You ignited love in me and fire
in my heart, now don't leave me."
"I am always yours but I was quiet
as I was shy, now tell me."
"You ignited love in me and fire
in my heart, now don't leave me."
"I am always yours but I was quiet
as I was shy, now tell me."
Why did you call me?
Hey, I am asking you why
have you called me here?
Come with me.
Asha.
- First, tell me why did you call me?
Listen.
- Yes?
I want...
- What do you want?
I want you to be close to me.
- And?
I wish to keep seeing
you all the time.
Always?
- Yes, Asha.
Since some days I feel that if I
don't see you for even a minute,
I will go crazy.
You will go crazy if
you don't see me!
I am going crazy just
thinking about you.
Really?
- Yes.
Asha!
Idiot! How dare you!
Manohar!
- Move aside!
How dare you do that?
Get out of here!
Why are you standing here?
Leave! Leave from here!
I will break your bones!
- Shut up! Go inside!
You are here already.
Did you get your brother
to study here..
..or was it for him to fall in love my
sister and capture all my wealth?
Have you seen his actions?
He is studying with my money!
And he is having an
affair with my sister!
Idiot! Insolent man! Leave from here!
Go away!
How dare you! I will kill you!
Get out! I was helping
you in your studies.
Now you won't study!
You won't get a single penny.
If you ever come back,
I will kill you.
Get out!
Listen, I am sure something is wrong
because of which he did this.
I didn't know anything about it.
I am shocked that he
went to such an extent.
But now I take the responsibility.
I promise you.
Nothing will happen in the future.
Please forgive him this time.
Hey! What do you think
about yourself?
You shared your point of view
and now you are leaving.
What he has done...
- It isn't a small thing.
I agree he did a very wrong thing.
Is that enough? I am not ready
to listen to anything about it.
First, I want him out of this house.
I'll ask him to leave right now.
Yes, ask him to leave
and then come here.
I'll throw him out of the house.
Please don't stop his studies.
Why? Why not?
His studies are not for him.
It's for the betterment
of my other 6 sisters.
But he never thought of it.
Had he thought about it, he
wouldn't have done this.
You won't say a word to
your brother, will you?
Instead you are speaking to me.
Go from here!
I completely agree.
What my brother did was wrong.
He deserved more punishment
than what you gave him.
I'll get him to you right now.
Beat him up black and blue.
But please don't stop his studies.
I beg of you.
You know my attitude.
I will do what I say.
I am not used to go
back on my words.
Even I know that you won't
go back on your words.
You promised me that you will
fund his final year studies.
That too inside a temple.
Not just an ordinary place.
Yes, I did what I said. I have
been funding his studies.
I have taken care of
your family members.
But are you treating me the
way you are supposed to?
What are you saying?
What haven't I done?
- What have you done?
- Don't you know how to treat me?
What are you saying? First, tell me..
..what is my fault?
So that I don't repeat my mistakes.
Hey! You are my wife. Right?
Have you ever told me that its 10 pm..
..and I am standing
outside in the cold.
Have you asked me to come inside,
have some milk and fruits.
I feel like choking you to death.
I keep coming to you.
But you always go back in the reverse
gear thinking about the kids.
I know everything.
What do you mean?
- I know that you don't like me.
Wow! You are a great actor!
Did you get married
because you liked me?
I am a rich man. You married
me because of my wealth.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
have touched me either.
You are always with the kids
because you think you love them.
Do you really love them?
No need to cheat us.
Today, you came close to me but
this never happened before.
Today, you want to make sure
your brother keeps studying..
..that's why you are touching me.
Get lost!
Listen, you said that I
don't treat you the way..
you expect me to do.
I agree this might be true.
But this is because of my innocence.
Nothing else.
But when you say that I
don't love your kids.
That's not true. It's wrong.
What is wrong?
Do you really love these kids?
You are being pretentious.
No point in acting like crying. Go!
What about this studies?
- Don't talk to me about it. Go!
I have 6 helpless sisters.
One of them is dumb.
I don't care. Go! Get out!
Why did you do this? Do you remember,
you had promised me something?
Unless you get all
your sisters married..
..you won't think about your marriage.
Today, you forgot everything
because of a girl.
You forgot your promise!
Had I not got married to him
after listening to you..
..do you know what we might
have to go through?
We would've been out of our house,
the entire city would laugh at us.
Look at me.
Had you been concerned
about you dumb sister..
..would you be able to look at Asha?
What's the point of crying now?
He has asked you to leave.
I cannot keep you here
against his wishes.
Go away.
Listen.
If you have a bit of shame
then fulfill your promise.
Go and arrange for the money yourself.
Somehow, complete your
studies and become a doctor.
Until then if she
remains single for you..
..then come back as a
doctor in this house..
..and ask her from him officially.
Even then if he doesn't agree,
I will take care of everything else.
Now go away.
"A woman's life is like a swing,
at this end and at that end."
"Sometimes there's smile on her face,
sometimes tears rolling down her eyes."
"A woman's life is like a swing,
at this end and at that end."
Suresh! Come, son.
Didn't you go to college today?
No, mom. I thought of
meeting all of you.
Kamla, look Suresh has come.
Son, wait I'll get some tea for you.
Take it, son.
Suresh, may God always
bless Manoharlal.
He sends money every month,
we manage with it.
Please ask him to send this
month's money today itself.
Why, mom?
- There are no grains in the house.
How do I hide anything from you?
Your sisters haven't eaten
anything since yesterday.
What happened, son?
Nothing, mom.
There's no one to help me push it.
I think the government has solved
the problem of unemployment.
Alright. I think I
will have to push it.
What are you doing?
- Pushing the car.
Really? I hope you aren't
trying to steal anything.
No. I am pushing the car.
- I see that.
Thank you very much.
The petrol is over.
We'll have to take it
till the petrol pump.
You seem to be decent man.
Alright. Stop.
Hey, put 10 liter of petrol.
Come here.
Take this.
- What's this?
No one would pay anything for
pushing the car. I paid Rs 2 to you.
Do you know why? Because
you helped me voluntarily.
And you want more money.
- That's not what I meant.
I am desperately roaming around
to earn this Rs 2 since morning.
But I didn't know that I will
be able to earn it so soon.
My family is dying of hunger.
If you roam about in these
clothes all around the city
then the family is bound
to die of hunger.
That's not true. We had
trusted on a rich man's word.
That's why we are suffering.
Listen.
If you don't mind,
can I say something?
If you say something good then
why would I mind. Say it.
Please help me get a job.
- Job? Me?
How can I get you a job?
You seem to be an educated person.
Until I get a good job,
keep me as a cleaner.
Cleaner?
Will you be able to do it?
- Absolutely!
Alright. You will get Rs 3 everyday.
Agreed? - Agreed.
Come tomorrow.
- Listen.
Now what?
- Where's your garage?
You are strange. Even if you
ask an animal in the city..
..where the garage of a rich man's
brother, Ratanlal cab driver..
..they will tell you. Go on.
Kamla, Vimla, Shanta...
I have got food. - Suresh! Suresh!
Kamla, take this. Feed them.
Kamla. Kamla.
- You too have some.
Go slow. Don't shout.
What is the matter?
- Mom, I have got a job.
Job? What job?
- I will tell that later.
First, take this money, go and
get some rice and lentils.
I have had, Kamla. Give it to mom.
Keep it there, dear.
Mom, I am telling something.
Always remember it.
A man is the one who eats whatever
he gets out of hard work.
The one who wants to live
on someone else's money..
..suffers just like our
family is suffering.
This is my experience, mom.
I am telling the truth.
Take it.
- Right. You used to sit ideal here.
Now you are earning because
of us, so you are being rude.
Enough, man. How much will
you clean? Go and rest.
I don't need to take rest.
- At least my cab needs to rest.
You are cleaning as if
your washing vessels.
Elderly people have said, one should
work a bit and rest a bit as well.
When you start, you
don't seem to stop.
Hello, who are you?
I am Suresh here.
Uncle Suresh. I am Vinod.
Vinod, is dad home?
Yes, he is.
- Will you help me with something?
Sure. Tell me.
Make sure your dad
doesn't know about it.
Quietly go and get Asha on the line.
Uncle, if aunt comes here
dad will learn about it.
She is inside the room studying.
I'll take the telephone to her room.
Okay. You are very smart.
Go and give it.
Hey, why are you getting
the telephone here?
Uncle Suresh, wants to talk to you.
Hello, Asha here.
Suresh here. How are you, Asha?
Asha, why are you crying?
Tell me.
Suresh, I hope you won't forget me.
What are you saying, Asha?
If you were away from me then
I would've forgotten you.
But now we are one.
How can I forget you?
Is this guy speaking on
the phone or cleaning it?
Asha, how is Parvati?
- What can I say?
Parvati, keeps crying all day.
Complete your studies
anyhow, Suresh.
I came out from there with the
idea of completing my studies.
But Asha, my family members
are in a bad condition.
I can't even think about studying.
No. What are you saying?
Yes, Asha. Your brother, Manoharlal
is responsible for that.
Asha. Manoharlal.
My brother and sister.
Who is he?
They used to send money to our house,
now they have stopped it.
The condition of the
house is very bad Asha..
..but with effort I got a small job.
Whatever I earn,
I somehow manage to support my family.
But Asha I will try to
complete my studies.
Asha, I will call you
at this time every day.
And I will wait for your
call every day at this time.
Hello?
- Hello?
Who are you? Hello?
Idiot!
- I am Ratanlal. Not idiot!
Ratan! Was Asha speaking
to you all this while?
Yes, she was talking to me.
Who else?
Donkey! When you have left home,
why do you have to call?
Donkey's elder brother, if you can
talk properly to me then it's okay.
If you want me to talk like you..
..then I will talk to
you when I meet you.
I am cutting the call.
So, that's what you are doing.
Come out.
Look, don't get me wrong.
The girl I was talking
to is a relative.
Relative. What do you mean?
She is my brother-in-law's
younger sister.
Brother-in-law? What do you mean?
My sister's husband.
I was talking to his sister.
Since how many days is
this affair going on?
Well, I...
- Alright. Don't tell me.
Tell me one thing. If you face problems
and troubles, will you still be with her?
Even if I die...
- You will take her along.
I think so.
Does the girl feel the same way?
- Both of us feel the same way.
Now listen to what I have to say.
Stand here. Don't move.
Put your hands down.
Wait, I am coming.
Oh God! I think I will lose my job.
So, is she the relative you
were talking about. - Yes.
Is she your brother-in-law's sister?
Yes. Do you know who
your brother-in-law is?
Speak up.
- Who is he?
He is my elder brother.
Asha.
- Yes, Suresh. He is my brother.
That's great. You spoke
to her in front of me.
Ratan. - Quiet. Nowadays,
lovers speak over the phone..
..for such a long time.
I am telling the two of you.
If you want to talk to each other..
..let me know in the future. Got it?
Now go and talk.
Ratan, this is not the time to talk.
There are two very important things
that we need to finish right now.
Which ones?
- Didn't I tell you while coming here?
Manohar broke the promise he
made to Parvati during marriage.
Because of this his studies
and family is destroying.
What?
How many people do you
have in your family?
Eight of them including my mom.
Eight. How do you manage
your food everyday?
The Rs 3 you give, we
manage to get something.
Just Rs 3?
Nowadays, in Rs 3 not a single
person can eat properly.
How can eight people eat?
You are a strange man.
Anyway, first let's get
some food for the kids.
Then we will think about your
studies. - Come, Asha.
What are you looking at?
Help me out.
Are you asking me the amount?
I am selling anything. Where's your mom?
You might not get anything to
eat but you know to dance.
I am asking where is your mom.
You wish to answer this
also using dance moves.
Ratan, what are you doing here?
- Thank God you are here.
Why didn't you tell me that a strange
girl roams about in your house?
She was shouting so much...
- Ratan, don't you know.
No.
- She is my sister, Kamla.
She is dumb.
- Dumb?
Oh!
I am sorry. Whatever I
said was unknowingly.
It was my mistake.
I hope you have forgiven me.
Greetings!
- Greetings!
Suresh, who are they?
Ma'am, I am Vibhishan.
She is my sister. And my
elder brother is Ravana.
Where is this procession going?
They are my sisters.
- All of them are your sisters?
Ma'am, there is nothing
to worry about.
You can consider me as
your family member.
Take a look. We have got
all the grains possible.
Now no need to suffer.
Please cook something.
Today, even I will eat here itself.
Please come. Come. Let's cook fast.
Parvati's husband's younger sister.
What is she asking? - You are standing
quietly since you have come.
She is asking whether
you can talk or not.
Asha, you had said two things.
One was the food necessities
of this house. What's next?
Come here.
Now come with me and tell Parvati..
..that you have taken the responsibility
of this family from now on.
And somehow manage to help
Suresh finish his studies.
She keeps crying all day and
night as she is worried.
She has stopped eating as well.
What is this, mother?
- Have it, dear.
Have some.
- No, mother. I am not hungry.
You are lying.
You are lying, Parvati.
You are dealing with a monster.
What better can happen?
You will have to suffer.
Look, your kids are sitting with you.
Look at them.
Have something for them, dear.
Eat something.
I'll get water for you.
Mom, why are you sad?
I am not.
- Don't worry, mom.
When I grow up, I will earn a lot.
I will make sure uncle studies.
I will take care of you as well.
I'll feed you, mom.
You will eat, won't you?
Parvati, I thought that I will
feed you with my own hands.
But these have done it.
When these kids love you so much..
..then why are you sad?
Parvati, don't you
consider us as your own?
Then wipe your tears.
So what if Manohar has gone back
on his words? I am still alive.
Parvati, I visited your family.
Yes. And I have taken up the
responsibility of your family on me.
As far as Suresh is concerned, I will
make sure he completes his studies.
Hey cabbie!
What did you say?
You will make him a doctor!
Can you do it?
What do you have?
- What do you have?
I have a lot of money in many banks.
I have wealth. - If you have wealth,
I have determination.
If a man doesn't have anything,
how will determination help?
C'mon! Anything earned with
determination will remain for ages.
While the wealth you are talking
about will vanish soon.
I will make sure he becomes a doctor.
Not just that.
I will get Asha married
to him as well.
I see. So this is what
you are thinking.
I don't just think. Whatever I think
is what I will eventually do.
I would've done this long back
but Parvati came in between.
She wants him to become a doctor
first that's why I am not insisting.
First, let him become a doctor.
Then we'll see.
Do you money to make him a ward boy?
Whether I have money or not,
if I fail to help him become a doctor..
..then I won't ever
show my face to you.
Get lost! Let's see what you can do.
Greetings, sir.
- Greetings, Ratanlal. How are you?
I am fine. How are you?
- I am fine.
Sir, the car you had
given to me..
..thanks to the almighty
its running well.
Please keep this month's amount. Rs 200.
- What's the hurry?
There's a reason, sir.
- What's that?
Sir, I need Rs 1000 by
10th of this month.
Will you be able to help?
- You belong to a rich family.
When I was able to give you a car worth
Rs 15,000, then why not Rs 1000?
When do you need it?
- Right now if possible.
Right now? I don't
have any money now.
Do one thing. Come on the 7th.
Rs 1000 is nothing.
I can give you more.
No sir. I don't need
to build a college.
I needed the money to
get a boy educated.
Come on the 7th.
I will give it to you.
Sure?
- Absolutely!
Don't forget.
- I will surely give you.
Alright. Thank you.
Whether I have money or not, if I
fail to help him become a doctor..
..then I won't ever
show my face to you.
Greetings, sir.
Greetings.
- Today is 7th. Give me the money.
I am asking for money and you
are giving me the newspaper.
First read what is written
in the newspaper.
I don't have time to
read the newspaper, sir.
Please give me the money, I need to
meet the principal of the college.
Your brother has given an
advertisement in the newspaper.
Manohar? Advertisement?
- Yes. Read it.
'This is to inform
everyone that I have..'
'..earned all my wealth
through hard work.'
What a lie!
'My brother or sister
or any other relative..'
'..take any kind of loan
from anyone using my name..'
'..then it won't be
my responsibility.'
'Manoharlal.'
Forget about my brother, you
please give me the money.
Forgive me. I have been lending money
to you because of your brother.
Get an agreement from
him and take the money.
Agreement? Neither am I going to
ask and nor will he give it to me.
Then even I can't give you.
Don't joke, sir.
Please give me the money.
I am not joking.
Now listen to me carefully.
The loan amount that you give me
every month, if you ever become late..
..I will seize your car.
If I am unable to give it
then you can seize it.
But please give me Rs 1000 now.
Sir, if you don't help
me with this money..
..then a poor boy will not be
able to complete his studies.
Please look at me, sir.
Sir. Really?
Are you promises so fragile?
You asked me to come on the 7th.
After all you have
showed your true colors.
Have you read this?
If I give you a loan..
..then your brother will
lose his cool on me.
I am helpless. Forgive me. Bye.
Where is Ratan, Suresh?
- He said he will come with the money.
Today is 7th. Hasn't it
arranged for the money yet?
The money is arranged that's why
he has gone to get the money.
There he is.
Did you get the money, Ratan?
Tell me. Did you get the money?
Look at this.
Manohar has posted this on the
newspaper. Who will give us money now?
The lenders who were
ready to give money..
..aren't ready to pay a penny
because of this advertisement.
Whoever I went to ask for money,
he got me out from there.
That's fine brother,
but we should do something.
Only two days left for college to start.
So tell him to jump over
the wall and enter the college.
What nonsense ?
- Now you tell me what should I do?
I am very angry on brother.
- Listen!
It's not your brother's fault.
My fate is to be blamed.
Fate on your forehead
not in the newspaper.
Why drag your fate in it?
Of course it is.
I am really unfortunate.
I think I am destined in
not becoming a doctor.
It's the final year of my studies.
My sister had faith on a lender.
Even he couldn't pay her.
After that my sister sacrificed
her happiness for my studies.
Such a huge sacrifice couldn't
help me finish my studies..
..how will anyone's sacrifice
help me in anyway?
Forget it. Forget everything.
Now nothing can happen.
Whether it is possible or not,
leave that to us.
Ratan, come here.
Why, Ratan? Why are you
quiet listening to me?
We don't have any other way, Ratan.
If you agree then I'll go.
Else, I won't.
What are you thinking, Ratan?
Okay. Alright.
After all you are going there with the
idea of helping him in his studies.
No problem. Go.
Come, sir. Come.
Hello!
- Good evening, sir.
Good morning. Good morning.
Sir, why don't you come
to our hotel these days?
What's the use of
coming to your hotel?
Your hotel doesn't serve drinks.
What do you want, sir?
Tea, coffee, cold drinks, juices?
Do human beings drink these things?
I have already had what I want.
In fact I have some as well. See.
Keep it inside. The police might come.
- Why? Are you afraid?
Idiot! I am a permit holder.
Understood?
Who is this girl?
Good.
Has she come here alone?
- I am seeing her for the first time.
She is new here.
- Really? Go and find out about her.
No sir, I can't do this.
If my manager learns
about, I will lose my job.
First, listen to what I
want you to find out.
Find out whether she has
come here to have tea..
..or have food or to make a call.
Can't you find that out?
- Yes, I can.
What do you think?
- I thought something else.
What's the need of this?
- Go. Hurry up.
Sir, you were right.
She comes here for money.
Oh! Very good.
She has connections with a rich man.
- Didn't I tell you?
Go and find out more about her.
She is coming here. Go and find out
about her. - No, sir. I can't.
I am going.
- He is going! Idiot!
Can I do anything for you?
Sorry. Ma'am. Please listen
to me, ma'am. Excuse me.
Idiot! You came in between.
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Ratan, why are you worried?
- Keep quiet.
Today is 9th and tomorrow is 10th.
Asha had gone to get money.
She hasn't come back yet.
I won't go back on my promise
that I made to Manohar.
There she is. Asha, have you
got the money? - Yes, Ratan.
Come. Sit in the car.
Go. Hurry up and submit your fees.
Some people are still going.
We have time.
A huge responsibility
has been taken care of.
Take it.
Hey. Come here.
Is this the way to serve milk?
Are you showing your anger?
A waiter from the hotel also
serves it with a smile.
Beloved wife, is this milk?
You have made your face as if
you have served poison to me.
Look, if you want to stay
with me then keep smiling.
Be happy. Else, I will leave
this house and go. I am serious.
What are you saying? Come here.
Sit down.
Tell me something. What has happened
that is making you so angry?
If I have made a mistake then
you should let me know of it.
You can correct me at any
given point of time.
Then I will do what
you ask me to do.
You never do that instead you are
saying that you will leave this house.
If you leave then
what will we do here?
If you talk to me like
this just once a day..
..then I will be so happy.
Here, have some milk.
- You have it.
You first. If you don't
have it then even I won't.
Manoharlal!
- Who is it?
Loser! Gooseberry!
I can see that you sitting at ease.
I hope you are alright.
Who are you? Get up! Who are you?
Where are you from? - What?
What is this, Manoharlal?
- You didn't recognise me?
5 years ago the two of us
together took big contracts.
We earned a lot of money.
We used to be together all the time.
Have you forgotten already?
Fine. What do you want now?
Me? I have come to fix the marriage
of my son and your sister.
I know you son. He keeps roaming
about the city in a drunk state.
You want my sister to get
married to a drunkard. No way!
He is young man.
He is bound to do such things.
Once he gets married, things
will fall in place for him.
Forget about him. First you tell
me when will you mend your ways?
What's the point of mending
our ways at this age?
You enter a gentleman's house, climb the
staircase without informing anyone.
You enter his bedroom without
even knocking like an illiterate.
Above it all, you want my
sister to my your son!
Get lost!
- C'mon!
Don't sit! Get up!
Manoharlal, remember one thing.
Even I am wealthy just like you.
Go and enjoy with your wealth.
Get out!
I am going.
- Go!
Wow! The girl has come again.
Greetings! I have waiting for you.
Please say something. Listen. Listen!
Ma'am, please! She's gone. Gone.
She won't talk to me. Alright.
Take it, Ratan. - What is this?
Suresh gave his exams a month ago.
Why have you brought money then?
- How will his family survive?
Oh! So you are worried
about his family already!
I am right here and so is my cab.
Alright. No problem. Give.
- How did his exams go?
How would I know? He is right here.
Ask him yourself. - Go ahead.
My exams were good, Asha.
I will surely pass.
Ratan, as soon as his results are out,
I should be the first one to know.
Surely. But before Manohar
learns that you are here..
..please leave immediately. Go. Go on.
Ratan, the results will
be out in some time.
Why did you send her away then?
- You are very innocent.
In case, out of ill-fate you fail..
..then she would've been shattered.
She would've fainted here itself.
Do you get it?
The newspaper has come.
Wait! Give it to me!
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Here it is!
1st Class! Take a look.
Wow, son. Great!
You did a fantastic job.
You have passed with first class.
Ratan, this has been
possible because of you.
C'mon! I did not write the exams.
Doctor Suresh, I have just kept
my promise unlike my brother.
Come. Let's inform Parvati first.
Come.
Parvati! Parvati! Parvati!
- What is it?
Parvati!
- Tell me, what is the matter?
Parvati, you will be so proud today.
Your wishes have come true.
Your brother... Come here.
He is a doctor now.
Take a look. His percentage is given.
Take a look.
Ratan, you helped my brother complete
his studies and not just that..
..you gave a life to
6 ill-fated girls.
It's because of your
blessings, Parvati.
Go and take her blessings. C'mon!
Suresh.
- Parvati.
Parvati, I need to talk to you
about something important.
He is a doctor now and can take care
of all problems, even heart problems.
Manohar has some
serious heart issues.
I mean he is stone-hearted.
Don't mind, Parvati.
Doctor Suresh, why don't you start
your practicing from Manohar. - Quiet.
If you say such things,
he will lose his cool.
Yes, I know my brother.
But today I will say what I have to.
- C'mon, doctor.
Brother.
- Hey, why are you shouting?
I am not shouting, my dear brother.
Remember, you had said one day.
What did you say then? That I won't
be able to fund his studies.
Take a close look. Today, I have
managed to helped him become a doctor.
MBBS. His percentage is here.
Take a look.
Don't be mad, brother. I have
come here with a good news.
Also, I would like to
request something to you.
Now get Asha and Suresh married.
This is so that you
don't feel left out.
Do you think I am ready
for this association?
Whether you agree or not, I am ready.
How will that help?
- Oh really!
They will become husband & wife.
- Come, doctor.
Listen. Come here.
The beggar Manoharlal must have
had food here so many times.
You must've served him as well.
Forget about it. For how long
will you keep cribbing about it?
What did you say? Am I cribbing?
Do you know what he said to me?
He called me an illiterate man!
Won't I feel bad about it?
Sir!
- Get lost!
Mr. Manoharlal has come.
- Who?
Mr. Manoharlal.
- Oh!
Mr. Manoharlal! God has sent him.
I will seek revenge.
Take these chairs away. Hurry up!
Listen, sit here.
- What are you doing?
Leave me.
- I said, sit here.
Listen! Go and send him inside.
Hurry up!
Let him come.
Greetings, Mr. Dinanath! Wow! What a
beautiful pair this is! - Who are you?
Aren't you able to see that a
husband and wife are sitting alone?
How dare you enter the room without
knocking like an illiterate?
Do you have any manners?
Mr. Dinanath, I know you are seeking
revenge for what I said that day.
The thing is that I had a small
argument with my wife that day.
That's why I lost my cool.
Everyone loses someone's cool but
that doesn't mean you speak rubbish.
That day it was my mistake.
But you are my friend.
If you don't forgive me, who will?
Listen, today I have come with a
suggestion. - What suggestion?
Get your son and my sister married.
Forget about the old tiffs.
Don't be mad.
Manoharlal, I wanted you to realise.
That's done.
Listen, get a chair.
There's no need for chair.
I am happy now. Let's go. - Where?
Let's begin with the preparations.
You are strange man.
It isn't my marriage
First, let the girl and boy meet.
- Get the boy along. Let's go.
My son isn't at home now.
I will get him to your house on an
auspicious day. - Don't forget.
Yes. - Ma'am, it seems he
is still a bit mad at me.
It would be your responsibility
to get him. I'll take your leave.
Asha!
- Yes, Manohar.
You will not go out
of house from now on.
If you do, you will
see the worst of me.
Driver! Where are you?
- I am here, sir. Please come.
Hey, what's this?
A cab always has 2 colors.
But yours is just one color.
- This is a private cab, sir.
This runs inside the city as
well as outside the city.
I have my license.
Please come and sit.
I asked you because we are going
to see a potential bride.
Oh! - If someone stops in the middle
of the road and creates a ruckus..
..we'll get worried unnecessarily.
There will be no problem, sir.
Whoever has traveled in it
to visit a potential bride..
..have got married happily.
Please come. There's nothing to worry.
That's great.
Gopal, behave yourself in front
of them. - Sir.
Have you come here to
meet a potential bride?
Why?
- Had you come in your own car..
..even then you wouldn't
have received any honor.
You have come here in a cab!
This house belongs to
a very rich man, sir.
Am I a poor man?
- No.
Both are equal.
- Isn't it?
Yes. Go on.
Come.
Hey, come. Sit down.
We thought you will be coming in
the morning. Anyway, no problem.
What would you like? Tea or coffee?
First, we wish to meet the girl.
Tea and coffee can be done later.
- Alright.
Mom!
Hey! Did he call you? Sit down!
Parvati, it is late. They are waiting.
Where is Asha?
Asha is coming.
- Yes, send her soon.
She is coming in sometime.
- No problem.
We thought you will be
coming in the morning.
That's why she got ready
in the morning itself.
When you didn't come, she changed.
Now she is getting ready again.
Oh! She is getting ready again.
- Yes, she is coming.
Okay.
C'mon. Wipe your tears.
Go on.
I would suggest let them get
married as soon as possible.
Find an auspicious time
in this week itself.
That's the reason I had come
to meet you the other day.
Forget about it.
Dad.
- What is it?
Is she the one?
- Yes.
Is she good?
Then what's the problem.
- Do you know who she is?
His sister.
- No. I am not saying that.
We will talk about all this at home.
So? I hope he likes her.
What is your son saying?
Nothing. He is asking
is she your sister?
Yes. Just get the auspicious
time for marriage fixed.
Let's get it done this week itself.
We'll take your leave...
Wait. Please have some tea.
Now we will have a
grand wedding feast.
Alright. No problem.
Greetings!
- Greetings!
Let's go.
Ratan, won't win.
He was challenging me!
Dad. Dad, that girl...
Oh God! Why are you
irritating me so much?
I have fixed your marriage with her.
That's not the point. That girl goes
to the hotel and earns money often.
Shut up, idiot!
A rich man's sister
will go to the hotel!
I am telling the truth. I have seen
her in the hotel a lot of times.
You must have seen some other
girl in a drunk state.
Crazy fellow!
He is telling the truth.
- Shut up! What is right?
Don't be mad, sir.
Nothing is hidden from a cab driver.
I have seen her go
to the hotel myself.
What?
- Yes.
Manoharlal is such a creep.
So this is how he became a rich man!
Do you still want to get
your son married to her?
Reverse the cab.
- That's a like a man!
Manoharlal! Manoharlal!
Please come. What happened?
You have come back.
Is the date fixed? - Shut up!
After seeing what your sister does,
no one would want to marry her.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Are you trying to fool us?
Am I fooling you? Really!
Yes, you are.
You pretend to be a rich man!
When I came home to talk about your
sister's marriage with my son..
..you insulted me and
asked me to leave.
Then you came to my house asking
to consider the alliance.
I knew it that moment
that something is wrong.
What's wrong?
What nonsense are you talking?
Am I? Your sister goes to the
hotel to earn money. Yes or no?
What did you say? Get out of here!
Now that the truth is out,
you are getting wild! - Get out!
A rich man's sister doesn't
need to do that. - Rubbish!
Rich man! Not just once, my son has
seen your sister a lot of times there.
Your son is not truthful either.
Not just him.
Even the cab driver said so.
Which driver? - He is waiting outside.
Call him and ask.
Driver!
Oh! It's you!
So you are doing this so
that they don't get married!
Hey!
- It is true.
Asha used to go to the hotel.
Now what do you have to say?
- Shut up!
Hey!
- I am telling the truth.
So, our sister Asha used to go to
the hotel! - Why don't you ask her?
What if she refuses?
First, call her and ask.
- What is she refuses?
Then I will kill myself.
- Asha!
Did you go to the hotel?
- Yes.
Why did you go?
- For money.
For money!
First, ask her why she needed money.
Then you can do what you want.
Ask her.
Why did you need money?
To help Suresh finish his studies.
- You went to the hotel for that!
Is it right for a girl to
go to the hotel like that?
Was it right for you to promise a poor
family and go back on your words?
Shut up! Else...
- I won't keep quiet!
Suresh wasn't able to study because
you went back on your words.
His family couldn't survive.
Thanks to our sister that Suresh was
able to complete his final year.
Because of that his family
will be able to survive.
Ratan, she went to the
hotel for a dumb girl.
She went there for 6 helpless kids.
Why? Why will our
sister go to the hotel..
..to feed an unknown family?
Not just for that, she completed a
responsibility you had taken up.
So, it is true that you
went to the hotel.
That too for money.
Not for money, Manohar.
For Suresh's studies.
How dare you do something like that?
One needs to be courageous
to be able to do good.
So, you knew that she
went to the hotel!
What do you mean?
I was the one to send her there.
Idiotic girl! Go and die!
Did you really go?
- Yes, I did.
You did! Idiotic girl!
Shameless woman!
You have defamed our family.
Had you died for Suresh's
studies, I would've been happier.
Shameless! Die!
How can you be so shameless to say
that you went to a hotel to earn?
How dare you! How dare you!
How dare you!
Parvati! Listen to me.
What is left to be heard?
You were the one who sent her there.
Yes, I did.
Shameless! You sent a
girl to the hotel.
You sent your sister to the hotel!
Yes, I sent my sister to the hotel.
You did! You did! You did!
- Parvati!
Even you had been to the hotel once.
Right?
Why are you quiet now?
All the girls who go to the
hotel don't always do wrong.
Do you really think Asha
will do something like that?
Had she done anything wrong..
..do you think I would've been
standing here alive in front of you?
This great man standing here.
My brother.
I had to lie so that he
realizes his mistakes.
Lie!
- Yes, Parvati.
You just beat us up really quick.
Parvati, you were in love
with someone, right?
Do you know that he was fighting a
case for the wealth worth Rs 4,00,000?
Do you know that he had won that
case and he got that money?
Do you know that he made
a hotel from that money?
Do you know that this
is the same hotel?
No. - Then you don't
know us either, Parvati.
Parvati, he met Asha one day and
asked her about you and Suresh.
He had asked her to inform him
if we ever needed his help.
He said if he was able to help,
he would be more than happy.
Asha told me about it.
When we desperately needed money,
I asked her to get the money.
He isn't an unknown person.
We would've returned the money.
That's when Asha went to the
hotel and got the money.
Even mom knew about it.
- Mom!
What is it?
- Mother, what is all this?
Yes, dear. I agreed to it.
Nothing is wrong in this.
I did this to make him
realise that he is wrong.
I agreed to this so that
this family is happy.
Parvati, you are so pious and pure.
A girl from the family that you are in
can never do anything wrong.
Can Asha do anything wrong?
Manoharlal, stop!
Stop it, Manoharlal!
Let me die!
- Stop it! Stop!
Wait! Stop!
- I have committed a sin.
I doubted my own sister.
Not just you, even we
did so, Manoharlal.
But now that we know the
truth, we have learnt..
..that your sister is a gem.
I am ashamed of myself.
If possible, please forgive me.
- What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Suresh, please forgive me.
Come. Come here.
Always be happy.
- Wow!
Whatever God does is for the good.
You are behind all the good
things that happened to me.
I just learnt that you helped my
brother complete his studies.
I will always remember your favors.
Parvati, I am not here to
hear good things about me.
I have come here to ask
something from you.
What?
- I hope you won't refuse.
If I am able to give you,
I definitely will.
First, tell me that
you have forgiven me.
Forgiveness? For what?
I hope you remember,
you had asked me..
..to get married to someone
and be happy. - Yes.
After a long time, I really liked
a girl and I got married to her.
Really? Why did you have
to apologise for that?
I got married without informing you.
That's why.
I have got my wife along.
Where is she?
- Wait.
I'll get her.
Kamla!
Sir, you are great!
May God always bless you.
Mr. Dinanath, don't you wish to go back?
The cab meter is on.
Let's go. Let's go.
- I don't sit in cabs much.
I had to sit today because of him.