- Hey, what's up guys,
MKBHD here on Super Saf TV.
- This is iJustine on Super Saf TV.
- Hey guys, this is
Gaurav, better known as
Technical Guruji on Super Saf TV.
- Hi I'm Michael Josh for Super Saf TV.
- What's going on guys, I am
Jenna Ezarik on Super Saf TV.
- Hey there guys its Mr. Q, friendly
neighborhood Qatari on Super Saf TV.
- Hey guys, its Krystal on Super Saf TV.
- Hey guys, this is
Austin Evens on Super Saf,
and it is dub dub DC my friends.
Which is apparently like
what the cool kids call it.
I don't know.
- What's up guys, Saf here on SuperSaf TV
and we've just finished WWDC which was
crazy packed with lots and lots of stuff.
Lets go and find out what the reactions
from some of my friends have been.
- Man that was a lot, that
was a lot of, of a lot of
announcements in a short amount of,
not even a short amount
of time, it was two hours.
- It was rapid fire, like
every single time like
a new screen popped up it would disappear
in like two seconds
because they would have
so much information that was
just happening so quickly.
- Dub, dub, dub, dub, dub, dub, dub, dub.
- Well you know, "dub
dub" is a software show,
but I was always excited,
its always exciting
when there hardware and we got that today.
I mean after how many years?
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18,
six years of waiting!?
We now have a new, Mac pro so that's
pretty exciting, for creators especially.
- Okay not gonna lie, when I first saw it,
it looked like a cheese grader.
I was like, is this a
new kitchen appliance?
But the power behind the Mac Pro
is absolutely incredible.
- Everything man, but I
liked the Mac Pro of course.
Like being the hardware guy,
that's the one that excites me.
- That Mac Pro, mmm mmmm.
- And you, made a little Instagram video.
It was like: "do you think
their gonna show the Mac Pro?"
I was like of course not.
Well they did and it is
absolutely fantastic.
I am so excited to spec this thing out
because I feel it'll probably be like
$75,000 like by the time
you spec that thing out.
Maybe even more because if you
wanna get multiple monitors.
I don't even know, oh my gosh.
Am I gonna be doing an unboxing of
a hundred thousand dollar Mac Pro?
- Has everybody been
talking about the Mac Pro?
- Mac Pro modularity
we've been asking for this
for ages, and now we have a computer
which basically we can keep
for lets say 5, 6, 7, 8 years
without worry of having to
throw away and buy a new one.
- But like that Mac Pro
looked really dope, right.
And what I really appreciate
is that they actually
gone sort of above and beyond
to make sure this is super modulate.
So its not one of those things
where, oh you have to buy
like the Apple adding parts all the time.
Or anything like that.
Obviously the offer
though is a nice sort of
as a feature to have, but you could
also just buy your own
graphics card and throw it in.
As long as you have the
drivers, it should work.
And so I was able to take
a look on the inside.
The cooling seems to be solid,
its got a huge power supply, but
importantly you just got a
bunch of PCI slots, right.
Put whatever you want in there.
And it even seems like that zion,
even though I wasn't able to
actually take off heat sinc,
is also fairly user upgradable.
So its one of those things where its like,
imagine if Apple makes a
super high end desk top
with all the features of
a super high end desk top,
and the price of a
super high end desk top.
- Oh my gosh, there's so much stuff,
like just where do we even, watch OS
I mean the IOS, oh gosh
I'm just, new maps.
The new maps looked actually amazing.
Oh, and also Siri, she has new voice.
- The photo and video editing on IOS 13
was really cool, because
I feel like for me
that will replace that
extra step that I do
in visco for videos at least, like
Instagram videos you know
like editing on there,
but straight on the
camera app is really cool.
- Think that I've been
looking forward to the most
of course is dark mode.
I'm a simple man, I just
want to save my battery life.
- Actually, I lied my first highlight
is gonna be dark mode IOS.
That's what we wanted,
I feel like we've been
wanting this for the longest
time and its finally here.
- Dark mode, hello?
- The dark mode like we were expecting
that more to come and its happened.
Also the new watch faces
of course and the new maps.
So like a few things.
- Well obviously dark
mode, like its a favorite.
I was waiting for it
for the longest time so
I use dark mode on twitter, on my Mac Book
on everything so definitely dark mode.
- Yo dude, this is
actually, there was a lot of
stuff here, right so its cool to see like
watch OS updates, I'm actually like
low-key excited to see all the iPad stuff.
Like, for me the iPad Pro is
so close to being a machine
which can really be like a
good for almost everything
besides editing sort of thing.
Like its super lightweight,
I love the software
I love the hardware, its just nice
its actually getting
some more Pro features.
- So I'm a big fan of
the iPad Pro, last year.
And that's really like the tablet getting
closer to the laptop and you know
Apple has tried to keep
those two worlds separate,
but we're seeing over the last two years
Mac OS and IOS kind of merge
the two worlds together
and that new iPad OS is
probably a step in the
right direction, I'm pretty
excited as an iPad Pro user
because that's really going
to increase my productivity
and be able to use that
tool to do more things.
- Oh, Side Car?
The iPad is a second display and also
you can use it as a
tablet, which is amazing
because I love using tablets.
- Obviously the Mac Pro is the
one we're all excited about.
That stand and that
monitor got my attention.
The $5,000 monitor with
an extra $1,000 stand,
I don't know if a lot
of people caught that,
and then there's another
$1,000 for the matte finish.
So that's an exciting
display, but its very pricey.
But its for the pros so
we'll see how that goes.
And then there's a ton
of features in Mac OS
in watch OS, in IOS, in iPad OS.
Its all good stuff.
- There's so much stuff,
I don't even know.
This made no sense.
- And there we go guys, highlights from
DubDub, its been absolutely
awesome, so much stuff.
For me personally, dark
mode, something that I was
definitely looking forward to, you
guys have hear me say
"dark mode all things"
so its great that we now have that.
And also, sidecar, being
able to use your iPad Pro
with the Apple pencil,
that should be really cool.
I know somebody who uses
that Wacom bamboo tablet
so it will be nice to be
able to experience that.
And Mac Pro, I mean that thing is a beast.
I know there's going to be a
lot of cheese grater jokes,
but how powerful it is, is pretty crazy.
And that's it for this video.
Make sure you subscribe
to all of my friends.
Big shout out to them for joining in.
Their channels will be linked
in the description below.
And if you enjoyed this video,
then be sure to smash that like button.
Thanks for watching this
is Saf on SuperSaf TV.
I'll see you next time.
Also don't forget to
subscribe to me as well.
- I'm just gonna ramble and hope you
make me look good in post.
- I *gibberish* okay hold on sorry
*laughter*
- *laughter* stop you're messing me, its
its been too long of a day.
- I don't actually have one, that
sounds dumb, don't use that.
I love that you're able to actually...
I'm definitely gonna use that
- It's about three kidneys,
is the rough, rough price.
The display is cool
- Two of yours one of mine.
- I only have two, so I
think I can only give up one.
- We all throw one in
- I'm good, I'm good.
(upbeat music)