this is a jet powered car and that is Mr
Beast how's it going and if this car
can't jump over those school buses my
video's ruined and to make things even
more interesting we put this whole thing
together in about 30 days and we have no
idea if it works send the jet engine go
go
go I'm James welcome to
Donut we have a LIF off so Mr Beast hit
us up and asked us to build him a jet
powered car this dude is the biggest
YouTuber in the world so obviously we
said yes and we're all super stoked and
optimistic about this project there's no
way there's no way come 30 days to build
a rocket car why not explain okay so
technically we have a few problems to
actually pull this off we're going to
need to find a car that we can attach
Jets to we're going to need to find Jets
and then figure out how to put them on
the car and we need a way to control the
car without someone having to be inside
of it luckily we're really good at
buying dumb Vehicles so first things
first we hopped on Greg's list to find
ourselves a
car and this is what we ended up with
it's a 1997 Firebird a car that sort of
looks fast but it's not something that
we really feel too bad about destroying
you ready to hear this baby
purr that's what a V6 supposed to sound
like take the thing for a spin there's
something loose on this front left I
don't know what it is I thought I could
hear a little squeaky noise coming from
the left rear listen the thing really
just has to live for about 2,000 more
miles so now that we have our car all we
got to do is put Jets on
it um you just can't go to Jet
engine.com but we're not even figur
we're not even figuring that part out
turns out buying Jets isn't as easy as
you'd think you need all kinds of
permits to buy the type of engines that
we need plus we've never worked with
jets before and haven't no idea how to
even use them but we told Mr Beast we'd
build him a jet powered car so we have
to find a solution and that's when
Jeremiah came up with a brilliant idea
go on YouTube and type in jet engine and
that's when he found a guy who just
might be crazy enough to help us out
Matt take it away yeah my name is Matt
from warp
perception turns out Matt has put jet
engines on a bunch of things not only
does Matt have access to the jet engines
We need he also volunteered to help us
put them on the car all right Matt so Mr
Beast wants us to jump a car over the
length of a football field is this
something you think we're going to be
able to do ah yeah yeah that's
doable so we have our Jets but that
brings us to a new problem Matt lives
all the way in Chicago and we're going
to need to bring the car to him now you
might not be surprised to learn that we
didn't exactly buy the best conditioned
Firebird so we're going to need to do
some road trip prep I will see you in
Chicago very soon Matt see you here
you're welcome in Chicago yeah
baby step one install a sick vinyl wrap
we're also going to need beefier
suspension to withstand the impact of
the ramp at high speed we've got a few
things to do to get this thing ready for
the big jump uh we're going to be
replacing the stock wheels and tires
with a six set of esrs and we have some
fresh suspension just to freshen this
thing up a little bit so that we leave
the ramp nice and predictably after a
few days of work it's finally time to
hit the
[Music]
road Justin is making great time and
certainly nothing bad will happen in
Nebraska what happened whole pulley fell
off there's supposed to be a pulley
right here and now the belt is just
rubbing against this be
bearing we only have 15 days left before
jet car needs to be in North Carolina
and not broken so unfortunately we have
to get a trailer and tow the car the
rest of the way to Matt
Shop push it into the shop all right
guys I'm here ready to get started
what's up Matt what's up Justin what's
up first order of business now that
we're in Chicago check out that shiny
Bean second order of business fix that
pulley that made the car undrivable so
all I need to do replace the belt and
replace this pulley should be simple
15-minute job never works out that way
and with the F bird fixed it's finally
time to check out the Jets why not take
Matt's jet powered scooter out for a
spin dude this thing is
terrifying dude this guy's a warrior man
just should not be doing that now when
you think of a jet engine you probably
think of the big old Honkers on a
fighter jet we're going with something
obviously a lot smaller now specifically
this is a single stage turbo jet engine
it actually has a lot of similarities
with a turbo that you'd find in a car
engine now there are a couple components
to focus on now this compressor wheel is
what pulls in air into the combuster now
this would be the equivalent of a
combustion chamber in your car now air
gets pulled through and compressed in
the combuster fuel gets squirted in
through these nozzles right here now you
have compressed air you have fuel you
get spark in there when that spark
happens you get exhaust coming out which
spins the turbine wheel and this turbine
wheel is on the same shaft as the
compressor so you get more air being
pulled through so you can see how
similar that is to how turbo works now
the excess exhaust gas gets shot out
this nozzle right here and you get
forward thrust we'll be attaching seven
of these Jets to our Firebird for a
total of 500 50 lb of thrust now that's
not much compared to a commercial plane
like a 747 which makes over 100 times
that but when we combine this with the
acceleration from our V6 it should give
us enough beans to clear the football
field also unlike a regular car the Jets
will keep our Firebird accelerating even
after it leaves the ramp pretty cool so
now we just need to slap seven of these
bad boys on the back of our Firebird
should be easy right all right so we are
waiting on some parts to get here supply
chain issues have delayed some of the
crucial parts to mount the jet engines
so instead we got to move on to the RC
system our solution to this problem is
to attach big servos to the steering
wheel and the throttle so that Nolan can
drive it like a regular remote control
car we're pretty much building a full
scale RC
car going to do this sort of uh quick
coupling adapter the steering wheel
Amazon does not have the hub adapter for
the steering wheel for this car for some
reason so it looks like we're just going
to have to make it and I love making
parts from leftover scraps now that our
hub adapter is made everything's looking
good and moving swimly our plan actually
worked so yes good thing happen this
remote control system here actuates the
brake pedal as well as a there's a
steering servo so now there's no you
know human controls so the wiring is
good the system has power oh my God it's
turning what that's so sick
[Music]
sure what that is sick at the P look at
the PD oh it's
moving look I'll be honest I am a little
nervous cuz I want us to be able to jump
this thing but I'm also really excited
to do this like this is amazing this is
super
cool after a few days of working on the
RC system the missing jet Parks finally
arrived so now that we're this far the
only real thing that's causing us issues
is we don't have a lot of time to test
it we are in a rush so uh hopefully we
can get as much development time in this
very short amount of time we have
[Music]
left all right it's been a long day we
have the fuel lines hooked up all we got
to do is put some fuel in the tank and
we get to fire it up and here it for the
first time you nervous yeah to test this
we have to start all seven engines at
the same time to check the amp draw we
are in the neighborhood it's 1 p.m. but
got to do what we got to
[Music]
do the Jets are finally running or so we
thought so we got one 1 two three yeah
four
started three didn't so we're going to
do something with that battery and try
again right only two of the engines had
actually fired up at Full Throttle
meaning we have a serious wiring issue
to figure out and the jump is like in 3
days so we have no choice but to deal
with those issues when we get
there this is WD40 brand and guess what
they're the sponsor of today's awesome
video Let's Go the WD40 brand is more
than just a classic name they're game
changers born out of literal rocket
science you can Google it and they've
got more than just the original WD40
formula with their Innovative specialist
line we're talking dozens of specialized
heavyduty Solutions with tailored
Delivery Systems for the garage the
Factory The Farm wherever the tough job
is with Delivery Systems like easy reach
smart straw and big blast the original
WD40 formula and specialist line help
Next Level Pros get the job done right
we've been using WD40 products at donut
since the very beginning and to be
honest everyone around the world's been
using them since 1953 for a reason if it
works great in outer space it works even
better here on Earth so whatever kind of
Next Level Pro you are find your next
level solution at WD40
docomo so now while the boys made their
way to North Carolina I hopped on a jet
powered vehicle of my own a
[Music]
jet
we just found out that Nolan and Phil
and Justin are about 2 hours uh late
they're 2 hours later than they said
they would be
here so it's not a really great look for
donut there they are jet car has landed
with all of us finally together we got
our first look at Mr Beast
jump a full4 mile drag STP leading to a
massive ramp over an entire football
field with 12 school buses on it I love
the optimistically tall Landing ramp as
well Landing ramp is taller than this
ramp and Meanwhile we're sitting here
thinking should we tell him our car
doesn't work
yet we still have to address all the
problems with the car plus we haven't
done any testing to make sure Nolan can
actually drive the thing without
crashing and to make things even worse
we were informed that the algorithm
doesn't like green Flames so we had to
take them off okay we're at the track
the jump is tomorrow but we still don't
know what's up with those five engines
that didn't fully spin up so uh we got
to test that and then we opened up the
trunk and found another problem we got a
giant pool of kerosene sitting in the
bottom of the trunk the kerosene fuel
from the Jets spilled everywhere during
the road trip and all of the electronics
got soaked oh that was sick did it all
come
out cap this dude that's a lot of oh my
God we spilled a bunch of kerosene on
our engine control units so uh Matt and
I have taken them out of the car Matt's
going to clean them uh and then we'll
put them back together hopefully no
kerosene has gotten into weird
electrical connections and messed it up
I'm so tired and this is very stressful
if the electronics don't work neither
will our Jets so we have no choice but
to sit here and wait for them to dry
out a few hours later everything seems
dry enough I think they the purple
temperature so Matt and Nolan wired up
the first jet but I'm actually nervous
here because we won't be able to get
another one if one of these uh gets
damaged so no sleep now it's time to see
if it actually
[Music]
works okay so that's one that we know
Works uh so now we just kind of have to
connect the stuff back together how we
already did and hopefully all seven fire
back up we're going to test all seven
engines at the same time make sure they
can all hit Full Throttle at the same
time Perfect all right so we're in the
car now uh we're going to see how much
the Jets can move the car on their own
we're going to put in neutral and see
what happens
uh
yeah
chcken down dude I'm not I'm not I'm not
Mak that bro let's cut
it no no no that's not what I me that
was no engine that was just all jet all
Jet and neutral nice okay so that was
only slightly terrifying uh but we have
run out of daylight and we still haven't
tested the RC system yet so we have a
very little time in the morning and then
we have to do the
[Music]
jump we're back I've got a full night's
sleep and I feel great okay we got 2
hours until Mr Beast gets here 2 hours
sounds like a lot of time but it's
really not when we got here the jet
engines were pouring gas all over the
track luckily we addressed that still
the brakes don't work I've never driven
it with the RC system but I guess the
good news is that Jimmy gets here in 2
hours
so we have 20 minutes left we are
finally testing the RC system uh we're
still having some trouble with the
brakes right down to the wire as we
always are okay here we go
so it works perfect all right we're
going to go to the uh midpoint location
where I'm going to be sitting for the
Run car uh works now we just got to test
it with driving with the fpv system get
some practice in oh yeah not only will
Nolan be controlling an actual car with
a remote controller but he's also going
to be wearing fpv goggles from a drone
and we have done absolutely no testing
with any of this stuff either we better
not crash it now cuz we only got one jet
[Music]
car
my
god oh oh I just lost feed dude break's
not working oh yeah it is dude that was
a minute of of helmet time before it cut
out like the feed cut out uh a little
stressed right now yeah uh near the end
of the track like the feet on the
goggles cut out so I just lost control
man dude that was a little
nerve-wracking I got to got to be
honest big time big time but before we
can figure out a solution to the goggles
we just got worded that the Beast has
landed Jesus
Christ oh my God oh my God are you going
to start all the way down there
thankfully Mr Beast and his friends are
all impressed I'm bringing my 2-year-old
out here this is like I feel like going
to make me the coolest dad ever so I
turn this into the hypothetical wheel
turn oh my God
oh that's so cool where it is very cool
but I don't I don't know I'm just used
to things breaking whenever sometimes I
touch stuff like this and then it just
stops working and it delays set by it's
not going to stop working okay here just
I here make sure it still works all
right I'll see you in a minute car got
speed car where is it going all you I'm
done and now it's time for the jump but
here's the thing we're not going to jump
jet car just yet we're actually going to
jump not a jet car not a jet car a it's
just a it's just a regular it's a
regular now in order to demonstrate how
good jet car is Mr Beast also bought a
second Firebird that we also need to
jump off a ramp and the entire time that
we've been working on jet car Justin has
been working all day mouning the remote
control system to not a jet car but
there are two problems number one the
fpv issue if Nolan falls out of range he
can crash the car so I came up with the
idea to drive down the drag strip in a
side by side to stay close close enough
to the signal problem solved but there's
also a more complicated problem I can
hear the bottle moving there you go not
a jet car might look the same as jet car
but it's a different model gear and our
remote controlled gas pedal won't work
with the newer throttle body and we have
no time to fabricate a new system so
we'll need another way to accelerate the
car we didn't get this car working the
way we wanted but we're going to do it
the caveman way throw a brick on the
pedal and send it to the Moon
bricks all right we're just waiting for
the goahead from the team to send the
stock car down over the ramp I still
have no camera no camera no camera okay
is it good good to go is uh Justin clear
does Justin have a walk no no
no oh go
[Music]
go
okay it's
going
[Music]
he destroyed that wow oh my
God we got to get over there where's the
golf cart D dude that was the sickest
thing ever Against All Odds not a jet
car was a success Nolan laced it holy
crap boys this is insane it went through
a bus it went right through the
emergency
exit but it's not time to celebrate yet
got
it so sick oh man oh my ridiculous oh my
God I can't wait any longer J in let's
do we still have a jet car to jump and
if it doesn't do better than not a jet
car the whole project will be a failure
and we'll be so embarrassed and with the
sun going down on North Carolina the car
was as ready as it can be it's time to
line it up on the drag strip and get
into position okay I still I do not have
camera feed we still don't have camera
feed you have no camera feed we still
don't have any feed from the fpvs we
lost the feed into the fpv you are
currently trying to figure it out
because that is the scariest thing that
can
happen okay I got it I got it we have
visual let's go is uh throttle I hear
them I hear them they're throttle all
right jet car time baby the car is in
park why' they put it in park God damn
it God damn it send the jet engine put
the car in
drve back on Full Throttle wait for
confirmation
go wait for
confir H here we
go here we go here we go
James Here Comes oh it's going way
faster it's going so much
faster
oh oh it pushed the bus over it just the
bus over the bus fli it's on
fire I'm feeling so relieved
dude
man hope it look cool did we jump an
entire football field no was jet car a
succcess yes there's no way there's no
way why 30 days to build a rocket car
sick oh man oh gosh look at this wa I
don't know what I was expecting it to
look like it wasn't that W the hood got
peeled back oh that's what that is wow
what if you had to play football in
this boys I just want to say thank you
so much boys you guys killed it that was
so epic thank
[Music]
you big thank you for watching uh make
sure to like And subscribe check out
Mass Channel warp perception he's done a
ton of crazy stuff on his big thanks to
Mr Beast and all his dudes for having
out this is so good go watch their video
you probably already have yeah go check
out this little Channel go check out
this small Channel called Mr
[Music]
Beast what the
f there's a car in the school bus this
is going to be the best year ever we got
to get out of the bus getting
up