'He is my son, Raghav Kaul.'
'And she is Preeti's daughter,
Pashminna Suri.'
'We received a fake letter
with a forged signature.'
- Fake letter?
- Paras.
How can Paras be so pathetic?
Look, Mr. Kaul. Our mothers
have always disliked each other.
Look at them now.
They are keeping
their differences aside
and are there for us as our mothers
in front of the world.
This is good.
These wounds didn't go in vain.
No matter how dense the clouds are,
they eventually burst.
A sunbeam, like a rainbow,
spread over them.
'The one who gives us
any information about them'
'will be rewarded
with Rs. 10,00,000.'
[tense music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
It's fine. We will see.
Kailash Durani!
Wait, sir!
I will call you back in some time.
What are you doing? Tell me!
Let me go. I need an answer.
Did you think
that I wouldn't know
who attacked Raghav?
You made a grave mistake
this time, Kailash Durani.
You attacked my daughter and Raghav.
Your son is behind
the accident, right?
Or is it your allies? Answer me!
I need an answer!
I am not your employee, Mr. Sharma.
We are business partners.
Who gave you the right
to show up like this?
I will see to it that you are
not capable of doing anything.
I will ensure your son
gets capital punishment.
Really?
What for? Is someone dead?
If any harm befalls
my children, then...
Neither you nor your children
matter to us.
Whether they are legitimate
or illegitimate.
Why do we care?
Therefore, rather than
ruining your image any further,
it is best if you leave.
I am leaving!
But I will bring the police
this time.
Your son has been in prison
for a year.
Rest assured, I'll see to it
that he goes to jail this time,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
If you do anything to my son...
You and your son
will both go to jail.
I don't spare anyone
who attacks my children.
Don't forget, Kailash Durani.
You don't know me.
[tense music playing]
I will deal with those women
who have patched up.
But Avinash will ruin the game.
You can keep all of this
if you want.
No! Not me.
Please help us.
You are helping us.
We didn't run away from home.
There are goons after us.
The police are with them.
Our families will get into trouble
if we are caught.
Please help us.
There is so much pain and wound.
Who inflicted them?
Where will you go?
I will be right back.
[tense music playing]
Mr. Kaul, I think
he will help us for sure.
But as long as we are in this city,
we will be in danger
because of Paras.
How do I save you?
How do I protect you?
[tense music playing]
'Lord Shiva, please
protect my daughter.'
'Protect Raghav!'
Preeti,
waiting back won't help.
They will call us once
they get any news.
- Get some rest.
- I cannot do that, Avinash.
Rather than going home and
being restless, I might as well...
Until I find out
anything about Poshai...
Preeti, everything will be fine.
Fine?
What will be fine, Avinash?
My daughter has been through a lot.
What makes you say
everything will be fine?
Preeti!
Lord Shiva will
make everything right.
Avinash had said something once.
And I was against it.
But I agree with him.
I always wanted Raghav
to be in love.
I wanted him to know what love was.
[pensive music playing]
When Raghav and Aisha
were getting engaged,
I prayed to God
that my son should know
what it is to be in love.
'I wish I could tell you'
'that when you fall in love, '
'it is not in our hands.'
'This is something you
understand once it is fulfilled.'
[somber music playing]
And he listened to me.
What I wanted
is what happened.
Just that things didn't go
the way I wanted them to.
Ms. Mohena!
I wanted the same.
I wanted my daughter to find someone
who loved her immensely.
And doesn't betray her.
[somber music playing]
And doesn't show his back
and leave her for good.
Preeti, that is what happened.
We got what we
wanted for our children.
But it took us too
long to realize it.
'I couldn't give you my father's
name, or family's acceptance.'
'But'
'I can teach you from my mistakes.'
'never trust an outsider.'
'They come here and leave.'
'They leave us alone.'
'They don't even look back, Poshai.'
I always told Poshai
not to fall in love
with an outsider.
You know what?
She was so happy
that she fell in love
with a Kashmiri man.
'Mom, may I ask you a question?'
If a Kashmiri settles
in another state'
'then is he from Kashmir
or is he an outsider.'
'I mean, '
'that doesn't make him
a tourist, right?'
Her innocence
made me and her realise
that Raghav is from Kashmir.
He belongs to this land.
He's just a little far away.
And for Raghav, Pashminna is the one
who introduced him to his home.
Made him feel the essence of love.
Pashminna is Raghav's home
and his Kashmir.
Mrs. Mohena, then why did we...
Why did we tear them apart?
Stubbornness got the better of us.
I was convinced
that Poshai's love was wrong.
Aisha tried her best
to explain it to me.
She distanced herself from Raghav
and Pashminna. But I...
I felt like Raghav didn't
break Aisha's heart,
he broke my heart.
And I failed to understand anything.
Preeti mom, did you
find out anything about them?
We have broadcasted the reward
on TV and radio channels.
If anyone finds out,
they will contact us.
- Tell me!
- There was news
about a boy and a girl.
I know them.
Tell me the address.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello, Paras!
Badri here.
I have the address.
I am sending it to you.
Excellent, Badri! I am impressed.
You've defeated renowned hackers.
You even made your own caller tune!
Good job!
[engine whirring]
'Dad!'
[slapping]
'You brought shame to our family!'
'I should've left you in jail!'
'You would have rotten there.'
'They took him for surgery.'
'He's alive'
'because of your incompetence.'
'If you wanted to kill him, you
should have finished him off! '
I will finish the job today.
I will teach Pashminna
and Raghav a lesson.
Both of them will die today.
Pashminna, leave!
Be quiet, Mr. Kaul. I won't leave.
Don't argue! It's pointless!
I won't go.
Listen, go away!
I'm more stubborn than you.
[ominous music playing]
[tyre screeching]
Pashminna and her Mr. Kaul
will not survive.
[tense music playing]
Your hero is here, Pashminna.
[thud]
[tense music playing]
Where are they?
Where did they go?
Old man!
You gave me this address,
didn't you?
Where are they?
Tell me, or I will shoot you!
Untie me first.
Wasim! Munna! Untie him.
Old man, you can't
do anything right!
Tell me, where they are?
Sir, you're also hitting me.
I was the one who
informed the police.
They heard the conversation
and tied me up here.
And they left.
They just ran away,
they might not have gone far.
Paras Durani, what are you doing?
They can't have gone far.
Search every corner. Find them!
You can't do anything
right, can you? - No!
Tell me where they are, tell me!
Paras Durani,
what are you doing here?
I'm asking you, Paras, speak up!
Poshai
Posh...
Where is Pashminna, tell me!
Where is Raghav?
What are you doing here. Paras?
Where is Pashminna?
Where is she?
Where are they?
They were here.
They must have run away.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Sharma, I am a
servant of Kashmir,
doing my duty.
A boy and a girl
from our valley are missing.
Stop your nonsense.
Everyone knows who you are.
You even falsely accused my father.
- I'm telling you again,
stay in your limits or... - Or what?
What will you do, huh?
Poshai is not here. Where is she?
Your pain, your tears,
your screams,
we should broadcast
it on the radio.
Someone might help us.
Go away from here. Go away.
We don't need your help.
Poshai!
I was just trying to help.
[emotional music playing]
Did they come here?
They were here. They ran away.
Let's go, Preeti. There's no point
in wasting time here. Come on!
Inspector,
how did Paras Durani get here,
following the call you received?
Are you trying to say that we...
Find out, Inspector,
who in your office
is leaking information
to Paras Durani.
Otherwise, I will find out.
[tense music playing]
What happened?
Did you find out anything?
Nothing yet. But Uncle Avi is in
touch and Preeti mom is with him.
It's strange, isn't it?
We always put Uncle Avi
before our dad all our life.
He had done so many
favours for our family.
And then, the truth changed.
He went from being our benefactor
to our biggest enemy in a second.
And then because of
Aunt Preeti and Pashminna,
he came back into our lives,
and yours too.
- True.
- He's your father-in-law.
You know, sometimes
I think that maybe,
because of age and loneliness,
they'll get back together.
Everyone needs a companion.
I doubt Aunt Preeti
will ever forgive Uncle Avi.
And maybe she shouldn't.
Because some wounds never heal,
they just hurt less.
You are being so emotional!
Have some faith in romance.
Let's make plans.
I have an idea.
When everything is right,
when Pashminna returns
and we get married,
then we'll plan
to get Uncle Avi and
Aunt Preeti married.
It's the best idea, the
hashtag will be #PV.
And yes, we'll involve
Raghav in this too.
We'll involve Pashminna too.
Because Pashminna is
the most romantic of all.
And we'll get them
married on a houseboat.
If not a houseboat,
then in Kaul Cottage.
Otherwise, they won't agree to that.
We can do that.
I mean, Uncle Avi
is genuinely sorry.
And everyone should get a chance
to correct their mistakes, right?
Makes sense.
After getting them married, do you
know what my last mission will be?
To get you married.
To carry your palanquin.
What are you talking about?
There's a limit to joking.
I'm not joking, I'm serious.
Believe me.
- But I can never be with Sunil...
- I am not talking about him.
You're still stuck on Sunil.
We'll find a handsome man
for you who will love you
and respect you.
I won't be able to do all that.
Sunil has ruined everything for me.
We will work on it then.
Why don't you have an affair
or be in a situationship?
What nonsense are you talking about?
And what is a situationship?
You don't know, right?
I will explain.
In situationship, you can be
together if you want to or leave.
Thank you!
You thanked me.
This means you are ready.
Nowadays, there are dating apps,
I didn't thank you for that.
I said it because
you made me forget about
my problem for a brief moment.
Rishi has that kind of personality.
Even if Pashminna looks
at the sun with a torch,
she will never find
a diamond like me. Never!
You are a nice person.
And Pashminna is very lucky
to have found someone like you.
And Raghav too,
- to have a friend like you.
- Thank you.
It's getting cold. Shall we drink?
Help yourself!
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
'Neem leaf!'
'This is made from
neem leaf paste.'
'It looks freshly made.'
'Poshai.'