today I'm going to take up a very common
problem that a lot of English learners
face the problem is that they translate
their sentences from Hindi to English
whenever they are trying to speak
something in English and I know this
because of course it has happened to all
of us at some point of our lives
whenever we were trying to learn a new
language
we definitely faced this issue because
we are habitual to thinking in our
native language now the issue is that in
that process of translation a lot of
time is lost and the moment just
vanishes most of the times we lose the
moment the translation takes a lot of
energy a good effective conversation
requires snappiness it requires to think
on your toes that charm that is required
now let's address a few issues that are
connected to this problem is this good
or bad it is bad should it happen no it
should not happen will it happen yes it
will happen will it go away yes it will
go away I'm going to tell you how it is
going to go of it let us first
understand one thing it is not something
that happens in absolute that either you
are going to translate or you're not
going to translate at all no it is
something that will happen more in the
beginning and then eventually decrease
when the time passes and when your
practice happens it is going to decrease
to a very low level and then eventually
it will completely vanish here we agree
on one thing it is a continuum it's not
going to happen with the click of a
finger so how will it exactly happen
I'll show you this is you translating
every sentence and this is you who does
not have to translate anything at all so
how will this happen right now this is
like zero so zero and right now this is
you okay so you are translating
everything once you start practicing
okay this is you practicing giving it
time giving it a lot of energy this
keeps on coming down and as this comes
down this keeps on increasing little by
little little by little and then again
it keeps coming down and this comes here
okay now you're 50% through
eventually what will happen this you are
going to grow and this you is going to
become small and eventually this is what
it looks like you become this from this
let's talk about your instincts let's
talk about your intuition do you know
how to drive I'm sure most of you
already know how to drive so do you
remember your first day are driving the
person must be telling you about the
clutch the brake the gears how to keep a
little distance with the other cars and
which lane to take etcetera etcetera at
that time I'm sure it must have felt
cumbersome it must have felt difficult
but now when you drive don't you think
you don't have to think about it you
don't have to actually apply your mind a
lot of people drive listening to music
lot of them drive talking on the phone
which is absolutely wrong but they still
do so that means there comes a point in
your life when you don't have to any
further think when you have to drive you
don't have to think about driving that
is what I meant similarly it will happen
for any other skill whatever you're
trying to learn it will become automatic
initially it always faces friction but
when you keep providing it the fuel of
practice
every now and then you're giving that
signal to your mind that you're going to
do it you're going to do it you're going
to keep practicing you're going to keep
doing it you're going to keep working on
your language eventually your brain will
stop resisting the change it will start
accepting it ok and your brain is going
to actually start supporting you you
will not have to consciously try to
speak in English English is going to
flow out of your mouth it will just flow
like that now the point is how do we do
that ok I will answer this question with
another question you tell me how much
time in the last 30 days have you
actually given to learning English
have you actually given it 30 years in
the last 30 days and if I have to give
you a figure and I can assure you that
these many number of hours if you put in
into learning English you will
definitely be
able to speak proper English I'm not
saying advanced level English just a
basic level English you will be able to
speak with fluency if I give you a
figure will you be working on that I
have a figure for you I'm giving you a
figure of 1000 RS 1000 okay if you give
it 1000 hours you will be able to speak
fluent English basic fluent English that
is a very good book that I read just a
few years ago the name of the book is
mastery and it was written by Robert
Greene mastery has this point that when
you give something ten thousand hours
not one ten thousand hours you come to a
position that you are an expert of that
particular skill and now you are in a
position to teach that skill to other
people I'm not asking for ten thousand
hours from you because we don't have to
become experts we just need basics I'm
going to call it the 1000 hours rule if
you give it your 1000 hours I am
promising you you will be able to speak
proper fluent English with confidence
and without hesitation
one last fundamental that I'm going to
talk about with you today is effort
expectation ratio the name is itself
self explainatory
how much is your effort and how much is
your expectation the ratio right now is
pretty disturbed the effort that you're
putting in is around 10 which is pretty
low and the expectation that you have
out of yourself is pretty high it's
somewhere around 90 we need to maintain
this ratio a little we need to make the
effort more and expectation little so
the ratio instead of being one is to
nine should be nine is to one the effort
should be 90% and your expectation
should be 10% stop expecting too much
out of yourself at such an early stage
because as I said unless you give it
your 1000 hours no big thing is going to
happen for you and as a good teacher I
have a homework for you like always that
you have to listen to me carefully and
you have to do this you have to
in front of the mirror okay let's first
break the hesitation to ourselves and
then we will talk about breaking the
hesitation to the outside world so you
have to go stand in front of the mirror
of your room your washroom anywhere and
you have to speak to yourself for ten
minutes okay ten minutes that's all I
ask you for and once you do that come
back to the video comment done simple
keeping a record of your own growth is
very difficult it's important that
somebody else is watching over you you
can keep doing this in your regular days
keep doing it daily and keep informing
me I'll be more than happy to know tell
me if you liked today's video personally
I love to raise video connect with me on
Instagram because I post a lot of stupid
stories over there to find out a little
more about my life and of course you can
subscribe to the channel and let me know
in the comments please please share
something on the comments I wait for
your comments
I love reading them and please press the
bell icon because that's how you get
updated on my videos and I'll see you
again very soon
bye bye take care of yourself and keep
smiling
good bye