'Some characters
are written with blood.'
'Some characters are written
in tears.'
'This is the story that is
written in both blood and tears.'
'The story of blood and tears.'
- Sir.
- Good morning, Sir.
'I have been called to Delhi
for an emergency.'
Okay, sir.
- Can you hurry up, please?
- Sure, Sir.
- Thank you.
- Sir.
[phone ringing]
'Mr. Vikram, Code Red.'
'Get here immediately.'
Coming, sir.
Rajput sir called.
He says it's a Red Code.
It's freezing here in Delhi.
Yeah, it's so cold.
- Taxi!
- Sir!
Sir, ID, please.
All okay, Sir.
They are waiting for you.
- Thank you.
- Come quickly.
This way, please.
Thank you.
Gentlemen,
this is Viswanath Sastry...
DSP - Crime Branch, Guntur.
And this is Mr Anuj Gupta,
In charge of VIP security, Delhi.
Sir.
Mr Singh,
Commissioner of Police, Delhi.
Sir.
This is Mr Vikram Choudhary...
In charge, of personal security
to the Prime Minister of India.
I'm Raghavendra Rajput,
Chief of Intelligence Bureau.
Sir, may I ask
what this is all about?
You called at midnight
and called me to Delhi.
What's the emergency, Sir?
Mr Viswanath Sastry,
IPS 1963 batch.
First posting, Bapatla division.
Second posting, Chirala division.
Third posting, 1979 till date...
DSP - Crime Branch, Guntur.
So primarily...
you worked in the tiger zone.
The zone of...
Tiger Nageswara Rao.
Sir, I'm sorry I don't get it.
What does PM's security have
to do with Tiger Nageswara Rao?
Mr Sastry...
In this meeting,
I'll be asking the questions.
Please sit down.
Now tell me everything
about Tiger Nageswara Rao.
Sir.
Sir, if Nageswara Rao
entered politics,
he would have won every election.
He would have bagged a medal
for India if he were into sports.
If he were in the army, no one would
have dared to challenge our borders.
But unfortunately,
he chose to be a criminal.
I have seen many people
like him in my service.
Mangal Singh,
Omkar Singh Yadav, Piyula.
[scoffs]
Is he a bigger robber than them?
Sir, thieves attack
without intimation.
Robbers attack suddenly and rob.
But if someone challenges and then
comes, that's Tiger Nageswara Rao.
Sir, whoever saw Nageswara Rao
was either killed
or remained silent in fear of him.
In fact, even I, too, never saw him.
Some years ago, when I was posted
at Chirala police station
on special duty...
I received a phone call.
I still remember that voice, sir.
That was more like a roar.
[phone ringing]
- Chirala police station.
- 'Remember this voice.'
You must have seen a tiger
that hunts deer,
but I am a tiger that hunts tigers.
Who is it?
An appeal to the cops...
The Circar Express
bearing number 17643,
running from Kakinada to Madras...
is about to be looted en-route.
20 tons of grain was being sent
from Kakinada to Madras
for storm victims.
And someone called
and threatened to rob it.
Who gave you that information?
Stuartpuram Nageswara Rao.
We are fond of declaring war
before starting it.
Um...
- Call the Control room!
- Okay, Sir.
There is a distance of 242 km
between Kakinada and Madras.
21 stations fall en-route, and there
are ten policemen at each station.
There was an RPF personnel
in each coach.
There was only one chance
of robbing the train.
The Godavari Bridge, which runs
over a length of 2300 metres.
Amid such tight security...
To rob 20 tonnes of grain. That,
too, in four and a half minutes.
Do you really think it's possible, sir?
It takes five hours to load it.
Robbing 20 tonnes in
four and a half minutes?
It's impossible.
Sir...
The job which you think is
impossible, he can do it easily.
[train honking]
Tiger starts thinking at the point
where the common man stops thinking.
[train honking]
[whistling]
Come on, hurry up!
[train honking]
The bridge is about to end.
Get out, all of you!
Hey! Turn around quickly!
- Come on, quickly!
- Turn it! Come on, turn! Hurry up!
Remove it, hurry up!
No!
Nagi, jump!
Did you get him?
- Come on, move!
- Look over there.
- Over here.
- Come on, hurry up!
- There is nothing here.
- Hello!
- 'Sir, he is not here.'
He wouldn't have gone far...
How will we get him?
We've never even seen him.
In olden times, just as
kings used to enter a kingdom
and take away things,
considering them as their reward,
Nageswara Rao's
thinking is also similar.
He doesn't consider
these things as theft.
He considers them as rewards.
Sir, we got all the crime files
on Nageswara Rao ready.
Has he written so much crime
literature in a span of 25 years?
He started very early, sir.
Like when he was ten?
- No, eight years.
- Robbery at the age of eight?
It was a murder.
No, sir! Don't do this.
This is wrong.
I didn't do anything. Leave me.
- Yelamanda.
- Sir!
He was the linchpin
of Stuartpuram's crimes.
Every crime that happens in
Stuartpuram is on his instructions.
He always has a share
that comes out of that crime.
Hey, Sir is here.
Hey, stop. Stop doing it.
Can't you see Sir is here?
How dare you steal without
my permission! What did you think
that you would take it all alone?
I break into pieces, anyone
who doesn't give me my share.
That's the money I robbed
through effort and risk.
I only have the right to it.
Does the ox own the crop
just because it ploughs the land?
Does a dog own the house
just because it stands guard to it?
How can you claim
the money to be yours
when I hold the
rights on Stuartpuram?
[blowing]
Nail his knees.
No!
Don't do it!
Damaging the knee joints of a thief
is akin to slicing
fingers of a guitarist.
Greetings, sir.
Hey...
- Is he your younger son?
- Yes, sir.
Do you want to sit on my chair?
Get hold of him.
Don't let him out of your hands.
Why did you call me?
You know Kanaka Rao? He went
to the city and made a fortune.
All the money is
lying in his bungalow.
I'll steal it, sir.
- Listen!
- Sir.
Give him thirty rupees for this.
Sir, please give me two rupees more.
Did your mother store
her fortune with me?
Don't take me wrong,
but Manoj was also caught stealing,
and people beat him so
much that he broke his leg.
He is unable to walk anymore.
- Think about his children, Sir.
- [lady]: Hey, Dayavan!
We are not responsible
for his children.
If they want bread to eat,
tell his wife to sell her body.
Or poison them all.
Just think about
the job given to you. Go!
It is a bad omen for theft tonight.
Yelamanda has ordered
this job to be done today itself.
Come.
Why are you digging here, Father?
Because there is a rat hole here.
A rat digs precisely
where the wall is vulnerable.
Got it?
Hurry up, son. Get out quickly.
Here, grab this.
Stop!
Nagi, someone is pulling me inside.
Pull me out. Come on!
Hey, the thief is escaping!
Come over here!
- Come on!
- Wake Sir up!
- Come!
- Hurry up!
- Come! Catch him!
- Pull him inside.
Guys, there is no
chance I can escape now.
Take this sack
and give it to Yelamanda.
He'll give you three rupees.
Give one rupee to Kalua
and keep the rest.
We toiled for this money.
I won't give it to anyone.
Don't leave him.
Catch him!
Don't be stubborn. I've been caught,
and the police will reach you soon.
- Go now!
- Quickly, climb the wall! He must have colleagues on that side.
Father, they won't find us,
If they don't recognise you at all.
How can they not recognise me?
How can they recognise
a headless body, Father?
[screams]
Animals like lions and tigers
also drink milk in childhood, Sir.
But he started hunting
in his childhood.
By the time the food fed
by his father reached his throat...
he slit his father's throat!
Is he even human?
In order to understand
Nageswara Rao,
you need to know
about Stuartpuram, sir.
Their profession was hunting.
But gradually, they started hunting
travellers along with animals.
They would pounce like
a wolf on those passing
through the forest and
rob them of everything.
Just as prey cannot escape
from the claws of a lion,
no one can escape
from their clutches.
An English officer
named Stuart built a colony
for them to remove
them from the forest.
It was named Stuartpuram.
He thought they would live a
decent life by leaving the forest,
but cruelty had settled
in their nature.
So they started looting
and killing again.
Bijli Prasad... the Dronacharya of
the Kurukshetra called Stuartpuram.
All the gangsters currently
ruling Stuartpuram...
were trained by Prasad in the past.
Hey!
Eating pork curry and
rolling isn't enough.
You must drink donkey
blood and run like a horse.
No cop will be able to catch you.
Ten rupees.
Who wants it?
[all]: I want it! I want it!
- Do you want it?
- Yes, sir.
Take it.
There is a scorpion inside,
along with the note.
Nageswara Rao came under
Bijli Prasad's wing when he was 14.
Courage alone isn't
enough for stealing.
Sometimes, you need intelligence.
Because intelligence...
He is Venkat's son.
He is a strong boy. Do you
want to learn the skill from me?
I will rule the whole world.
If one drinks donkey blood,
one has to run for some
hours without resting.
Otherwise, the blood in one's body
would clot and
eventually, death happens.
Bijli Prasad mentored Nageswara
Rao under such rigorous training.
Tiger Nageswara Rao.
'Tiger Nageswara Rao.'
Before any gang
in Stuartpuram could steal,
they had to win the area
in an auction.
Under the watch of Yelamanda.
In those days, three major
gangs operated in Stuartpuram.
Pawan Suri, Doga Raj
and George Babu.
Yelamanda entered
politics and became
an MLA with money
from Stuartpuram's crime.
And his right hand is his
younger brother Kashi.
While Yelamanda was
running politics from Hyderabad,
his brother took care of the
matters of Stuartpuram.
Hey!
Start the auction.
Guntur railway station...
The opening bid is 25000 rupees.
- 30000 rupees.
- 35000 rupees.
That's it? Brother is an MLA now.
All the cops are in our reach now.
You can rob like a king.
Call higher!
- 50000 rupees.
- Yeah! That's like it!
Would anyone like
to bid more than that?
First call!
Second call!
Third and final call!
Sold!
Guntur Railway Station is sold
to George Babu for a year.
If any other gang member
steals even a penny
from there, his family
will be wiped out.
Where have you been?
Let me give you a tour of heaven.
Once I taste something,
I lose interest in it.
Vijayawada and Guntur's
opening bid is... One lakh rupees.
Young man, can I bid too?
You need a gang to steal
and a chair to bid.
Who the hell is he?
He is Angee Seth.
He smuggles gold in
tobacco boxes, but last week,
customs seized his goods
at the Bandar Port.
He has come to seek help
from Yelamanda to get it back.
- Bro... - I told you
we can't take up your work.
Didn't you get it?
Listen to what I have to say.
Listen, this job is not
for anyone here.
Our business is different.
Listen, Pal! My goods are stuck.
If this were my Kolkata,
I would have got the goods
taken out within an hour.
But Bandar port is your area.
Which is why
I'm asking you for help.
I will give a share
of twenty per cent
to the one who will
get my cargo out.
Hey! I told you it won't be done.
Leave!
Thirty per cent!
Hey, Pal... forty.
Forty per cent!
I want fifty!
Here comes the tiger.
Give me half the share,
and I'll retrieve your cargo.
Will you?
Hey!
Decisions around here
are made by Brother.
Who are you to make decisions?
Are you trying to act smart with us?
That Cargo is yours.
You will have to take the decision.
Deal?
- You bloody...
- Wait, Kashi...
He claims to complete this task,
something no one here can do!
You all will see
what I do by tomorrow evening.
Okay. But be ready to drink
my pee if you don't get the cargo.
I will.
Oh, man! Would you need a glass,
or would you drink directly?
See you tomorrow.
Sir...
You told me the
punishment in case I lose.
But you didn't tell me about
the reward in case I win!
What do you want?
The chair, sir.
What?
If I get the stack,
add another chair
to the three that are present here.
And one of them should be mine.
Let us meet tomorrow evening.
There are customs people everywhere.
It is pretty risky to go inside.
How will we find gold
in so many tobacco boxes?
Do you know how it feels
to smoke a ton of tobacco?
Bro, don't tell me that
you want to burn all the cargo!
How can a rat do what an
elephant and a lion cannot do?
Nageswara Rao is here!
All the goods are on fire.
Let the fire brigade come in.
Box number 6943 contains my goods.
Miraculous job, Bro.
Hats off to you!
Let us take him to
Kolkata, along with us, sir.
He is not a normal guy but a spark
that will one day become
a fire and burn everyone.
Are you crazy?
If he even sets foot in Kolkata,
we will have to leave our business.
Let's go.
Brother! If you ever need help,
remember the name, Angee Seth.
Kashi!
Bring the chair.
'Do you want to sit on my chair?'
'Did your mother store
her fortune with me?'
- Nagi!
From that day, a new force
was born in Stuartpuram.
Nageswara Rao eliminated all the
gangs from Stuartpuram one by one.
People's souls trembled
upon hearing his name.
How can he enter my area?
He's not even afraid
of your name, sir.
Anyone who raises
their voice is cut off.
We have come to you with great hope.
Only you can solve our problem.
We, goldsmiths, get threats
every day. Where should we go?
We shall guarantee your safety.
You have to pay us a tax
of 2000 rupees per month.
Otherwise, Nageswara Rao
will cut you off!
To eliminate Nageswara Rao, someone
more dangerous than him is needed.
And that was Circle Inspector Mauli
of Stuartpuram.
Your Honour, not one
but three people have
lost their lives
in Inspector Mauli's custody.
It takes the law into its own hands.
This is the postmortem report
of the boy who died in his custody.
Look how brutally he was beaten.
- I object, Your Honour.
- Have some shame.
This beast has murdered
three people in his custody.
You are rooting for this man
who is mentally ill!
He should get himself treated.
The one who died was a criminal,
that's why I am leaving him.
He will remain suspended
as long as the case is ongoing.
I did not steal anything, Sir.
I'm telling the truth, Sir.
Hey, how dare you raise
your voice in front of him!
- I'll treat you a lesson.
- No, sir!
- Please forgive me, sir!
- You want to steal, huh?
- Sir, it hurts!
- There you go!
- Take this!
- Sir, no, please!
- Will you raise your voice?
- Please leave me, Sir.
- Will you open your mouth now?
- No, Sir!
Hey! Did he faint?
Sir, he is dead!
You killed a boy in your custody!
Mr Ramamurthy,
when is the next hearing?
Next week, Sir.
- Huh?
- Next week, Sir.
It's okay, sir. You can talk loudly.
- You'll have to pay a fine
of Rs 250. - A fine, is it?
Stop.
So, how are you?
He is running faster than a leopard.
Give him some sense.
Yelamanda and his men
want to kill him.
- You know that?
- Hey.
- Cool down.
- Here, sign here.
Garika Diwakar!
- The Judge is calling, come.
- Garika Diwakar!
I'll be back.
Lawyer sir!
Listen!
Why have you stopped, Pal?
The vein of my love is fluttering.
Oh, damn! Not again. You just
had fun in that village, didn't you?
You will never change!
It’s been a while, let’s go?
Don’t you dare touch me next time, pls leave!
Oh, is it?
How dare you?
i killed you
Well done, Nagi!
This briber is worth it.
Hey, keep quiet!
Hey, bro! What are you doing, bro!
Hey, bro! Leave him!
Let him go. He's a policeman!
Let him go.
Let's go from here!
There's no one
in the landlord's mansion.
Everyone has gone to the city.
It's a good opportunity to steal.
There is nothing to steal there.
Rusted utensils and broken items.
Stingy landlord!
Try to make a big deal sometimes.
Only when you aim at the hawk
will you hit the hen.
What are you thinking?
Enough of these small heists.
We must get out of here
if we want to pull off a big heist.
Broaden your horizons.
I met someone in the prison.
Have you heard of Madras Port?
Gold is smuggled
from Burma to Madras every month.
How much of it?
Could it be 50 tolas?
Oh! We will win the lottery.
300 kilos.
[coughing]
The shipping of Madras Port
is taken care of by Basant Rao.
It is difficult even to breathe,
let alone steal under his watch.
He pays attention everywhere.
He has 300 men around him.
He is that crocodile of the sea
whom no one dares to collide.
Officer Sharma had come here to
raid and has been missing for three days.
We're here with a search warrant.
Do you know what he does
to his enemies?
He cuts them into pieces
and feeds them to the fish.
That looks like Mr Sharma's ring.
Hey!
Who chopped Sharma into pieces?
He didn't even notice
the gold on the finger.
Goddess Lakshmi will get angry.
Remember...
To win a big war, along with
bravery, weapons are also needed.
We need guns.
Nageswara Rao was the one
who stole out of Stuartpuram
and used a gun for the first time
instead of a knife.
He was so clever that he did the
gun transaction on the train itself.
And that journey
changed his life forever.
This one is locally made.
This can be loaded
once to fire two rounds.
This is a pistol.
This has six bullets.
It is easy to both keep and use.
- I need five more of these.
- Move,
- let me go.
- Please wait, Ma'am.
Why should I wait?
It looks like Ma'am is having
trouble stopping herself.
Who the hell are you to stop me?
What's going on there
will make you scream.
Uh...
[shot fired]
- Isn't the chick rocking, pal?
- Be respectful.
Isn't the respectable
chick rocking?
She is your sister-in-law.
What?
Hey, pull the brakes! Do you even
know how to talk to decent girls?
Talk about love and feelings.
Then she will fall in love with you.
You are gorgeous.
What?
I said you are gorgeous,
and I'm in love with you.
If you pull the chain, there is a
temple six kilometres from here.
Let's go there and get married!
- Are you crazy?
- Yes, I am.
But seeing you
brought me to my senses.
I never had the habit
of asking permission.
For the first time in my life,
I'm asking for permission.
Marry me, will you?
What is this nonsense? Who are you?
I'm Nageswara Rao.
Stuartpuram Nageswara Rao.
Nowadays, boys have
only one or two degrees,
but I'm wanted for
more than 150 cases.
I have committed
countless murders and thefts.
Can I show you by robbing
this train if you don't believe me?
The moment I see a woman,
I feel hunger of a different kind.
But for the first time,
the hunger is up here.
Hey, don't you know
how to speak to a girl?
Babe, it won't take me much time
to woo you with sweet talks.
Girls everywhere are really into me,
but my heart has fallen for you.
Nowadays, boys want only one thing,
but they get their way by talking
about love and affection.
Do you want someone
with a pure heart
or someone who gives fake respect?
He nailed it, man!
You guys are just students.
How do you plan to arrange the
capital for setting up a factory?
We'll take care of the funding, sir.
But please see that we get
the approval for the factory.
Okay. I'll forward the application.
Let us see.
[all]: Thank you, sir.
Chirala college.
Nagi gave pocket money
to the boys there,
solved their internal feuds
and strengthened his hold
on the students.
Here. You also have it.
She was not there
when I looked there.
Then they were acting so smart...
- Greetings, Bro!
- Greetings!
Hey, do you know that girl?
She is Sara from BA 2nd year.
She is a Manara's classmate.
- Oh! - Earlier, she used to study
in the neighbouring college,
but after her wedding was
cancelled, she changed her college.
She continued her education
because her wedding was cancelled.
How did you find out?
Because the person who broke
her marriage is sitting right here.
Are you crazy? You want to destroy
her life before she gets settled!
I will have to destroy it
to establish my life.
- It's time for the nuptial rounds.
- Bring the dowry money. - Okay.
Hey, the bag is empty!
There is no money in it.
Is this some joke, sir?
- Please calm down.
- This wedding is called off.
- Please don't do that. - We don't
want a daughter of cheaters.
Let's go!
Nagi, you're so mean!
Nagi, if she suspects that
you broke her marriage,
she would hate you forever.
What is this?
The dowry money that went missing
from the bag on the wedding day.
- Hey, what is he...
- This is it.
How did this reach you?
I stole it to stop your wedding.
- Let go of me!
- What is he doing?
If he had said he doesn't
care about the dowry
and only wants to marry you...
I would have bowed down
before him and doubled the money.
I could have become
a hero by lending
a shoulder at this critical
time if I had wanted.
But I don't want a relationship
based on lies.
Do you want a dishonest person
who lives on dowry money
or an honest person
who returns stolen money?
There... he nailed it!
We gave you gold
worth Rs 10 lakh to sell,
but you are giving us
only Rs 3 lakh.
Sir, I went to Mumbai only to sell
gold worth Rs 10 lakh to Mr Hassan.
But the police raided
and caught everyone.
I saved my life
by giving them one lakh.
I swear, please grant me some time,
and I will repay
your money, brother.
Mr Kashi... Mr Kashi... Sir.
I swear I will repay you
at any cost.
- Come!
- Hey!
- Kashi... Mr Kashi...
- Sara!
- Please leave my daughter.
I'm taking her as collateral
so you don't run away.
Give me my money
- and take her with you.
- Please leave her.
Make the principal
payment within three days.
If you don't repay the loan quickly,
- I'll make her repay in my own way.
- No. Please leave her.
Or the other option is...
To get the money back from you
by I'll have to make
her work as a prostitute.
Do you get it? Tell me.
What should I do with her?
Kaasi, I have another option.
There's a rule of collection.
You can seize his property
for the debt he owes you.
That chair, that table, her house.
Take whatever you want to.
But not that girl.
She is my property.
- Hey, don't try to tell me
what to do. - Dad.
Otherwise, you will
come to regret it.
The ones living off someone else
will now teach me my place, huh?
Leave the girl, or else
I'll bury you right here.
Just because Yelamanda
is sparing you,
doesn't mean you'll act
according to your will.
Why do you wish to get yourself
into trouble because of this girl?
Do you not realise that
Yelamanda is the MLA?
It'll take less than three
seconds to get rid of you.
Do you want Sara or Stuartpuram?
You desire something
which is not yours. Sara is mine.
She'll always be, and
so will Stuartpuram.
Hey!
- Hey!
- Kaasi.
Don't do anything.
The boss will take care of him.
Let's go.
Kaasi let's go.
Understand the situation.
We'll take of him later. Let's go.
Kaasi and his pets, hear me out.
Starting tomorrow, Stuartpuram
will be under my ownership.
Any gang operating in Stuartpuram
must pay taxes to me, not you.
Nageshwar Rao is not
known for Stuartpuram.
Stuartpuram will be
known for Nageshwar Rao!
For Nageshwar Rao!
Let's go Kaasi.
Come on.
[music]
'Now it was time to
attack Madras port.'
'Nageshwar Rao's
life's biggest theft.'
'He abducted the most
important man of the support.'
Hey, tell me.
Speak up.
[man groaning in pain]
When and where is the gold arriving?
The ship carrying gold
will halt near the port.
We'll barge into the
ship and take the box.
Nagi!
Sister-in-law is here.
Who did this?
They'll marry her
off day after tomorrow.
I made every possible
effort to persuade them.
My dad isn't listening.
What shall we do?
Will you marry me?
Nagi, please hear me out.
Once we're married,
everything will be fine.
Come on, get ready to leave.
Nagi, tell me.
Nagi, the vehicle has arrived.
Are you all going somewhere?
Can't you stay for a day?
Please, Nagi, wait for a day.
At 05:00 AM sharp,
come to Chirala station.
Nagi has given his word.
He won't do anything before the
wedding that will attract trouble.
Nagi, tell her.
Don't you worry.
Finish this quickly.
The ship is about to come.
'Hey, come here.'
'Yes, yes, sit over here.'
'Hey, what do you
think of yourself?'
[sound of the flare]
Nagi, Yaari has signal led.
The ship must have been docked.
'The Gold is in a container, it's
identification number is 459865.'
Where were you?
Why did you get so late?
Hurry up, or else
someone might see us.
'Every box within
the container will bear'
'a fish symbol
orientated to the right.'
'However...'
'The box containing the gold
will have the fish facing left.'
What's he applying?
Acid, to melt the metal.
- Nagi, hurry up.
- I'm on it.
Come.
Over here.
Put this seal on the other box.
This is it. This is the box.
Take it away quickly.
Let’s get out
This way
Where are Chote and Munaa?
'How did Andhra's
beedi reach Madras?'
Give me some fire.
I've been ruling over the Madras
port for the last twenty years.
I know about everything
that goes on here.
And you tried to steal from me?
Now I'll cut you myself.
The time for the
dogs to bark is over.
Now listen to a lion's roar.
At the age when you're
playing with bat and ball,
I had already started doing murders.
At first, I only wanted to steal
but now I'll kill you all as well.
Dare to stop me
if you have the courage.
Bring him to me.
Go fast.
[groans]
Aghh.
Hey.
Hit him.
Surround him.
Hey.
Don't spare him.
[multiple shots fired]
'Is he a human or a monster?'
'He entered my area
and stole my gold.'
'Just wait and watch, he'll
snatch your chair as well.'
Don't worry.
I'll retain my chair,
and you will have your gold.
Chote, stop smoking
beedi from now on.
Not your you but for us.
What's the matter?
Nagi, it's the police.
'Police, over here?
There's something wrong.'
Hide the gold at
the designated location.
Sara must be waiting for me at the
station. All of you take the boat.
Do you realise how worried I
was that you might not arrive?
Did you bring the nuptial thread?
Huh?
Don't worry, I bought that too.
What's wrong?
You appear to be troubled.
Last night, you made
the theft go very smoothly,
but how did you
forget to hide the bodies
of the people you killed?
The Madras police is here
to arrest you with proof.
Hey.
Go rot in the jail now.
Your dream of ruling over
Stuartpuram will never come to life.
Now Sara is mine,
and so is Stuartpuram.
Your property
is being seized by me.
Didn't I ask you?
Didn't I request you to
wait for just one day?
If you had waited for one day,
we would have been on that train.
This sacred thread would
have been on my neck.
Inspector, take him to Madras jail.
Sara.
- Sara.
- Let's go.
Sara. Sara.
- Sara. Sara.
Sara, hear me out.
Take him away, come on.
Sara, don't do this.
Leave me.
No.
My daughter!
Nageshwar was not only in danger
from his enemies but
from his loved ones, too.
He murdered his father.
He became the reason for the girl
he loved to take her own life, too.
The police tortured
him a lot, but still
he refused to disclose the
whereabouts of the concealed gold.
Because the crime
occurred in Madras,
he was kept in Tamil Nadu's jail.
The court sentenced him
to life imprisonment.
He was caught. The story ends here.
Stuartpuram's Nageshwar
Rao's tale ended there.
However,
Tiger Nageshwar
Rao's saga begins now.
Hey! Open the door.
Quick!
Hey! Open the door!
There he is.
Hey, what's the matter?
Why aren't you having your meal?
Just because the tiger is
held captive, it doesn't mean
he'll start eating grass.
This is jail and not
your in-laws' place.
When I said you must eat,
then you must eat.
Do you understand?
When I get out of this prison
tomorrow, I'll then have food.
Hey, this is the largest
jail in South India.
To date, three hundred
men have tried to escape.
Not even one managed
to escape from here.
Escape if you can!
I want to see if you can escape.
Try your best. You...
Even our trained dogs
can jump up to six feet, sir.
This wall is nine
feet taller than that.
Sir, even in the Olympics, the
record for the high jump is 8.25 feet.
But this wall is
higher than 15 feet.
'To climb on a wall that high,
the run must be at least 70 km/h.'
'The officers were baffled that'
'the jump was only possible
for a tiger or a cheetah to make;'
'how could a human do that?'
He escaped like a
tiger and escaped, sir.
Not like a tiger, he is a tiger.
Nageshwar Roa was yearning
to take revenge for Sara's death.
After escaping the jail,
he went straight to Kaasi
and Yelmanda's factory.
He beheaded twenty-four
men with a single axe over there.
And from that day
on, Tiger is missing.
This guy is a serious threat.
Beef up PM's security.
And everybody on their toes.
- Sir.
- Sir, sorry to interrupt you
but I cannot comprehend.
Why beef up PM's security?
Nageshwar Rao sent a letter stating
that he'll rob the PM's
house within 48 hours.
It's a threat, it's a challenge.
Sir, this thing shouldn't
escape this room.
If they really robbed
the PM's house, then we'll become
a laughing stock in front of
the entire world. Please, sir.
Mr. VIP security!
It's not some central jail
where you can leap and escape.
It's a three-wing security force.
Despite years of efforts, no one was
able to breach the PM's security.
I know he's good, but
he is not good enough.
And I will prove it.
Follow me.
Sir, I made all the arrangements
as per your command.
Good! All checked?
- Sir.
- Mr. Singh, go to gate one.
And you go to gate two.
- Where is the PM?
- Sir, she is upstairs.
- Security, alert.
- Okay, sir.
You go that side.
Yes sir. Come.
'Security, alert. Alert.
Open gate number three.'
'Madam is coming.'
Sastry, what did you say?
That he says everything beforehand
and then does what he says.
Where is he?
- Sir, I...
- Breaching
the PM's security isn't
that easy, understood?
Stop.
- For whom is that?
- For madam, sir.
- For madam?
- Yes, sir.
But she just...
Madam Prime Minister!
Yes, Rajput.
Gate eight alert,
stop the convoy right now.
What happened, Rajput?
Sorry ma'am. It's just a routine check.
- Sorry for the inconvenience.
- It's okay.
Let the convoy leave.
Sir, if madam is in the convoy,
then...
He couldn't have come inside
without any help from one of us.
Gather every officer stationed here.
I will personally investigate them.
Sir, everyone has arrived.
I've verified the entire list.
However, Sastry sir's driver,
that soldier is missing.
My driver?
You had sent him to receive
me at the airport, right?
So I thought he is
from the Delhi police.
Who said that to you?
He was with you, so we
thought he was assigned to you.
Or else we wouldn't have
permitted him to get in.
But, sir, I...
Remember this voice well.
One who treads
through the forest must
understand the Tiger's
movements and the
police who work here
must recognise this voice.
- Taxi.
- Sir.
Sir.
Narasimha Raju, sir. Delhi Police.???
I am posted here for
the last seven years.
Sir, whoever saw Nageshwar
Rao were either killed
or kept their mouths
shut due to his terror.
I have never seen him either
A known criminal was standing right
besides you, instead of catching him
you disclosed all the
security details in front of him.
How can you be so careless?
Shame on you.
- But madam Prime Minister,
actually... - Hmm.
He was in this compound
for 12 hours.
He had a pistol.
I was in close proximity.
You understand the
meaning of this, right?
Madam Prime Minister,
grant us one week.
We will find him and eliminate him.
We will ensure that news of his
encounter does not leak as well.
Just think, why did he
risk his life to come here?
If his goal was to steal,
he is smart enough to
empty even the Reserve Bank.
His goal wasn't robbery, Rajput.
It's something else.
Figure out what he wants
and then eliminate him.
Criminals like him
don't deserve to live.
This is the letter he left.
'Respected Prime Minister,'
'I did as promised.'
'I am taking one of
your prized possessions.'
'I urge you not to fire
your security detail.'
'For the last 48 hours, they
made great efforts to stop me.'
'Yours sincerely, Tiger
Nageshwar Rao. Stuartpuram.'
Sir, he is genuinely a good man.
He saved us.
'What exactly did
he steal from here?'
You must have seen
a tiger hunting deer.
But I'm the tiger who
hunts other tigers.
I like to declare war
before starting a war.
So you lost your way
from the neighbouring
village and ended
up in Stuartpuram?
And you have lost your wallet, too.
Should I bring you something to eat?
Hmm.
POLICE ALERT - AWARD OF 10000 ON
CATCHING STUARTPURAM NAGESWARA RAO
I see his posters everywhere I look.
Even the villagers are
only talking about him.
Even the police said that they
won't spare you until he surrenders.
Who is this man?
Whoever catches him
will be rewarded with a
sum of 10,000 rupees.
Is he some monster?
After escaping the prison,
he killed the MLA's brother.
And since then, the police
has been looking for him.
And until they find him,
they've held us captive.
But tiger isn't a vilian but a hero.
So what the police
are saying isn't right?
'The forest where we grew
up was snatched from us'
'and we were thrown over here with
a false promise of development.'
'They told us to farm over
here and live a happy life'
'but the land over here was barren.'
'We were forced to choose hunting.'
'Even when we wished
to work as labourers,
we were accused
of stealing and let go.'
If there's any truth
in this world, it's only hunger.
In order to get two meals a day,
you don't just need to work hard
but you need to put your
lives on stake over here as well.
Looking at all the injustice,
tiger couldn't stop himself.
At that time, he was 18 years old.
'The crime could happen anywhere,
but the police used to mark the'
'residents of Stuartpuram as
criminals and take them away.'
'We were paid to become
criminals and the auction happened'
'in the opposite way.'
Who'll take the blame for a
theft at Guntur Railway Station?
Who wants to bid the lowest?
Star bidding.
A 100 rupees, sir.
- 80 rupees, sir.
- 60 rupees, sir.
'Jewellery worth 5,000 were stolen.'
'Everyone from the top to the
bottom had received their share.'
'And the residents of
Stuartpuram only got 60'
'rupees to do the jail
time for that crime.'
You can get a maximum of six
months of punishment for theft.
And these people are asking for
60 rupees for such a little jail
time. They've become greedy.
Hey, put him in the car.
Sir.
Where's the thief who was caught
stealing at Guntur Railway Station?
He is the one, sir.
You little mole. That
jewellery was worth 5000.
Where did you sell them?
Tell me, where did
you pawn them? Tell me.
- Tell me.
- I didn't do anything.
I am from Stuartpuram. I was
paid 60 rupees to take the blame.
What is he saying?
You make them lie?
- Sir, he is lying.
- Sir.
That kid is telling the truth.
This is how the Stuartpuram
police station operates, sir.
They take a hefty sum from
the real thief and let them go.
And then they frame
someone from Stuartpuram
saying the stolen
goods were not found.
You are suspended.
Sir, please listen to me.
- You've made a joke out of the law.
- Sir, please, I won't do it again.
Sir, you may keep a 1000 rupees.
What did you say to me?
Do you think I take bribes?
- You're fired.
- Sir, take 2000 rupees.
I want it by evening.
Sir.
I made a loss of 7000
rupees because of you.
My son!
My kid! My kid.
You killed my son.
He opened his mouth after
just a couple of beatings.
Have you stopped feeding
donkey milk to the kids?
Do feed them or
else they'll die sooner.
Before he died, he told the truth
about Stuartpuram to the DSP.
As punishment, the orders are to
frame all of you for
all the pending cases.
And this time, we don't
want old, weak, or ill people.
I will take away good
and strong men with me.
Like the one who's standing
at the back over there.
Catch him.
Him too.
Hey.
Get the one who's
standing at the back.
- Hey, where are you running?
- You killed my kid.
My son!
Hey!
Hey you! Stop! Where
are you escaping?
Sir, please!
Nagi, look, they killed my son.
Ambedkar's education
brought about a transformation
in the entire community.
'Sir, please let me go.'
'Like the first ray of the sun
brings hope for everyone,'
'Stuartpuram took
a breath of relief that day.'
'That day, we learned
to live again.'
'The name of that ray of hope
was Nageswara Rao.'
'I will play the game of auction
with you today. Let's play.'
'Someone bashed and injured
the policeman of Stuartpuram.'
'Hey, Nageswara, are you crazy?
Will you attack the police?'
- 'Start bidding.
- I'm bidding 300 bucks.'
'I'm bidding 350.'
'Hey, crush his bones!'
- 'Hit him!
- Yeah! Bash him.'
- 'Hit him.
- Hit him a lot.'
'Hey, Nageswara!
Don't mess with the police.'
'You don't know what I can do.'
'Yes, you won't be spared.'
'Strike him, Nageswara. Kill him.'
- 'Hit them. - Hit them.
- Hit them a lot.'
'No lives will be auctioned
in Stuartpuram starting today.'
'Nageswara Rao decided to
educate every child in Stuartpuram.'
'You might recognise him.'
'People pay fees to read and write.'
'But without giving it
a second thought,'
'he battled death to study.'
'If we enrol him,
everyone will think'
'that we are promoting robbery.'
'You can also say'
'that you're teaching the son
of a thief to live a decent life.'
'We are not born as thieves.'
'Our circumstances have
turned us into thieves.'
'Now, we want to fight
those circumstances'
'and change. Please don't snatch
this opportunity from them.'
'Changing his ways will
require health and books.'
'Who will pay for their food?'
'Sir, that responsibility is mine.
They will never starve.'
'Starting from tomorrow, nobody
can stop you from attending school.'
'Yay!'
The food on this plate
is also Nageswara's mercy.
The government was sending grains
for the flood victims.
Those grains were in the train.
But, some MLAs and politicians used
to distribute it amongst themselves.
Before that could happen, Nageswara
risked his life to steal it.
He distributed the aid
among the villagers
and flood victims, and that aid
is still feeding them.
You claim that Nageswara
is a good man.
Then, why did he murder
those 24 people?
'Nageswara Rao wanted employment
for the youth of Stuartpuram.'
'But he didn't know how.'
'Despite being educated,
nobody had employment.'
'How can we find
employment for everyone?'
- 'Won't you say something?
- Let's see what he says.'
'Sir, why don't we construct
a factory over here?'
'Yes, Sir. We'll be able to earn our
daily living if we are independent.'
'It will secure our future.
The educated will get a job.'
'It will also give some income
to the labourers.'
'The idea is excellent.'
'But will the government
permit us to build a factory?'
'Let's apply for it first.'
'What about the expenses
required to set up the factory?'
'Nageswara Rao needed money
to set up a factory in Stuartpuram.'
'That's when he stole 300 kg of gold
from the Madras court.'
'He hid that gold somewhere.'
'Tell me, where did you
hide the gold?'
'It's not merely gold.'
'It represents the future
of Stuartpuram.'
'I won't reveal it,
even if my life is at stake.'
'Yelamanda feared that
a factory in Stuartpuram'
'would end his rule.'
'Sir, try as much as you want,
but he won't reveal anything.'
'He is not telling me where
he hid the gold.'
'Catch the college students.'
'They might know
the gold's location.'
'The cops crushed his bones.'
'But they couldn't crush his will.'
'His heart was already broken.'
'That's why,
despite the life sentence,'
'he didn't have a single
wrinkle on his face.'
'Why do you look so upset?'
'Have you commenced the
construction of the factory?'
'Are the villagers happy?'
'Will I get a job in the factory?'
'Or do people who have lived
in the jail not get jobs?'
'These kids gave Nageswara
the idea of a factory.'
'They will know where the gold is.'
'But they're
not revealing anything.'
'Where is the gold?'
'We don't know, Sir.'
'Do you know what this is?'
'An application seeking permission'
'from the government
to set up a factory?'
'None of you have enough money
to earn your daily bread.'
'So, how did you acquire
the funds to construct a factory?'
'Did you sell the stolen gold
to set up your factory?'
'Nageswara Sir went to jail for us.'
'You can kill us if you want.'
'But we won't disclose
the whereabouts of the gold.'
'There is a party meeting
that I need to attend.'
'I want the gold. Do as you please.'
Attack!
He is the only one who remains.
Don't let anything happen to
him, or we won't find the gold.
Just drug him.
He'll then start
speaking everything.
Nageswara Rao was the first person
who was successful in eloping
from Madras Central Jail.
Hey, Nagi.
We put that gold near the students.
But Kasi killed all of them.
Sir.
Nageswara Rao
escaped from Madras jail.
Let him come.
There are 40 of us.
400 guards were present in
the jail that he ran away from.
Go and run for your life.
Looks like he has come here.
Finish him.
Why are you going one by one?
Hit him together.
No matter how many flocks
of sheep surround the tiger,
instead of preying on the tiger,
they become the
tiger's prey instead.
When a hungry tiger goes on a hunt,
he calms down
after he gets his prey.
But Nageswara Rao
created havoc that day.
He created the most horrific
event in the history of crimes.
He killed around
24 people with just an axe.
Hey!
Kasi... Hey.
Hey, Kasi.
No. Leave him.
No... Have mercy.
A lion doesn't return home without
killing when he goes for hunt.
Yelamanda's brother Kasi
was killed in front of him.
This was a declaration of war.
The police of the whole state
were searching for Nageswara Rao.
- Who is he?
- Nageswara Rao from Stuartpuram.
Hey! Not Nageshwar Rao,
call him Tiger Nageswara Rao!
The one who didn't shed
a tear when his father died,
the one who didn't
cry when he lost Sara,
many years later, his eyes got teary
due to the death of those children.
Nageswara is hiding somewhere
after killing Yelamanda and his men.
That's why, the
police are after him.
Whenever a tiger hides,
it's never to get saved.
He always hides to attack.
Stuartpuram is under
police surveillance.
Houses are being searched.
It was dangerous to live
there, so I brought him here.
The police will come
here if I live here.
The police don't know that
you're hiding in your
father's best friend's place.
After your mother passed away,
there has been no
communication between us.
Do you remember your childhood
friend, Mani or did you forget her?
Okay, that's enough now.
He's going to stay
here for ten days.
You'll get many
chances to impress him.
Come inside.
Why just ten days?
Once he sees me like this,
he'll probably propose to me.
Hey Mani. How are you?
Look, Nagi has come.
Make some fish for him.
'Why isn't he paying
attention to me?'
'Fine. I will serve less rice.'
'He'll have to look at
me if he needs more.'
Mani cooks fantastic fish fry.
Nagi, too, likes dried fish a lot.
'You still won't look at me?'
'Fine. I will serve
less fish as well.'
'Now, I'll see how
he doesn't look at me.'
Did you catch Nagi?
Sir.
We're trying, sir.
You're trying.
He slashed my brother into
pieces in front of my eyes.
When the axe is hit in the chest,
it slices the chest
with every breath.
Do you know that, commissioner?
Go away.
In order to hunt the rat, his
burrows need to be torched up.
Gather the whole village
in the police station.
Sister, this engagement is
happening with your consent, right?
Yes.
Are you aware that this
is his second marriage?
I know.
It seems he has a
daughter your age.
I know.
If everything goes as
planned, then along with him,
he will also marry
off his daughter.
But you mentioned
that you liked Nagi.
That's why we arranged
this matchmaking.
Hmm! Now tell me. What
if Nagi sees me like this?
In order to appear
attractive to Nagi,
you agreed to the engagement.
Hey, Nagi. Yelamanda ran away.
He is about to frame false cases
on our people at the police station.
Do something or
everything will be ruined.
Hey, come here and place
your thumb impression.
- Do it. Go.
- Let us go.
Sir! Don't ruin our children's future
- Please, sir!
- Let us go.
Sir, please.
Sir, if our names are
listed in police records,
it will be impossible
for us to secure a job.
We will have to be
thieves like our ancestors.
It might be better if
you end our lives, sir.
I have no interest
in ending your lives.
I want to end your dreams.
The dream of honesty.
Earning honestly,
living a dignified life...
I need to crush that dream.
Come here. He has
been a topper in college.
Don't accuse this guy of theft.
It will tarnish the
gentleman's reputation.
Just file a murder
case against him.
One of our men has committed
a murder in the village Kaava.
We need a scapegoat for that.
Pin that case on him.
Sir... sir... sir...
Let my brother go.
Sir, his life will be ruined.
Don't do this, sir.
Sir, I beg of you.
Please let him go. Have
some mercy on my brother.
Sir...
I knew that you'd surely come.
Look around. A lot of
guns are aimed at you.
I won't make the mistake of
just sticking an axe and leaving.
I will keep pumping bullets
into you till your heart stops.
Last time I hit your
chest with an axe.
But this time, I will I'll detach
your head from your body.
What are you looking at? Shoot him.
Hey.
Sir.
It's gunpowder, sir.
I acquired 30 kilos of
it for a heist in Madras.
But only five kilos
were needed there.
25 kilos is still remaining.
Mallika.
Sumathi.
What are you looking at? Shoot him.
We celebrated Holi
with you with gunpowder.
Even if there is a spark,
you'll burn like the
Diwali firecrackers.
Indeed, sir. Gunpowder
is highly explosive.
Everyone will turn into ashes.
We have no other option.
We'll have to let them go, sir.
Picking locks and killing people
has been a game for
me since childhood.
If I kill you today,
people will turn you into a martyr.
I don't want you to be respected.
I want to humiliate you by starting
a factory in front of your eyes.
On the day of the
factory's inauguration,
you will lose your head.
This is Tiger's promise.
We don't need rented goons.
We need someone
who has enmity like us.
I know a guy who can get it done.
CI Mouli.
He hates Nagi a lot.
Call him soon.
Do you know what you're doing?
Will you become a second wife?
He has a daughter of your age.
Why are you ruining your life?
You'll find someone else.
Fix the wedding date, Dad.
Just think about it once again.
I have thought about it, Dad.
Nagi. I hope no one saw
you coming over here.
Don't sacrifice
for your little sister.
I will take care of your
wedding expenses.
Uncle, look for a
good groom for her.
That's not required.
Uncle, I have to talk
to Mani for a moment.
He is marrying again
while his wife is still alive.
What if he marries for the
third time after he marries you?
Then, I would have two
co-wives instead of one.
Listen, Nagi.
If we end up liking someone,
it's hard to like someone else.
It doesn't matter if the person
that I don't like is married or not.
Do you want to eat dried fish?
Do you want them
fried or with soup?
Mani.
What do you want?
I'm not asking you
to marry me, Nagi.
If I can't marry you, then it
doesn't matter whom I marry.
Alright. Look for another match
if that gives you some relief.
It doesn't make
much difference to me.
I'm making a soup out of them.
You don't know about me.
The entire state
police are after me.
The whole Madras police
is doing that as well, right?
You've escaped from
the Madras prison, right?
I've killed 24 people.
It would have been 25 if
you had killed that MLA.
Don't spare the MLA, Nagi.
One. Two.
I, too, loved a girl.
I lost the count.
Only one girl?
You've been with almost all the
prostitutes of Chilakaluripeta.
There are shoot-at-sight
orders in my name.
I don't know when the
police will do my encounter.
Just be with me till that moment.
I'm fine if it lasts
even for a moment.
This moment is enough.
Tiger Nageswara Rao.
Nagi shot him and ran away.
Prepare shoot-at-sight
orders on his name.
- Bijli Prasad.
- What happened?
CI Mouli has found out
that Tiger's wife is over here.
What did you say?
He must be coming here.
Do one thing. Look for your
mother and get her here soon.
You wait here.
Hey, Rajesh. Jagdish.
Everyone, come here.
Hey, Mariamma. Hey, Mariamma.
- Yes, Uncle.
- Come here.
Hey, remove everything.
Be careful.
Mani. You'll have to come out.
CI Mouli has found
out that you're here.
We have to take her out.
Throw the ropes down.
Yes, come on.
Hey! Hold it.
Hold it tightly.
- Be careful.
- Ah!
Be very careful. Don't leave it.
- That's it.
Hurry up. We must hide
her before the cops arrive.
- Hurry up.
- Hey, you keep watch at the back.
She has started to have pains.
Don't worry. Nothing
will happen to her.
Sir, let her go.
Untie her hands.
Sir... Sir, leave her.
What kind of monster are you?
Leave her.
Don't commit this atrocity.
Sir, I beg of you.
- Sir.
- Ah!
Sir, please.
Please.
Let her go, sir.
Don't do this, sir.
Sir, please.
Madam. Madam. Madam.
Look at him. He is
torturing a pregnant woman.
I don't know if your
mother is alive or not.
But she would have taken her own
life, if she had seen you doing this.
I have lost trust in God
because of people like you.
She is suffering from pain.
Why are you screaming about it?
Get out of here.
It's written in history books
that before the independence,
the Britishers didn't oppress us
with their weapons and army.
It happened because
of the fear within us.
But history has witnessed
that when we fought
against them together,
they had to bow
down in front of us.
He'll lose his power to torment
once you stop fearing him.
He'll bow down in
front of you as well.
Are you trying to
provoke these people?
I'm making them realise
that they need not fear the gun.
After you run out
of your six bullets,
have you thought about
what they will do to you?
I'll take the first bullet.
I'll take the second one.
I'll take the third one.
I'll take the fourth.
You just wasted one bullet,
you scoundrel!
I'll take the fourth.
- We'll take it.
Sir, things are getting out of hand.
Let's go from here.
- We'll take it.
Everyone, let's get out of here.
- Let's go from here.
- Nagi! Nagi!
- Let's take Mani inside quickly.
- Be careful.
- Pick her up quickly.
- Hurry up.
- Be careful.
- Come on. Be careful.
- Let's go.
Brother, who is this woman?
She is Mrs Hemalatha.
All the progress that
our village has seen,
It was all possible from the moment,
she entered our village.
She is a social worker.
Just like Nageswara, she wants
to bring changes in Stuartpuram.
But without violence.
She met Nageswara a few days ago.
Then she...
Nagi. She is Mrs Hemalatha.
She wants to change
the condition of the village.
- Like you, she also... - What's her
real intention of coming here?
You'll be able to change the village
when you change yourself, Nagi.
Change always starts with us.
I'll fulfil your dream, but
by walking the right path.
I'll start the factory
for the villagers.
You just have to surrender.
You're wondering, where will I get
the money for the factory, right?
I know someone who'll give us
money in the form of donations.
Well, you'll get the money.
But the permission
to start the factory
will never be given by Yelamanda.
He'll create obstacles in your path.
If he does, Madam will go
to politicians superior to him.
But what would you do?
Everyone hates our village.
We are like animals to them.
When no one is
listening to your problems,
you become a problem yourself.
Do you think that I won't
be able to set up a factory?
I don't doubt it. That's the truth.
Would you surrender if I'm
successful in setting up a factory?
I'll get arrested the day
the factory is inaugurated.
Fine.
Madam.
I haven't finished talking.
You didn't tell me what
I'll get in case I win.
- What do you want?
- I'll tell you the day I win.
You're making a mistake, Nagi.
For the first time, I
wish for you to lose.
Until I change the
condition of Stuartpuram,
I'll live with you in this village.
- The village needs proper roads.
- 'Namaste.' - 'Namaste.'
We want the
development of the village.
Electricity is necessary for that.
- 'Namaste.
- Namaste.'
Here. Do it like this.
You all were working
in different states.
There's a reason that you have been
called from different departments.
Nageswara Rao.
He remains alert even
when he is asleep.
His special men,
Yaari, Mari,
Jaya Rao, Suryam,
Veera... Come on, boys.
Let's get charged.
He is killing our
people one by one.
The next turn is ours.
Do something, Nagi. Do something.
Madam has submitted a
new application for the factory.
But till Yelamanda is there,
he won't permit the application.
I need to write a
letter to someone.
Letter to whom?
To the Prime Minister.
He gets many letters
daily from people.
Why would he focus on our letter?
Because we won't go
to him with our problems.
But we'll give him such problems,
that he'll be forced
to listen to us.
'Tiger wrote a letter to the PM
that she is going to rob his house.'
Ah!
I've understood the problem.
Now, I'll bring the solution.
Let me go, Nagi.
I'll tell you where the gold is.
It is kept in locker number
26 of the Bangapur Bank.
If you want gold,
you'll have to steal
it from the bank.
There's no other option.
Nagi, Mani is here.
I brought your
favourite fish curry.
You eat it. Then we'll go.
Where will we go?
We have the
permission for the factory.
Tomorrow is the inauguration.
So what?
You said that you would surrender
once the factory is started.
Everyone is waiting for you there.
Let's go, Nagi.
I won't come.
Why not?
Because I have things to do.
You leave.
Hey, Yaari. Drop her home.
Where? Are you going to rob again?
Madam promised that you would not
face any danger if you surrender.
What will happen to me and
them if something happens to you?
Have you ever thought about it?
No harm would come to them.
Their father is here.
They were always with
you. Maari, Veera, Surya...
You couldn't save them.
How will you save us when
we'll be far away from you?
I know in which
bank the gold is in.
I need to get the
gold out of there.
No one will be able to
understand what I'm doing.
But it's not about you today. It's
about the children's happiness.
Take care of them, Mani.
Go now.
Yaari.
Mom, she is here.
Mani, did Nageswara Rao refuse?
Nagi just lost the final
opportunity to remain alive.
No one can save him now.
Just shoot him when you see him.
Search the entire forest.
It's not needed.
I will tell you where
Nageswara Rao is.
- Don't do it, Mani.
- Wait, brother.
I'll tell you everything you want.
But you must oblige my request, too.
What do you want?
You must take back the
shoot-at-sight orders on Nagi.
Alright.
Mani.
Getting arrested in the forest
and surrendering to Madam
are completely different
things. Mouli can do anything.
Mani.
The SP has given a
word to you before me.
Tell us where Nagi is hiding.
Tell us where Nageswara
Rao is hiding quickly.
How will you save him?
Uncle is here.
- Hey, Mahesh.
- Yeah.
What's happening?
It seems Nagi went to
rob the Bangapur Bank.
And the cops went to catch him.
Who informed the cops?
You will be shocked to hear it.
His wife informed them.
What did you do, Mani?
We have to send gold to Kolkata.
You know what you have to do next.
While Nagi robs banks
and enjoys that money,
the police punish our
children for his crimes.
Why does he need to rob when
everything is fine in the village?
We thought that he
did all of this for us.
But everything has been a lie.
No matter how many rivers
we pour water into the sea,
the seawater remains salty.
No matter how well
people like you are treated,
your minds think negatively.
What do you people even
know about him? Huh?
He has committed
thefts in running trains.
Three hundred guards...
14 feet of walls...
None could stop him.
Nagi even reached the Prime
Minister's place as a challenge.
He can easily make the world
bow to him if he wants to rule them.
We accept it.
We accept everything
that you've said about Nagi.
But would the police have
tormented us if he had surrendered?
The villages have roads, electricity
and the factory because of madam.
That monster deceived her as well.
Madam worked hard
but it wasn't her application
that got electricity in the village.
If Nagi hadn't run in the dark lanes
of the village, risking his life,
there would've been no electricity.
He deliberately made the
police run after him in the dark.
He takes advantage of the darkness.
We'll catch him if there's
electricity in the village.
He forced the police officers to
get the electricity for the village.
When he made the police
officers run on sandy roads
and wounded himself deliberately,
that's when you got proper roads.
The tyres get stuck when we
chase him with our vehicles.
And we can't run
like him in the sand.
We need proper roads to chase him.
The roads wouldn't have been built
if he hadn't spilt his own blood.
Then why did he challenge
me to build a factory?
Challenging Mrs Hemalatha Lavanam
and making a factory
through her was his first step.
It was because, his own money
was from robbery and was illegal.
So, through Angee Seth,
he helped that money reach
Hemalatha in the form of donations.
This was his second plan.
Please remember me
if there's any work for me.
'My name is Angi Seth.'
Nageswara Rao will make sure
you get the donation money
via Angi Seth.
The law has started accepting.
Nageswara's traps because of you.
That is why he kept the condition
so that you fulfil this task.
'Ah!'
'Nageswara, you've been
with me since childhood.'
'But I am
leaving you today, friend.'
He would've not become the police's
fodder if he had been selfish.
Neither would he live
in a worse condition
than animals in the forest.
He didn't go to steal people's
money in the Bangapur Bank.
He is going to steal
Yelamanda's gold from his locker
and give it to Angi Seth.
'He is bleeding so much.
Driver, call the doctor.'
'Seth, bullets couldn't harm me
since childhood.'
'Convert this gold into money
and give it to Madam.'
Madam Prime Minister.
Nageswara Rao has planned his final
move before starting the game.
There is a system exploiting
the helplessness
of the people of Stuartpuram,
including politicians,
police, and bureaucrats.
Despite all this,
Nageswara Rao devised
a grand scheme to build a factory.
Robbing your house was
a small part of that scheme.
He knows that we
wouldn't care about
the village if
we received applications.
So, what did he do?
He deliberately caused trouble
by making us visit Stuartpuram
and discover the issue ourselves.
Madam Prime Minister,
this is the note he left for me.
He knew that I would come there.
He even knows that I came.
Lord Krishna
has mentioned in the Gita
'Selfless work
is a strong deed.'
That action can
neither be good nor bad.
Neither is it a sin nor
a virtue. It is nothing.
If the cops catch Nageswara Rao,
I will fight in the court for him.
I will get him out with
a lesser punishment myself.
I came wherever you asked me to
and did whatever you told me to.
That's because you are
from Nageswara's gang.
But you've never shown me
a glimpse of Nageswara Rao.
- Shh!
- What happened?
- Come.
- Hey, who is it?
- What is it? What happened?
I've caught the police informer
who killed Nageswara Rao's people.
- I'll kill him myself, then.
- Hey! Wait.
Nageswara Rao will kill him.
Will Nageswara Rao come?
- You will meet Nageswara Rao today.
- Really?
You tie up the informer.
- I will get Nageswara.
- Alright.
Are you waiting for Nageswara Rao?
Didn't I promise you that I would
kill him after showing him to you?
He is Nageswara Rao.
Huh?
No, let him go, Sir.
No! Ah!
Ah!
No, Sir. Let him go.
'Sir, don't worry.'
'I will get Nageswara to you.'
Madam.
Madam!
Mouli has taken
Nageswara Rao to the factory.
Please save him!
I beg you.
- Let's go quickly.
- Run.
- Let's go.
- We must save him.
What is this? You've tied up
a tiger like a pet.
Oh, no! He is bleeding.
You killed my brother.
You stabbed me with the axe.
But you are still breathing.
Do you know why?
Upon slitting the neck,
a person dies once and for all.
But when you shatter his dreams,
he dies every day.
Sir, shatter his dream
of changing Stuartpuram.
I will kill him.
I've made arrangements
to close your factory.
Yesterday, we met Hyderabad's CM.
He told me,
'I don't want to disgrace
myself by supporting'
'a disgraceful village
like Stuartpuram.'
'Permission cancelled.'
After killing you, I will snatch
your village's dream of education.
I will show them their place again.
Sir, there's a call
from the party office.
'I don't understand
what's happening here.'
'You have been dismissed
from your post of MLA.'
'You've been dismissed
from the party, as well.'
The factory you wanted to stop,
the Central Minister will lay
its foundation tomorrow.
Hey! What are you blabbering?
I met the CM yesterday. I got
the permission cancellation order.
'Do you know where the order
of building the factory came from?'
The Prime Minister!
Nageswara Rao's way was wrong.
But his intentions were pure.
Any soldier would do
what he did to save
his motherland.
That's why Nageswara Rao
is not a criminal.
He is a revolutionary.
You met the CM,
but I met the PM, Yelamanda.
You are fortunate.
I won't leave you to die every day
after butchering your dream.
Instead, I will behead you
according to my promise.
I won't spare anyone. I will turn
the whole Stuartpuram to ashes.
Shoot him with all you have.
I am not a pet that you can chain.
I am Tiger.
Hey!
Ah!
Argh!
You turned peaceful
forest dwellers into thieves.
You used us for your selfish needs.
You didn't give us a chance
to educate ourselves.
Nor did you give us any jobs
if we were well-educated.
You also stopped
the factory's construction.
Argh!
You are the root cause
of our destruction.
I can die in peace
after uprooting you.
Today, our stories will end.
- Ah!
I am not leaving empty-handed.
Wait.
- Break it.
- Be quick. Break it.
Please save Nageswara.
Nageswara is here.
- Save him!
- Do it here.
They will kill him.
- Nageswara!
- Someone save Nageswara.
Nageswara, we are here.
Nageswara!
Nageswara, what happened?
What has happened?
Nageswara!
Nageswara, why aren't you talking?
You cannot leave us, Nageswara.
- Hey, Nageswara, what is this?
- Nageswara!
Uncle.
Nageswara, nothing
will happen to you!
Nageswara!
Nothing will
happen to you, Nageswara.
Nageswara! Someone, save him.
Nageswara.
You have won, Nageswara.
You helped us win this battle.
Madam, do you remember I said
I would ask for something if I win?
I might have done
a lot for the village.
But I did nothing
for my wife and children.
Their responsibility is yours.
Look after them.
Nageswara, nothing
will happen to you.
Perhaps not in this life,
but I will be a better husband
in the next life.
Nageswara!
You did so much for us, son!
'You will also get caught
if I am caught.'
'If the money slips
out of our hands,'
'Yelamanda will exact his revenge'
'by starving our people.'
'Listen, Nageswara.'
'Remember one thing.
If one person's death can save a hundred,'
'there is no greater victory than
that. My death is my victory, son.'
'Don't think, son. Kill me!'
"Hey!"
'You waged a war for your people.
Your sacrifice won't go in vain.'
'Tiger Nageswara Rao,'
'your name will be remembered
till this village exists.'
'We won't belittle your sacrifice'
'with closed eyes.
You will live forever.'
'I salute to you.'
Our village looks so beautiful
from the top. Right?
Oh no! They rang
the bell. I must leave.
- Where are you going in a hurry?
- I am going to school.
You won't have to steal
if I am well-educated.