If you rewind and remember
your life's first movie which developed
your interest in movies
100% it must be an action movie
So this video is like an action buffet
In this video I've made
10 categories of action videos
and selected 2 best movies in each category
So today's review I'll do
World's TOP 20 action movie
which are emotions rather than movies
Assemble
Number 1 category is Disaster Action Film
nature and human have done all big blasts
Which we see in these movies
VFX of disaster movies are great and realistic
That's why these movies are visual treat
*building crashing*
And the first movie in this list is
INDEPENDENCE DAY
*building blasts*
We celebrate
our independence day
and second is 2012
Are you sure you want to come with me
so beautiful I wanna stay
Number 2 category is Action Martial Arts
Almost Zero VFX, Zero graphics and
100% talent in these movies
You'll see hand to hand combats
faster than bullet trains
I've selected 2 movies in this category
First is THE RAID REDEMPTION
*kicks and punches*
And second is KILL BILL Vol. 1
Any more subordinates for me to kill?
Hi!
*metal crashes*
*music*
On number 3 Victory Over Fear
Action Horror Movies
This category movies didn't mery on us
Zombies, Vampires, Demons,
Super Natural evil Force; everything is in it
Number 1 in this category
THE MUMMY
You're in serious trouble
*intense music*
and on number 2, A Korean movie
TRAIN TO BUSAN
*intense music*
Number 4 category is
Action Drama
Movies of this category are epic and legend
Kids are named after these characters
There's character build, serious theme
and climax in Action drama
In world's top 20 action movies,
having the name of an Indian movie
Its time to feel proud once again
and that by BAHUBALI: THE CONCLUSION
Bahubali
*dramatic music*
The second movie of this list is
THE LORD OF THE RING
RETURN OF THE KING
The end has come
*screaming*
*music*
*screams*
On number 5 Science fiction Action Movies
The movies of this category are futuristic
Can see weird weapons and has space battle in it
This category has series instead of movies
We grew watching them
First is TERMINATOR
*gun loading*
Excellent
Its definitely you
*music*
ASTALA VISTALA
Baby
No!
Stay down!
*music*
and second is THE MATRIX
*crash*
Tonight I belive we can end this
That's a nice trick
Upgrade
On number 6 is Spy Action Films
In this category of movies one spy agent
is like one man army
and in whole movie
Shows different skills and kicks everyone's ass
And we might've noticed in this category
Great movies are made by Britishers
In this category all movies of James Bond falls but
the most liked is CASINO ROYALE
*car screeches*
*suspenseful music*
*car crashes*
The second series in this category is
MISSION IMPOSSIBLE
As the parts are getting released
Tom Cruise is breaking his records
Oh my god!
*music*
We've kept 2 categories for number 7
Both are very similar to each other
One is Action Thriller and second is Action Crime
There're 2 movies in Action Thriller
First is
THE DARK KNIGHT
*music*
and second is RAMBO SERIES
We deny any participation or
knowledge of your existence
Live for nothing
or die
*bombing*
for something
Now let's talk about Action Crime
In which all illegal businesses, Mafia,
Blackmailing, robber-police
and JOHN WICK series is full of it
*bike accelerating*
and second series is
FAST AND FURIOUS
Out of which 7th part ONE LAST RIDE
is our favourite
*GET LOW WHEN THE WHISTLE BLOWS*
Number 8 is Superhero Action Films
Hope it was real
In Superhero Action category
Chose 1 Marvel and 1 DC movie
In which first emotion is AVENGERS ENDGAME
Its not over
This is my destiny
Ah!
*Snaps*
Avenngers
Assemble
and second movie is
SUPERMAN RETURNS
*music*
On number 9 is tie between 2 categories
First is War Action Movies
This is most underrated category in action movies
But you'll see most hard work and large scale
cinematography in these movies
First movie is of Steven Speilberg
SAVING PRIVATE RYAN
*gunshots*
and second is
This is sparta
*music*
One more at number 9 Action Comedy
Father of Action comedy Jacky Chan
If there's a museum of action movies
the first statue should be of Jacky Chan
Do comment and tell me
do you watch Jacky Chan's movies
and action scenes again and again
You'll see best Action comedy of Jacky Chan
in DRUNKEN MASTER
*music*
The numebr 10 category; almost our favourite
category Action Adventure
The real fun is its experience
Every character has their life on stake in it
We've selected 2 movies
In which great chase sequence, physical challenges and
has exotic locations
First Action adventure movie is
INDIANA JONES SERIES
Second movie is from 21st century
which took action movie on net level
name is
MADMAX : FURY ROAD
*music*
Do tell me in comments about your
first rememberable action movie
There's list of randomly selected Top 10
action categories and its movies on your screen
If you like my small effort then please like this video
For such best movies and web series lists
Subscribe ABHI KA REVIEW channel
Thank you so much
Love you Take care
Bye bye