- This is $1 in penny. This is $20.
This is $100 in pennies.
That is $1,000 in pennies.
This is $2,000.
This is $10,000 in pennies.
Give or take like five
grand. I stopped counting.
And this is $20,000 in pennies.
- Wait, no it's not.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Alright, now it's $20,000.
So this is $20,000 in pennies.
We're gonna take these
$20,000 worth of pennies
and empty 'em on the backyard,
and Chandler's dad has no idea,
so when he gets home
there's gonna be $20,000 in pennies laying
across his entire backyard.
And then we're gonna help
him pick up all the pennies
and go buy a car,
'cause as you're remember
in the slime video,
he said he needs a car.
- I bought six cars, all for my kids,
and I'm the only one without a car now.
- So yeah guys, let's spread
the pennies across the yard.
I can't wait to see his reaction
and I can't wait to buy the car.
Alright, we're officially
gonna start covering
your dad's yard in pennies.
How does that make you feel?
- Good.
- How do you think your dad's gonna react?
- I don't know, honestly.
- Yeah? Alright.
- Whoa, that's a whole lot of pennies.
- Flashback to Chandler
doin' that to Chris.
- Good luck.
Actually, no.
- There you go.
We currently have seven
people opening up rolls
and we have five more coming.
But even once all 15 people arrive,
if we're all goin' super hard
there's no way we're even
gonna do like 10% of that
by the time Chandler's dad gets home.
Or maybe like 20, 30%,
but we're not gonna be able
to do like majority of that.
So me and Chris are gonna test some ways
to crack open these roles,
because these are what are taking forever.
It's just really time consuming
to bust them and get
the pennies out of it.
So we're gonna try to
find a more efficient way,
because if we don't figure somethin' out,
I guess we're just gonna have
to lay the rolls out in his
backyard, which is kinda lame.
It'd be so much funnier if
it was just the pennies.
But, I don't know, we're
running out of time.
So now we're gonna see what happens
if we try to burn off the paper.
'Cause maybe we can
just burn the paper off
this whole mound.
Apparently you can't
just burn the paper off
for whatever reason it doesn't burn.
We got two hours left
till his dad gets home.
We wanted to cover the
entire backyard in pennies,
but they're still wrapped up.
What do we do?
Alright, we're really desperate,
we're gonna see if this works again.
- I think it's just puttin' the fire out.
- Are you tellin' me firefighters should
just use pennies?
- It looks like it, man.
- What?
- Yeah, you're definitely
doin' stuff there.
Oh, you're gettin' 'em now.
- I think I am.
How do we unravel all these pennies
before Chandler's dad gets home?
- You havin' fun?
- No, just tired.
- I'm breakin' 'em open.
We're desperate.
- What would be good to mash-
- Ow, that hit my . Hit that direction.
Garrett's first swing.
- Just straight,
"Ow, my !"
- Fired it right at it.
- Yeah, I got hit in the eye.
How do you think I feel?
- Feel like this isn't very effective.
- Now we're gonna test the brick method,
'cause the golf club method
isn't really working.
I missed.
- Those look like the Ten Commandments.
- So I think at this rate
we'll cover this whole yard
in about a week.
- Yeah, unfortunately we only have
an hour and a half, though.
- Next we're gonna test the car method.
Alright, now let's see. How easy are they?
- Is that a good way to
pop the tire, actually?
- Dude, that tire looks
a little more deflated.
I got my secret weapon on my side now.
- Chandler, what are you doin'?
- Almost helping.
- Remember that time when we
threw a baseball bat at the car
and it almost killed Garrett?
- Yeah.
- Watch out.
- Oh.
- If we just had a bunch of pickaxes
this might actually work.
Surprising my friend's dad
with a lot of trash in his backyard.
What do we do?
I wanna surprise your dad
with a bunch of pennies in his backyard.
- I don't know what to do.
- I don't either! We're almost outta time.
Do we just leave 'em in the rolls?
Would that make our lives easier?
- It would make our lives 1000% easier.
- But is that what we're about?
- We've got that pile, that pile,
and then a couple in here.
It's currently, what, 3:00?
- We did this when we
bought the car with pennies
and we knew this would take forever.
- But we did it anyway,
'cause we're ab-so-lute
- Mad lads.
- mad lads.
- Yeah, but how did we know
this would take forever
and not realize it would take forever?
- Sprinkler.
- Oh my god.
- I actually didn't get hit by anything.
- That all hit me right in the head.
- I didn't get hit.
- Again.
- Put this in slowmo.
So we've got a mini army over
there, bustin' up the rolls,
but I really don't think
we're gonna open up all the rolls in time.
His dad's gonna be home in an
hour, what do we do, Chris?
- Even the greats fail sometimes.
You think Michael Jordan
hit every single dunk?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I guess you're right. Yeah.
I guess you just suck.
- Just so you guys understand,
we're tryin' to put out multiple,
really crazy videos every single week.
Our videos are so crazy
that we're working on
so many different videos
at the same day so we can do
at least two videos a week.
I really wanna get all the
pennies unrolled and laid out,
but we just simply didn't have time.
They're still gonna get the money.
They're still gonna get the cars.
The point I'm trying to make is that,
we're just trying to film so many videos
that sometimes it's hard for
every video to be perfect.
And also, his dad gets home in an hour,
so no matter what-
- Even if we didn't have videos
for the next four days.
- Yeah, we gotta be done
within another hour.
- Stick to the end
so that way you can see
the dealership's reaction
to the pennies
and what car Chandler and
his dad decide to get.
- Can you go back to work?
- Yeah, yeah, can you-
- We weren't done.
- Dad, you need M&Ms to
go with them Cheerio's,
don't you?
- Yeah.
- What's up, boy?
- Oh my goodness.
- Aw, he was ready
for another sandwich, bro.
- He has it.
- You thought he was.
- I mean, he's home.
I guess we can't keep it a
surprise anymore, let's just.
- All right, yeah, come on.
- Come on.
What do you do you think
we're doing at your house?
There's 14 people in
your backyard right now,
what do you think they're doing?
- I thought y'all was gonna
put that slime thing over.
- Yeah, we did.
We did put the slime tank in the backyard.
- I'm not gettin' back in that.
- We just wanted to put
it back there for fun.
Come look at it. Come on.
- Can't see right now.
- You can't see the slime tank
until you get closer.
- Three, two, one.
- Surprise.
- What the man?
- We were gonna put a bunch of pennies
in your backyard, but we couldn't
- You did.
- unroll them in time.
So we were gonna take 'em back,
but then you still came back.
So now we don't know what to do.
So there's a bunch of rolled
up pennies in your backyard.
- I think we could just leave it here
for you, right?
We don't have to clean 'em up anymore.
- You can take 'em to the bank for me.
- We were gonna unroll 'em all
and cover your entire
backyard in pennies, but-
- Apparently it takes a long time.
- It takes longer than 10 hours,
- Oh my god.
- which we didn't know.
But you have a lot of pennies now.
- Oh, I getta keep 'em?
- Yeah.
- We're gonna get a car.
- With pennies?
- With pennies, yeah.
It would've made so much more sense
- They have pennies there?
- if they were just laid out.
This is a dollar.
- I'll make sure I get
at least $1 outta this.
- 5 bucks in a box, right?
- How many pennies do you
think were in your backyard?
- $1000.
Times?
- 10?
- Keep on goin'.
- A little bit warmer.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- There's 21,000 here.
We were gonna surprise
you with them, but...
- $21,000 worth of pennies?
- Yessir.
- Yeah.
- We called the dealership,
they said they would
just take the pennies.
- They're gonna come get 'em?
- No, you load 'em up
and just go buy cars right now.
Whatever you and Chandler want.
- For real?
- Yeah. Sure.
- yeah. Dude, that's awesome, man.
- Yeah?
- Hold up.
- The fact that-
Awe. Yeah, look at that.
- There we go, man.
I'm gonna have a whip.
- Alright, let's get back
to loadin' 'em up.
I find it hilarious that
you thought it was slime.
- I really did.
Yesterday I'm like, oh god, you know what?
They said whoever won that
thing, they wanted to slime 'em.
- Y'all are some good people, Chris.
- Yes, sir. What do you think about it?
- I've been havin' to get
a ride of class every day
'cause he's usin' my car.
- Uh huh.
- So now that he has
his own, let's get it.
- What do you think about it?
- I think it's awesome.
- Mid chew there.
- Mr. Beast is a good guy.
- There you go.
- I'm glad I get to sit back
and watch what he does.
- Finally gettin' me a ride. Yes I am.
- You gonna get you a ride?
- yeah, dude. That's crazy.
- I got that.
- This just looks like pennies,
what it is is a new car.
- It's a new car?
- This sure is, brother.
- Who's your favorite president now?
- Jimmy. Mr. Beast is.
I actually got enough money
to get me a sweatshirt now.
I can get me some merch now.
- Some of that shopmrbeast merch.
- Good boy, man.
- Yeah?
- So I bet you didn't know havin' a son
would get you hooked up, did it?
- Finally paid off.
- Just have your son
work for a YouTuber.
- Right. Yeah.
- Hey, usually
havin' a child is really expensive.
- You guys should have children
so they can become friends with YouTubers
so you can get cool stuff.
Also, both of you guys lost
the slime video, so this is...
- This is redemption.
- This was worth it.
Dude, I can't believe this.
I can't believe this, boy.
- How long has it been
since you've had a car?
- So it's been six months.
I've been borrowin' Hannah's car
to get to work in the
mornin', come back home,
then take Zach's car to work.
Or they drop me off, I gotta
ride back with Uncle John.
It's been a pain in the butt.
- You picked out your car yet?
- Uh uh.
- You should probably do that.
- Oh yeah. In about 20 minutes
we're gonna go buy a car.
- Cool.
- You kinda gotta pick one.
- I haven't given you a hug yet, so.
Awe.
- Dude, it's just crazy.
I swear, man. I don't even know.
No, I did not expect none of this.
Dude, I thought I was
gettin' kicked outta my house
when I pulled up and saw the U-Haul.
Chris finally got rid of me, man.
- It's good content, so we all win.
- Yeah.
- I definitely won.
- I drank one of your drinks. Here you go.
- Hey.
- Oh, yeah. Actually-
- Root beer?
- Yeah, your root beer.
- I also ate some of your M&Ms.
- You can have your dollar back.
- Oh, thank you.
- Get me another quarter, though.
- You wanna help us?
- Heck no, I got a bad back, man.
I'm tryin' to recoup.
- He's rich.
Rich people don't have
to pick up their money.
- Boom.
- You know what, you're right.
- I'm glad this worked out really good.
- This worked out really good. Trust me.
- For you.
- Yes it did.
- Hey, when's my pennies
in the backyard video, though?
- Stay tuned.
- It's comin' up.
- So I'll give you guys a
little behind the scenes peek
of one of our videos.
This is usually the
amount of people it takes
to do these videos.
15 if you include me. 16 of
you include Chandler's dad.
Just movin' pennies.
Some of our videos literally
require an entire army.
We can do it on our own,
but if we wanna upload two
to three videos a week,
there's just no way.
'Cause this would literally
take us about two weeks
if we did it ourselves.
So we just finished
picking up all the pennies
and we put 'em in all of these boxes.
As you'll see, these
boxes are full of pennies.
We're gonna take all these
boxes to the dealership
and hopefully they give us a car.
We just got done surprising
Chandler's dad with the pennies.
And now we're gonna go to the dealership
and buy him and Chandler
whatever they want.
So let's talk strategy.
You guys could buy two $10,000 cars,
you could buy one $20,000 car,
you could put $20,000 down on
a car, $10,000 on two cars,
or you could just spend
it all on groceries.
What's the game plan?
- Groceries.
- Groceries?
- I'm gonna spend $10,000
on a down payment.
- Okay, so you're gonna put
10 grand on down payment.
So what are you gonna do
with the other 10 grand?
- I'm gonna try to get a car for 10 grand.
- Alright. That's the game plan.
He wants to put 10 grand down on a car.
He wants to buy a car for 10 grand.
Let's go see if we can make it happen.
Hopefully they take the pennies.
- So when I got home from work today,
and even after I saw all
those pennies in the yard,
- Yeah?
- I'm like,
yeah, it was a mess in my yard.
I'm like, oh we actually
get to keep these pennies?
- Yeah.
Well, when I told Chandler
I was gonna prank you,
Chandler was like, "Okay."
And I was like, "You get to keep 'em."
He's like, "Oh wait, what?"
Hey Chris.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey.
- Where are you guys goin'?
- We're going to get Chandler a car.
- No way, me too.
- Oh, I'll see you there.
- Alright.
- Hey, don't forget me!
- Oh, Chandler's dad a car.
I keep forgetting this is about you.
- Yes.
- That's the manager of the store.
Yeah, we returned a
destroyed rental car here
and we also bought a car from here.
Oh, and then we also
smashed my friend's car
and bought it from here.
Chand, come show us your new car.
Oh, look at this.
- My interior's black
and white. I love it.
- Whoa. That's actually
a pretty good interior.
- Isn't that nice?
- Dude, it's got the two tone.
It's got the new car smell.
- Sir, do you need help?
- No, I'm okay, man.
- Dude, I love the interior.
- Dude, it does look pretty dope.
- Yeah, this is a nice-
- What I wanna do is make it
matte black on the outside.
Dude, I've never bought a new car before.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- It's a fun experience.
- This is Chandler's special moment.
He's about to drive
his new car on the road
for the first time.
- Yeah.
- Dude, what if you got in a wreck?
- What if he just starts-
- Oh .
- Oh gosh.
- What the ?
- What is she doin'?
- You almost did get in a wreck.
- It's not meant to be.
- Chand's like, what did you say, Chris?
- You want me to hit him? Okay.
Sure. Whatever.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, this is my jam!
So how much is this, Chris? This is 4,650?
4,650 are still in the boxes.
Are you the accountant?
- This is our accountant right here.
- Sorry.
- Y'all are gonna help, right?
- Do you have experience
with counting pennies?
- Yeah, nah,
I haven't done it man.
- You got kids, right?
- Yeah, I've got two kids.
They're gonna help too.
- Okay. Perfect.
- Yeah, there you go, brother.
- Money's money, right?
- That's right, brother.
Money's money.
- We're buyin' two cars.
How do you like your car?
- I like it.
- Yeah?
- Brother Todd, what have you done
with that nice whip?
- It's not bad, is it?
- It's not bad at all, man.
You've even got the wood interior, man.
- These seats are cool,
air conditioned seats.
- You be ridin' in style, man.
- Yes, sir.
- Look at this thing.
You gon' pull up to the bingo
place like you own it, man.
- Yes, sir. Ridin' in style, baby!
- Hey Jake.
- What's up man? I like your car.
- Thanks. My brand new car
and my brand new Beast merch.
- Hey, that stuff looks fire.
- Isn't this car amazing?
I love it so much.
And my dad really loves his car.
And I just wanna say thank
you again for the car.
I'm gonna drive it every day of my life
for the rest of my life.
- Every day?
- For the rest.
- Forever?
- Forever.
- And ever?
- And ever.
- Hey.
- That's a good horn.
♪ MrBeast, oh ♪