- For thousands of years,
humans have tried to fly like birds.
- We can't do it.
- We couldn't before, but we can now.
- We can?
- Watch this clip.
Oh my goodness!
He is literally flying.
Tell me, what's the difference
between this gentleman here and Superman?
- This guy has probably
a million dollar suit on.
More of a Ironman really.
- I just wanna make sure it's very clear.
I've never seen Superman
and this guy flying at the same time.
- That's true.
All right, this is a little speedboat.
The sea breacher.
It looks like a whale.
Oh my God!
- A whale boat!
Whale boat!
- It's so cute!
- Wait, since when were
whale boat's a thing?
- I don't even want the
flying thing anymore.
I just want this cute thing.
- Comment down below.
Whale boat or flying thing?
- Whale boat.
- What happens if you just--
- Whoa!
Yeah, whale boat all day.
- Aww! The whale boat lost its owner.
- Its nose is waiting for me.
All right. Boston Dynamics.
Everybody's seen them.
Let's see what it can--
- Oh.
Oh, that's smooth.
- It is more nimble than us.
- Oh my God!
We need to be careful.
Boston Dynamics might take over the world.
So now we got a plane.
- How's this allowed?
- Those guys are flying by themselves.
- With those jet packs.
- What?
- This is some GTA 5 stuff.
- Oh my goodness!
Dude, they're getting
so close to the plane.
Dude, chill out.
- Dude. That just goes to show you.
In Dubai, if you got enough money
you can do literally anything you want.
- That's probably the coolest
thing I've seen all day.
- You know what's really cool?
- What?
- Slow-mo shot walking outta the water.
Oh wait, he's not walking.
- He's flying.
You idiot.
- What? I'm stupid.
- Nicompoop!
- I'm just so dumb.
These things are so hard to use.
Have you ever seen people
that don't know how to use them use them?
- I feel like I would just drown.
- They'd just go, " ".
Oh, he's just dropping this guy.
- Bye bye.
- That's so humiliating.
Just getting dropped
by the flying cool guy.
- He's dumping man.
- There's no way that's real.
I refuse.
- Flying bike!
- Does it turn into a normal bike, please?
God!
Oh, I need it.
This is definitely the car you unlock
at the end of some James Bond video game.
- No way! Is this actually a flying car?
No.
- This is so cool.
- Is that spinny thing
usually on the front?
- The propeller?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, usually. Except
for this is a flying car.
- Oh my God!
- That is so cool.
- I'm gonna go rob a bang and
then just get away with this.
- That is so cool.
- Bravo to whoever built that.
First I thought that was a real person.
- It's a plasma torch style lightsaber.
- AKA lightsaber.
- Hack Smith, please let me use it.
- I meant to reach out to him
to ask if we could borrow his lightsaber.
I think I forgot though.
- You should remember to
do something like that.
Look at this.
You forgot this?
If we had this when we were
doing the bounty hunter video
it would've been over instantly.
What would you have done if
I had somehow contacted--
- Yeah. Oh yeah when I
was stuck in the save.
And you had that? Oh!
- Yeah.
- I mean I just would've ran
out the secret door faster.
- It's the drone.
It's the pizza delivery drone.
Oh my God!
- You're telling me there's pizza drone?
- Yes. I want this in my neighborhood.
It gives you your little pizza
and it keeps it warm in the pizza warmer.
- Whoa!
- Oh, get pushed over.
You stupid robot.
- A dog!
Do you want robots to take over?
- How about you stop being an idiot?
- Jimmy? He's getting up.
It was the one thing robots
were never able to do.
They can do it now.
They can get up.
- Oh, you pushed me down?
I'll just run away.
- I'm leaving.
- This looks like a
sad scene from a movie.
- Jimmy?
- Yes, Chris.
- I found your car.
You need this.
- Oh my God!
- The tires were enough
reason that you get this car.
- Controls are.
- Crab car.
Yo, he's literally surfing on a drone.
That's so cool.
I never would've thought to
do that, but now I want to.
Oh and there's a disclaimer.
I can't replicate this.
They're dancing!
- Robot dance party!
- Yeah!
This makes me happy.
- I personally accept our robot overlords
and I'm looking forward to serving them.
Please spare me.
- As long as I get to make
YouTube videos, I'll be fine.
I just love how that guy
right up there is just like,
"Yes, dance for me robot."
- And they're like, "Ah! It hurts."
I love the dog one.
He's really--
- I also love the guy
in the background just walking away like,
"Yeah. I've seen the robot
dance party a thousand times.
"Nothing special."
- This seems like it would
be a part of a movie.
It's all happy.
And then all of a sudden the music stops.
Their lights turn red.
- Yeah. And they just start
taking over the world.
- And this one is like the leader
'cause he is like the snake
and he is really smart.
Oh no!
- No! Robots!
How many robots do they have?
- Yo, he's racing a Lamborghini.
- Who's faster Lamborghini or--
- Fly guy?
- Ooh, that fly guy just fell off.
- I don't think he can.
I think he's like locked to it.
That's so cool.
- It's so dangerous.
- He only lived one life.
"I just had a little fun.
"Fly through the sky every now and again
"at ridiculous breakneck speeds."
- Is this an ad?
- No, this is a video.
Razor made of masks.
It just goes to show gamers
will put RGB on anything.
- Anything. Yeah.
- Literally anything.
They got me though.
I want it.
This is just something some guy made.
This is cool.
- It looks like the
thing from Tron: Legacy.
- Yeah, it does.
- I feel like he's not going that fast.
- No, I was about to say that.
- Like I feel like I could
walk faster than this.
- But you have to think.
I mean he's probably
doesn't wanna go too fast
'cause it looks really dangerous.
- He's just on a rotating tire.
- That he built that.
That's so crazy.
Yo, did this guy just
interrupt a soccer match?
- Is this planned or not?
This is planned, yeah.
- Oh wait, he's delivering the ball.
- No way.
- That's so cool.
- That's cool.
Man, this guy probably
has a lot of girlfriends.
It's a shame if he only
has one girlfriend.
- Oh, that's when you wanna
reveal your full face.
That was really cool.
- Drone bike.
- Dubai Police.
The Dubai police is gonna
fly through on drones?
- Oh my God!
- You're trying to steal
some old lady's purse.
- And then--
- Drone force!
You thinking of Mackerel or shrimp?
- I'm thinking of U-Tube.
- Just the capital U.
- Yeah, it is.
I wonder if people working
at YouTube sees this video
and they're like, " ".
- They were like, " We
were gonna sue him but."
- It's not YouTube.
It's U-Tube.
- Whoa! Mini helicopter.
- If there's one thing
I've learned today is that
literally anything can fly.
A car, a jet pack, a bike, anything.
- Even man.
- I wonder if he prefers
flying over land or water?
- Water. 'Cause if you fall,
water doesn't hurt as bad,
I guess, and then is he just gonna land?
- No way.
- He lands on the Rock.
- No, that wasn't the Rock.
That was a rock.
- Oh, the Rock is probably
busy filming a movie
or something.
- Exactly. Exactly.
This robot's good at Minecraft Parkour.
- This is the next dream.
- Yes. This is dream Iro.
I mean, dream hasn't done a face reveal.
For all we know, this could be Dream.
- Dream actually might just
be a robot we don't know yet.
Oh gosh!
No. I don't like this.
Microsoft can own every
fabric of your life.
- I want this.
- You want holograms?
- Of course.
- Once they can implement
it to video games.
- 12 seconds later.
- Oh, there it is.
Okay. Yeah, you got me.
It's cool. All right now it's fine.
All right. Nevermind, Microsoft.
You can have every right to my body.
- Wait.
- The Marines were like,
"We need Jet to go fast.
"Fast from beginning. At all times fast."
- They're like, "How can we get this plane
"to ascend fast?"
- Explosions!
- The plane's literally on fire.
- It really does look, not look okay.
Like, oh and now it's fine.
- Yo, I love these things.
Do you know what these are?
- No. What is this?
- So it's an artist
and he builds these contraptions
that move on their own
on the beach.
- They propel their-self.
- With wind.
- That's so cool.
It looks like a creature.
- These things are crazy,
but sometimes the wind takes him over.
Guess what?
Another jet pack.
- But this one has wings
now instead of on his hand.
- Literally. How many
kinds of jet packs exist?
- 38.
- The Falcon Rocket Landing.
Yes.
- Yes.
- Land.
Land. Look at that vertical precision.
Elon Musk is perfect.
- Tell us how you really feel Jimmy.
- That's the Elon meme and let's go.
- Hey, you know what's
cooler than a rocket landing?
- Raft surfing?
- Raft hang glider playing.
- Did you see? I gotta
look back at the camera.
He's like, "You, you getting this?"
- He's like, "That's cool, I guess."
It's kinda like the one
wheel but with two wheels.
Yeah. I'm gonna need that.
- You're gonna need a lot
of things from this video.
- If any of these companies
wanna send me any of these
things I'll take even this.
- What about giant moped?
- I don't know. It's kind of chunky.
Wait, that's a moped jet ski.
Yes!
Yes, yes! Give it to me.
I don't care how goofy it looks.
- I was like, "I take it back too."
I was about to trash on it.
You should have started off
by telling us it was a moped jet ski.
- Yeah, like this shot.
Start with this.
This is how you sell this.
- Wow! It's that easy?
That's a smooth transition.
Robot man.
- Is this a Honda robot?
- Honda made a robot.
- Wait, this is CGI, is it not?
- Oh, no. Asimo's real?
Yeah, Asimo's been in
development for a long time.
- Oh, CGI.
- No.
- Asimo more like Asim-no.
- No. Oh, he's sad.
Hey, who's this nerd?
- It's that guy no one like.
- He's definitely not cooler than us.
- He ruined vlogs.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm gonna call Casey.
I love that guy.
- Yeah, same.
- I miss when Casey
used to do these videos.
I don't think he does them--
Oh my God!
Casey, you are literally insane.
- This is literally Ironman.
This is like the Cave Ironman too.
Oh, this is gonna be so cool.
Imagine movies when this stuff
gets like more streamlined.
- Yeah, they don't even
have to CGI or anything.
You know what everybody?
I'm gonna need you to hit that
subscribe button right now!
We are closing in on
10 million subscribers
and if we hit 10 million
subscribers, I'll be very happy.
- I will also be happy.
- Does this make you happy?
- Yes.