- This is a video of the
best workers on the planet.
- The best.
- Like this guy who can make
a whopper in under one second
or this person who can do
the job of a hundred people.
- That's crazy, we should hire him.
- All right, so we have a bus
boy cleaning a table, bro.
This dude's cleaning at
like his life's on the line.
- He's sonic and he is speed
- For some reason this reminds me of like
a battle in Naruto.
I wanna go there and
order a hundred pancakes
but each on a different plate.
So then he has to pick up all of them.
I wanna see a God in action.
- Oh, this is the type of stuff I like.
This is working smarter, not harder.
- No way, is this how you actually do it?
- This is how you break
things if you want to.
But this guy got lucky.
- That is probably the
coolest thing I've ever seen.
I wonder if it costs less to hire him
because he doesn't need a real truck.
- It probably calls more to insure him
because there's a good chance
he's gonna break something.
- Bro is moving.
- Oh my goodness.
Oh, it's firefighter truck.
- Oh, snap.
- We assume he's a firefighter.
He could just be a guy who
really likes climbing ladders.
- We?
You!
- Sorry.
- All right.
This is the fastest Whopper ever made.
- I'll be the judge of that.
Actually, that person with the clock
will be the judge of that.
- Look at him, his positioning, his face.
That is intense focus.
We're about to witness history.
- Oh, ketchup fell over part of his plan.
See, now it's ready.
Oh my God, it was ready for the squirt.
- Yes.
- I would say I'm impressed,
but Burger King sucks.
Go order Beast Burger
it's 30 times better.
- Burger Kings do Beast Burger better.
- Oh my God.
- Oh, that's sick.
- Oh
- He's just popping off.
- If I saw that, I would
just walk up to him
and give him a $50 bill.
- Yeah, I have a strong urge
to give him tons of money.
I wonder what's gonna happen.
Oh wait, that's not what
I thought would happen.
I thought they were about to pop off.
- This man knows physics,
geometry, and math.
He's unstoppable.
You know what's more impressive
than that guy who's
clearly forklift certified?
- Who?
- This rectangular ice cream cone.
What is this?
- I got it.
Circular ice cream cone.
This ice cream goes up to
the edges when it melts,
it drips down the side.
It's sticky and it sucks.
This one, it drips into the box.
- Yeah, it's like a bathtub.
- It is.
It's like an ice cream cone bathtub.
- Oh my God, this is genius.
- Whoa, it's still going.
- Look at that.
And he made a sword with it.
This guy's smart.
I've always thought about doing this,
but I've never done it
- Until he falls.
- I like the music.
It makes it feel like I'm
watching a Disney princess
- Making a fence.
- They make it with sand.
Oh my God.
That's so genius.
Cause then they can just pour.
Oh my God.
That's Minecraft.
But real life.
- That's cool.
This is the world's best cucumber chopper.
- I've already sliced my
hands a thousand times
if this was me.
- Wow.
- That's paper thin.
- Here's the problem.
Cucumbers tastes horrible.
- Whoa.
Oh, when the clip said a bunch of men
pounding on the title card,
I thought something else.
This is cool.
- More importantly,
where's that spike going?
Are they like literally
nailing the parking lot
to the earth?
- I know what they're doing.
They're building experiences together.
- Losers.
Window cleaning contests.
I wouldn't believe if it's real
if there wasn't a giant
banner in the background.
- You're not telling
me you're not a big fan
of the International Window
Cleaning Association.
- IWCA?
- It's just a bunch of old dads.
This guy's good though.
Marty's killing it.
Yeah!
- Cleaning up dishes.
- He's making a flower.
- Somebody's dad.
He's making a flower.
I strive to be that annoying of a dad.
- Wow
That's impressive.
That's someone who loves their job.
- [TikTok ker} Got
something new for y'all.
I am super proud of this one.
- Is that toilet paper?
- I'm going to call the
mega multiverse combo.
- Oh, I did not know where that was.
Oh my God, that is insane.
- Wait so he tie dyed that?
- He tie dyed that with rubber bands
in certain ways that those
patterns would get on the shirt.
- Some would say, Epic.
Oh, it's the attractive
guy that hits wood.
- I see the comments all the time.
Everybody's mom is on
this guy's TikTok page.
Oh, he's ripping it this time.
Nice.
- Moms, leave a comment on the video.
I really want to get our mom
demographic up a little bit.
Bobcat Pro driver.
- Whoa, he nice with it?
- Oh, oh.
- Bro, why is this guy so good?
I would love to see what
jobs he gets hired for.
- I'd hire him for a circus.
Hey, let's watch this
guy work with his wood.
- Wait, no, that's not his wood.
That's a piece of wood.
- Oh, is this a bed post?
- That or a lampshade.
- We'll never know.
- You will forever wonder
and never get the answer.
Ever.
Good luck sleeping tonight.
- Oh yeah.
I did this as a kid with my four wheeler.
I lived in the country.
I had a four wheeler.
We didn't have these fancy go-karts.
- Oh my God.
That's pretty innovative.
- Fun fact, I heard that go-kart.
Speeding past my house
at 3:00 AM last night
and I looked out and Carl was
doing donuts in my front yard.
- Bro, why don't I get
invited to the adventures?
- I guess you just gotta
be there when Carl has his
3:00 AM adventures.
Whoa.
He said physics pause for one second.
I gotta look cool.
Okay, it touched his
finger on the last one.
Did anybody see it pour down his finger
and go into the drink.
- Oh wow, I'm still taking the shot.
Of great juice, shot of great juice.
- I mean, I could trim a
bush like this, I feel like
I don't feel like this one's any special.
Show me a penguin or a giraffe.
- Oh, he missed a spot.
- He missed a spot.
- He missed his spot.
- He's about to hit that spot.
- Hit the spot.
- Hit that spot right there.
Yeah, there we go.
- I almost ended the video.
This person's cutting up some food.
- They have pretty hands.
Is that Chandler?
- Today we are making
HelloFresh stir-fried tacos.
- Wait, since when can Chandler cook?
- With the sponsors video, HelloFresh.
Anyone in the world can cook.
They have 30 different weekly recipes
that you can choose from to
have delivered to your doorstep.
HelloFresh even cuts down on food waste
over using grocery store.
And most importantly,
you save time and money.
Instead of ordering delivery,
going to a restaurant
or a grocery store, just
use HelloFresh, instead.
If you don't know what to cook
or just in general wanna
upgrade your meals,
go to hellofresh.com right now
and use code reacts65 for 65% off.
Plus it's free shipping.
No reason not to.
- Do it.
Look how good that food turned out.
If Chandler can make food like that,
anyone can make food like that.
So go to hellofresh.com and
use code reacts65 for 65% off
and free shipping whenever
we finish this video.
Let's go eat at Chandler's house.
- As long as he's making HelloFresh.
Building a cell tower.
Oh my God, that is insane.
- How'd they get up there?
Oh my goodness.
- Old man with ten lawnmowers.
- This is probably the coolest thing
I've ever seen in my life.
- This is the smartest old
man in the entire world.
- This guy pulls up to your front door,
demands your girlfriend.
What's you doing?
- It's hers.
I mean, it's his, I don't know.
I'm so confused by these lawnmowers.
He can have whatever he wants.
He can have the house.
My dog.
The yard.
- Wait, what's going on here?
- Oh
- Drift.
- Drift acholic.
Yeah, this guy's good at parking.
This is the most British
thing I've ever seen
a man getting excited
about parallel parking.
Oh my God.
They're playing Minecraft IRL,
put the Minecraft music over it
and then when he puts
it in the wheelbarrow,
make the chest sound.
That's funny now.
Lighting a lighter with an excavator.
- No way.
- What?
- How did he do that?
That is so cool.
- Why did he have to use
seven phones as a table?
Couldn't he use like a rock or something?
- He just borrowed everyone's
like, Hey everyone,
gimme your phones.
- Give me your phones.
I need them, they might break.
This guy needed a trim bad
giving a good shear call him Ed Shearing.
No
- That's not the same person.
There's no way that's the same person.
Hold on. It is!
He made that guy look like a
completely different person
with that haircut.
Wow, that's wild.
They say the hair makes the man.
- Wait what happens here?
- He's destroying the,-
- The ceiling he's on.
- But he's on a crane.
He's like, I'm free.
Oh my God.
It's Jason Bourne.
I feel like I can do that.
Oh my God.
- Delivering your food on time.
- I want to go here right now.
- Hey bro.
It's the hundred pancakes
I ordered earlier.
- They're finally here.
- One for a bowl.
Oh my gosh.
I didn't even know this was here.
- Let's go, with the
call back of a century.
- Whatever this restaurant
is, bring that guy in.
He can clean it up quick.
- I'm leaving whatever
this job can be considered
to go be a rollerskate-
- You don't work here.
- Yeah, you're right.
They just keep unlocking
the door and let me back in.
- I give him free food.
- That's gotta be in Japan.
And why do we live in America, man?
Look, they got it figured out.
- But is she drawing?
Oh my gosh.
- Is she better with her
feet or with her hand?
- She's doing them all at the same time.
- The ones with her hand
are so photorealistic.
- There's no way this is real.
I, I refuse to believe it.
If this is real, it is factually
the coolest thing I've ever seen
and I've said that many
times in this video.
Zoom in on the bottom right one.
She drew that with her foot
while drawing with her other foot.
You have no talent compared to her
- I, you're right.
- Neither do I.
- This looks like a really good way
for a customer to be like
all right I'm walking out
and then just bang, tire.
- Using a water shield.
- Oh, that's cool.
Oh, it was like a propane
tank that was on fire.
So he is using the
water to shield the fire
so he can turn it off.
Genius.
Where do you, where did
he get that fire from?
- I don't know where the fire came from.
- He is Prince Zuko.
Refueling an RC car.
Oh, this is one of those cars that runs
off of like pure alcohol.
That's why they're so fast.
Look at that thing.
- Remind you, when we tried
to push a car with RC cars.
Oh my god.
- Oh my God.
- Wait, is that really how they film?
- Wow, he is really good at that.
- He might just put Tariq out of a job.
Oh my God.
So the wasps were just
like standing there.
It's like the wasps are paid actors.
- Well, I think the wasp for
like God wouldn't intervene
between the fights of wasp
and bees and then God's like.
Makes sense.
- Funny pan sound.
Is it the spin and drummer guy?
Yeah.
Go drum guy.
- Would you say he's the
best drummer in the world?
- I would say he's probably
the dizziest drummer
in the world.
- Thank you so much for watching.
I hope you enjoyed it.
If you haven't already subscribed.
- Please.
- Right now.