We are leaving from
Delhi to HongKong.
And we thought of eating something
in the lounge, we were very hungry.
We sat in this lounge,
I didn't like anything,
I said let's go to
another lounge.
I went to stylish, I didn't
understand anything there.
Now we try Delhi capitals.
When we went to the second lounge, I said,
let's order something to eat.
Meanwhile, I did some check-out, I
was told that Cathay gave me some gifts.
I found this while checking
in, let's see what's in it.
I am calling Anish, his
phone is switched off.
When I checked out in the
second lounge, it was not fun,
I thought while leaving.
The previous one was
good, it was useless here.
Then I thought, no problem,
we are traveling for business
class, we will eat delicious food.
As soon as we got on
the plane, we got screwed.
Bro, they didn't give us dinner.
Because maybe they don't have
late night dinner in HongKong.
They will serve breakfast in the morning.
It was night and I was feeling hungry.
We slept, finally I got my
breakfast in the morning.
We didn't have dinner, but
as soon as I got my breakfast,
It was time to land.
The captain announced,
cabin crew please prepare.
Bro, I just put the first
morsel in my mouth,
The cabin crew pulled
the tray from in front of me.
Sir, we are about to
land, you can't eat now.
Zooming in to see who
is bathing on the beach.
Finally we reached our room.
On the way, I was feeling so sleepy.
I thought we will see Hong Kong later.
Brother, I slept in the car.
Right now we have reached our room.
I was so sleepy, as if a drunk person
doesn't know what is happening all around.
I was so sleepy, I came to the room.
Although this view is super awesome.
Now I am thinking, this
is it,
This is where I have to sleep.
Should I put a bedsheet here?
I mean, I don't like this bedroom.
Then I am thinking, from where should I go?
I think that is also a
mirror, this is also a mirror.
I thought it is a mirror.
After an hour, I realized
that no, this is the bedroom.
So let's do one thing,
I will sleep now.
I will give you a room tour later.
It is a very amazing room, but I
will definitely give you a room tour.
Look at this brother, awesome.
Awesome view, one of the best views.
This is a coffee station.
Coffee machine.
And here you will get a liquor machine.
Here are all the things
to make coffee and tea.
Here is a mini bar.
This is the workplace, they
have given me a good fruit basket.
And the chocolate was amazing.
Look at this, awesome, amazing.
They have given me this, a
bottle of alcohol, to drink at night.
Brother, look at the view.
This is a value for money view.
This is a jogging track.
People have been
jogging here since morning.
The sun is not so bright
outside, because they are jogging.
But the view at night here,
There is a whole building in front.
Okay
And here at night, when the
lights will be on, it will be amazing.
This is our bedroom.
This is the bedroom, sorry i slept here.
Bath area is amazing.
There are two bathrooms and
two washbasins don't know why.
This area is so big here you can...
Here are the amenities.
This is a shaving mirror.
You must have read
in the chapter of optics.
This is a concave mirror.
This is a concave lens.
Let's go out now.
Let's explore the city.
I saw two Indians here.
They are not interested in this dog.
Actually they are hitting a girl on thr pretext of dog.
I can bet 100%.
Is Bruce-Lee is from HongKong?
Yes, he is born in Hong Kong.
He went to primary school in Hong Kong.
We have come to the heart of Hong Kong.
This is old Hong Kong.
The guide told us, this
street is full of original shoes.
No bargaining.
One fixed price.
It feels like we are in China.
This is a ladies market.
Here fierce bargaining is done.
And original item is not available.
This is a whole shoe market.
We are going to the shoe market.
Finally I bought this shoe .
I came here to make a vlog.
But the shoes are very cheap here.
Sneaker fans from India will
empty this store in a minute.
I can bet on it.
This shoe is for 9000 rupees.
After getting free from this market,
We went to the most
amazing place in Hong Kong.
We took this train which took us
directly to the top of the mountain.
And from there
Woooooo
You can see the best view of HongKong city.
Enjoy this view.
That's it for today's video.
See you in the next video.