O' Lord, when I came to this house,
I had imagined I'd leave
this house only after dying.
But the circumstances
and my fate have compelled me
to leave this house.
I can't bear the heir to this family.
But it is my duty
to ensure the happiness of this family.
I have no option but to leave this house.
Take care of Vinayak, O' Lord.
Make sure he never misses me.
And ensure Maya gets every joy in life.
She should get whatever she wants.
In order to give this family its heir
Siddhi will make the sacrifice
and not Maya.
[Sanskrit chants]
I love you, Siddhi.
[Devotional song]
O' Goddess, You know
that I have no bad intentions
or malice in my heart.
I have left the house.
But I am clueless as to
where I am going to go.
I am facing this dilemma
of relationship and life.
I see no future for myself.
Show me a way, O' Goddess.
Help me.
Take me under Your shelter.
[Devotional song]
[Sanskrit chants]
Wait. Careful, dear.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Careful, my dear.
You should not stand up suddenly
in this condition.
You must be even more careful now.
Why? What's wrong with me?
You are pregnant.
I am pregnant?
No. How is this possible?
Why are you saying so?
You should be happy and not shocked
for the Goddess has blessed you.
But the reports clearly stated
that I can never conceive.
So how can you be sure of it?
Doctors are humans too.
They are not greater than God.
Before giving you joy,
the Goddess tests
her devotee's faith at times.
When you collapsed,
I was right there.
I have years of experience.
I knew the moment I read your pulse
that you are pregnant.
Indeed, you are no lesser
than a Goddess for me.
Bless you, dear.
Hey, where are you going
all alone with the bag?
To find the answers
to some unanswered questions.
Beware.
In this selfish world,
not everyone who claims
to be your own is so.
At times the person we love the most
turns out to be our greatest enemy.
What are you saying?
How can you accuse me?
I am not accusing you.
I just want to know the truth
as to why you lied to me.
Why did you say that I can never conceive?
Why did you make fake reports?
I never lied to you.
Nor did I make fake reports.
The truth is that
you can never conceive a baby.
Shame on you.
Not just me,
you have cheated your profession too.
You must be penalised for it.
Let me call the cops.
I will make sure you are thrown in jail.
What are you doing?
Please do not call the police.
Please, I have family.
I have a good reputation
in the market. Sorry.
I am really sorry.
I did not do it on my will.
Someone asked me to do it.
Who told you to make these fake reports?
Tell me.
You have no idea that these reports
have wreaked havoc in my life.
Please tell me.
The truth is bitter.
Will you be able bear this truth?
Please tell me.
Vinayak Pandey told me
to make the fake reports.
Yes, your husband asked me
to make fake reports.
He was the one who told me
to lie to everyone.
No.
You are lying.
My husband can never do that.
You are lying, aren't you?
Why don't you ask him why he did that?
But the truth is that your husband met
me personally to discuss this matter.
And he paid me
one lakh rupees for the fake report.
This can't be.
Vinayak can never do that.
What proof do you have?
Tell me. What proof do you have?
I have the proof.
This is the CCTV footage from my cabin.
See it for yourself.
Yes, your husband asked me
to make fake reports
He was the one who told me
to lie to everyone.
And he paid me
one lakh rupees for the fake report.
How could you stoop so low, Siddhi?
How can you doubt your husband Vinayak?'
The Vinayak who stood up for you.
The Vinayak, whose love changed your life.
You are mistaken, Siddhi.
Vinayak has just betrayed you.
He faked loving you and then married you.
Then he put the crown of thorns on you
and threw you out of the house.
If there is someone
who has made a mockery of your life
then it's only Vinayak.
These are things of the past.
Vinayak loves you.
And he has proved it a number of times.
Maybe.
But Siddhi, if he can betray you once,
he can betray you again.
His love is fake.
It is not true.
Maya, I'll burn my hand
if you leave the house.
I must meet and talk to Vinayak.
I will talk to Vinayak
and find out the entire truth
no matter what.
'Siddhi.'
Siddhi, where are you?
You are not answering my calls
or replying to my messages.
I have been looking for you like crazy.
Where are you?
And where did you go without informing?
I want to meet you.
But not at home.
I am sending the location.
Okay. But where are you?
Just do as I say.
Okay. Send the location.
I am coming.
O' Lord, please do not let my trust
get broken.
A woman can bear the greatest betrayal
but not the betrayal by her husband.
I have years of experience.
I knew the moment I read your pulse
that you are pregnant.
Why are you standing far from me, Vinayak?
What's the matter?
Aren't you happy to see me?
I am going to ask you something.
If you've ever loved me truly,
swear to it
and give me an honest answer
to the question I ask.
Is it true
that you told the doctor
to make the fake report?
What rubbish!
Why would I make my wife's fake reports?
Before you say anything
let me tell you
that I have seen the CCTV footage.
I saw you paying the doctor
to make the reports.
I just want to hear it from you.
Say that it is a lie.
I will think that my eyes lied to me
and forget it.
Vinayak, look into my eyes
and say that you did not betray me.
You are my wife, Siddhi.
I have married you.
How can I lie to you?
Why are you laughing, Vinayak?
You want the truth, right?
So here it is.
Yes, I made those fake reports.
I paid that doctor
so that my family thinks
that you are infertile.
And you can't give it an heir.
The CCTV footage is also real.
And what the doctor said is also true.
And it is also true
that my dark-skinned wife...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I wanted to get rid of
my very dark-skinned wife.
It's simple.
Why would Vinayak Pandey
who is every girl's dream man
love a dark-skinned girl like you?
Hence, I want to get rid of you.
And there is an even greater truth.
Do you want to hear it?
Tell me. You'll be devastated if I say it.
So what?
You want the truth, right?
So here it is.
I love your sister, Maya, and not you.
Maya is my first love and my life.
And Maya is someone
who matches Vinayak Pandey's
class and stature.
And Maya should have been
Vinayak Pandey's actual choice.
And you...
You are the mistake
I am going to rectify very soon.
And Maya and I...
Enough!
Don't you dare even utter
my sister's name.
I am ashamed of myself
for I made the mistake
of falling in love
with a disgusting man like you.
I thought I was wise.
But I am so dumb for
I fell for what you said.
What's done is done.
But I will not let my sister go through
what I've been through.
I know you will bewitch my sister too.
You will pretend to love her
and then ditch her too.
But I will not let anything of
that sort happen to my naive sister.
I will expose you.
I will tell your family
how disgusting
and loathsome a human being you are.
My bad.
Calling you a human being
is a disgrace to mankind.
Leave my hand.
You will expose me
only if you stay alive, right?
You have nowhere to go.
Ever since you have come into my life,
my life has become miserable.
Now that you know the truth,
you have made my job easier.
Now I have no option
but to get rid of
a dark-skinned wife like you.
Don't worry.
Siddhi's dead.
She is not coming back.
Maya is so wise.
She fears no one.
But she never gets angry.
Siddhi is her sister so true.
I can't live without you.
Well done, Vinayak.
Oh, come on.
At least you don't call me Vinayak.
The mask maker is brilliant.
So was your acting.
The moment you changed
your voice and mannerisms,
the circumstances changed too.
Now Vinayak has killed Siddhi
in the eyes of the world.
So no one's going
to find out about our plan.
Did Siddhi recognise me?
Are you sure she thought I was Vinayak?
Let alone Siddhi.
No one can recognise you in this mask
that you are Tanmay and not Vinayak.
Your idea of the mask was quite something.
You are quite smart
and also possessive about your plan.
You got me out of jail
so that you can use me
to do these things.
Use?
This word runs the show.
You have been of some use to me
and I have been of use to you.
Right.
By the way, what's the plan now?
Have some patience.
I am yet to weave my magic.
Just sit back and enjoy.
Fine. Send me your location.
I am coming.
'The person I am going to send'
'will go meet Siddhi and not Vinayak.'
Your plan was amazing, Maya.
You managed to convince Vinayak
that Siddhi is jealous of him.
And then me too.
Siddhi.
Vinayak.
Vinayak! Vinayak!
- Vinayak, Siddhi...
- Maya.
Tell me. What happened to Siddhi?
Siddhi, she... She...
Siddhi committed suicide.
Siddhi jumped off the cliff.
And I couldn't even save her.
She couldn't have children.
So she...
Vinayak...
No, this can't be. Siddhi cannot leave me.
This can't be.
Siddhi...
Siddhi, please!
No. No, Siddhi.
You can't leave me.
'Siddhi is dead, Vinayak.'
'Now no one can stop me
from making you mine.'
'I will go down in history
as the most treacherous sister.'
'But as they say.
Everything is fair in love and war.'