English Subtitles : Doylebrotus26
Tell me son, why is your head down?
You used to laugh a lot, why are you silent now?
People front of our doors with boards,
I know very well who they are and their motives.
Among them, some are here to shine silver,
Some want to grab you and pull you down,
Some are framewhores,
Some wants the spotlight by saying your name,
Tough times always come to strong men,
Don't fall back, the world will enjoy it,
And the path you are walking on,
You'll get high rated defamation.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
Lots of people grouped together to save our culture,
Literally everybody gets up and gives lectures,
And i feel like even god has surrendered,
When i read newspapers in the morning.
Stay quite son, don't reveal the secrets,
Leader's here deserve to be shot,
And people who name their kids John and Steve,
Are trying to become saviours of our mother language.
These aren't lies, they are the facts of here.
Robbers are disguised as social workers,
And those that loot people in the attire of truth,
They will all be punished soon.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
People throw rocks at trees filled with fruits,
Within minutes they reach the mother's womb.
Who's dog, who's a pimp, and who's evil,
Here these certificates are given on facebook.
Politicians give bribes to get votes from them,
They take their votes and the voters are slapped.
Don't know where their conscience is then,
They don't speak, they are shameless.
People applaud when they see you fall,
They keep long beards[Religious Tradition] and spew hatred,
And what is the difference in your mother and his,
[People using mothers to insult]
They will learn this a bit late.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
You are here because of your dedication,
They aren't here taking pictures because of your face.
How much someone here believe's in god,
People judge it based off of their actions.
You may have bent, but you never blow down.
You have a turban on your head, you are not bald.
Ask one thing from these contractors of religion,
Religion is ours, not just yours alone.
Get rid of dirty politics from your heart,
At least leave people alone to go to the temple.
You won't find any kids with long hair [Religious tradition]
Other wise you will soon see those days.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
Illitrate people run today's media,
They tell the same lie over and over again,
They sit with women and gossip,
And call the show "Chajj da Vichar" "Informative Discussion"
All day and night they look for drama,
Without reason they quarrel with you,
They condemn you 24 hours a day,
Yet they know all of your songs by heart.
Even though the crowd is hard on you,
They yell at you without reason,
Remember one thing my son,
Your father is very proud of you.
You've been suppressed, the world is in mistaken
Get up, my wrestler son moosewala,
If you continue speaking the truth in your songs,
You will find an educated new generation.
Everyday controversy will be created,
With the excuse of religion you'll get a debate,
If you speak the truth you'll get 295
[Criminal code 295 : intent to insult religion]
And if you are successful then you'll get hate.
English Subtitles : Doylebrotus26