Hello, friends.
If you remember, in 2017,
the video of Paytm's CEO and founder
Vijay Shekhar Sharma went viral.
You could see the excitement,
as he was celebrating Paytm's success.
He famously said,
"Those who are not with us, will cry."
But sadly, 7 years later,
the situation has completely changed.
Those who are with Paytm are crying.
Over the last few days, we saw
a horrific crash of this company.
On 30th January, the stock price of this company was at ₹760.
Today, it has fallen below ₹380.
What is the reason behind this?
Let's understand the rise and downfall of Paytm
in this video.
Paytm began its journey in 2010.
But initially, it was just a mobile recharging platform.
An app through which you could
recharge your phone and pay landline bills.
The company gradually added more features to its app.
It was only in January 2014 that
Paytm Wallet was launched.
With this, you could pay online using Paytm.
By 2015, it was possible to pay for metro
recharges, electricity, gas, and water bills.
But the real jump in the company's popularity
was seen only after 8th November 2016.
That day when demonetisation happened.
"₹500 and ₹1,000 currency notes
will no longer be legal tender
from midnight tonight."
The very next day after demonetisation,
the frontpage ads in many newspapers
across the country looked like this.
"Paytm congratulates Honourable
Prime Minister Shri Narendra Modi
on taking the boldest decision
in the financial history of independent India.
Now, no ATMs, use Paytm."
The first controversy about Paytm was raised here.
People questioned whether
Paytm has any link with the government.
Using the Prime Minister's face in this way
while advertising their platform.
And the decision of demonetisation,
which was said to be secretive,
was declared on 8th November at 8pm.
So how did it happen that the very next day,
in the morning newspaper on 9th November,
this was the front page ad?
Did this company already know that
demonetisation was going to happen?
Whatever happened, one thing was clear.
Paytm benefited a lot from this decision.
According to Euro Money's report, before demonetisation,
Paytm had 125 million customers.
But only after 3 months of the demonetisation,
Paytm's had approx 185 million customers.
The CEO of this company, Vijay Shekhar Sharma,
did not miss the opportunity to capitalise on this opportunity.
Paytm hired more than 10,000 agents
to distribute their QR codes
to local shops and vendors.
Shopkeepers were encouraged in every city
to use Paytm.
The company was growing tremendously.
But around this time,
there were 2-3 other controversies.
One was Paytm's Chinese link.
In 2015, a Chinese company named Alibaba
invested $680 million in Paytm
and 40% stake in Paytm company
went to this Chinese company.
Alibaba's founder is Jack Ma
and Vijay had said that he was his hero.
He had given a statement to the Financial Times newspaper.
"I became totally interested in China,
Alibaba, and Jack - all three things."
You must be aware of the recent
relations between India and China.
China is repeatedly intruding on the Indian border.
In 2017, the Doklam border standoff took place.
Many people had criticised Paytm for this.
Claiming that the company pretends to be a patriot
when they want to sell something.
But they have been taking Chinese funding secretly.
Because of this criticism,
the Chinese stake in the company was reduced
in 2023, Vijay transferred about 10% stake back to himself,
and the Chinese stake in the company
is around 13.5% as of now.
In May 2018, the next controversy arose regarding Paytm
when the investigative news agency CobraPost
conducted an undercover operation.
Their undercover reporter
went to meet the Vice President of Paytm,
Ajay Shekhar Sharma,
Vijay Shekhar Sharma's brother.
When he was asked
if he would spread the propaganda
of a political party through the app,
he happily accepted.
"There will be videos of Guruji too,
there are other things as well,
I give those to you later..."
"We'll take care of all of that
if RSS tells us to.
Because loyalty to RSS runs in our blood."
He went on to say that
when the government asked them
for the data of some Paytm users in J&K,
during the stone peltings,
they happily gave the data to the government.
"When our operations were shut down in J&K
-due to the stones...
-The stone peltings, yes.
the PMO called us personally
asking us to hand over data to them,
of the Paytm users."
I made a video on this 6 years ago,
if you remember,
if you are a veteran viewer of my channel.
But nothing significant happened with these controversies.
The company kept growing very fast.
Generally speaking,
there are many companies who
don't care about your data.
They sell your data to other companies.
Especially online, it happens a lot.
Your data is used to create a digital profile
so that you can be shown online targeted ads.
A good way to avoid this is to use VPN.
A VPN encrypts your internet traffic.
In my opinion, one of the best VPN apps
is NordVPN,
which is also the sponsor of this video.
One of the advantages of using NordVPN is that
you can use it for content streaming.
If a specific show, movie or video
is banned in your location,
you can bypass these restrictions
by setting your location somewhere else through VPN.
Recently, due to increasing customer demand,
NordVPN has added a server in India.
This is a virtual location server with Indian IP.
And when you browse the internet with a VPN,
your data is secure.
You can't be tracked online by other companies.
If you are interested, check out NordVPN.com/Dhruv
You will get a huge discount.
Plus, you will get 4 months free
if you use this link to subscribe to NordVPN.
It's a risk-free offer
they give a 30-day money-back guarantee.
So, NordVPN.com/Dhruv
You can find this link in the description below.
Now, let's get back to the topic.
In 2017, Paytm launched Paytm Payments Bank.
They started offering banking services.
Payments Bank is like a bank to some extent.
You can create a bank account,
deposit money, and get a debit card.
But compared to a normal commercial bank,
there are some important differences.
Payments banks focus mostly on digital services.
There are very few
physical branches of payments banks.
And according to RBI's Rules,
payments banks cannot offer
credit card and loan services.
Normal commercial banks
like HDFC, SBI, ICICI,
do not have any deposit limit.
You can deposit as much as you want in those banks.
But RBI has prescribed a limit for payments banks.
You cannot deposit more than ₹200,000 in these banks.
I am telling you all this in detail because
the current state of Paytm
is largely caused by Paytm's Payments Bank.
RBI, the Reserve Bank of India,
is the central bank of the country.
It decides the monetary policy of the country
and also works to print money.
All the banks and financial institutions in the country
have to follow the rules and
guidelines prescribed by the RBI.
So on 31st January 2024,
the Paytm crash
happened because the RBI
imposed operational restrictions
on Paytm's Payments Bank.
RBI said that Paytm's Payments Bank
kept violating our rules repeatedly.
There was 'persistent non-compliance' by them.
And that's why RBI put restrictions on the bank.
After 29th February 2024,
Paytm's Payments Bank can't accept any new deposits.
There can't be money top-ups in customer accounts.
New customers can't be on-boarded.
And RBI said that all the nodal accounts
with this Paytm Payments Bank
should be closed by 15th March 2024.
Nodal accounts are those accounts
which are used by e-commerce and online services businesses.
And as far as Paytm Wallet is concerned,
you can use your existing balance
but after 29th February,
you can't deposit any more money in it.
So, obviously, this is a major decision by the RBI.
And such decisions are not taken in a jiffy.
It's not like RBI randomly decided one day
to take action on Paytm
and implemented these decisions.
In fact, there is a very long history behind this.
The truth is that Paytm was time and again
warned by the RBI for years,
but it still didn't rectify its actions.
In November 2017,
Paytm's Payments Bank was launched
and in June 2018,
RBI issued the first warning.
An audit found that Paytm
was not following the anti-money
laundering regulations properly.
And the identity of the customers
who made their accounts with their bank
was not being verified properly by Paytm.
The KYC, or Know Your Customer compliance
wasn't adhered to by Paytm.
So RBI told Paytm to stop onboarding new customers
until it fixes all these issues.
Paytm took some action regarding this warning
because in January 2019,
RBI allowed Paytm to resume onboarding customers.
The restrictions were removed.
But after 2.5 years, in October 2021,
came the next big shock.
A fine of ₹10 million was imposed on Paytm.
Because while filling in their licence application,
they submitted incorrect information and documents.
The issues that RBI had flagged before
customers not being verified properly,
regulations are not being followed properly,
the same issues were seen again.
Once again, customer onboarding had to be stopped.
In October 2023, another huge fine was imposed on Paytm
this time, it amounted to ₹50 million.
RBI hoped that after 2 warnings and 2 fines,
Paytm would meet the regulatory requirements
and start verifying its customers properly.
But even after all this,
Paytm did not take these seriously.
And for this reason, on 31st January 2024,
RBI had to take concrete steps.
Since Paytm could not follow
the rules and regulations properly,
RBI had to stop its operations.
RBI's findings were very shocking.
According to CNBC,
Paytm allowed hundreds of thousands of
customers to open bank accounts with them
without proper KYC documentation.
There were thousands of cases where
thousands of customers
had opened multiple accounts
using the same PAN card.
In some accounts, transactions were worth
millions of rupees.
Here, the risk of potential money laundering was evident.
It is possible that money laundering
was taking place through Paytm.
Outlook reported that according to an analyst,
Paytm had around 350 million wallets.
Of which around 310 million wallets are inactive,
no one is using these.
And in the remaining 40 million wallets,
most of them have no balance or very little balance.
Because of this, they can be used like mule accounts.
A Mule account is an account
that is used for illegal activities,
like money laundering.
After this, there are concerns about data privacy too.
RBI said that Paytm's parent company,
One97 Communications Ltd,
there is no operational segregation
between it and Paytm Payments Bank.
There was cash flow between the two,
which was not disclosed in the financial statements.
So many rules and regulations were ignored.
Is the arrogance of their CEO Vijay Shekhar Sharma
responsible for this to some extent?
He gave many interviews to media channels
this arrogance was seen in his words in those interviews.
"If you fundamentally believe
that Paytm is #3 payment player,
that is where the beginning of the problem is
in understanding."
"I'm surprised that people don't know this
in this country, but
we make profit, so it is."
"Somebody who has not met us
and has an opinion on us
is not my opinion
to keep an opinion on that."
After RBI's announcement on 31st January,
a commotion broke out.
People started taking out
the money they had invested in Paytm.
So, Paytm's stock crashed very fast.
To calm people down,
Paytm posted on its social media handles that
there was nothing wrong.
On 2nd February, Vijay Shekhar Sharma tweeted this.
"To every Paytmer,
Your favourite app is working,
will keep working beyond 29th February as usual...
For every challenge, there is a solution
and we are sincerely committed to serve our nation
in full compliance.
India will keep winning global accolades
in payment innovation and
inclusion in financial services."
As you can see, once again,
patriotism was used as a shield here.
'Don't see us as a company,
see us as patriots serving the nation.'
Using India as the shield
Paytm tried to hide behind it.
This reminds me of a quote.
"Patriotism is the last refuge of a scoundrel."
You must have heard this quote.
In my opinion, we should be wary of such companies
which rely too heavily on nationalism.
A few years ago, there was a phone Freedom 251.
They printed India's national flag on the back of the phone.
It was sold as the 'world's cheapest phone'
but it turned out to be a big scam.
If a company's products and services
have intrinsic value,
they sell it by promoting those values.
But if they don't have much to say
about their products or services,
then patriotism is used as a selling point.
Urging you to buy their product
just because they are Indian.
Because they are an Indian company,
they use it as the only reason
why you should buy their product.
Anyways, if we come back to Paytm,
the question is, what will happen next?
Internally, the employees of the company
are facing a lot of uncertainty.
They are not getting much clarity from the leadership
about what will happen next.
Economic Times reported that
an executive of the company told them that
their business model might change.
Now, instead of being a bank,
they might try to become a third-party payments app.
So they will have to change
some things on the back end.
And they will have to make the change in a limited time.
If you look at Paytm's annual report,
to check how much has it earned each year,
you will see that it has always been
a loss-making company since
its shares were listed on the stock market.
Look at this chart,
in FY 2021, the company incurred a loss of ₹16 billion.
In FY 2022, a loss of ₹15 billion.
In FY 2023, a loss of ₹1.7 billion.
The good news was that year after year
the company's losses were decreasing.
So, it could have been expected that next year,
that is, this year, in FY 2024,
the company would earn its first profit.
But now, after everything that has happened,
it seems difficult.
The company expects that this year,
the company's loss could increase by ₹3 billion to ₹5 billion.
Paytm has revealed this to the public,
saying that they will now comply
with the guidelines issued by RBI.
But after this announcement,
the company's stock price fell further.
"What is the path to profitability Vijay?
What is... by when will Paytm make money?"
"Make more money?
By making more money.
By making more money!"
Vijay Shekhar Sharma will have to come up
with better answers to these questions
if he wants to convince people.
Actually, convincing people
will be the biggest challenge for Paytm.
An average person is very picky about choosing a company.
And public's trust plays an important role here.
Once people choose their toothpaste,
they decide that they will use
that company's toothpaste forever.
They don't change their mind easily.
Here, they will be more cautious as this
involves their money and banking abilities.
Bringing customers back
won't be easy for Paytm.
But convincing customers will come later.
First, Paytm will have to convince RBI.
That won't be an easy task.
But there is light at the end of the tunnel,
a way to get out of this can be
to have another company
buy Paytm's wallet business.
A Business Standard report suggests that
HDFC Bank and Jio Financial Services
might just do this.
But Jio has denied this speculation
saying that they have no intention of doing so.
And anyway, before executing such a sale,
they'd need RBI's approval.
If you liked this video,
I have done similar case studies on other companies
like this one on Amul.
What is the secret behind
the success of companies like Amul?
You can click here to find out.
Thank you very much!