this is a level one trick shot and this
is a level 50 trick shot and this is a
level 100 trick shot there's no way I
can do that well these are the craziest
trick shots on the internet starting
with level one legendary bottle flip
this is gonna be the most insane bottle
flip on the internet let's see how it
goes he's building up he's wearing all
white he's got white socks
he did it right when the beat dropped
that was level one for sure
next this is level five he's gonna throw
the Mentos into the coke
and the Chug and the Chug yo walked by
faith do you think Jesus is up there
being like I got you bro I mean second
try level 10.
what how did they think they timed that
perfectly that was incredible he threw
the ball he threw the paper the ball hit
the scissors the scissors cut the paper
Target sign plunger Target like the
place or Target oh my goodness oh my God
he made a Target into the target this is
a perfect plunger Bullseye oh that is a
bullseye oh my God there's so many meta
things in here level 17 skimboarding to
the alley-oop all right we're going down
the sand how do they build this oh my
God this is so early 2000s
he didn't dunk it but he made it just
dudes being Bros right dude's making
baskets what a great shot level 17 was
insane no way level 20 is as crazy as
that toilet paper ping pong trick shot
what does that even mean are you spun
the roll he's got the ball in his mouth
that he's doing a handstand oh my gosh
how did he think of all these variables
or you got to be a gymnast and a sniper
hey dude I don't think I could do that
no level 23. over the two-story house
shot we can't even see the rim can't
even see the rim oh my God
whoa It's a football cross map football
I wonder how many tries you know
honestly the toilet paper was better
than that one I could do that
let's see if level 25 can beat level 17.
basketball shot on a moving hoop Lefty
that wasn't I mean that's very good
timing I could
I could level 30 cup pyramid trick shots
this guy's potential look at that spin
he knows nice he has to do it in one
take no edits no Cuts level 30 is not
really anything look at that oh one more
[Music]
and the toilet bowl swish dude I bet
he's relieved that took him forever to
do Humanity has been made better because
of that video level 32 Lighthouse to
ship basketball shot I'm noticing a lot
of basketball shots it's kind of not
good for you watch because you're good
at it
did you do that could I do that with
enough tries yes I don't think they had
a lot of tries we've done a lot of
things with boats and boats are
notorious for having the skedaddle very
quick that's the best basketball shot so
far level 35 basketball shot let's go
[Music]
boring off the easy off the side double
Bank
this video is filmed on a toaster I was
gonna say this is like 2007 cool how
much crazier can these get I guess we'll
just have to keep watching to find out
level 37 ping pong Domino's trick shot
thank you
yeah like like how did you think of this
no way like this is equally as cool as
the shot like yeah the bar is raised
this is the best one I've seen so far
this is incredible level 40 roller
coaster trick shot
they're just literally on a roller
coaster and they shot the ball oh it's
the Harlem globet I loved it I just
don't understand how there's any way you
could be a guy on a roller coaster
making a basketball shot watch this
level 43. all right we got some kid from
the stands doing a oh my god oh he
didn't mean to do another one and that
hurt
[Applause]
look at his legs so 90 degrees he's a
scorpion he was on top of the world when
he landed because of adrenaline and 10
minutes later he had the worst head and
neck hate level 44.
kick oh he makes that one and he turns
around no looks the other one that was
crazy he put two soccer balls into one
trash can you mean footballs it's soccer
The Whole World's Gonna say it's
football the mobile app top 11 sponsored
this video and they call it soccer so
can't argue with that hey top 11 allows
you to make and manage your own soccer
team by picking your dream players to
even building your own custom Stadium
it's like a soccer team in your pocket
the game has been played by over 260
million players worldwide 5.5 million
reviews and has won multiple Awards so
you can literally play with any of your
friends all around the world to win
championships this game is available on
the app store Google Hawaii Microsoft
store and any web browser wait it's
available in Hawaii it's worldwide like
Pitbull download top 11 now to get your
custom in-game Beast reacts gear like
this premium Jersey and this awesome
emblem sign up today using the link in
the description click it level 45
two arrows shoots one up in the air gets
another one ready boom shoots the plate
through the thing catches the arrow in
his quiver that's how you do it what if
he didn't catch that whoa he's Green
Arrow well no way the next one's gonna
be even crazier than that see level 47
helicopter hockey trick shot what no way
there's a go on the helicopter
and he sinks it up
the thing about a lot of these the
coolest part about them is how they came
up with the trick themselves who would
have thought of that someone with a
helicopter someone with a helicopter
indeed level 50 frisbee accuracy shot a
full-length frisbee shot there's a trash
can lid wow okay
here
oh and he makes it uh I gotta say
helicopter's cooler I agree the
difficulty of the last one was harder I
feel like I could do that the helicopter
one I could not level 55. I'm going to
attempt a world record of scoring a goal
from the highest height ever in history
oh my goodness that's pretty high up
Chandler I'm afraid of heist this would
destroy me I could not do this I
couldn't even stand near that edge to do
that striking
kicks It Off
oh he did it go
I don't know how it's going to get
better from here that was amazing it's
level 60. behind the back crossbow shot
no weight is using a mirror that's a
phone as a mirror oh no way he hits that
balloon
[Music]
hey that was impressive that beats the
helicopter in my opinion oh he missed
one he missed the first shot you saw
that yeah we see that on a little arrow
in the back yeah okay level 69 Jenga
piece wait a minute
[Music]
I don't think I could do that
across the water yeah I play golf I
might could have thrown it yeah level 75
basketball backflip trick shot
what oh that was pretty sick you need to
be in the Olympics for gymnast what are
you doing that was insane that was
better than the last one 100 yeah
there's no way I could do that back
handspring back flip wow that was crazy
all right this next one is a level 80
world record basketball shot where the
heck are they we actually don't know
what he's behind the back behind the
back oh bro look at the backspin what
the heck oh wow get in get it oh
what up
that was insane look at that baby the
baby's like oh my God baby's scared oh
my God what happened level 85 drift King
yeah I love this guy yeah
open it
oh
they opened it it was a baby bottle I
love that guy I'm not gonna lie I'm
biased that was amazing until this one
level 90. I shot a Tic Tac in the air
dang you checked the number one spot sir
oh that was crazy you know how accurate
you have to be about the accuracy of a
Tic Tac this one is going to be insane
high is slam dunk oh bro these people
are crazy they're at an airplane they're
about to jump out they were in an
airplane now they're falling out of an
airplane this guy's crazy you can't even
see the basketball goal what do you mean
would you do this no you're telling me
you not falling out of the sky you have
to land perfectly
that's the craziest dog I've ever seen
what you don't think about is if like he
had to like misjudge that even about an
inch they would have smacked their head
into it that takes Precision yeah timing
and you gotta know how to dunk level 95
served good job now it's time level 100
here's what you've been waiting for you
clicked on the video for this level 100
helicopter basketball shot
is an eye
oh oh my God how did these absolute Lads
get access to this helicopter who knows
who cares if you think you can do those
subscribe I'm not