Good morning! We're... here at our breakfast spot!
Yeah...check it out
There's Susie, after a bout of mustard hit (Susie finds mustard oil too pungent in food)...
She is a little under the weather.
So...as you can see, she is having oats.
And here is my breakfast as usual, with the speciality of a duck egg...
...that comes from ducks that swim around in that pond.
Come! ...come, come!
...a 450 year old Vaishnavite monastery, before heading out of Majuli.
Check out our other vlogs on Majuli, if you haven’t already!
There's Susie coming down... with the load...ha...ha
As is customary, we had to miss at least one correct turn off.
Dokhinpat Satra was established in the late 1500s, during the Ahom Kings of Assam.
You live here?
Aah...yes.
How many years?
Very nice place.
Yes.
Very big place!
Ya, big place.
This is where you stay?...These are rooms?
Do you grow some food here?
What?
Vegetables...growing vegetables?
Oh...yes, yes. Somewhat.
Okay...okay :)
Around there they grow some vegetables.
This is the man you met?
Yes.
Meeting Sri Sri Ramananda Devgoshwami, the Xotradhikar few years back, was a lesson in humility.
From Calcutta...folding system.
Hmm...I didn't think the house itself was made in Calcutta.
I was looking for what was made (in Calcutta) around the house! :)
This is where they stay.
Okay!
Come, come...come, come!
...between humans and animal.
Beautiful, ha? ...wow!
Look at that...hmm.
This is the...this is called 'Gagori' (Jug for storing liquids).
Such a pretty face!
Ya, they must get out and about.
Hello beautiful...ooh what a beauty, what a beauty.
She likes the pats. :)
Cute bunnies.
Hi guys...look at you, how cute you are!
Say something, Mr. Goosie.
If you go near, he'll threaten you. :)
Talk to us...'tak, tak' (clicking of tongue)...hmm!
...to be part of a unique travel experience!