Hello. Dial 100.
Hello. He will kill her, sir.
Hello. Hello, madam
He forcefully entered our house.
Forcefully? Hello.
I don't know what he
has done to our daughter.
Madam, where are you speaking from?
-Please save my daughter.
-Hello?
He is coming this way.
-Madam, don't be scared.
-He will kill her, sir.
Sorry. I wanted to call my daughter.
But the battery of my phone conked off.
It's only a matter of 15 minutes.
I will leave as soon
as my phone is charged.
Take a seat.
I'll get the charger.
Kabir, I need that man out of my house.
Its only for 15 minutes.
I think you should leave now.
I don't think you understood.
I am not leaving.
Janvi, stop your dad.
What is he doing?
Dad, he is not going anywhere.
Janvi, out of my way.
Dad, he is going to stay here.
He will stay right here!
Janvi, eat the tea leaves.
No.
Slap yourself.
Harder.
Once more.
What have you done to my daughter?
What have you done to her?
Hypnosis.
Your daughter is now my puppet.
Kabir, do something.
And I am her god.
What rubbish.
Janvi, slap your father hard.
I must take your daughter away
with your blessings.
I won't let him take her.
Will you set my daughter free or not?
Tell me.
Do you know who you are facing?
Who am I?
Sister.
What am I capable of?
Janvi, if anyone comes
close stab him, okay.
Thanks.