This boy
this truck
this girl
this car
Look at these four words
With all these nouns
we used only one demonstrative adjective
that is 'this'
If you look at the first two words,
I'm sure you know their French equivalents
because we've already learned them.
but what about 'this girl' and 'this car'?
No......
Here, 'ce' won't do
but what will?
cette
So, tell me, what should we say here?
So now, can you tell me,
I used 'ce' with the first two words
And I used 'cette' with the last two words
Whay?
I'll tell you why
The word 'fille' is a feminine noun
That's why I used 'cette' there
The next word is 'voiture' (car)
'Car' is also a feminine noun in French
and 'voiture' is the French word for 'car'
So I used 'cette' with 'car'
I already told you that 'voiture' is a feminine  noun
and hence 'cette' with this nou
Let's try some more examples...
If 'this girl' is 'cette fille',
then what about 'that girl'?
In order to say 'that',
there is no special word in French.
So, there also you can use 'ce/cette'
Okay' let's do one thing.
Let's make some more sentences
and practice further with them.
We'll meet again in the next video
until then,  bye
ma'm, wait ma'm
Oh, what happened?
We need  more sentences ma'm
Oh, you're saying you need more sentences?
Do I Need to say this? that...
go to the description box and practice
Bye!
Don't forget to visit
www.novafrenchcampus.com