maybe we should just settle this
one-on-one
but where
oh i know
how about up there
oh you must pardon me
i forgot you have no way of making it up
to that divine beast on your own
[Music]
actually scratch that one for now link
canonically cannot jump upwards
infinitely let's not be silly here
yet you have no way of making it up to
that divine balloons
link fueled by rivali's reverse
psychology scoured the land sending the
octorocks of hyrule to near extinction
for their balloons wielding a korok leaf
and mounting a trusty wooden box he set
sail
[Music]
with patience and precision link's
dangerous excursion upwards leads him
straight to rivali on vonnetto
to accept his one-on-one challenge and
then kick his ass hypothetically
unfortunately in my demonstrations
vomitto doesn't come with collision
link did not have the paraglider back
then but it wouldn't be a stretch to say
he could make one
and with that
chaining together a series of spicy
peppers in order to create an updraft
even taller than rivale's gale
can't reach high enough this gets left
out as an honorable mention
okay this method requires the sheikah
slate which was in the possession of
zelda 100 years ago
but hypothetically speaking let's say
link was
fueled by reverse psychology
this is the sheikah slate eh
[Music]
he steals it enters oman aw shrine as
the sword's chosen one gets magnesis and
constructs his own flying machine out of
two mine carts to go kick rivali's ass
hypothetically
stealing the sheikah slate and exploring
ancient chica structures for power is
the norm now do you want to prove your
volley right no you have stasis now a
paraglider you constructed yourself and
a pretty metal box you're ready to hit
yourself really hard with to prove a
point
get a fairy you'll be fine climb to
hebrew peak build up enough kinetic
energy to kill a henox hit yourself with
it and glide over to valmeado to kick
rivalli's ass
[Music]
how did link get a wooden box on top of
hebra peak
i don't know he built it with all of his
wood or something
with similar disregard for one's own
body a well-placed bomb with this light
wooden box can send link far and fast
enough to reach valmeado and kick
rivalli's butt
do you need a butthole to have a butt
i don't know the full anatomy of a rito
but if we assume they're like other
birds he has a cloaca
but does that meet the specifications of
a button
[Music]
then link kicks him in the cloaca
that doesn't have the same ring to it
sometimes there's just a single moment
the straw that breaks the camel's back
the burning rage in your soul unlocks
your potential
to do
the impossible
[Music]
we're disregarding the laws of physics
now
rocks no more than you can fathom
study them empathize with them shift
your values to theirs
and with new understanding
you may become untethered to the earth
[Music]
and we're back it's the moon jump glitch
i can't explain this one immersively you
mount a horse you mount a different
horse and then everything is wacky
[Music]
link makes it to varmetto
rivali is in disbelief this isn't
possible
in a moment where his insecurity should
have been reinforced
the act is dropped
and he confesses his feelings for link
after all these years i simply must
admit the truth
they embrace
forever sealing the darkness of their
bitter history into the past
the true darkness
that which holds true love from
flourishing
ride to the highest peak of hebrew
mountains
create a time split and instruct your
split self to ride back to rito staple
position their steed on a slope facing
away from the divine beast
and remount to tether your alternate
existence back together
[Music]
reforming the split timeline generates
enough force onto link to send him
flying at mach speed towards vametto
[Music]
to look at your world
its possibilities
its limitations and master them
is
remarkable
to look beyond your world your time
and seek a new level of possibility
that is what you must do
enter a shrine with a device known as an
apparatus
traverse to an alternate timeline as you
interact with it
do this twice
the power of the apparatus travels with
you
and bonds you to the very earth you
touch
head to the death mountain of this
timeline
and bond yourself to its molten lava
becoming one with fire
[Music]
head to the monster camp west of rito
village
[Music]
with precisely 550 bomb arrows stashed
for use
right when va meadow's flight path fully
crosses over the entrance of passer hill
leap off the cliff edge and grab hold of
your bomb arrows one by one
[Music]
hey
is
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
given that your calculations and
execution were precise your 550th bomb
arrow will safely land you on top of von
meadow from the second loop of its
flight path
where you can finally meet revolve
[Music]
and then link kicks his cloaca
[Applause]
thank you to all my patrons over on
patreon
you people are wonderful
e says nice this is awesome
no e you're awesome
jonathan shamus says why advise people
on proving the odds are you planning to
just purposely not read those comments
now this is a good question
toavah says bionicle
thanks for watching bye
you'll have a precise speed on ganon
from this vantage point
and when the time is right
give him everything you've got
now we wait for that perfect moment
meadow we've been artfully patient for
the last 100 years
i doubt you'll suffer a feather over a
few more moments
you