A battle is raging outside India
and soon it will be
fought in India.
You have to fight for your freedom,
nobody gives it to you.
We'll have to shed blood for
this freedom struggle.
Our blood.
The cost of our freedom
will be our blood.
Every story has a beginning and an end.
If you are born,
your death is inevitable.
Except few stories
which don't conclude at all.
The number of people who died...
is still yet to be confirmed.
It's been confirmed that
Subhash Chandra Bose...
Chief of the Indian National Army
and also a freedom fighter
has died in the plane crash.
It is a sad day for Japan also
because they've also lost a general
in the crash.
We'll be back with more information
on the crash as soon as we get it.
This story is about
Subhash Chandra Bose
whose death
gave birth to countless stories.
It's a telegram.
Bibhavati.
Gandhiji says we shouldn't perform
a post-death ritual for Netaji.
Subhash.
Is Subhash alive?
[Title Montage]
If Netaji is alive,
why doesn't he come out?
Who would want to see
his own funeral?
Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose's
childhood friend,
Hemant Sarkar.
He has only one dream.
To kick the British
and their government out of India.
So that people like you and me
can breathe in free India.
Do you think it's the first time
that Subhash has disappeared?
Karna accepted Parshuram as his guru
but, Parshuram didn't know that Karna
was a kshatriya, not a Brahmin.
I curse you.
-Sire...
-During the war,
you won't be able to use your knowledge.
-My dear nephew...
-Yes, uncle.
It's our only chance
to finish off the Pandavas.
Uncle, your wish shall come true.
Duryodhan!
Grandsire!
You bunked school to watch a play.
God, I've been looking for you
since morning.
Now answer me.
Father, I think...
-I shouldn't go to school.
-Why not?
From tomorrow, you'll go to school
and come back home straight.
You won't step out of the house
without my permission.
Understood?
You can leave.
Subhash.
Eat something before you sleep.
All right.
Boys of his age
crave for sweets.
They want to see fairs.
But...
what's with Subhash?
Subhash, why did we run away from home?
Because we are free now.
And what will we do with this freedom?
We'll do whatever we want!
What if we make mistakes?
Only humans are fortunate enough
to make mistakes.
Look at those cattle,
do they make any mistakes?
No, right?
It's up to you. Do you want to
live like humans
or meander like cattle?
Come on.
"This is my destiny."
"To be free! Be free!"
[Mr.Janki] Rein in him now or cry later.
Well, I'm crying now.
[Rahman] Subhash came back home after seven months.
Back then, Subhash was only 14
and yet he stayed hidden
from his parents for seven months.
Can't a 48-year-old man stay hidden
from the British government?
Bose is alive and...
he'll be back soon.
There's neither a dead body nor a photo.
Why should we believe that Netaji
died in the plane crash?
[Speaker] Netaji has tricked the British government.
[Speaker] He's just biding his time
to strike the British Raj
[Speaker] and blow it to smithereens.
Long live the revolution!
[Speaker] Free India!
[Stanley] 25th August, 1945.
The world thinks that Bose is dead.
Because Bose wants the world
to think that he's dead.
He's alive.
And we should be worried.
He's dead, Stanley!
Everyone says he's dead.
You can get over this now!
There's a rumour that says
he faked his own death!
What if it's true?
We have guests here
and they are waiting for you.
What if it's an error in judgement
on my part again?
You can let go of all this.
Bose is dead!
Give your obsession a decent burial!
I'll be there in five minutes.
You can cage me, but you cannot
suppress my voice!
Mr. Bose is alive
and he will be back.
No food or water for him today.
Long live Mr. Bose!
No matter what rumours they spread,
the whole country knows the truth.
Netaji is alive.
Netaji has contributed greatly
to the Indian freedom struggle
and even our children know that.
Netaji's demise has sent
shockwaves throughout India.
Netaji is immortal.
One has to die first
to become immortal.
Netaji is alive.
How do you know that?
Just like you know.
Dear...
[Man] God makes everything in pairs.
Like man and woman,
cigarettes and matchsticks!
There's another fellow
who is as crazy as you are.
Even he believes that Netaji is alive.
[Darbari Lal] I say, the British are playing us.
Netaji is alive and will be back soon.
Stop harping about Netaji!
When will he be back?
What a wretched man!
He only talks about one thing.
-Look here.
-Yes.
I fought with him in Burma.
I know Netaji is alive.
But where is he?
-Have you met him after Burma?
-No.
So how do you know he's alive?
Because I know there was no plane crash.
You say there was no plane crash,
but people are saying it happened.
There was no plane crash!
Because no plane flew that day.
-I see, the plane didn't take off.
-Yes.
Where did you find this moron?
Ram Singh.
Open the door.
For a few more days,
I mingled with the prisoners
and tried to find out
if Bose was alive or dead.
But I couldn't find out anything.
Perhaps, nobody wanted to
tell me anything.
Sir, I'm telling you
it's all in your mind.
Were you really convincing
with the prisoners?
If they were hiding something,
would they have shared it with you?
Everyone spoke their heart out.
I know about their kids, their wives,
about their families...
They even shared intimate details
about their wives.
But they know nothing about Mr. Bose.
Why do you think Mr. Bose is still alive?
Because I know it.
It has been 27 years
but Stanley continues to be
obsessed with Subhash Chandra Bose.
I still remember 1918
when I confronted Mr. Bose
for the first time
in Presidency College.
What is that?
Are you cheating?
No, sir. That's Gayatri mantra.
Oh, yes.
We try and we try and we try
to rid you of your superstitions.
But we fail, every single time.
Sir, please don't do that.
You'll are beastly people
with a beastly religion.
And I shall have none of this
frigging nonsense in my classroom!
If any of you
is carrying a totem
which you mistakenly believe
would call upon some deity in the sky
to swoop down
and assist you in passing my examination.
I assure you, it'll not.
Take your totem and place it in this box.
Now!
Hurry up!
Please understand
there's no real power...
attached to any of these objects.
Except that which you,
yourself give it.
Sir...
Yes?
I find your idea quite liberating.
Nice.
So, if I don't attach any power to your
position as a professor or teacher...
then I'm free to do something
which I wanted to do
since the day I joined your class?
What is that?
"It's difficult to understand Subhash."
"Difficult to understand."
"Weapons is the only answer."
"Conversations don't bring about change!"
"The enemy intimidates with torture."
"But carefree, we shout Long Live India!"
"Bose!"
"Fought for freedom, fought injustice!
He looked the British in the eye."
"Bose!"
"A mysterious man, not easily nabbed!
A genius, when it comes to results."
"Bose!"
"Killed in a plane crash, says history
but his death remains a mystery!"
"Bose!"
"His death remains a mystery."
"The call for freedom
from millions of voices."
"Look straight into
the eyes of the enemy."
"A story from Tokyo to Rangoon."
"A steadfast mind makes a man get up."
"Get up, stand up."
"Freedom knows the need of now."
"He demands a new time,
the keys of independence."
"He is a revolution, he needed a revolt."
"And revolution needs blood."
"In uncertain times,
in a nation that's confused"
"It's difficult to understand Subhash."
"Bose!"
"Fought for freedom, fought injustice!
He looked the British in the eye."
"Bose!"
This is a very dangerous precedent.
We need to have Subhash arrested.
If we don't take strong action now,
we can have a student rebellion
on our hands.
Hold on a minute. What's my fault?
-You attacked a Britisher.
-So what?
Is it a sin?
I'll take you to the professor now
and your patriotic fervour will die down.
We're equal in the professor's eyes.
Slaves. He won't be able to
recognize me.
Move it.
Professor Otton's honor
was crushed to bits
and along with it the notion
that an Indian will turn the other cheek
if slapped once.
This time the cheek was that of
a British!
And the one who slapped was an Indian.
-Cigarettes?
-Keep it inside.
But, Stanley, you have to charge him.
Yes, but for that, Professor Otton
needs to press charges.
Professor?
I wouldn't like to file a complaint.
I don't want people to talk about it.
Do you understand?
Hail Subhash Chandra Bose!
Wait! Put him down.
I'm asking you to put him down!
Sir, you should have been there.
Subhash has avenged our insults.
He has been rusticated
for his behaviour!
Father, history has taught us
that freedom is not given.
-It is taken.
-That's right!
Okay, calm down.
Hail Subhash Chandra Bose!
The transformation from Subhash to Bose
and from Bose to Netaji
was still years away.
But that day, Stanley saw a glimpse.
A glimpse that struck
fear in his heart.
Who are you?
What are you doing in my house?
I don't understand.
These are my personal letters,
you can't just come to my house...
When did he send those letters?
Are there any more letters from him?
These letters are sent from
Singapore, Burma.
Are there more letters or this is it?
How did you enter my house?
-You are not allowed to...
-Are there any more letters from him?
If Bose communicated with anyone,
it would be his wife.
Do you know where Bose is?
Did you speak with Bose
after the 21st of August?
What?
How dare you ask me that!
Bose passed away on 19th August
in a plane crash!
Are you saying that he is alive?
Are there more letters or just these?
Look at you!
Aren't you ashamed to betray
your own country?
Tell me, what do you know?
Is he alive? Is he coming back?
-Please...
-What's wrong, Emilie?
Mom, stay there.
Either you tell me what you know
or leave now.
Get out of here!
Emilie, turn the radio on.
There is news about Bose.
According to the Japanese government
there is no mention
of Subhash Chandra Bose
in the list of those who died
in the plane crash.
-Hello.
-[Emilie] Hello, this is Emilie.
Emilie, listen, Subhash is safe.
This is not the first time
he's just disappeared like this.
In German papers, there is no name
on the passengers' list.
So he's definitely alive.
You need to know that
he spoke of some people in India
-who wanted to hurt him.
-Yes.
I know, I know.
I will call you back, Emilie.
Take care.
I think, we have our lead.
It's been three months, Emilie.
You really trust him to come back?
He's done that before.
So why not do it again?
They hated you for marrying him.
You know, you're not safe here, Emilie.
You're delusional, he's not coming back.
Sorry for the interruption.
Standby for an important broadcast.
INA leader, Subhash Chandra Bose
wants to read out a message for you.
Dear Emilie,
So many have loved me before you.
But, I've never looked at them.
You got that? Now show me.
Got it? Show me how to do it.
Sister, it is a fish fork.
Kindly, use the fruit fork.
I know the difference between
-a fish and fruit fork.
-Hello.
Mother, listen...
[Kalandi] The Prince of Wales is
coming to Calcutta.
He has invited a chosen few
for tea and snacks.
He's also invited Nandini.
-Congratulations.
-[Kalandi] Thank you.
They need Indians
only for decorative purposes.
We are Indians who...
Nandini, come on.
[Nandini] Greetings!
[Kalandi] We've sent Nandini to the best finishing
school in Britain.
She speaks English like the British.
Subhash, you can take Nandini to the
terrace and show her kites.
That's the way, right?
Nandini can see the kites without
going upstairs.
How can you send her with a boy...
-It's nothing like that.
-Mother...
I trust Subhash completely.
[Kalandi] You guys can go. Go.
1921, Calcutta.
Bose had cleared
the Indian Civil Services examination.
The kite season was upon us.
The kids were busy chasing kites
while all mothers wanted
to steal the best groom!
I'll be right back.
Subhash was a high-flying kite.
[Subhash] The black kite, the blue
and that's the green kite.
Done? Let's go.
Subhash, help me out here, please?
ICS!
Thank you.
You've researched about me
before meeting me.
My mother checked you out, not me.
Your mother's research is incomplete.
Why?
I've quit my job.
-Sarat.
-Yes, mother.
I get restless when someone comes
with their daughter.
I need your help. You should
have a classified in your paper.
-I don't like to say it all the time.
-What?
That Subhash stood 4th
in the Indian Civil Services.
He then quit that job
and came back to India.
Print anything you like.
Kids are scared of big cats
and girls from Beni Ghat
are scared of me.
You should go downstairs.
If I go downstairs,
they'll send me up again.
Why did you quit your job?
Because I am free to do it.
What makes the British so special
that they're free in this world?
We are slaves in our homeland.
Some people are slaves, not me.
I am free to play
and to do whatever I want.
I can fly kites too.
That's what you think.
Care for a smoke?
No, thank you.
Aren't you free to smoke?
Freedom is only for men,
not for women.
Freedom is everyone's right.
But do women want to be free?
Subhash has resigned!
Yes, Kalandi, I just told you.
But, you don't want to believe it.
But, you should have at least
told me before.
Did you tell me you were coming
with a marriage proposal?
-[Kalandi] Nandini!
-Here.
Mother. Thank you.
What did you do to my daughter?
-She wanted to smoke.
-And you let her!
-Mom...
-Shut up!
Do you smoke?
-Subhash.
-Just shut up.
Prince of Wales is coming to Calcutta,
I'll see you there.
I will see you there, Subhash.
I will see you, too.
-Let's go.
-I will see you there, Subhash.
-Mom, what are you doing?
-Nandini!
-Subhash.
[Mr.Janki] How many times will you
embarrass us?
Okay, the kite incident.
I don't know, dad.
The women who come with marriage proposals
are stubborn, they don't give up!
You think it's a joke?
[Mr.Janki] Do you even realize
what you have done?
I probably shattered the dreams of the
damsels of Calcutta to become my wife.
It was a prestigious job.
Father, it was slavery!
I would've been reduced to a slave.
Really?
So what are you now?
A revolutionary.
There's only one difference between
a slave and a revolutionary.
Intentions.
A slave intends to serve,
without any purpose.
While a revolutionary intends
to be a soldier.
-So what are you?
-Revolutionaries!
Darbari Lal, keep an eye out
for anything suspicious.
We don't know what Gandhi is planning.
Gandhiji has asked us to boycott
foreign products.
Gandhiji was talking something
about boycott.
But it's nothing new and
it isn't happening for the first time.
This time, we'll not only boycott
foreign products,
but we'll also sell our products
to the British.
A prince is coming to India.
We shouldn't let him leave
empty-handed.
That won't look good.
Go and spread the word.
Stop!
What's in the bale?
Clothes.
Where are you taking it?
Prince of Wales is here.
We want to sell him khadi.
Do you think Prince of Wales
would wear your clothes?
-What is this?
-Bring them here.
Give it to me.
Prince of Wales will trade with you?
-Open and check, both of them.
-We are forced to buy what he sells.
If he buys our khadi
it won't kill him.
-Open it and check.
-We won't charge him much.
He should buy it just to honour
the 250 million Indians he rules.
-Prince of Wales, Prince...
-Mr. Bose...
[Subhash] It's just Khadi.
You've come to sell khadi?
To the Prince of Wales?
Yes, it's called trade.
Arrest him.
-Take them to the police station.
-Prince of Wales...
-Take him.
-Keep moving...
-Where?
You've been robbing us for years,
buy some of our khadi.
-Nandini.
-Subhash.
They didn't let us meet
His Royal Highness.
-But you can meet him...
-Move it.
-Subhash.
-Take them.
-Prince...
-Move it.
-Hello, Mrs. Winterbuttle.
-Hello.
-I hope you're having a good time.
-See you soon.
See you later.
Oh, thank you so much.
-I hope you enjoy your stay.
-Thank you.
-Come.
-Excuse me.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Oh.
That is going to be 50 rupees,
Your Highness.
Excuse me.
50 rupees? For what?
That is the price of our khadi.
For all the cloth that you have been
dumping on us from England.
Nandini...
-Welcome to India.
-Let's go.
-Welcome to India!
-[Prince] Excuse me.
-[Man] What is this?
-[Prince] This woman misbehaved.
Your daughter won't emulate
the British anymore.
You wasted your time
on fish forks, fruit forks...
Finishing school.
[Kalandi] Mr. Janki, your son, Subhash...
He's a disease.
My daughter wouldn't have acted so rashly
before meeting your son.
-He has brainwashed everyone.
-Mother, calm down.
Keep quiet!
Nandini is the only woman in Calcutta
who has shown the courage to sell khadi
to the Prince of Wales.
You should be proud of her.
Keep quiet.
This is just the start, Subhash.
[Judge] Silajit Sengupta.
[Judge] Satyajit Ghosh.
Himadri Chakraborty.
-Adhiraj Bandopade...
-Bandopadhyay.
Shivprasad Mukopady.
Subhash Chandra Bose.
Having been found guilty by us,
of offences under section 294
and section 268
of the Indian Penal Code
for trying to sell khadi
to the Prince of Wales.
are hereby sentenced to six-month
imprisonment.
Six months, that's it.
Did we steal a chicken?
[Judge] Order, order in the court.
Are we being punished for
stealing a fowl?
Or maybe we should beat up
one of your officers
so that you can increase our imprisonment.
[Judge] The accused will maintain decorum
in this courtroom.
The police may proceed.
Yes, milord.
Opium?
Cocaine?
No.
Gandhi?
Gandhiji.
People were sent to prison for
smuggling cocaine and opium.
Nowadays they go to jail
for following Gandhi.
You collaborate with the British
and throw your countrymen in prison.
Do you enjoy doing it?
Don't you feel like joining Gandhiji
and contributing to the freedom struggle?
You're a scheming man, Mr. Bose.
Are you implying that
Gandhiji's ideas are scheming?
What did Gandhiji do?
He only demanded a boycott,
but you jumped a step ahead
to sell khadi.
Right?
Nobody was ready to buy from me.
You serve a bunch of beggars
and yet you slave for them.
Mr. Bose, there are
so many prisoners here.
They do time for six months
quite peacefully
and outside the prison too.
They get married and
fight for the freedom struggle.
But you're obsessed...
obsessed with your motherland!
[Stanley] You will be released tomorrow.
12 Noon.
Pack your belongings and be ready.
Darbari, if your boss ever needs khadi,
let me know.
We have enough clothes.
Ask him to buy some
for the sake of his destitute government.
They've been living off us
for quite a while now.
Don't think you'll get away
with this, Bose.
I always get away, Mr. Stanley.
[Stanley] Bose got away.
The Japanese press has not
one mention of the crash.
A plane crashes and not one
mention of it?
Are you quite sure,
you're not obsessed with him?
Why would he stage his own death?
Sir, I know him.
I've watched him from close quarters.
He plays everything like a game of chess.
While, you're busy saving your queen,
he's already attacked your king and
before you know it, checkmate.
Do not contribute
to the hysteria,
which is already out there.
[Man] Checkmate!
"You raised an army in the forest."
"You wrote this incredible tale."
"You designed a rebellion."
"No, no you never died."
"You never lost your resilience."
"You woke and shook the nation."
"You taught us
the meaning of the country."
"And vanished into immortality."
"But my blood still boils."
"No, I am not satiated."
"History is cursed."
"Your secret, secret story."
"In a nation that sleeps."
"Is difficult to understand."
"It's difficult to understand Subhash."
"In times like these..."
Mr. Nehru, I have a reliable source
who tells me, he saw Subhash Chandra Bose
in Saigon
11 days after his supposed demise.
What do you have to say about that?
I have no comments on that.
No more questions, please.
Bose was alive.
Or it's possible that
the faith of thousands of people
kept him alive, making him immortal.
Emilie. Your call.
Operator speaking.
Yes, sir, I'm connecting you
to the line two.
Thank you.
Ever since she heard
the radio announcement
Emilie would always be lost,
thinking about the radio.
She always hoped to hear
Bose's voices.
After 165 letters,
nine years and bidding goodbyes
eight times,
Emilie was getting used to
the life of waiting for Bose.
Who switched off the radio?
Bose's death sparked so many questions
which not only troubled Emilie
but also Stanley.
On one hand,
there was Bose's ladylove
and on the other,
there was a British officer.
Both had one thing in common.
Both of them were convinced
that Bose would return.
They were all looking for the link
which could help them find Bose.
[Man] They know about you.
You will have to leave this place.
It was unbelievable that in the airplane
crash that killed Bose...
two of Bose's fellow passengers,
an INA Officer Rahman and a Japanese
Officer Nakamura escaped unscathed.
In fact, Bose's confidant Ayar too
was unable to believe
that Bose was no more.
I'm telling the truth, Ayar,
Netaji's upper body was badly burnt.
Rahman, forget what I think,
no one in India, would believe
that Netaji's no more.
Bose's upper body was badly burnt.
I used my coat to put out the fire.
Everyone had their own versions
about the fateful plane crash.
But in the end, all the stories reached
one conclusion: Bose's death.
Can we...
fly down Netaji's body to Singapore?
The size of the coffin...
won't fit in the aircraft.
None of us have seen his dead body.
You performed his last rites
without informing us.
Why the rush?
So then we can transport
his body by ship.
That won't be possible.
The body is in such a bad condition,
it could start decaying any moment.
And the chemicals required
to preserve the body...
are not available in Formosa.
Okay. I believe you for the moment
that you're telling the truth.
But at least a photograph.
You don't even have a single photo
for his family?
Take the photographs.
Don't take photographs of the face.
You couldn't preserve the body
because chemicals weren't available.
Also, you performed
the last rites in a rush.
You couldn't take a photo of his face
as it was badly burnt.
Do you seriously expect me
to believe that?
What is that you're not telling us?
[Stanley] What are they not telling us?
It's a British contingent
on its way to Taiwan
to look for Bose!
Where are you, Bose?
Where the hell are you?
Bose has just been released.
We can relax for a couple of days.
-I mean, he will relax for few days.
-He's a loose cannon.
Even Gandhi can't control him.
Put all eyes on him.
Yes, sir.
[Stanley] Darbari Lal!
The British government's police
intelligence had sent
many of their spies behind Bose.
They were waiting for something
big to happen.
[Subhash] Faster.
Use both hands. Wait.
Come here. Look ahead.
Okay.
Maintain distance.
Make sure you don't hit each other,
we have to hit the Brits!
Hey!
Strike up, down.
On the head and then block!
All right! Let's begin.
Sir, he's teaching them
to fight with sticks.
And you're sure it's only sticks?
[Stanley] There are no guns involved...
They had sticks, right?
No guns or weapons?
No, sir, but it's confirmed.
Bose has nothing to do with non-violence!
He's building an army!
An army with sticks as weapons?
[Man] Sir, one more thing.
he had organized a camp for the people
affected by the flood.
A whole group of spies were
tailing Bose.
Bose was a law-abiding
and a model citizen.
Stanley was frustrated after
what his spies were telling him.
Sir, it's confirmed!
Bose is about to marry the Congress leader
Kiran Shankar Roy's sister.
[Man] I have also found out
[Man] that Kiran Shankar Roy will send Bose
to England after his marriage
[Man] to study law.
Mr. Bose has resigned from
civil services.
Why would he go to London to study law?
[Darbari Lal] You're talking nonsense.
-You wasted his time. Now leave.
-[Man] Okay, sir.
Put more men on him, Darbari Lal.
I need good men!
In fact, I want you to be his shadow.
Sir, me?
What information can I extract
that these spies couldn't?
You have an edge over them.
You know him.
If I knew Mr. Bose,
he also knew me very well.
-[Child] Where do I go?
-[Subhash] Right here!
-[Subhash] Good, keep it up!
-[Child] Be alert.
-[Child] Come here.
-Here!
-I am here.
-Right here.
[Child] Come here!
Hey, where are you going? Come here!
-A cup of tea, please!
-Sure.
I'll be right back!
Excuse me, my money?
-Aunt!
-Subhash.
-How are you?
-I'm fine, how are you?
I'm good.
It's raining heavily.
Where are you coming from?
From home.
What are you looking at?
Who is it?
He spies for the British.
[Aunt] So what is he doing here?
As if you're starting a movement
right here!
-How about some tea?
-Sure.
I'll get it for you.
Darbari, Darbari, come here.
Come here.
Here.
-No, I'm fine here.
-Take it. It's raining.
Thank you, Mr. Bose.
Have some tea.
-No...
-Drink it while it's hot.
Care for a smoke?
No.
Take it, I won't tell Stanley.
No, thank you.
So what did you find out about me?
Mr. Bose, you're very stubborn!
You'll again create problems
for the British.
Will you tell this to Stanley?
He'll realize it.
-You are very...
-Intelligent, I know.
Listen, go home.
It is raining, you'll catch a cold.
Take this umbrella with you.
Bring it back when you spy on me tomorrow.
Okay, I'll leave right now.
And listen...
a spy should always do the job
from a distance.
Go now.
Mr. Bose was a master of disguise,
he could vanish in a blink of an eye!
We followed Mr. Bose for months,
but we couldn't find anything.
-Go home, pal!
-Sure.
-Go home!
-Whatever Bose was planning behind doors
was about to change everything.
[Subhash] I am coming!
-Hello, sir.
-Hello.
Here's your parcel.
Can you sign here?
Done?
-Do you want water?
-No, sir.
See you.
-Hey, postman!
-Yes.
-What were you doing inside?
-Delivering a parcel.
-A parcel for?
-For Mr. Subhash.
Oh, Mr. Subhash.
Let me see.
Okay, great. Can I keep this?
-What do you mean?
-You may leave.
-All right, off you go.
-What a nuisance!
Darbari Lal says a uniform
got delivered to Bose's house.
Apparently, it was a GOC's uniform
that was mistakenly delivered
to Fort Williams.
The officers at Fort Williams
had quite a laugh about it.
It was an army uniform.
Doesn't that bother you?
Maybe Bose likes to dress up!
Who knows?
[Darbari Lal] Sir, even I feel the same.
Mr. Bose always tries to spite us.
[Darbari Lal] It was just one uniform.
It's not a big issue.
No one knew why Bose ordered
khaki uniforms.
Before anyone could find the answer,
in 1928 the streets of Calcutta
witnessed the unthinkable.
Mr. Bose was marching on the street
with two thousand people.
The British and the Congress government
were reduced to mute spectators.
-Your Excellency, had we known...
-Nonsense!
How could you have not known two thousand
people would descend upon our city
wearing uniforms and carrying weapons?
That chap Bose has made
a perfect arse out of us!
You have got to get a grip on things.
[Stanley] Do you know you're a traitor
to the empire?
But he gave me money. I made him clothes.
It was not just clothes but uniforms.
You have raised a standing army
against the British Raj!
But, I was just trying to make...
[Stanley] Some Indian comes and gives you money,
you make him uniforms!
-I was, I was...
-To fight against your own people!
Do you have any idea
how much trouble are we in?
I'll make sure that you never
do business in this city again.
-But, please listen...
-Shut up!
You didn't tell anyone about this.
What should I say?
We Indians should have our own army!
-[Man] Pratik, say something.
-It's my country, my people...
why should I inform or ask anyone?
Subhash, weapons and chaos are against
our rules!
Who made the rules anyway?
And what have we achieved
with these rules?
Do you know the real reason
behind our slavery?
It's your thinking and nonviolence.
What do you want to do, Subhash?
We are talking with
the British government.
For years, we've been talking,
but have we achieved freedom?
But this might scare them.
That's good.
They should be scared for a change.
For now, all of you
look more petrified to me.
You're about to make a huge mistake.
It will upset Gandhiji.
The British are upset too.
Gandhiji...
Mr. Bose along with
two thousand people...
attacked Fort Williams,
do you think it's justified?
Mr. Gandhi...
doesn't this go against your basic
tenets of nonviolence?
In your country England,
don't they have
the Bertram Mills Circus?
That is all it was. A circus.
-So, we have dried mix vegetable.
-Can I have a bite?
Enough.
[Darbari Lal] Mr. Bose, you have to come with us.
Can I eat first?
Eat it at the police station.
Wait. Let him finish his dinner.
I thought your boss had
forgotten about me.
So, what's the charge this time?
-Come with me, you'll get your...
-[Sarat] Subhash!
I'll get you out on bail tomorrow morning.
It's Friday. You won't get
bail for the next three days.
You see,
the British are getting smarter.
Mother, pack my dinner for the jail.
And pack a little more.
-Darbari likes mix vegetables.
-No, I won't eat.
What's the matter?
You've have been chasing me for months.
What's there to hide?
Also, I think betrayal is
not new to you.
I mean, for people like you.
So, now you've got yourself a uniform.
Last time, when we were selling you khadi,
you had a problem.
And now that we're buying khaki from
you people, you still have a problem.
You descended on the streets of Calcutta
with two thousand people.
What makes you think you can do that?
Because it's my country.
And I am free to do whatever I want.
I don't need anyone's permission.
Do you really think
you can get away with this?
Mr. Stanley.
I always get away.
[Stanley] April 1928, Subhash Chandra Bose.
Dangerous enemy of the British Raj!
He can't be controlled by Congress.
They have an army of
two thousand natives today.
Their numbers are going to surge.
What is the news from Taiwan?
Bose may still be alive.
[Man] Are you sure?
[Man] If he returns to India now
neither the British government
nor the Indian Congress would be
able to stop him.
No one has seen this file.
[Stanley] Kinji Watanabe says that he saw Bose
get on the plane with four big boxes,
5 feet by 2 feet,
all filled with the INA gold.
How much gold do you think
that would be, Darbari Lal?
People have given gold, diamonds and
ornaments in huge amounts to the INA.
-Women have given jewelry in kilos.
-He was carrying so much gold!
But wasn't he going to Singapore
to surrender?
[Stanley] So why was he carrying so much gold?
Stan...
Is it that Bose chap?
[Woman] Aren't you getting a little
obsessed now?
[Woman] Just get done with it, will you?
We're getting late for the show.
Let's go.
Stanley.
You're not listening to me.
Sorry, dear, what?
He's the greatest escape artist ever!
Wish I could see him in person.
Who?
Many believed
that Bose was carrying
11 kilos of gold in four boxes.
But Stanley believed
it was not possible to have
only 11 kilos of gold in four boxes!
About 11 kilos of gold were recovered
from briefcase.
that Bose carried on the plane.
Sir, I don't understand.
He was carrying four giant boxes,
5 feet by 2 feet.
It means...
You don't carry 11 kilos of gold,
in four huge boxes!
Bose escaped!
The crash was a ruse!
Rahman, why don't you just tell them?
You can end this torture now.
Is Bose dead or alive?
Stanley was convinced
that Bose was alive.
All they had to do
was to find Bose.
Meanwhile, British officer Anderson
and Hayat were also looking for Bose.
Soon they managed to nab
seven INA officers.
Hasan, Pritam, Gulzara,
Chatterjee, Thevy, Sahay and Rahman.
We're not making any progress, Hayat.
Sir, they are INA soldiers.
They're tough.
It's not easy to break them down.
We're running out of time.
Stop!
All of you, outside.
Rahman, I'll ask you again.
What happened after the plane crash?
Netaji...
was trying to take off...
his coat and my clothes... caught fire.
But you already told us, you had no idea
how Bose was removed from the plane!
I don't remember it!
-I, I forgot!
-Does he always stammer this much?
He stutters every now and then.
For the...
last two days...
you're repeating the same thing...
-Again and again?
-Yes.
Do you have a cigarette?
Bloody hell!
We're not torturing him,
he's torturing us.
Is Subhash Chandra Bose alive?
Is Netaji...
alive?
Mister, we want to know
the answer from you.
Are you asking me?
I wasn't even there when it happened.
What can I possibly tell you?
Gulzara...
Rahman has told us four different
versions of the same story.
Sir, how can you believe him?
Rahman is a...
is a damn good storyteller.
He tells a story with such conviction
that you won't be able to understand
the difference between fact and fiction.
Well done. Well done.
Do you think it's a joke?
It's not a joke.
He is Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose!
They're laughing at us.
Can't you hear them?
It's a game to them, you see.
Biding their time while
Bose is slipping away.
Have you any idea what it would mean
if Bose did get away?
-Bose is dead, sir.
-Ah, yes of course.
The British contingent found
some clues but
none of them confirmed that Bose is alive.
And I think they are creating
this fear in us.
By making it seem that
they have something to hide.
What do you make of this?
It says, Bose is dead.
No.
Gandhi says Bose is dead.
Gandhi, you see, is protecting Bose.
But, if Bose does return to India,
we will execute him as a war criminal.
-Very true.
-And he will.
If he intends to lead his army.
Do you know who else was on the plane?
Colonel Shidei, another war criminal.
Stanley Allen, IG, Calcutta Police.
-David Anderson, a pleasure to meet you.
-Likewise.
Hayat Khan.
Please have a seat.
So now you accused two people of
faking their deaths.
-Isn't that a little paranoid?
-No.
It's not paranoia.
You don't know Bose like I do.
He poses the greatest risk
to the British Raj.
Not Gandhi, not Congress.
Right now, we don't know where he is.
And that should make us very, very afraid.
1930, Calcutta.
After resigning from ICS,
selling khadi to the British
and after coming out of jail,
Bose was elected as the Mayor of Calcutta.
Hail Mr. Bose!
Now, you're the Mayor of Calcutta.
So, no more armies marching
through the city.
Calcutta is too small for my army,
Mr. Stanley.
My army will be marching throughout
the country now.
And how exactly do you plan to do that?
It will be one step at a time.
It will be when you least expect it.
It might be happening now.
So, sleep light.
I always do.
Sir, it's not just uniforms,
but weapons that make an army.
Now that he is the Mayor,
he won't get a chance to fight.
Am I right, Mr. Bose?
Only you can give me
that chance, Darbari.
People like you never mend their ways,
do they?
Hail Mr. Bose!
The British gave him
another chance.
There was an uprising in Bengal
and Bose wouldn't back down now.
He gave fiery speeches
and joined the protests.
They are trying to infect us
with venereal diseases.
"Stand up together and unite together."
"Stand up together and unite together.
Stand up together..."
A rope is a rope, but it can also
be a noose around your neck.
"Stand up together and unite together."
In 1931,
the British arrested Bose, again.
Bloody hell!
I think that's enough.
Is he really going to use it?
I don't know.
I have a proposal for you.
All of this can stop.
All you have to do
is come with me to Taihoku
and show me the crash site.
You know, I can't touch you, Rahman.
You're the only eyewitness.
The rest of you, however,
are of no use to us.
Except for one thing.
Darbari Lal, everybody out.
Darbari Lal?
Now, with each turn...
these screws will go deeper
into your skull.
The British tried everything.
They used a torture device known as brain
crusher from the era of World War.
But, these were INA officers, after all.
They were unbreakable.
Sahay sang like a canary.
Japanese officer Isoda met them
on 20th of August at Hanoi.
He informed that Bose has escaped
to Manchuria.
Brilliant, Stanley!
But, did he say why Bose was going
to Manchuria?
He wants to get to Russia.
And why Russia?
He's building his army.
The one he's been always talking about.
Well then, I must get a man
in Manchuria immediately.
Did you know he has
a German wife and child?
Really?
That cad!
Emilie Schenkel!
He's contacted the family
a couple of times.
-We need to put eyes on her too.
-Of course.
If Bose is alive,
he will attempt to get in touch with her.
Give me two apples.
Yes, sure.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
Mrs. Bose...
Mrs. Bose, has Subhash Chandra Bose
contacted you?
I don't understand.
Mrs. Bose, we know you speak
fluent English.
We are aware of your relationship with
Subhash Chandra Bose.
-We want to speak to you.
-I don't understand.
Listen, we can help you out.
It's Emilie Schenkel, not Bose.
Mother.
How was your day?
-Where's Anita?
-She's asleep.
Vienna, 1934.
Bose feigned illness and
slipped through the British net to Vienna
to complete his book about
the freedom struggle.
Miss Schenkel, Mrs. Strauss.
-Lovely to meet you, Mr. Bose.
-Pleasure.
-Good morning.
Please sit.
Dr. Mathur must have mentioned.
I'm looking for a stenographer.
Someone who is skilled with shorthand.
-Shorthand?
-Yes.
I need someone to take dictation
for the book I'm planning to write.
So proficiency in English is a must.
Mr. Bose, my German is much better
than my English.
But my English is better than
anyone around here.
Dr. Mathur spoke very highly
of your English.
And your shorthand skills.
Good to know.
-Dr. Mathur is very kind.
-He is.
What about you? How's your English?
-English?
-Yeah!
Can you speak English, can you write it?
(Speaking German)
I think, she doesn't understand.
Well, in that case,
you're the chosen one.
-Thank you. Thank you for coming.
-Sure.
I don't think if she's getting it.
(Speaking German)
She looked miffed, what did you tell her?
I told her that, this man doesn't
intend to pay you
and that he will make you work for free.
But I have a stipend. I can pay.
I know, Mr. Bose, it's just she would
feel really bad
knowing that she's losing
on a paid job.
You're very kind.
Dr. Mathur told me you were
going to be a nun?
My father wanted me to be one.
I went to nunnery for four years.
Was married to Christ.
And?
And nothing.
After that, I realized that
it's not something I want to be.
What about you, Mr. Bose?
Not my father but my mother
wanted me to be married...
Not to Christ, of course.
But to a girl.
I'm married to a cause now.
Liberate India!
Azidi, right?
Azadi, that's how you say it.
Freedom!
It's kind of being married to
Christ only.
I can't marry anyone else now.
I am glad you told me before I asked.
1934.
When Chancellor
Engelbert Dollfuss was murdered,
situation started
to worsen in Austria.
The new chancellor and the fear of
his army could be felt on the streets.
Bose, the dictator has been shot dead.
That means now Anton Rintelen
would take over
and become the next chancellor of Austria.
The Nazis will be rising now.
Subhash, how can you admire the Nazis?
There is so much violence,
can't you see that?
Freedom comes with a cost, Emilie!
And sometimes that cost is violence.
The army... it turned against
their own government.
-It means they're all traitors.
-That is exactly what India needs.
An army, an uprising, an insurgency!
But we don't have money for that.
Come.
12th November, 1945. That's it.
Looking for him in Manchuria
may help, may not.
Spying on Emilie Schenkel
may help, maybe not.
But if we want to find Bose,
we need to find the gold.
Follow the missing gold.
He needs it to build his army.
"The call for freedom
from millions of voices."
"Look straight into
the eyes of the enemy."
"A story from Tokyo to Rangoon."
"A steadfast mind makes a man get up."
"Get up, stand up."
"Freedom knows the need of now."
"He demands a new time,
the keys of independence."
Only one person knew about
the INA gold apart from Mr. Bose
and he was an INA soldier
and his trusted confidant, Ram Murthy.
A secret so difficult to hide.
Good to see you, Colonel.
Would you like a seat?
I'm not here to have a cup of tea.
And what you have is for safe keeping
and not for spending.
I'm spending just about enough
to mend the dent.
And just so you know,
there is a price for recklessness.
Be careful, Mr. Ram Murthy.
And what if the British find out
who you are?
We're war criminals.
I think, you should be careful.
-And when Netaji gets back...
-Oh you think he'll be back?
He was an INA soldier.
Although, I can't understand
why he came back to India.
Is it ancestral?
Show it to me.
Keep it here. Keep it.
You see, even the dead have
a story to tell.
There's an odor to gold.
No matter how hard you try,
you can't suppress it.
I'm getting that odor from this.
What's this?
The dead man we found
was bringing this to show
someone in India.
As you know, the poor Japanese
don't have any food or water.
And yet, two Indians
are having a ball there.
Mr. Bose was in Japan
and he's also in Japan.
What does this say?
Sir, it's written in Japanese.
[Speaking Japanese]
Hey, English, talk in English!
In English, you...
-Can you speak Japanese?
-No, sir.
So, stop staring at my face
and get me someone who does!
No one knows Japanese, sir.
How do you talk to him then?
We don't need to talk, do we?
I'm not getting my daughter married
into his family.
Stop giggling, you fool!
All they know is Bengali, not Japanese!
I feel we're banging
our heads on the wall!
Hang on!
We have someone who knows Japanese.
You've spent a lot of time in Japan.
You were quite close to Bose.
Netaji is... dead.
What's the point in raking up the past?
Forget about past.
We're here for something else.
Bring him in.
You may leave.
Translate this.
Ram Murthy and J. Murthy,
are enjoying
and having a nice time in Japan.
They used to drive around
in luxury cars.
They own a bungalow,
a restaurant and two luxury cars.
What does it say?
Ram Murthy and J Murthy...
live a very luxurious life in Japan.
They're often seen travelling...
in expensive cars.
What else?
They own a bungalow,
a restaurant and two sedan cars.
Who were Murthy brothers?
Were they close to Netaji?
They were INA officers, living in Japan.
What's the connection between INA gold
and the Murthy brothers?
You're saying...
in a poor country like Japan,
two soldiers had so much money?
Well, you stole all our money.
At least, spare the outsiders.
They already know
that this is about the INA gold.
The Japanese Army handed it
to the Murthy brothers.
And you trust everything that
Japanese tell you?
Rahman, you stopped stammering
all of a sudden.
Where's the INA gold?
[Speaking Japanese]
What are you talking about?
Why did he say Netaji?
The Japanese POW told Rahman
that Netaji was alive.
He further said
that the wound on Rahman's hand
was not from the plane crash
but it was rather an acid burn.
Rahman, is Bose still alive?
Stanley suspected something
strange and important was afoot
but he couldn't quite put
his finger on it.
Bose's story was turning out
to be an endless drama.
If we follow the rumors,
before anyone could solve
the mystery of Netaji's death,
someone had spotted Bose
or Bose's lookalike in Manchuria.
-What?
-I want to send a message.
No, no. I will type.
-What?
-I will type.
No...
Move.
Sit.
There's a telegram for you, sir.
Keep the gold safe,
we will need it to raise an army.
-Hello.
-Hello, this is Ram Murthy.
I've got a telegram from Bose.
He's alive... in Manchuria.
British officer John Figgs
was in Manchuria
and he also got the news
that Bose was alive.
Ram Murthy graduated from
a traitor to an informant
and all it took was a phone call.
Bose got in touch for his gold.
He did?
He wants to get his army.
What's the story with this man?
When does he give up?
That's the thing with Bose.
He never gives up.
We need to raise an army now.
The British have divided
Hindus and Muslims in our country.
For the Hindus, they have Congress
and for the Muslims, Muslim League.
They've issued an arrest warrant
against you.
It clearly says you'd be arrested
if you go back to India.
The entire British Raj
is after your life.
Tell me something new.
People are chasing me since my childhood.
Mark my words, Dr. Mathur.
I'll be chased even after my death.
Then why are you going back to India?
To form my government.
And you think they'll let you do it?
Mr. Bose... Please.
Dr. Mathur, there are more Indians
in India than the Brits.
I'll form my government with their help.
Mr. Bose, you've just had surgery.
Please.
I have a better reason
to stay back than the surgery.
Can you give this letter
to Miss Schenkl?
See you soon.
You're very kind.
Azidi, right?
Azadi. That's how you say it.
Even the iceberg sometimes melts.
And so, it is with me now.
I have already sold myself
to my first love,
that is my country.
I don't know
what the future holds for me.
Maybe, I'll languish in prison.
Or perhaps,
I'll be sent to the gallows.
Maybe a single bullet
will bring everything to an end.
We'll probably never meet again.
I may not even write to you again.
But, you're always in my thoughts.
1937, Bose left Emilie
and despite several warnings
from his supporters
Bose returned to Calcutta.
Back in Vienna,
Emilie's long wait had just begun
but for Indians,
the four-year long wait was over.
Long live!
How are you?
"...beyond the sun..."
-How are you?
-All good.
Hemal.
Why did you come back, Subhash?
I had to.
This is my country.
You know, I always come back.
"...it will go away!"
"...with passion..."
Move aside.
-Move.
-Bose, you were told not to come back.
And you were told to go back.
You did not listen to me.
Why should I listen to you?
Darbari, you have aged terribly.
Stop chasing me
and take care of yourself.
We'll achieve our freedom very soon.
Subhash Chandra Bose,
you're being arrested.
On what grounds?
Let's go, Bose. Come on.
Come on.
Long live the revolution!
Long live freedom!
I don't need to give you a reason.
We told you not to come back.
Darbari, you had no one to chase
after I left.
Did you arrest anyone else
or were you just waiting for me?
Why did you come back, Mr. Bose?
We told you not to.
No one can stop an Indian from
coming back to his own country.
This is my country.
-There will be no British rule.
-Calm down, Mr. Bose.
We've been calm far too long, Darbari.
Not anymore.
Release Bose now. That's an order.
Sir, that would be a mistake.
Bose needs to be locked up.
He's a disease.
He needs to be contained.
Do you see the crowd outside?
Do you want to make him a martyr?
Hail Bose!
Release him now.
You there! Now.
"This adroit voyager"
"for the love of his land"
"will head back home!"
Bose was exiled,
but his impassioned countrymen
propelled him straight into
the Congress headquarters.
Bose won the 1938
the Congress president elections.
Apart from the British, there were others
-who were troubled with Bose.
-Hail Bose.
Congress was soon to witness
the battle between Khaki and Khadi.
All hail Mr. Bose!
I've spoken to all the party workers.
We've explained everything.
Everyone's ready.
Baapu, Subhash is here.
Subhash.
-How are you?
-I'm fine.
-I'm fine, too.
Have a seat.
-Greetings, Baapu.
-Kindly wait outside for ten minutes.
How are you?
Subhash, you're going down the wrong path.
I respect your principle of nonviolence.
But I don't think we can achieve
freedom with nonviolence.
-Subhash...
-Baapu, half the world
is preparing to fight
against the British.
If we support the Brits now,
India will never achieve freedom.
If we have to sacrifice,
why sacrifice for the British?
Why not for our country?
Subhash, your ideals are at loggerheads
with the Congress ideals.
Our ideals are at loggerheads,
but our goal is the same.
To liberate India.
Since you refuse to listen...
I can't support you, Subhash.
"It's difficult to understand Subhash."
You can at least
grant me your blessings.
You call me Bapu,
yet you don't listen to me.
As you wish.
I'll take your leave.
Nehru.
"It's difficult to understand Subhash."
-I'll just be back.
-Okay.
Nehru, you must speak to Bapu.
We need an army to fight,
not a spinning wheel.
-How can we raise an army?
-Why not?
Look around you.
You're surrounded by an army.
If 250,000 Indians can fight
for the British,
why can't they fight for us?
"His actions faster than thoughts."
Talk to Bapu.
"They'd look for him where he was not."
"Bose!"
"Incapable of being caught."
"His lines were sharp
and theirs would blot."
What is about this Bose chap
that drives people to frenzy?
I have been hearing reports
that he's on his way to Manchuria.
So if there's anything that
we need to know, we should be informed.
Do you think Bose is alive?
Hypothetically...
if he is alive
and he does return
who would be Prime Minister, Mr. Nehru?
"Right, right, right."
"What I said is right!"
-I want to meet Mr. Andrew.
-And the purpose of your visit?
-He wanted a file.
-[Man] Which file?
Jai Hind!
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning.
Bapu was remembering you.
The British were remembering you too.
My Congress presidency has created
troubles for Bapu and the British.
I'm the man who united them.
If I could do the same for India...
That's all I hope for.
Subhash.
But Mr. Bose, Congress?
I'll talk to them.
And Gandhiji?
-You got the papers?
-Yes.
Mr. Bose, you sure have style.
Have a seat.
Be seated.
You come strolling into
the police station as if it's a park.
-[Darbari] Will you have some snacks or tea?
-No.
So what brings you here?
I'm here to put up bail
for Benoy's accomplices.
Why?
For years, the Congress encouraged
protestors to go to jail.
We want to reverse the trend
by freeing the protestors.
But Mr. Bose, how can we let them go?
They are rioters.
We've also recovered a pistol from them.
I'm impressed. The British Police
are finally learning the law.
This time, you've got a reason too.
Mr. Bose, you aren't behind, are you?
On one hand,
you chant the virtues of nonviolence,
but shoot the British
in broad daylight on the other.
That's fine.
Benoy didn't shoot anyone
in the back.
Unlike the British
who stab you in the back.
Get the papers.
Tell me something, Darbari.
Is the law of nonviolence applicable
only to Indians?
Did you ever hear a Britisher
talking about nonviolence?
Well, I never did.
Matto, get the bail papers.
Mr. Bose, you're making a huge mistake.
This goes against your own values.
Strange! Darbari is lecturing us
about values.
Benoy Bandopadhyay's
actions are wrong.
You validated his actions
with Congress support
and are encouraging
violence and brutality!
Do you people seriously believe
that you can bring about revolution
by wearing pristine white clothes
and without shedding a drop of blood?
It's hardly a year
since you're back from Europe.
Do you even know the ground realities?
Subhash, have you ever taken
any advice from anyone?
We all want freedom.
Really?
-You want freedom?
-[Man]Yes.
Well, you've kept it quite
a secret, then.
Benoy Bandopadhyay is an example
of what a gigantic failure we are!
What he did is an act of desperation.
How do you plan to achieve freedom?
Do you have a blueprint?
You must have a plan.
Subhash, it won't happen in a day.
How much time will it take?
Six months, a year, five years
or ten years?
When will we achieve freedom?
No one has achieved freedom
only by talking and meetings.
For freedom, you need a revolution.
All of you are contesting
the upcoming elections.
You're forming a government
with the British.
There's exchange of money!
The Congress is only interested in
forming a government!
They have no interest in freedom!
By the way, it's because of the Congress
government that trade unions exist.
It's because of us.
The workers finally got their rights!
And when the same workers were
rotting in a prison cell?
What will you do if this government
asks you to shoot workers?
Will you support the government
or the workers?
Do you know what the Congress is like?
It's like a street dog.
-It neither has a master nor a home!
-Mr. Bose!
Save your anger for the British,
it will be useful.
Here's your government.
You shouldn't let me out.
Tell me, Mr. Stanley, a war is coming.
What if all Indian soldiers
refuse to fight for His Majesty?
Will you dare take on Hitler
without us?
Or will you beg us to support him?
Take him.
Did Bose actually say that?
That is a threat.
Well, that is what I heard.
And did he say, if someone slaps you once,
slap him twice!
No, no. That's... that's just a rumor.
Long time ago, he slapped a professor...
then this whole legend grew out of
that unfortunate incident.
Isn't that the complete opposite
of what Gandhi said?
Turn the other cheek!
I believe, Bose commands
quite a following.
But I like Gandhi.
[Woman] I wish more Indians were
like Gandhi, I feel terribly unsafe.
No, there's nothing to worry about.
Bose is well taken care of,
for the time being.
-Cheers.
-I hope so.
You didn't hear me,
you can't get bail that easily.
It requires documents, a lawyer,
you have to make rounds of the court.
Mr. Bose cannot be released.
You people can leave.
[Bose] Greetings.
What are you doing, Mr. Bose?
Your revolution is spreading
like a disease.
But don't you worry,
the British are equally irrepressible.
They'll figure out
something very soon.
Darbari, you can throw revolutionaries
behind bars
but how can you possibly tame
our revolution?
Ask Stanley and open an account for me.
For bail, you know.
[Bose] I'll be a regular here.
Here's your confession.
The quicker you sign it,
[Darbari] the quicker you'll get
your bail papers ready.
-Why should I sign?
-Don't you want to go home?
No.
I want to send the British
back to their homes.
Is there any document for that?
Mr. Bose, you shouldn't rub shoulders
with these junkies and thieves.
Just sign and leave. What are you doing?
Back in Europe, I learnt a trick, Darbari.
Would you like to see?
Go ahead.
What's your name?
-Anirudh...
-Keep quiet.
Is he a revolutionary?
He's a junkie.
-Where is the paper?
-[Anirudh] How did you do that?
It's called illusion.
You saw what I wanted to show you.
You couldn't guess
what I really wanted to hide.
Mr. Bose, return the paper, please.
Sadly, I didn't learn
how to bring it back.
Mr. Bose, it's a government document.
Please stop joking.
-Where did it go?
-What are you doing? Where is it?
-What are...
-You get worried so fast.
You're always after my case.
Kindly sign here and spare me.
I would rather stay in the jail
than sign any papers
from the British.
"Better than the world..."
"is my India."
"We are its nightingales"
"and this is our garden."
"Better than the world"
Very good. Very good.
One at a time.
-It's confirmed.
-Very nice.
Netaji is alive.
The British are also aware of it.
We have to warn him somehow.
If the British find him,
it'll be terrible.
Why? Let them arrest him.
People have made a deserter
their God.
Bose can be anything, but he's
not a deserter.
Three years ago, you said
that if Subhash comes back, you'll be
the first one to take this to him.
Bose was hounded by the British,
but did the Congress treat him
any better?
That's for me?
You may leave.
Yogita, very nice.
Dear, thank you.
Come. Come.
Did anyone follow you?
Well, I think I saw Bose in Manchuria.
Don't worry, Mr. Murthy.
-You're quite safe.
-The joke's on you Figges.
Bose is alive and he is dangerous.
He's a fugitive, all alone, on the run.
Bose is never alone.
Are you going to kill him?
The British government doesn't
share its plans with...
everyone.
As if you could kill him!
We all know what happened
the last few times you tried.
Where is the telegram?
The information's right.
We will bring Bose back.
Beware of the mole who can bring
down the empire.
Ram Murthy was a mole,
but someone had
double crossed him too.
Mohan Singh, Bose's confidant.
The brothers have tipped off
the British about Netaji.
The British Army has sent a contingent
behind Netaji.
Do not worry. We call on the Ikirio.
Bose will be safe.
Ikirio means Japanese ghost.
According to the Japanese,
a living man can also be a ghost.
Mohan Singh couldn't understand
what Nakamura was trying to say.
But what happened that day
baffled even the British contingent.
Get him!
Hey.
The Ikirio has protected Bose.
Bose... is safe.
You're not Bose.
Who is Bose?
The man they got hold of
was not Bose.
But the man who got away
could have been Bose or an imposter.
It was hard to say.
If you're not Bose...
why did you run away
when you saw us?
Sir, in the normal world
if you're chased by two gunmen,
you will run like hell.
But that doesn't mean I'm Bose.
Where is Bose?
Didn't you read the news? He's dead.
He's just fooling us around.
Do your sources have anything on Bose?
Yes, sir.
We just found that Bose has
rented a room in a nearby hotel.
Is it confirmed?
Excuse me.
It was hard to say
if Bose stayed at that hotel.
Meanwhile, the British Police
nabbed three Indians.
Yes? How may I help you?
A bus driver, a ticket master
and a hotel manager.
Have you seen this man before?
Are you kidding me?
He's standing right behind you.
Do you take them for fools?
Will they parade me around
while toting my photo everywhere?
-The man in the photo is someone...
-Don't say his name.
Take a closer look.
Tell me, if the man in the photo
was at this hotel or was it this man?
No, sir, he was someone else.
Although, he looked like him,
but he was different.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, sir.
Who was he and when did he
visit this hotel?
He visited the hotel three days ago.
-I need a room.
-Okay.
-Your name?
-Joseph.
Your signature.
It's original.
Room 102.
No, thank you.
Go straight upstairs.
-Go up and check.
-Sir.
What would he do?
His room always stank of burnt pages.
[Manager] He would be holed up in his room
all day long.
[Manager] He wouldn't open the door
for food or for room service.
[Manager] He would just write and burn pages.
[Manager] I was puzzled because
the war was over...
[Manager] I wonder what he was up to.
[Manager] He was eager to leave this hotel.
He asked me if he could rent
a car or a bus.
I'd have driven him to
nearby places.
Later, he asked me to
drop him to a stop before hell.
He was quite a character.
How long have you been working here?
-Three years.
-Sir!
These were found in Bose's room.
Sir.
Call up Anderson and ask about
Watanbe. I need details.
-Yes, sir.
-Move.
-Are you an Indian?
-Yes, sir.
What are you doing in Manchuria?
I am laborer, sir.
I will follow the money.
We don't call India our home anymore.
It belongs to the British now.
Do you know him?
No.
I haven't seen him before.
Sir, he's lying, I can tell!
Where did this come from?
It belongs to my wife.
Yes, he was here.
[Bus driver] He was in a tearing hurry.
[Bus driver] He wanted to reach
Incheon in a day.
[Bus driver] He asked me to book
an entire bus to Incheon.
I want to go to Incheon.
This bus won't go anywhere.
Do you know me?
Stop bugging me, will you?
I'm tired, let me sleep.
Make a choice.
To Incheon and please hurry.
When did he leave?
Two days ago.
Sir, may I leave?
He wanted to reach Incheon in a day.
He was in a great hurry.
Bloody driver.
You're an Indian, right?
Yes.
You're about to contribute
to a noble cause.
What's the hurry to reach Incheon?
You've rented the whole bus.
I'm expecting some old friends.
If I don't make it, they'll feel bad.
If you need food or drinks,
I can arrange it for you.
You can get just about everything.
I need an army. Can you arrange that?
What?
An army with tanks,
grenades and rifles.
Such a strange man.
I've seen far too many horrors
in this war,
so I can smell trouble from a mile.
I decided not to follow him
for the same reason.
Was he a dangerous man, sir?
He vanished before reaching Incheon.
Fine.
There's nothing nearby,
so he must've gone to Incheon.
He must have gone to meet someone.
Must be an old friend. Who can he be?
We're not quite sure,
it was Bose outside of Incheon.
We have made that mistake before.
Sir, he's definitely Mr. Bose.
He has hoodwinked us countless times
and vanished without a trace.
That's his hallmark.
We need to think like Bose!
We need to find out where he's going
and get there first.
-That's the only way.
-Indeed.
An old friend.
All right, well, let's see.
Rahman's already in custody.
Ram Murthy has already stabbed him
in the back, so he's out.
Who'd he want to make contact with?
Especially, now that he seems to have
something on his mind.
It was Watanbe's name on the burnt pages.
He was close to Bose
among other Japanese soldiers.
Right. We'll get Figgs to track him down.
Find out if he is in Incheon.
Nakamura too.
Anderson sent Figgs and a contingent
of the British police to Japan
to apprehend INA officers,
Kinji Watanbe and Nakamura.
Hello.
The first thing they learnt
is that both of them got a phone call
at the same time.
The person who called Watanbe
and Nakamura was a man.
A man who spoke in Japanese.
But, his mother tongue was not Japanese.
Let's get to the point, Darbari Lal.
The point is that
he spoke Japanese that the meeting was
an underground celebration.
Underground!
What the devil does that mean?
Underground! He's talking about bunkers.
We have no idea how many bunkers
the bloody Japs built out here.
We don't need to know,
we just need to follow them
to know where they are going.
That's what I was saying.
What's shocking is that these people
were also headed to Incheon.
We got him.
We got Bose.
After all these years,
we've finally got Bose.
Well, that would mean
he's beginning to slip up.
He didn't even try to cover
his tracks this time.
That's what I find strange!
Don't you think he's deliberately
leading us to Incheon?
Like he wants us to go to Incheon.
You're giving him too much credit,
Darbari Lal.
He's alone, he's tired.
He's making mistakes!
No, sir. My mother used to say,
a tired or wounded wise man
is still wise, nonetheless.
And I'm telling you,
Mr. Bose is never alone.
Is your Darbari Lal in love
with Bose or what?
You tell him to shut up now.
We'll send Figgs to Incheon.
And just to be on the safe side,
keep an eye on anyone
Bose might get in touch with.
We've got it covered, sir.
Anyone Bose may try and contact
is under surveillance.
Excellent.
That'll be all!
Get me Figgs.
Emilie, I don't know whether
you believe in this or not.
But people say, Bose is alive.
They are not liking it, aren't they?
Maybe that's why,
I'm still being watched.
Watched?
By whom?
And since when is this going on?
Dr. Mathur, if you were
careful enough...
you would see that, probably,
you're being watched too.
Why?
Is Bose alive?
You see...
You can't spy on dead people.
How have you been dealing
with this all alone?
He trained me well.
Write to me in German.
Our British friends read
your letters before I read them.
It's been more than three years
since I saw you.
Do you not miss me?
I've sent you a picture of myself.
It's a Bengali dress called kurta.
Uncle, what did your friend say?
She writes that the sleeves
should be shorter.
Who wants your sleeves to be shorter?
It's understood.
She wants you to
extend your arms and...
She's obviously talking
about the kurta.
I want some bangles.
Pack a kilo of bangles for Subhash.
Stop joking and ward evil off him.
Subhash, whom are you sending
these bangles to?
She's the one who writes to him.
One needs a pen to write letters, right?
-Not bangles!
-They don't sell bangles in Vienna.
So, she has asked for them.
Even you aren't in Vienna
right now, are you?
Hasn't she asked for you?
Is she the one who looked after you
after your surgery?
Mr. Bose!
-Mr. Bose, come with me.
-What's wrong?
They are conducting meetings
without your knowledge.
-Please come with me.
-Okay.
Dear God...
The Congress party has its own
ideals and rules to follow.
And every party worker should
abide by those rules and regulations.
If a party worker disobeys these rules,
then the party won't tolerate
such behavior.
Subhash...
Nehru, I'm the president of the Congress.
We all have to follow the rules,
don't we?
You should have at least informed
me about the meeting.
Any association with
Hitler is just wrong.
The Congress is upset with
your behavior!
Did I speak of any association?
Nehru, we need a deadly weapon
to deal with the British.
And Hitler is that weapon.
Hitler?
Well, he believes Indians are inferiors
like the Jews and Africans!
Such a strange weapon you've chosen!
A weapon is only as good as the
character of its wielder.
Hitler is a murderer, Bose.
What about the British?
What would you call them?
They didn't kill anyone, did they?
For years, they slaughtered us
right in our homeland.
What's the difference between
the British and Hitler?
Bapu won't go with this
nor will the Congress.
I can't ever agree to this.
It will be only your decision.
Indians will fight World War Two
for the British.
Bapu made this decision on his own.
Did he ask us?
Did he ask Indians?
-Bapu believed...
-Did he ask the soldiers?
Bapu believes the British would agree to
our demands in return for our support.
To fight for the British
and to put our lives at stake
is that what you call
nonviolence, Nehru?
A piece of advice for you.
Ask Bapu to reason with the British
to win World War Two
with nonviolence.
Why just the British? Ask him to
teach Hitler about nonviolence.
Why is nonviolence only
applicable to Indians?
Nonviolence will never help you
win every battle.
Subhash...
Gandhiji and Nehru
refused to support Netaji.
But Bose wouldn't give up
so easily.
In 1939, he resigned from the Congress
and formed his own party,
All India Forward Bloc.
Hail Bose!
Brothers and sisters,
we have started the war for freedom
and we will continue our war
till we achieve complete freedom.
The faster we forget our personal issues
and come together to be a part
of this war,
the faster, we'll achieve freedom!
It's time to sacrifice yourself.
The war bugle might sound anytime.
The situation is conducive for us
right now.
We have to take advantage of what's
happening in the world right now.
We've been exploited for centuries
and we're struggling
to escape this crushing poverty.
We're struggling to provide
a decent meal for our population.
Freedom is the only surefire way
to rid ourselves of this malaise
which in turn hinges on
our national unity.
To be weak right now
is the greatest sin possible.
Slavery is the root of all problems!
It's about time when all of us
should break the shackles of slavery.
All of you must come together
and cry revolt in unison!
India won't be a slave anymore.
There is no power in the world
that can keep us enslaved!
Of course,
we must pay a price to achieve freedom.
All of you, I mean, all of you
must be prepared for this mission.
We were born in enslaved India,
but we shall live and die in free India!
Long live the revolution!
Hail Mr. Bose!
"This adroit voyager"
"for the love of his land"
"will head back home!"
"This adroit voyager...."
The police were here.
They came and left!
-Where are they now?
-In Incheon.
"will head back home!"
Okay, what about Mr. Bose?
Russia!
Where's Bose?
Dead!
[Stanley]This is ridiculous!
Bose played us.
How could we miss this?
Of course, he went to Russia.
Obviously Russia!
Why would he go to Incheon?
I think, we made a mistake again.
Everything happened right
in front of our eyes.
I tried to warn you earlier,
even if a wise man is tired or wounded,
he's wise, nonetheless.
He remains wise!
Mr. Bose has made a fool out of us.
It wasn't
for the first time though.
Four years ago, he used the same
trick and made a fool out of us.
Tired with Bose's relentless tactics,
the British
kept him under house arrest
and I was asked to man the door.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Let me carry that for you.
-No, it's okay. I'll do it.
-No, don't trouble yourself.
-Don't bother.
-It won't be a problem.
Very good! Come on.
[Subhash]Mother, I've made up my mind.
I'm going to retire.
You're thinking of retirement.
How about getting married?
Or starting a family?
Start my family, eh? In India?
You want me to raise kids
as slaves for the British?
Mr. Bose, you're not the only one
fighting for freedom.
There are so many people.
Gandhiji, Mr. Nehru.
Mr. Rajendra and they all are married,
by the way.
Who says only unmarried men
should fight for freedom?
The problem with you
is that you're always in a hurry.
We'll achieve freedom eventually.
But you want freedom right away.
Why? Mr. Bose, stop being childish.
From now on, I'll have only one meal.
Although, it'll take a while
to quit smoking. But...
This...
You've been abroad.
Didn't you find anyone?
[Darbari]Won't you eat this?
Fine, I am eating it.
[Darbari]These days, he is busy meditating.
He doesn't talk to anyone.
Now that doesn't make sense.
Why would Bose retire now?
Maybe you've finally managed
to break him down.
Darbari Lal, I want you
on the job 24 hours.
Sir, I know the house
like the back of my hand.
I'll be the first to know
if anything goes wrong.
Very good.
[Darbari]Can I take a banana?
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
This dhoti is worn while offering prayers.
Are your hands clean?
My hands are pure. Check yourself.
May I ask you something?
Sure, go ahead.
Why are you still unmarried?
I don't know what to say.
I blame Mr. Bose for it.
I'm too busy chasing Mr. Bose
to get married.
He doesn't stay put in one place.
He's a nuisance.
The day he mends his ways,
I swear, I'll get married.
I'm desperate to get married.
I don't know what's wrong with Subhash.
He feels utterly depressed.
Tell me something.
Is Mr. Bose planning something?
Did he tell you about it?
We can't ask him that now.
He's taken a vow of silence.
He doesn't talk to anyone.
-[Darbari]Sir.
-[Stanley]What?
Mr. Bose has taken a vow of silence.
Really?
Stanley, can we go one evening
without talking about Bose?
He's under house arrest
for God's sake.
Finally, I muzzled the rabid dog.
Make sure he never leaves that house.
Yes, sir.
[Darbari]Listen, clean my ears so thoroughly
that I'd be able to hear
Mr. Bose's heartbeat.
[Darbari]Be careful.
[Man]Mister, please turn your head
this way.
Or the oil will block
your ear canal.
"To be free. Be free."
"This is my destiny."
"I hold a machine gun."
"Beware Imperialists!"
-"Keep walking...
-Gun, Gun."
-"Don't turn...
-"Or you...
-Gun, gun!"
"Will burn..."
The entire family colluded
in helping Mr. Bose escape.
While I was having my ears cleaned,
his nephew Aurobindo
took Mr. Bose's place.
"...free. This is my destiny."
[Darbari]Mr. Bose, the guava is quite ripe.
Care for some?
I've left some guavas
for you outside, do take it.
I'll post the letter and be back.
[Darbari]The silence is deafening.
I can't believe Mr. Bose
has taken a vow of silence.
After all, his speeches roused the nation
not so long ago.
Nowadays, he neither speaks
nor does he meet anyone.
Is he into meditative
consciousness?
Should I break the door?
Well, I can smell cigarette smoke
and hear music from the lighter.
It assures me
that that everything's fine.
[Man]Bibhavati!
Yes, I'm coming.
-[Man]Bibhavati!
-In a minute.
This charade continued for ten days.
Mr. Bose wouldn't meet anyone,
but the cigarette smoke,
music from the lighter
and the constant flow of letters
assured me
that beast was in control!
But, Mr. Bose had
already reached Peshawar.
Put your gun down.
Your German friends have sent me.
-Subhash.
-Rahmat Khan.
Sir.
Royal Bengal Tiger has passed
through the checkpoint B.
Reaching checkpoint C in next two days.
Activate your group.
Thank you.
Every second face you see here
is a British spy.
In India, they call me Bhagat Singh Talvar
but here, just call me Rahmat Khan.
Rahmat, I want to get to Russia.
As soon as possible.
-Who's in Russia?
-No one.
So?
Russia will help us fight
against the British.
After all, Russia won its freedom
through a revolution.
But Gandhiji wants us to wait.
How long do we have to be patient?
So for the next hundred years,
or thousand years, if the British aren't
satisfied with nonviolence and patience,
then are we supposed to do
only protests?
Mr. Bose, we should leave.
Just keep walking straight and
don't look back. See you later.
Hello, officer.
[Darbari]Hey!
Where's Bose?
He's made all of us
look like fools, Stanley!
This is despicable!
Find him!
Ten days had passed till
we found out
that Mr. Bose had broken house arrest
and vanished into thin air.
[Darbari]Sir, I was manning the door.
I feel like slapping myself right now.
[Man]He ran away!
Just wait and watch.
The British didn't know how
to trace Mr. Bose.
But the British were certain
of one thing
that Bose hadn't gotten far away.
If he wanted to get out of India,
he had to cross the borders.
Passport, please!
Are you from India?
Once we're through this,
you'll be close to your destination.
Once you cross the Indian border,
that's like half the job done.
You'll run into a few
British officers at the border.
You will have to answer them
very carefully.
Mr. Bose, do you understand?
Why don't you say anything, Mr. Bose?
Passports, please.
Go on.
Passport, please!
Who's he?
He's my brother.
Cat got his tongue?
Let him speak for himself.
What is your name?
He can't speak, sir.
He lost his voice in an accident.
I'm taking him
to the tomb of Adasharif.
It's really unfortunate, brother.
All right.
Adasharif will make everything right.
-God willing!
Hold on a minute.
Will you leave them without checking?
What if he's lying?
Open your mouth and show me your tongue.
Oh no. All right, off you go.
Poor guy's got a twisted tongue.
No way he'll ever talk.
21st January, 1945.
Subhash Chandra Bose has fled the country
to Afghanistan.
We don't know what he looks like,
so we have a difficult task ahead of us.
Both, Mr. Bose and you have
a scheming mind.
Don't lose hope.
Mr. Bose doesn't know the local language.
How far can he go?
Mr. Bose.
I'm trying to get in touch with
the Russian Ambassador.
But it seems a bit difficult.
Had it been easy,
would I need your help?
Keep trying...
Police.
-[Man]Open the door.
-[Rahmat]Yes, I'm coming.
Yes, I'm coming.
-Peace be upon you.
Is everything fine?
Hold on. Who is this man?
He is my brother and
he's attending a wedding.
What's your name?
He can't speak.
Is everything all right?
It's all clear here.
Let's check the next motel.
Since he's your family member,
I must take good care of him.
You're one of us now.
No one can harm you till you are here.
I'll be seeing you again.
It's not a safe place to be.
Especially, when you're
wearing an expensive watch.
Goodbye.
Corrupt! Every single policeman
in the world.
You must meet the ambassador
at any cost. It's been long.
Mr. Bose, I'm trying my best.
I'm sure, I'll meet him today.
What if they won't let you
inside the Russian Embassy even this time?
I'll get hold of him outside.
Time's running out, Rahmat.
Listen.
Explain to him
that I must meet Stalin.
We won't be successful
without Russia's help.
I understand it very well, Mr. Bose.
You've said it many times. Shall we?
Rahmat.
You spoke to him?
He disagreed.
I think, the British have brainwashed him.
The Russian ambassador thinks
you're a British spy.
A British spy?
Where do they get their information?
Do I look like a spy?
Mr. Bose.
I think you have to leave this place.
There's nothing here.
If the British catch you,
everything will be ruined.
Now you have just one option.
Germany.
[Rahmat]The Italians have arranged
for your passport.
I hope Hitler agrees to meet you.
Mr. Bose...
You have kept the revolution alive.
It doesn't matter if you take help from
Russia or Germany.
While Mr. Bose was ready to travel
to Germany on his Italian passport
Stanley's obsession with Bose
refused to die down.
After all, Mr. Bose had vanished
right under their noses!
The British were bound to be dejected.
I'm sorry, it took me a while to come back.
I really thought
you're never going to come back.
I'm sorry, I couldn't write to you enough.
But, I've read all your letters,
several times.
Look at you, you didn't change!
I've lost a little bit of weight, I think.
-Or maybe, you've put on some.
-Some hair, for sure.
I've got something for you.
-What is that?
-Open it.
You didn't forget.
I never forget.
Subhash, I really don't think
this is a great move.
You know that Hitler is against
inter-racial marriages.
The British are already against you.
You might upset Hitler
with your marriage.
Just give it a thought.
Being slaves for the British
wasn't enough
that you want us to
be slaves for Hitler, too?
I'm getting married tomorrow
and you're coming.
[Speaking German]
Rassenschande.
A law imposed by Hitler
barred Germans from maintaining
any kind of relations with non-Germans.
[Speaking German]
This woman did not respect our rights!
She must be punished!
A non-German who marries a German!
Are you okay?
Subhash, I'm pretty scared though.
Don't be.
I'm right here.
I wish I could take you to India
with me.
Very soon.
Okay?
Come. Let's go.
Bose was the only man in Germany
who could have his way
without fearing anyone.
Bose and Emilie
flouted the Rassenschande law
and finally got married.
They had to pay a price
for their decision everyday.
Bose was not safe in Berlin
and yet his presence in Berlin
posed a great threat to
the British in India.
What is Bose up to?
-In Berlin?
-No.
In India.
Is he back in India?
Sir...
-I was about to tell you.
-What has he done now?
Come and you can hear for yourself.
I have a message for my fellow Indians.
Don't even think about volunteering
for the British Army.
They should leave the job
to the revolutionaries.
All these revolutionaries who are wearing
a British uniform,
but I'm sure
their heart bleeds for India.
When the day of freedom
finally dawns upon us,
the revolutionary should remember
and be ready to make the right choice.
Bloody hell!
He's preaching treason!
Our men are at the front line.
What if they are betrayed
by the Indians?
Azad Hind Radio.
Bose was speaking from Germany to Indians
and every Indian could hear
Bose's speech.
The British were petrified
when they heard Bose's speech.
The news reached Delhi.
Viceroy was trembling in fear.
In times of war, we must trust our troops.
The British officers depend on the
loyalty of these Indian soldiers.
Bose is inciting mutiny.
What are you doing about it?
We are working on it, Your Excellency.
Let me enlighten you.
You have failed miserably!
The British Secret Service
is taking over now.
Extend to them all the help you can.
Of course, Your Excellency!
Where is your younger, mute brother?
He came to attend a
close relative's wedding, right?
Peter Fleming.
The most proficient officer of
the British Secret Service
was now assigned to catch Bose.
You've been going about this
the wrong way.
Watch me.
Bhagat Singh Talvar!
We know you helped Bose
to cross to Germany.
Who are you talking about?
Don't lie!
Did you know that Hitler was going to
attack Russia?
Germans won't do that!
Seems like your information is outdated.
This is going to happen
and it's going to happen soon.
And if you want it to stop, help us!
Why me? I am no traitor!
The Germans have given you a transmitter
through which you provide
all information.
Help us stop the fascists!
This is your chance to do something
for what you believe in.
They trust you.
And they will believe
whatever you tell them.
Fleming was well aware
that Rahmat was loyal to Bose.
But Rahmat was more loyal
to the communist revolution.
Has Bose met Hitler?
Bose and Hitler were about to meet.
Hail Hitler!
[Emilie] Do not speak to him as an equal.
He's the leader, the Fhrer!
That means if you take any wrong step
it will lead to something really horrible!
Please think again, are you...
really sure what you're doing?
Emilie, I know what he's doing
is horrible.
[Subhash] But if he agrees to help us
against the Britishers,
I don't mind going on the wrong side.
[Subhash] We need him.
Hail Hitler.
Mr. Bose.
The Fhrer would see you now.
You should be careful of
what you say to him.
Are you ready?
I've had more than four months
to get ready.
Mr. Hitler.
So, Mr. Bose,
I have been very curious,
how did you know it wasn't me?
A fake Hitler has an image to maintain.
And a real one does not care.
The double seemed really offended
that I did not recognize him.
Thank you.
The British are right to worry about you.
How do you intend to
bring the empire down?
As all empires have been brought down
in history.
By an army.
Where do you intend to get this army?
You have it right here.
Give me the Indian prisoners of war
and I will build an army.
How will you take them
all the way to India?
My plan is to march across Russia
and free India from the British.
And why would they be willing
to do this now
when they have never thought of it,
until now?
Because until now,
they have never realized
they can!
Herr Bose, do you know what
Fhrer means in Hindi?
Yes, I do.
The Hindi word for Fhrer
is Neta.
And Hitler called you Netaji!
Except for these soldiers
who flatly refused to do so.
They believe the Germans to be their
enemy and consider you to be their spy.
So these British loyalists
take me to be a German spy.
Now let's see
if these loyalists can listen to a spy.
Go.
Go and tell Hitler
no matter what he tries,
he cannot break us.
No one will betray.
A lot of people have tried.
Mr. Bose, we are soldiers.
Not traitors.
What would that make
Mangal Pandey then?
He was also a soldier.
Or was he a traitor?
This is not our battle.
We are akin to weapons.
Just like a revolver.
A revolver has neither a mission
nor a goal.
It's used by the one who wields it.
What do you mean?
-Do you want us to fight for Hitler?
-Not at all!
I want all of you
to fight for yourself.
For your freedom.
If we have to bleed for someone,
then let's bleed for India.
Let's be martyrs for India
and not for the British!
I'm not here to ask for your help.
India is your country
just as it is mine.
I'm here to ask for India's freedom.
If this works, we'll have Bose.
We already have him.
Poor chap just doesn't know it yet.
Hail India, Mr. Bose,
Rahmat Khan here.
[Subhash] Hail India, Rahmat.
The British are feeling
the heat of your resistance.
What's going on there?
[Subhash] Rahmat, we've built
an army here.
[Subhash] We'll be reaching
India soon.
How come you found an army in Germany?
[Subhash] The British left them to die,
but now they're my soldiers.
[Subhash] The Indian POWs.
Mr. Bose...
This can pose quite the problem for us.
In 1928, on the streets of Calcutta,
Netaji marched with
2000 nominal soldiers.
Today he commanded an army.
Today, if Bose marches his army
into India...
we can't stop him.
And neither can Congress.
A person who seeks help from foreign
powers to attack India
is not an Indian, but a traitor.
If required,
I will be the person to
take the sword to Bose.
-Hail India!
-[Nehru] Hail India!
-[Crowd] Hail India!
According to Talvar,
soldiers from Northern Africa
have also joined Netaji...
-I mean...
-That's the name he goes by nowadays?
Netaji!
Attention!
"You rule the minds of the people."
"You are the dispenser
of India's destiny."
"Your name rouses the hearts of
Punjab, Sindh, Gujarat, Maratha,"
"Dravid, Orissa and Bengal."
"Your name echoes in the hills
of the Vindhyas and Himalayas,"
"and it mingles in the music
of the Ganga and the Yamuna."
"We praise you, always."
"You give us life, always."
"You give hope to everyone."
"You are the sun to the world"
"and bring fortune to the world."
"Victory to you!"
Hail India!
This battle has begun outside India
and soon it will be
fought inside India.
You have to fight for your freedom,
nobody gives it to you.
We'll have to shed blood for
this freedom struggle. Our blood.
The cost of our freedom
will be our blood.
India's freedom!
Our country's freedom!
Give me blood,
and I shall give you freedom.
Long live free India!
Move!
"Sure."
"He knew what he was gonna do
He did what he wanted to."
It was the year 1946. It had been
a year since Netaji had disappeared.
Netaji had sparked the mutiny
amid the Indian soldiers
and it was spreading like
a wildfire.
The mutiny that started with
66 ships and 10,000 sailors
now began to spread
all over the nation.
"...and theirs would blot.
A dance with futility!"
"Broken down to its utility,"
"Together, how can we be?"
"But our weakness is unity."
After 1945, no one saw Netaji.
Even if Emilie knew, she didn't share
the information with anyone.
Emilie...
-do you think Bose is...
-Dr. Mathur...
as I said, some people need to stay dead,
to stay alive.
Mr. Bose was never seen after that.
Whoever they saw
was he an imposter or real person?
The truth is still lost in the dark.
"Right, right, right."
"What I said is right."
"Yes, yes, yes."
"I did what I had to."
"I burnt in a fire of protest
I had to."
"I threw stones at the establishment
"I planted fear in the heart of my enemy
I had to - War!"
I've got a telegram from Bose.
"...the war cry from the people
I did right."
"Never listened to warning signs"
"Couldn't be a slave to the British"
"Never lost a fight.
History will be my story."
-"Bose!
-His actions faster than thought."
"Bose."
"They'd look for him where he was not."
"Incapable of being caught."
"Bose."
"His lines were sharp
and theirs would blot."
"Bose."
-He's alive.
-Who?
Bose.
It looks like he's hiding in Russia.
That's enough, I don't want to hear about
Bose anymore.
Done.
You want to talk about Bose? Now?
You do realize there is a mutiny
in the Navy.
Our own soldiers are turning against us.
The whole country's
up in arms, Stanley.
Exactly why we need to find Bose.
We are leaving this country.
We're finished with Bose.
-But, sir...
-It's enough!
Not another word, Stanley!
Bose is dead.
He died in a plane crash.
End of story.
In 1966,
Lal Bahadur Shashtri had to
attend the historic Tashkent Peace Accord
in Tashkent, Russia.
"Sure."
"He knew what he was gonna do
He did what he wanted to"
"They tried to blame him
and couldn't contain him before."
"He took the fight to the top of
the line through the door."
"He disappeared..."
Please book a trunk call to India.
"His actions faster than thought."
"They'd look for him where he was not."
"Incapable of being caught."
"His lines were sharp
and theirs would blot"
"A dance with futility"
"Broken down to its utility."
"Together, how can we be?"
"When our weakness is unity."
"It's difficult to..."
"It's difficult to understand Subhash."
-Hello.
-Sir, Darbari Lal here.
You were right.
Mr. Bose...
He is alive.
He's in Russia.
"Right, right, right.
What I said is right."
"Yes, yes, yes.
I did what I had to."
"I burnt in a fire of protest
I had to."
"I threw stones at the establishment
"I planted fear
in the heart of my enemy..."
After meeting the President of Pakistan,
Ayub Khan, in Tashkent
and signing a peace accord that ended
the Indo-Pakistan war
on the night of 11th January, 1966,
Lal Bahadur Shastri died
under mysterious circumstances.
"Bose!"
"His actions faster than thoughts."
Some stories don't really have an end.
Netaji's story has an end,
but it's difficult to accept it.
Netaji's story, whenever told
will force the listeners
to think hard
but the mystery behind
Netaji's death
will always remain a mystery.
"No paranoia of defeat."
"Only sublime strategies of war."
[Theme music playing]