Recently, Flying Beast
has filed a defamation legal case
of 2 crores against a journalist.
What is true and what is not.
Will discuss it today.
Let's know in this video.
The purpose of this
video is not to hate anyone,
only to put a researched
opinion in front of you.
And in the end I
will leave it to you,
what did you understand,
and what do you consider
to be wrong and right.
This video is just for education
and awareness, which is our mission
and we believe that
nothing will be hidden now.
All the things,
that I am sharing here, you
will find their public sources
through the link in the video description
and you can read them yourself.
Flying Beast has announced
on his Instagram handle,
that he has won a case.
Will analyze that case completely,
and together with the
Havan Controversy.
This tweet you are seeing,
was tweeted by Flying Beast
on its own Twitter handle.
and after that there
was a lot of trolling.
So was Flying
Beast right or wrong?
Whether his trolling
was right or wrong,
we will analyze it.
And together we will discuss
what's the responsibility of influencers,
journalists and brands.
Who should be guilty
in this whole matter
and who is not,
let's talk in this video.
Let's go.
Flying Beast is a person
who practices his culture
and talks about it loudly.
Someone has a face in their culture,
and feel proud about his culture,
and Flying Beasts do the same,
because their content is
family vlogging, real life vlogging,
which is visible in their
vlogs and tweets.
When Flying Beast does
this, Abhishek Bakshi,
a so-called journalist,
attacks Flying Beast,
and says that Abish
Mathew, who is a huge creator,
whose show is visited
by big celebrities.
[big celebrities]
How did this bring these people,
who do not know,
on which fruit their
daughter's name is.
Obviously here Abhishek was right
that there is a difference
between raspberry and Rashbhari.
It is not that
there is an English meaning
and its Hindi meaning is this.
It's not like this.  Both
are different fruits.
But...
But would you judge
someone's credentials by this?
Flying Beast is collaborating
with Abish Mathew here,
who has 1 million subscribers,
and Flying Beast has so many.
So, who has more advantage here,
maybe Abhishek
could not understand.
Maybe some people who
think they are intllectual,
and think that they are
creative. They think that,
understanding English
is very important.
He did not see how many amazing
stories Ritu and Gaurav shared,
on the naming of their daughter.
I guess he missed it.
Ritu and I were expecting
to download this app.
So, we downloaded this app.
Someone suggested, my sister suggested!
So, every week , it used to
show the progress of baby.
Now the baby is of almost puppy size,
grown to the size of this,
I think, during 8 weeks or nine weeks,
Now your baby's size is of raspberry.
That's she was pleased to know
that my baby is like a raspberry.
Like a raspberry.
And then Rashhnhari...Rashbhari..
-We started calling her.
Which was a very good highlight of
this interview of this entire segment.
These stories are not PR driven,
they are real.
Abhishek could not understand this,
but his attack continued,
and he has made four tweets.
He spoke dirty words
about Flying Beast,
and attacked Brands.
He started attacking the
livelihood of flying beast.
Abhishek If you are not
getting the brands yourself
then where is it right to make such
attacks on someone else's livelihood?
Is this right or wrong, please
tell me in the comments.
All who are watching this video,
before you think, that
videos is going to be biased,
Watch my video which was
about Flying Beast's birthday.
You will understand that I'm not a fan,
I'm not a fellow creator,
who's just trying to say goody
things about one of the creator,
I feel it was a huge blunder,
whether it was wrong or
right to arrest. I don't know!
But when you have
booked an entire metro,
and you have so
many million followers,
even after booking the entire
metro, you cannot handle them.
So it was blunder in a way.
Nobody can take that away!
Everything on this
channel is unbiased,
depending upon who's
right and who's wrong,
all that particular incident
on that particular day,
on that particular event.
And to analyze this event, many
things will have to be analyzed
and that is what we are doing.
Keep watching!
The fourth tweet of Abhishek in
this is very shameful.
In this, he is telling that the
flying beast is mysogynist.
Do you understand misogynist?
One who discriminates
against another gender.
Many more words have come from Misogynist,
like Patriarchy and many other words.
In this, he highlights an incident
in which Ritu is in labor pain
nd she touches Gaurav's feet.
He has shown a snapshot.
But I would love to show
you the full energy of that vlog,
See!
Now, Ritu is actually in labour.
But what she is saying
- I didn't touch feet.
So, I'm going to do that.
She's touching feet.
I don't know if those educated
and intellectual people know,
touching feet is not just about
mysogyny and
somebody being superior or inferior.
It's about transmitting energies.
When a woman is in labor
pain, she needs energy.
So touching her feet
means taking energy.
I think this is the thing which is in
our old culture that people do not know.
That's why people create
judgments and assumptions
and attack people in such a way that
why are you
collaborating with them.
Shameful!
I would like to ask,
if a man is practicing his religion,
practicing his faith and his
culture, what's wrong in that?
Could that be a basis whether those
brands collaborate with him or not?
Absurd!
Let's go forward.
Before we talk about Shephali's article,
on whom there is a defamation
case of full two crores.
Before analyzing that article,
I want to talk about
the Havan controversy,
which is related to this article because this
article starts from tweets related to havan.
tweets related to havan.
Let's talk a little bit
about this controversy.
I didn't give my take at that
time but I want to give now.
It's very important.
Gaurav tweets on 1st May that there
is 'house warming ceremony' in our house
which he writes as planet,
which is okay, people trolled him on this
which is again...
He says that we're doing
'house warming ceremony'.
Hinduism is a science based way of life.
On 3rd Dec. 1984,
two families remained
unaffected from Bhopal gas leak,
and fourth is that,
Havan which is a natural
antidote to polllution.
He said these four things.
Many people trolled him on this.
I would like to say
something about this.
Let us first talk abou
Bhopal gas tragedy,
More than 3000 people died in it.
More than 500000
people were injured.
And after this accident,
12000 people died.
And we are seeing the
after effects of that thing till today.
And it was because
that gas was too toxic.
One of the most toxic gases in the world.
Methyl isocyanate.
That's a very dangerous compund.
Due to this, there is maximum
penetration in your lungs,
then there can be choking there.
And because of this
many people also died.
And...
let's analyze this tweet a bit.
He said, Hinduism is
a science based of life.
I thought religion is a set
of believes and practices.
For ex, just like there are
mantras in our Hindu religion
I also chant mantras,
because I feel that the structure and
combination of some mantras is such that
it produces certain
vibrations and sounds.
And this sound very much
channelizes your state of mind,
in the right direction and
for which the mantra is,
for which that sound
is being produced.
Right?
And if that's the case,
it's a science, right?
Because science...science is what?
If you observe such things, if
you chant mantras for 1 hour
and then see how you are feeling,
and how is the energy around you.
If you observe and see some
difference, that's a science.
Science is all about that.
You take a hypothesis and if you
collect dataabout it and observe it,
that gives you the result.
So...
I'm okay with Gaurav's tweets about this,
that Hinduism is
a science based of life.
There're many things about
Hinduism, infact every religion.
If you understand it properly,
it is very scientific.
But people assume
as I have already said.
That's the problem.
Then the third thing that Gaurav said,
is that he told about an incident.
He told that the two families
were unaffected that day.
Infact he was referring to the
article which was published in,
English Daily in 1985.
According to that article,
there are two families
in which one is Khuswaha family
and the other is Prajapati family.
Those both families remained unaffected.
You read this entire article,
link is in the description.
You can read this complete
article and it has complete details.
But that article...
We can't research on this.
Because there are so many
things in it that are missing.
There may be some other
reasons that that family survived,
sometimes there are
casual relationships too.
Now coming to the fourth
statement of Flying Beast.
He said, they performed
regular Agnihotra havan,
which is a natural antidote to pollution,
kind of leading to this thing that
that perhaps they were saved only
by performing Agnihotra Havan,
which is written in this article.
It is not as if Flying
Beast himself is telling.
If we talk about this thing,
whether this is a natural
antidote to pollution or not,
Many people trolled Flying Beast.
Lots of intellectual people
and educated people.
They were blabbering
without doing enough research,
and gathering facts.
Dhruv Rathi asked which gases
are they, which compound are they?
Is it sulphur oxide
or nitrogen oxide?
Which oxide is that which gets reduced.
Akash Banerjee even spoke that
it was from WhatsApp University.
Abhishek Bakshi
came back and said,
And replied something
similar on the tweet.
I would like to say
that yes, I believe that
Methyl isocyanate gas,
is a flammable gas,
It interacts when it goes
into the atmosphere.
It changes its form.
And its effect is more on
the people living on the ground.
because there is
more density there.
But can you get relief if you are
performing Havan somewhere?
I don't know.
But guys, based on my research,
all the intellectual people,
all the big creators
who're watching this video,
I want to share a
research with them.
It is on Research Gate.
I am giving its link for
you to read yourself.
In that lab research
it is clearly written,
that when the Havan
material that is on your screen,
when put in a controlled environment,
it was seen that sulfur
oxide and nitrogen oxide
Respirable Suspended Particulate
Matter were reduced by 60%.
And these different
quantities are in front of you.
You can check those.
And you can read the complete research.
Link is in the description.
Sulfur oxide and nitrogen
oxide are reduced by 50–60%,
says that research,
by doing havan.
If you rubbish any faith,
any culture, it is wrong.
And if Gaurav is referring
to something and saying
it has happened,
should he be trolled?
And should it be accused that
he is spreading propaganda?
I think this is wrong.
And here comes the
responsibility of the journalist.
Is this personal hatred
or is it their profession?
It is very important
to understand this
Now let's talk about this article
on which this case has run,
on the basis of which Ritu and Gaurav,
has filed a defamation case of two crores.
Let us analyze
what that article says.
Shefali refers to the incident of that
havan at the very beginning of this article
and says how Gaurav
was very insensitive,
for all those whose lives were lost
people in that tragedy.
He did not do research
or maybe he was in haste,
or was using Abhishek for facts,
whose history is telling that
that he has been a hater
of a particular ideology.
All these tweets tell.
If you refer to a person who is
associated with the government
vs some creator who is practicing his
culture,
and who does not
differentiate. I think this is wrong.
But Abhishek was not able
to differentiate.
He felt that Gaurav is the
part of a propaganda machine,
and according to me he gave
all these facts to Shefali in haste.
And the facts which
he has given to Shefali,
is just a small sample.
Let's talk about this article
and what was the problem in it.
Shephali says that Gaurav
does child abuse.
And the incident that she has
highlighted, imagine what it could be.
It is that they are
piercing in her ears.
The girl is saying that do not do vlogging,
then he is telling her why not.
This is child abuse.
She drops a phone
from a very high building,
and her mother is scolding her,
so it is child abuse.
Shefali says that she has told
all this by a child psychologist,
Joy Santosh, which I
could not find anywhere.
But I would like to ask
whether it is child abuse or not.
How can you tell
from this reference?
You are targeting all the brands that
work with Flying Beast and Ritu Rathee.
based on your own
assumptions and prejudice.
And it is clear that
you do less research.
What is child abuse and what is not.
I want to understand that
you are saying all this on
the basis of Joy Santosh,
which I am not getting anywhere.
You are hunting brands and
asking them for a statement
that why are you
collaborating with them?
As if that you're not liking it.
You are not getting the deals,
and these people are getting it.
There are many such
creators all over the world,
who do very strange
and big things,
in fact there are many celebrities
who sell cancer.
You go to those celebrities
who promote such brands.
You go to a creator who
has a great track record,
who, even when in the fitness industry,
used to talk about facts.
While there are many people,
who make and have been
making very irresponsible videos.
It is a big deal that those people get
ranking in the big magazines of our country.
It is a big deal.
You fall behind because
of one or two references.
Is this right or wrong,
I would like to ask
you this question,
you guys tell me in the comments.
Shefali says that some
people are saying that
they will not even use brands,
which are promoted by them.
And Shefali quotes a gossip handle
of a gossip community that it is posting.
This gossip post of
this gossip community,
is it a good sample to tell
that people are not
wanting to use this product
you tell me in this comment box.
Or else it should be judged by that
what is the feature of the
product which is promoted by him.
How genuine is that product,
what are the reviews
of that product,
what is the actual experience
when you use that product.
I would like to understand
this from Shefali,
whether she has done
this research or not.
You must have seen that
I do very little advertising
of products on this channel,
it is because I am not satisfied
with that product.
And if that was the case,
maybe it would make sense.
Shefali highlights another issue,
where Flying Beast is stating that
about risks of live in relationship
and what can be its consequences,
so, on that basis,
that your opinion doesn't
match with her opinion,
so he shouldn't be working with brands?
Brands shoulsn't work with him.
Is it right?
He is just alerting people that
he has seen and heard this.
Such things come in the daily news
and if he is giving his opinion
on it then what is wrong in it.
He is saying that this is data.
Have a look on the data.
I am not saying that live in
relationship is right or wrong.
Infact, I myself say that first
stay with each other and see.
But if you have
data in front of you,
and you are citing only that
data have some problems,
then because of this brands
should not work with the creators,
how far is it right or wrong, I
leave upto you. Please tell.
And I would like to ask that
Shefali says in the same article
that all this is the fault of
the brands not creators.
There are brands in the title,
and only Flying Beast
is being talked about. Why?
Shephali very smartly
twists the article,
This article is not
for the Flying Beast,
even though I am talking about the
Flying Beast throughout the article.
This article is not for
Flying Beast, it is for brands.
What is Brand's Responsibility?
I would like to ask you,
what is the
Responsibility of brands.
Brands are commercial,
they only see profit
and use creators.
They know that
creators have real reach,
their loyalty is direct connection.
My audience has a connection with me.
I've connection with the
people who are commenting below.
When they listen to me, they DMs me
that brother, you speak
on this. You are our hope
and I feel responsible.
I've such connection with you guys.
These journalists like Shefali
will not be able to understand this,
or generalists like
Abhishek will not understand,
what is your connection with me.
how I make videos on your demand
and on my demand you do
campaigns with me on Twitter.
by devouting your precious time on my ask.
Such journalists
will not understand this.
And I am not at all
satisfied here with Shephali,
that it is only the
responsibility of the brands,
I think it is the responsibility of the
influencer to choose right product.
It is the responsibility of the journalist,
to write the article with full
research and with no hatred.
And the biggest responsibility here is
not that of influencers and journalists,
but your responsibility
here is that
if someone is selling pan masala
in the name of ad mouth freshener,
then please condemn them.
I think it is clear that there are
many problems in this article.
I think that is the reason,
I am not saying that Flying Beast
and Ritu Rathi are right in everything,
They both also make mistakes.
There is no human who
doesn't make mistakes.
Man is a mannequin of mistakes,
I also make many mistakes,
and it is very important to
acknowledge my mistakes.
Insinuating that performing Havan
is a political propaganda,
that's wrong.
Talking about one or two things
about someone that you think is wrong,
saying on the basis that no one
should work with him,
that's wrong.
You are insinuating on a post
from someone of any gossip group,
and when you are
trolled on your article
then it becomes hatred,
how?
Isn't this hypocrisy?
Do you fall behind such a creator,
who till date has not gone ahead
on the basis of controversies,
and has gone ahead on
the basis of his content,
vs you do not speak anything
to people who are selling cancer,
if this is not hypocrisy then what else?
If someone disagrees with you,
should it be the result that you
start attacking his/her livelihood.
And here you see the pattern,
that the person who is
supplying you the content,
is tweeting this again and again,
these tweets are from
a year ago, imagine.
A guy watches a movie
and promotes it, attack on him.
A man says that the vaccine
should be taken, attack on him.
You guys tell me
whether it's right or wrong.
And you think that
Intellectuals are right,
and do not mislead you,
you guys watch this video,
its link is in the description and
you will also see in the I button.
I will say that if you like this video
then share it in your community,
don't forget to like and
comment on this video,
and share your
opinion in this thread.
We have two new communities
on Facebook and Telegram,
join them too,
I am sharing their links.
Because I think we should
be present on all platforms,
if we really need change to happen.
Because you're watching
Peepoye, I'm Akassh.
And now...
nothing will hide.