Love makes a heart
Love breaks a heart
Erase me, or embrace me
I have chosen you
Dyed in your myriad colours
I belong to you
Love cannot be measured or hidden
I've left the world for you
I cannot stay away
when I hear you call
Lost in you, the world is lost
to me
I cannot stay away
when I hear you call
Lost in you, the world is now lost
to me
I've left the world for you
My heart is yours
I am all yours
I am lost in you
I've left the world for you
My heart is yours
I am all yours
I am lost in you
Love makes a heart
Love breaks a heart
Make me laugh or cry
I have chosen you
The world tells us love is a mistake
But my heart consents
I see God's light glow in you
I fill with pride knowing you're mine
I cannot stay away
when I hear you call
Lost in you, the world is lost
to me
I cannot stay away
when I hear you call
Lost in you, the world is lost
to me
Love is like a dream
My love has no bounds
I could kiss the words you speak,
soft as Urdu verse
Love is like a dream
My love has no bounds
I could kiss the words you speak,
soft as Urdu verse
I've left the world for you
My heart is yours
I am all yours now
I am lost in you