Hello, sir.
- Here you are.
- Yes, sir.
- How are you?
- Fine.
I was waiting for you.
Please, come.
Nandini, this is Mr Bakshi,
your teacher.
- Sir, please come.
- Yes.
He will be teaching you.
Hello.
'Wow, she's beautiful!'
Nandini is all yours.
Don't trouble him.
Study diligently.
'I'll handle Aakash later.'
'Let me devour
this pretty lady first.'
I looked for you all over
and here you are taking a stroll.
I have great news.
Aakash aims to educate Nandini.
He has asked her to study
and has hired a teacher.
How is that great news, shameless?
- But...
- Shut up.
My only solace was that she was
way more uneducated than me.
But Aakash wants to
rob me of that joy.
You...
Let me finish.
You're always aggressive.
The teacher is here,
but he has ill intentions.
Kamya quit playing games.
Tell me what he aims to do.
Bravo!
Let's start.
'Grandpa,
you always wanted me to get educated.'
'English Hero is fulfilling your dream.'
'Bless me, so I won't let him down.'
Why are you sitting there?
Sit here.
Let's study on the bed.
Teacher, where do we start?
Let's start from here.
What are you doing?
I mean, your mind.
That's it.
Use your mind.
Let's do this.
Look, M...
M for monkey.
Teacher, you stink of alcohol.
That's not alcohol,
but a potion to boost my brain.
- Want some?
- No, thank you.
Go on.
Write.
Let me show you.
Have you no shame?
What are you doing?
I'll tell my family.
Stop, listen to me.
Yes, I'm worried if
Nandini creates mischief.
She's restless and childish.
English Hero,
I won't study with that man.
Listen to me, he...
And your drama has begun!
- Come.
- No, heed me...
Quiet!
You promised you'd study.
- You did, right?
- Yes but...
I won't hear anything.
I won't go.
Why won't you?
You promised you'd study.
- Yes but...
- It's decided then.
Stay quiet.
- Come in.
- No, I won't...
No, listen to me...
- Quiet.
- Sir...
Sir, I'm so sorry about this.
- She had...
- You don't understand.
Quiet.
Stay quiet.
Sir, just ignore her.
Be strict.
Don't do this.
I'm not pretending.
- Listen to me.
- Shut up.
I said, quiet.
I am talking.
Sir, don't let her out until
she finishes.
Don't do that.
Listen to me.
Don't leave me.
English Hero!
English Hero, help me.
Don't leave me.
Open the door.
English Hero, no...
No... English Hero!
- Just give up.
- Leave me.
Your husband left you with me.
English Hero!
Don't you dare touch me!
You don't know me.
You'll pay for this.
Did you push me?
Let's see who saves you.
English Hero!
Help me.
Nobody will save you.
Let go.
English Hero!
Leave me.
English Hero, help!
- Shut up.
- Let go.
- No...
- Quiet.
Help!
'God, my honour is at stake.'
'Send English Hero!'
'Save me.'
How dare you touch Nandini?
How dare you?
Speak up.
He's not worthy of a teacher.
I can't forgive him
for misbehaving with you.
Nandini, avenge your tears.
Thrash him so bad that he'll
never dare to hurt another woman.
Hit him, Nandini.
[Sanskrit chants]
He forced himself on me.
He tried to rape me.
I'm sorry, Nandini.
I am such a fool
to have shut the door.
I promise, Nandini,
I won't let anyone harm you
ever again.
I promise.
'I better shoot Aakash Bharadwaj
and leave.'
Your game is up.
English Hero!
English Hero, get up.
Stop!
I won't spare you alive.
How dare you shoot him?
I won't spare you.
I will kill you.
[Sanskrit chants]
I won't spare you.
I made a mistake.
Forgive me.
You did make a mistake.
Tell me who sent you here.
Answer me or I'll kill you.
I'll tell you.
It was some Bharadwaj.
Someone from your family.
Please, spare me.
Nandini!
No!
He tried to...
kill my husband.
- I will kill you.
- I insist.
Stop.
English Hero!
Uday, Grandma, come quick.
- English Hero!
- Aakash!
Son!
- Aakash.
- Please, call the doctor.
He's bleeding.
- English Hero!
- Aakash.
Aakash, get up.
What happened?
Aakash...
You'll be fine.
Open your eyes.
English Hero!
Hello.
Grandmother, Aakash...
What happened to Aakash?
Tell me, Uday.
Somebody barged into the house
and shot him.
Please, come home.
I'm on my way.
English Hero, open your eyes.
Nothing to worry.
The bullet grazed his shoulder.
Let him get proper rest
so he can recover.
- Son...
- You needn't worry.
I will serve him well.
I'll take care of his needs.
Get out of here.
I beg you, wicked girl.
Just leave.
No trouble?
You're the cause of trouble.
Aakash can't bear you near him.
And you want to take care of him?
Uday will be with Aakash.
No! I have all the right to tend to him.
Being his wife,
I will do my duty.
I will tend to him.
Wife?
What do you mean?
What do you mean by his wife?
Wearing a 'Mangal Sutra'
means nothing.
Aakash doesn't take you as his wife.
Heard that?
Get going now.
- But Grandma...
- Stop.
Need I speak in English?
We don't need you around.
Spare us and get going.
You won't relent.
You won't?
Leave.
Get out of here.
Hey!
What's going on?
Can't you see?
We're helping your grandson.
Really?
Look at her, Kamya.
She's questioning me?
Sumitra, you don't need your family.
I am a fool
to come running all the time.
Come, Kamya.
Move.
Aakash!
How did this happen?
Grandma...
'No, Nandu,
don't say anything.'
'Let me first find out
why Aunt Kamya did this.'
'Then I'll tell others.'
I don't know.
I'll get turmeric milk for him.
First, we found a gun in the house.
Now...
Aakash got shot.
Who is my grandson's enemy?
Lord Ram,
keep Aakash safe.
Village girl, you want to kill me?
No, I'm not proving anything.
I'm here to tell you
so you can tell your shooter,
Nandu has his gun.
I challenge him to come get it.
What rubbish?
Are you implying I know that goon?
Are you casting doubts on me?
No, I know for sure
you know the goon.
Why do you want to
kill my husband?
He's like a son to you.
You raised him.
You are his aunt.
Then why kill him?
How dare you question me?
Don't talk too much
or I'll slit your tongue.
You don't know me.
I am Kamya.
And Kamya doesn't stay quiet.
Out of my way.
I don't want Kamya to stay quiet.
She should blurt out
why she wanted to kill my husband.
I promise, by tomorrow
morning, I will make you confess
why you tried to kill my husband?