Subscribe to technical guruji channel
and press bell icon to see more technical videos
Friends today
i have a special box
packed with ribbon by google
so lets unbox this and see
whats inside . And say together Ok Google
my self Gauruv
You are visiting Technical Guruji
So lets begain
So friends here comes our special box from Google
Great packing with ribbon oh its awersome
Dosen't know whats inside but we can see the Google Pixel 2 Xl upside
So by not wasting time lets cut this ribbon .
Awesome ribbon inside a ribbon great
So this is Pixel 2 Xl so everybody knows about it so ill not waste time on it
and lets talk about this huge box
Ummh lets see whats inside
Ok so here is
Gaurav Chaudhary great a special card
Here is written say hellow to your
New Google home
Here they have wrote good points about google home
Here comes this inside
Oh it was that childhood game which was
played like this by flipping
By folding like this and ill transform like this two fingers here
and two fingers of other hand in this one
Yeah 1234 something like this
in side this there are some fun commands about google home
and
main message is
make google do it so google can solve any quarie
from your whole life
so lets see other things inside
So its a Philips
U smart bulb
which can be controlled by google home
Aside that we have
Its a bridge to connect
this Bulb by this you can connect multiple bulb
and other USB
And inside this here comes the
main content
Which is this
Google home and here
cut its ribbon also
lets se what we will got?
Ok
okkk and OK so friends here
we have
goggle homes main box here are some
details about it like what it can do? how to use it?
Which apps were compatible for this
Here is written Mighty helpful and written so interesting features about it
on side there are some interesting commands
List is too long only few were written here
So lets remove this
tape
its price in India is RS.9999
Upper flap was removed
This is the main box packaging was too interesting
slide cuts at side
And a pull tab at frount
here's the Google Home
it is the standard variant also its Max and Mini versions of this is available in market
So this is Google home so aside this
we have
here is nothing its only covering
here comes some basic
paper work which tell us Getting started guide is here
and just start by saying ok google guide inside this again comes
So many commands which we can take in use
aside this we have waranty and safety information
along with this here is charger
so here is its charger
Indian pin charger with flat type cable
here is a round proprietary pin
so this is its charger there is nothing more inside the box
So lets talk about this thing which is
Google home
basically it was a smart speaker in which there was a inbuilt
Google assistant
just connect it by your networy
and place it anywhere in your home and shout OK Google
and ask whatever your question is
and it will answer you by its voice
and voice will came from here it has speakers below
and other than this here are some smart microphones
and this part is made up of some fabric
and you can purchase it in other colours
according to your furniture
it will lock magnetically
if ill talk about buttons so here is a mute button
when you dosent want that google hear your voice just click on this
there are some microphones also one here some at upside
on this area some lights also comes
and it was also a touch pad to control volume etc.
and here is area for charger
basically it was not a charger it was a adapter
cause you have to plug in it all the time for that here is a socket
so this is all about physical features of google home , lets set it
for that i have to download google home app in my mobile
and then we will do some fun questions with google home
To get started
Install the google home app on your phone or tablet
app was downloaded just click on setup
lets say yes to this
as im a user of assistant so automatically system of Hey google and Ok googl
came automatically and it was setting up
and it was doing all process by its own and i like the light button which was on upside of google home
cause all dots are multicolored and they keep rounding
and from here i can set volume
it was maximun
and
now it came at lowest point so it was a touchpad for volume
(Google home sound)
Hi! I’m your google assistant here to help
so here is the list of commands for different things
which we can use and the list is too
long that you just question
and you will got answer approximately
Ok Google!
How’s the weather
Great
dont know is answer was correct or wrong hope it was correct
if its listening properly
so this is goggle home a very interesting product
lets test it more
just talk to it day and night
aside fun you can also do serious work
you can shout or speak loudly
or can talk in low pitch you will always got your answer
so this is Google home
Thankyou google team for giving google home
for Philips smart bulb which i uses commanly
and for Pixel 2 XL
and check it more hope you like that
Great
it was too good
just do question and answers
and make all of your work done by Google home cause Make Google do it
friends enough for this video
thanks for watching if you have any suggestion so please comment down below
if haven't like and share this video
so now like share and must subscribe channel
cause i come with these type of amazing videos for you regularly
enough for today guys Jaihind and Vandemateram