This is my old Feastables chocolate bar.
And as you know, it tastes
better than a Hershey's bar.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
Jimmy, why are you in engulfing
your old Feastables bar in flames?
Well,
it all started about one year ago.
I was in a Feastables
business meeting,
and I realized tasting better
than Hershey's wasn't so special.
Doesn't everything
taste better than Hershey's?
Like, literally, doesn't anything
on the planet taste
better than a Hershey's bar?
- Yeah.
- I think so.
None of you felt the need to tell me this?
If everything tastes better than
Hershey's, what makes us special?
Yeah, well, the answer is nothing.
And to be honest,
myself and my entire company
weren't exactly fans of that harsh truth.
So I set out to do something better.
And what's better than being better
than Hershey's?
Am I fired?
Well, how about being better
than everyone?
The best on Earth.
And from that day forward,
we worked tireless.
Like I'm talking barely even sleeping.
I travelled from country to country,
chocolate factory
to chocolate factory.
Tried out thousands of formulas.
Which eventually led us to this.
The best tasting
chocolate ever made by mankind,
also known
as our brand new Feastables bar.
This is the best tasting
chocolate on Earth.
Good job, boys.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
How do we know that's
the best tasting chocolate in the world?
Why did he say that?
You're fired.
Leave.
I was just going to say
that we do a blind taste test.
Wait a minute.
We should prove it
in a blind taste test format.
That's genius.
You're rehired.
So I set up a random warehouse,
where I'm going to invite
hundreds of strangers
to do a blind taste test
of our brand new chocolate.
All four of these pieces of chocolate
have no branding,
and there's no labels distinguishing
anything between them.
The only thing
they are voting on is taste.
So now it's time to see
how our new chocolate formula
holds up to three
of the top European chocolates.
I like the first one the best.
Of course she picked Feastables.
- I'm going to go with the first one.
- Yep.
It has a really nice bite to it
and it's a little bit
richer than the other ones.
I'm not even surprised
by what she's saying.
- Another one.
- I like that a lot, it's really good.
I would eat that every day.
That is what
an intelligent man looks like.
It's a weird taste
I haven't tasted before.
It reminds me of like...
It's not Hershey's.
Hershey's is not that good.
Better than Hershey's. Spot on.
This might bankrupt Hershey's.
That chocolate. I'm pretty sure.
Another one.
Back to back, back to back.
To be honest, we just keep winning.
It's boring.
And the new bars come in seven flavours.
- Milk Chocolate.
- Thank you.
- Milk Crunch.
- Yes, please.
Almond.
Peanut Butter.
It used to be called Deez Nuts,
but you know...
- Peanut Butter Crunch.
- That one.
- Dark Chocolate.
- Mine.
And Dark Chocolate Sea Salt.
Thank you.
The new bars are available
nationwide in every single Walmart.
Go give them a try.
We've genuinely
put a ton of effort into these.
And if you spend your money on Feastables,
I really want you to enjoy it.
And starting February 17th,
for 30 days straight,
we're going to be giving away $10,000
to a lucky customer who scans the QR code
on the back of any new Feastables bar.
So go give the new bars a try.
You might win ten grand.
And I can't wait
to see what all of you think.
GO TRY A NEW FEASTABLES BAR!
YOU COULD WIN $10,000!