Hi!
If you want
Valentine's to be
Vanilla-ntine's
here's
the simplest thing
you can make for
Valentine's Day!
It's gonna be
loved by all!
So,
just a short
thing
here it is!
Take scoops
of vanilla ice-cream.
Put a
little bit of
red
color.
You can put
strawberry syrup
whichever syrup you like.
This is one color.
I prefer
a light
pink.
It's supposed to mix with the white
and give you a light pink color.
Okay..
You can take
this thread.
aur ye
craft store
ya
kisi bhi
a...
Ekdum simple sa
bas ice-cream
aur sprite ko
combine kar ke
ye..
Iske sath
aap
ek
chhota sa
token of love
de sakte ho!
Ye ek chhota
sa card hai!
It's written
Happy
Vanilla-ntine's
Day!
Isme
sara
pink color hai
basically.
Red
hai
but
background pink hai
taki
bohot red
overpowering
na lage
aur
pink hai
cute lagta hai.
If you want
a sign
from the universe
let this day be that!
It's very cute
expression
If you like this
you can contact me
on Instagram
Comment down
here
on YouTube.
Ispe..aap
Facebook pe bhi page hai
so
wahan pe bhi aap
message kar sakte ho!
Just let me know
aapko ye card chahiye!
Chhota sa amount
hai bas
Agar aap iss
tarah ke cards
aap market mein dekhoge
toh
bohot hefty price
hoti hai unki.