"How much money did you pay there?"
“I gave 50,000 rupees, Sir ” “50,000 rupees!” "Yes Sir"
"Rahul Manan is only concerned about his money, okay,
I have understood this after purchasing his course"
"What happened, I watched the entire course till the end, and everything is implemented from A to Z, still failed"
"When I went to watch his course, the comment section there was also filled with abuses"
There was no place left, Weather it's YouTube, Google, Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, Comments
Where people are not feeling cheated by buying this course
That we paid this money
and there is no value in that course
Earlier too, there have been complaints
about these fake gurus
That they sell courses in the name of money making.
Amit Parekh, Rahul Manan, Dev Gadhvi and now Vivek Bindra
Where Sandeep Maheshwari ji's video, people complained that they were sold a course and there was no value in it
The amazing thing is that,
this is spread across the world
But in India, it is the highest
You know, the net worth of e-learning and online courses was 190 billion dollars in 2018
And now it is estimated that by 2029
it will be 319 billion dollars.
Amazing thing is that, 32% of the websites
on Google are selling only online courses.
Every sixth-seventh video on YouTube
is promoting only make money online courses.
amazing thing is that in India, People are becoming rich by telling them how to become rich.
Are these the courses of money making gurus
Or 10 day MBA,
courses to make you a businessman?
Is this course fake?
Is it a lie?
No, this is not fake or lie
But this is a Generic course.
You are getting the same knowledge, the same knowledge or sometimes even better, for free on the internet on YouTube
Without telling you this,
they are giving it to you in the name of the course.
Then how does a person with normal IQ buy this course?
How does one get stuck?
How they manipulate?
The most amazing thing comes in this,
similar to what astrologers
First one is the Thirst Trap
Which means that a person is already hungry
to become rich,
They target a common problem of humans
and trigger it a little
Like, Let's say you're stuck in a 9 to 5 job
But you can't buy a car
"Being in a Job, I'm sure It's Going to Be Very Hard for You to Make a Lot of Money, Which Can Help You to Drive the Car Like This"
Or you want to earn money sitting,
there is no need to work
Or you want to become rich like me
Because Gen Z feels that one day they will definitely become rich
Or the biggest Amazing thing,
that they say that I was very poor, I had nothing
Now I have lakhs of rupees
"Meaning, the financial conditions of the house were very bad to spend, and as you can see now, 12 Pro Max is kept"
Hearing this, anyone thinks, man,
he was poor and became so rich
Everyone wants to become rich, and from here
And from here that small holding awakens in their mind
Where little by little they start taking interest in it.
And Seconds, here they trap,
Booby Trap
Which they show as show of life style
Here they show that I have this car, this is a sports car, I keep roaming around, I have a bungalow
"This live, traveling the world, I am in Dubai right now, living in the five stars, seven stars
They also show a fake account that I have so much balance in my account, I go in a private jet
Malaysian influencer took a jet on rent,
to show off how much money I make
Similarly expensive clothes,
expensive purses
Create a confirmation bias around you
That yes, this man is earning
Then they use such words, to sell their course
10 day MBA, financial independent or big words of strange things
That he has acquired amazing knowledge.
Create very impressive ads
Only shows wealth
Like iPhone company does,
like the company of Rolex does
They show their product only with a rich look,
that it is not for the poor
If you are poor and want to be like us
Then they create such an ad, what a lifestyle
That ad is run everywhere
On Facebook, YouTube, Instagram
Where they give you a catchy line
and make you click on the learn more option.
Below, if you want to become rich,
you were poor like me, click on Learn More.
Here your convincing mode starts on
But here your cognitive thinking is working now
Where you know that it can be fake.
They want to sell their course,
just want to earn money from us
But this guru also knows this
To break your cognitive thinking,
they use a word, 'Free'
Where they say, that we are offering a free session
"I have created an absolutely free training for you"
"By attending a free training, you too can earn Rs 7 to 10 thousand per day within the next 30 days"
I am giving a free webinar, or we are giving the registration for free, for 10 days, for 15 days
It will not be free after that
They cash the free word in such a way that
Your cognitive thinking gets broken
You think that it is being given for free,
so what's the problem
Right?
What's the problem with going and seeing?
So the earlier traps worked
Here you register for their webinar
That you are getting it for free,
there is no problem in Free
And my dear, Nothing is available for free in this world
If something is being sold to you for free
Then by making a product you will be sold
Third, after registering,
you reached their free webinar
The main purpose of calling here is
That the ad you were seeing was very short,
30 seconds, 1 minute long.
Where it was not possible to convince
Now they will keep you here for one or one and a half hour
And will create an echo chamber for you,
will create a bandwagon effect
Where all the psychology was used to convince you.
And here they will tell, first of all
How have I earned what I have earned?
I have written a book,
these are the proofs of my account,
What he told in the video,
he will explains in detail
This is my car, this is my net worth,
earlier I used to live there, earlier I was poor
And to prove this, many popular faces
will also be brought before you.
Which are obviously paid
Where paid TEDx interviews will also be shown,
their sessions will be shown
You will get podcasts and videos
with popular young people.
By including everyone, such an echo chamber
has been created in front of you.
You will feel that this cannot be a lie
50-40% of them are convinced to buy the course from there, that we should buy
If they are not, then they then target individual people.
In the fourth step,
where India comes,
Most of the people in India buy these courses
Convince their parents, or tell the parents that your son is poor, his life will become better
Or convince that son
Why do these people become convinced in India?
Because two things are special in India
That it has the highest population in the world
Secondly, the education rate here,
the children of tier 2 and tier 3 are around 12 pass
And they are not getting jobs but they Want to become rich
And thirdly, here is the US education system
Which only prepares you for job, not for business
In such a situation, everyone runs in the same race
So not everyone gets a job, only one or two get it
In such a situation, unemployment is very high here,
the numbers are very high
It is very easy to manipulate such people.
They create their courses on trending topics
Most of the people buy their courses
Now after purchasing the course, people realize
That there was no value in it
The things mentioned in it are not lies,
they are not wrong.
But it is not even worth the amount given.
"If you learn that course,
you will feel that I am not learning anything special."
"What you are claiming,
what this course claims, does not hold true at all.
I would not recommend even a single person,
who is watching this video, to buy this course."
In fact, the guy is not even getting extra support.
That give us some support to make us understand this, no?
Now they say that the more hard you work,
the more money you will earn, you will have to work hard
And people feel that
We are not the only ones earning from this course
Because 1 or 2 people are earning,
I don't know whether they are earning or not,
they just do advertisements.
So the person feels that maybe
I am not able to work that hard
But no one raises questions on the course
That there could be a problem in the course
Now tell me that if 100 pots have been planted
by some gardener
And one or two pots bloomed and 98 pots died
Then it would be the gardener's fault, right?
The gardener blames the plants for not working hard,
these two had also blossomed
Now those who have bought the course get self-blaming
And they don't say anything,
or there are some who do not know where to speak
There are children of class 10-12,
where should they go?
Here they raise the same question that we are not earning from the course.
Then they say no problem,
those who are not earning from this 3,000 course
We have another upgraded version on top of this,
that is for ₹ 10,000.
You buy that, it will make you money
Then people think, maybe I will learn from there,
So he buys a course worth Rs. 10 thousand,
but he doesn't know from there.
“So I thought, I have come this far, so let's try this course once and see if I can get success.”
Then they say buy it for 30, buy it for lakhs
Some people buy, some people run away,
some people leave
In the end there is a very good solution left for them
That if you do not learn business from our business course, MBA course,
Then do one thing, this course we have created
You sell it to people, we will give you commission.
The money you paid for the course will be recovered to you.
"If you come here, you will definitely learn the business
And you know what happens at the place of business
They do it so that their product gets sold.
Sell ​​their products, nothing else is happening"
"You are saying that you took that course, after taking which you realized that there was no point in it but
Now they told you that now sell ​​the course further,
you will get so much money"
"You will get this much money"
And for that also they give training,
that you go in front of the school and tell the children,
You go to their parents, tell them
How to sell their course,
they also give separate training for this
And it starts like an MLM business.
So, if you want to recover your money?
We've fooled you, so if you want your money back?
So you fool people too
Only then you can get money
And this loop keeps on going on and on
There is no legal complaint about it
Because the children of 10th-12th do not even know
how to make a legal complaint
Legal complaint cannot be made properly
Because what is mentioned in the course
There is nothing false,
nothing wrong in that course
But it is generic, and there is no refund policy,
Whereas a legal complaint can be made
Well, that will be done as a group,
and with time it has happened, and will also happen
But let me tell you one thing, clear
Any number of courses on YouTube
Like how to grow a YouTube channel?
"I provide India's number 1 course on YouTube,
I say this out of fear."
Or How to become a businessman?
Or how to earn money?
Or whatever type of training courses are given
I am guaranteed that all of them are available for free on the internet and on YouTube.
You don't have to pay money to anyone to get any course, any knowledge.
You will find it if you search properly.
Wherever this course is being sold,
it will be a generic course
Snd there is no value in it
And the amazing thing is that all the top businessmen
They didn't even do any courses or degrees.
Steve Jobs did not do any course degree
Zuckerberg, Bill Gates, Richard Bedson or Henry Ford
And there are an infinite number
who never did a course or degree
And the irony, it's amazing
That people are earning money by telling,
how to earn money, wow!
If you are going to buy any kind of course on YouTube
Leave aside lakh, thousand, 500
Even if you are buying a course worth Rs 50, right?
Aa.. Thu...