Welcome everybody to Chai pe Charch... Chai with Sai.
Where I will be giving my heavily biased opinions on mildly interesting topics.
So our first topic of the day is Amit Bhadana's new music video 'Parichay'.
Amit Bhadana is the biggest Indian Youtuber with over 13M subscribers.
Now Im not going to forcefully roast Amit Bhadana just for the sake of it.
The music was good and the production quality was amazing.
It's one of the most well-produced videos in Indian Youtube.
But the lyrics were a bit repetitive.
Who gives an introduction for 7 minutes? It doesnt take 7 minutes for an introduction.
This is not a roast, this is more like a 'Saute'. Im just going to share my opinions.
The most interesting visual I found in the music video was when a hater is holding a phone and seeing a photo of Amit Bhadana hospitalised, and laughing on it.
So he is trying to show that his haters make fun of him being hospitalised.
That's not true. Your haters make fun of you because of your content.
Please dont be so arrogant.
But the music video was good.
And just in case, you din't realise that Amit Bhadana has worked hard, he makes sure you know that.
"I have worked hard."
Wow nice everyone should work hard.
I got the point you have worked hard. No doubt.
"I have worked hard"
Okay I got that you worked hard, everyone works hard. What is your point?
To hell with your 'Parichay'
On this music video, CarryMinati's response was this.
"Yes Amit Bhadana's 'Parichay' song is great. He has worked hard."
And BB ki Vines said this:
"Very good. He has worked hard."
This is just my personal opinion Im not saying that this is the truth.
Looking at this reaction it feels that this is the kind of reaction you give when you don't like something but you still give a diplomatic compliment so that the person asking it doesn't feel bad.
You have worked hard, nobody's denying that.
But even Amir Khan worked very hard to make 'Thugs of Hindustan'.
This video has the 'humble brag' feels throughout. Jake Paul will be proud.
Its a really good music video.
I will not roast just for the sake of roasting.
But it was a bit narcissistic. I wont deny that.
More than an introduction, it was more like a CV, that Amit Bhadana made for Bollywood.
Because few weeks ago he uploaded a 40 min long sketch.
Looking at that it seems like he is telling Bollywood that see, I can make films as well as songs.
I sincerely hope, that Amit Bhadana makes it into Bollywood.
But it will be a very sad day for the Indian Youtube if that happens. Indian comedy Youtube scene will die.
"I made children and parents laugh. I made family friendly content."
Also credit where it is due, in Amit Bhadana's recent videos, he has reduced the amount of misogynistic content. So I will apprecitate that.
Maybe he saw my roast video, maybe not,
but that doesnt matter.
What matters is that he is improving.
But nobody can deny Amit Bhadana's success. You can question his content, but you can't deny his smartness.
That music video got 1M Likes in just one day.
Congratulations to Amit Bhadana,
lets move on to our next topic.
I always forget to announce this...
I have made a subreddit of mine. r/SaimanSays
So please submit memes, funny videos and other mildly interesting stuff, so that I dont have to struggle to find content.
Our next topic everybody, Technical Guruji exposed.
Now I respect Tehcnical Guruji a lot, because he uploads 2 videos a day.
And he is doing that since the past 2-3 (years).
But a Youtuber called TechStar Shahrukh has exposed Technical Guruj, saying that he is biased.
Technical Guruji is the leading Hindi technology channel and he uploaded a video where he did a bend test of the phone Redmi Note 7.
So the things about a bend test is that you have to apply pressure to the center of the phone,
to test the durability of the phone.
What Technical Guruji did is that he applied pressure to the edge of the phone.
"This phone is breaking into 2 pieces.
This is not a strong device."
The funny thing about this is that he applied so much pressure, that the bench shakes.
Youtuber TechStar Shahrukh says that Tehcnical Guruji did this bend test and broke the phone, as a revenge to Xiaomi's MD's tweet.
People are saying that this tweet by Manu Kumar Jain, who is the MD of Xiaomi was indirectly targeted to Technical Guruji.
And Technical Guruji did not like this, and that is why he did such an extreme bend test om Redmi Note 7 which is owned by Xiaomi.
TG is saying that the reason why he did such a harsh bend test on this phone is because this phone claimed that is is that tough.
"If any Youtuber does this test (bend test), there is a simple answer for that, and that's a publicity stunt."
Breaking a phone is easy, anyone can do that."
"Not necessary that if the phone is strong you cant break it. A man has a alot of strength."
"If you have decided to show that the phone breaks in the video, you can do it"
"You can make this video,
and then this video can go viral"
A lot of people are saying that technical guruji has sold out, and he is biased towards Samsung.
If Technical Guruji's channel gets shut down then who will say "Chaliye Shuru Karte Hai"??? (Let's Start)
Then we will have to "Chaliye band karte hai" (Lets stop)... Im not ready for that...
Please TG, I hope you have a good explanation.
Im rooting for you.
This tea gets cold very quickly in winter.
So our next topic is Pewdiepie vs T-series. Wow it feels like December again. I havent spoken about this topic since a long time.
SuperBowl is one of the biggest sporting events in the world, and definitely America's biggest sporting event.
And there was a lot of hype that Mr. Beast is going to advertise Pewdiepie on that show.
The SuperBowl show happened yesterday and Mr.Beast somehow promoted Pewdiepie, but people were underwhelmed.
Mr Beast and his team went to SuperBowl and they wore T-Shirts saying Subscribe to Pewdiepie.
That was funny but...
A lot of people thought that Mr Beast was going to buy billboards, or a TV commercial during the broadcast.
In my opinion it wasnt that bad because ESPN tweeted this picture. I dont know who Stephen Gostkowski is.
But in the picture you can clearly see Sub To Pewdiepie t-shirts in the audience.
And im pretty sure that ESPN tweeted this picture just because it had Sub to Pewdiepie in it.
So i guess in the end this strategy definitely worked. Mr Beast is smart.
Also the subgap was 29000 yesterday and most of the Indians were very excited that T-Series is finally going to take over Pewdiepie.
But as it always happends, the sub gap increased to almost 150000.
Mainly because Pewdiepie did a livestream playing Fortnite, which he hasnt done before.
and also VoiceOverPete and KeemStar did a livestream, which might have helped a bit.
I think this battle is going to go on forever.
And Im a proud insider/infiltrator, whatever my post is,
in the 9 YO army.
Also when popular Indian rapper Raftaar was asked who does he support between T-Series vs Pewdiepie...
He said that he supports Salil Jamdaar.
So Salil Jamdar made a disstrack on Carryminati, Pewdiepie and T-series. His diss on T-series is really damn good.
And Raftaar said he supports Salil Jamdar. Im happy that a superstar like Raftaar, is not being a sheep, and supporting Tseries because 'Patriotism'.
And of course, Amit Bhadana, Harsh Beniwal and Ashish Chanchlani have been promoting T-Series on their Social Medias.
"T-Series is very close to becoming India's No.1 channel, and I want everyone to subscribe to them"
"I have worked with them they are great people. T-Series values artists, they respect artists."
"You messages and comments have been telling me that T-Series is going to be the world's biggest channel"
"So subscribe to T-Series, so that when someone asks which is the highest subscribed channel in the world, people will say T-Series."
"Then people will ask that where is it from, people will say India. So that will be a proud moment for us."
I hope after few years when Youtube is dominated by corporations, these individual Indian Youtubers will realise, that they are digging their own grave.
If you keep supporting companies like this, in a few years no one will care about individual creators.
Also ending this video with a very wholesome news which happened on reddit.
So there is this subreddit called r/RoastMe
On that, one 17 year old Russian teenager posted this photo.
So the concept of this subreddit is that people post their pictures holding a card which says 'roast me'.
They get roasted pretty badly, but when this guys posted his picture, things were different.
If you see this photo, normally people are very enthusiastic in their photos, but this guy looks very sad.
Its really very sad, but people realised that.