Normally, we don't attend many events, but
today would be the first time we'll be attending an event
with many YouTubers and creators.
It would be quite exciting to see.
This is the Nas Summit.
This is why we're back in Dubai.
This is the largest gathering of international content creators
in the last 2 years!
This time, our hotel is quite close to the metro station,
so we'll take the metro for the first time
and see how Dubai's metro is.
Who actually cycles here?
There're so many cycles.
Look at that.
Emirates Tower.
There's even a gold class on this train.
-Book it!
-Oh, you did not book it?
-It's weird.
-Oh, true.
So overall, this metro is quite similar to Delhi metro.
So many things are the same.
The visuals that you can see from the train.
-What happened?
-Keep going.
I shouldn't be filming in such crowded places.
It attracts too much attention.
-I'll be filming today, okay?
-Great.
We found Mohit and Sandhya on the way.
-Hi!
Oh wow, this is the hall where everyone will sit.
I was wondering, in a hotel, how is there a place for 700 people.
It is more crowded than I expected it to be.
There are so many creators.
And several people actually recognise us.
-Snacks, snacks.
-Snacks?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Food, food.
We have no idea about what's going on here.
Who are the ones getting such an energetic welcome?
"Okay so, my name is Matt and this is Belik."
"The game we're playing, apply for a visa, in some cases,
find a hotel, and come here,
to learn with other people that are just like you.
Thank you for coming here."
It sounds like an Apple presentation.
"...you'll see in India..."
Greenland's biggest YouTuber is also here.
"...And she won the Biggest Creator in Greenland,
with ten thousand followers,
do you know why?
because fifty thousand people live in Greenland..."
That's 20% of the country.
Do you know the World's Biggest Fish YouTuber?
Yeah, if it is Graham Stepan, I know.
It's Casey Neistat.
"40-year old, married guy, with 2 babies at home.
That's what my life is right now."
There's also a pool party in this hotel.
And it is a special hotel because
it gets a truly amazing view of Burj Khalifa.
So we met Ranveer Allahbadia aka Beer Biceps.
-He's really hyper today.
-Is this the vlog?
This is a video now for our vlog,
because we haven't been filming a lot,
so I was thinking.
So how is it going?
Are you having fun?
I'm tripping out,
This is how Juli's puts her voice in the vlog and all that, it's crazy.
Love it.
Okay, I'm telling you he's so hyper.
Look at this, what am I supposed to think about this?
There's some serious bromance going on.
Everything you've seen on Beer Biceps' vlogs,
-he's even more hyper in real life.
-Yeah.
Because Dhruv's sexiness is 100 times more in real life.
He is quite sexy online,
but he is even sexier in real life.
I'm just expressing my man crush.
I mean, I don't disagree, it's just...
Another interesting thing,
normally the fans that I come across are from India,
but here I met a viewer from Myanmar.
I'm interested in the topic that you are saying, like geopolitics,
and since I'm interested in that topic,
I just know the topic that you are saying,
but I don't understand you.
-So I have been following you.
-Yeah, yeah, but you can use subtitles.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah, very interesting.
Today is the second day of the Summit.
The last day for us,
we aren't staying long.
We have a flight tomorrow.
I have a presentation today.
Well not a presentation really, I'll be on the stage to speak for a bit.
It's a panel discussion.
Not a presentation.
"...I swear that was such a brain fog..."
I'm backstage before the panel discussion,
Technical Guruji and Carryminati are already here.
And you can see Mostly Sane here.
"Let's begin."
Vlog section.
"Make sure you turn your phone towards the people the viewers want to watch.
The video would turn out great,
I have some really good people with me,
and the event is running 15-minutes late,
but a backstage video is important
so let's talk for a while.
How are you feeling in Dubai?
It's great, it's fun, so many things are happening all around,
I'm not sure what's happening,
but it was fun, it was awesome,
let's see what happens right now.
Did he know this question was coming?
No, he didn't.
Everyone on my vlog has to speak fast, let's go Dhruv.
What should I say?
-Today, tell us something about Dubai.
-But you have to speak fast.
I have explored Dubai for a while,
No, wait, wait, wait,
faster, faster.
-With hands.
-You have to speak fast.
Actually, I'll tell you a secret, I speak very slowly.
And I speed up the videos later.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm the opposite, people have to slow down my video to watch it.
This is Technical Guruji's phone.
This phone deserves an unboxing video.
What's on here?
The theme here is Space,
These pieces, 1...2...3... These 6 pieces here,
these are pieces of meteorites from Mars and the Moon.
-Really?
-Yeah, really.
And the theme is space, you can see the rings of a planet.
Plus, there's a quote by Albert Einstein here.
-This is a watch that runs.
-Wow.
For example, it's 2:50 now.
It's 2:50 here.
And then here's my logo,
this is all titanium,
this is my name here,
this is the only one in the world.
-This is all solid gold.
-You designed all of this?
No, it was by the company that made it, Caviar.
Oh, wow.
This is solid gold?
Yeah, that's why it's so heavy.
-Hi.
-So you're gonna have your panel discussion
Are you nervous at all?
Because I'm nervous on your behalf.
No, it's not a very complex topic or something.
But it's been a long time since I've been on a stage.
The last time was with Kunal Kamra in 2019?
In Amsterdam?
Amsterdam, yeah.
Since it's been a long time I'm getting some stage fright.
It's easier to speak in a video.
But to speak on a stage is tougher in comparison.
This was a small backroom.
Like they show in films,
a place for actors to get ready.
We had gathered here,
and then this is the way to the backstage.
-All the best!
-Thank you.
That looks like the backstage.
I'll be going up on a stage after a long time.
Guess who's coming on the panel now.
There he is!
Hi, guys, my name is Dhruv Rathee,
and I make explanatory videos on a variety of topics,
and I have around 7 million subscribers.
Things change like that!
In 2 days, the world will change.
I will say that probably the only thing you can say for sure,
is that more and more people are going to come on the internet right now.
So if it's only 50% of the Indian population,
soon you will see 60%-70%.
Once more people come, then
you will see that there are different markets within India also
based on the language they speak.
Welcome to the Second Day of the Nas Summit!
Okay, again.
I hate making videos.
1, 2, 3!
Welcome to the Second Day of the Nas Summit!
Perfect! Okay, cut.
Thank you so much for the amazing...
There we go, Ranveer all ready.
Clinging to Dhruv again.
He's stealing my husband.
Your love is back!
Group hug, group hug, group hug!
Look at the amount of cameras here.
How dare Ranveer steal my husband?
Today is the last day of the Summit.
But unfortunately, we won't be attending.
Because we have a morning flight.
Even the passport checking is so futuristic here,
you just need to scan there, and it automatically recognises your face.
You don't need to do anything else.
Where do you think we're going?
See if you can guess.
Welcome to Delhi.
Welcome to India.