Okay, so, one thing is that we haven't done
anything like this till now, right?
I mean, we've not gotten together.
The collective influence of everybody on this
table is crazy, right?
That's absolutely right.
Yeah.
I mean, this kind of influence.
Huh?
Gaurav bhai?
I mean, one thing is that we're talking about
the round table, but we haven't got the whole
round done.
We haven't got the whole round done.
It's half round.
Yeah, it's half round.
We kept the camera.
We needed a place for the camera.
So, the thing is that this discussion is very
important,
not just for today, but also for tomorrow.
What's going to happen tomorrow?
What is the future of technology?
And obviously, you guys are also here.
We'll talk about the creator life.
We'll talk about everything.
So, I just want to put… I'll put a bomb
first.
Okay?
Why haven't we done this till now?
Like, what…
Like, why haven't we gotten together till
now?
And why did it take us so long?
Because people have a perspective, right?
That outside… Is the tech community
not together?
Is it like that?
Or not?
Efforts take a lot of time to gather everyone.
Right.
That becomes a very difficult part.
You guys have sent us such a big invite.
So, how can we not come?
I can't do that.
No, it's all about taking one initiative.
Like, you guys took it.
So… So, I want to chime in here.
So, I want to chime in here.
So, we apply for awards at TrakinTech.
So even with this much value addition, I didn't
think… Because we can tell from a normal
video that about which phones we liked.
So, we thought what is it that will, you know,
you know, really bring value.
And I think that was the reason he said, nahi,
karna hi
hai, kitna bhi effort jaane do.
And I think Aishat pulled it off.
Nahi, meko controversial answer chahiye tha.
Yeh toh bahut hi diplomatic ho gaya hai.
So I'll give you the controversial answer.
I think yeh bahut hi hum log shuru kar rahe
hain with everybody loves everybody.
And you know, yeh bahut accha.
I don't think that's the real answer.
I agree with you.
Effort hai.
Initiative liya kisi ne.
But I also think that there is this thing
in this community that, why is it that we
don't have enough collaborations?
I mean, why is it that in most videos, we're
not doing things together?
It is because this is a overall community
jahaan pe each of us is very cocooned in our
own.
Hamara Instagram, hamara YouTube, hamara channel,
our personality, our identity.
There's not enough.
How many times have the three, four of us
collaborated?
Batao?
Nahi.
Zero.
Uska reason yeh hai na?
Ki matlab, okay, pehli baat toh locations,
koi Pune waitha hai.
Nahi.
Koi Chile bhi waitha hai.
Bihar wala menlo sab ek saath hote hain.
Kaunsi collaboration?
Aap hamishchah camera leke aate toh ho?
Ki aaj aapko karte hain ki...
Main toh all-inclusive bhi hai.
But I'm just saying that if push comes to
shove aur hum log ne, if this whole topic
and this roundtable is all about
being very, very honest,
I think I'm not saying that there is any controversy
to it,
but I think hum log sab bahut inclusive hai
within our own little cocoon of what we do,
hum log zyada collaborative nahi hai abhi.
And I think this could be the start of it
all.
Toh reason kya hai?
Kya hai reason?
I want to ask Devinder.
Because he comes from that...
I also agree.
I also agree with Rajiv ki I feel ki tech
community na
thodi si, it is a competitive space.
Actually aisa nahi hai ki...
Exactly.
Matlab wo setup hi aisa hai.
Ki jaise agar phone ka review jaata hai, toh
there's like three reviews going at the same
time.
Toh essentially everybody is competing with
each other.
Everybody will see everyone's videos, right?
Lekin ek baat bolo mujhe dusri industry mein
aisa nahi hota hai.
Every industry is competing.
Hota hai, but I think in the tech community,
specially
India, Asia, right?
Where we basically...
I think hum log ka competition zyada hai.
I think we...
The social media part of it is that we are
more with I have
to be out first,
I have to have the product first.
Hum log ki ego hurt ho jaati hain agar humare
koi product nahi bol raha hai.
Agar hum globally baat karte hain...
Haan, haan, hundred percent.
Ego hai baat.
Hundred percent.
I mean, isme na...
I think it's possible.
I agree with that.
Agar Shlok ne ego bola hai, toh at least itna
toh hum agree karte hain ki Shlok ko toh hai.
Haan.
Main kehta hoon mere ko bhi hai.
I am immediately agreeing, you know, everybody
else can be as diplomatic...
Ego doesn't have to be a negative thing.
Yeah, exactly.
There's no negative to it.
For growth, you have to respect yourself and
you have to have ego that actually fuels your
passion.
Jo aage leke jaate hain, isme kya galat hai?
But at the same time, I would also...
I would also add one thing ki I personally
have a huge
amount of respect for everybody sitting here.
Kyunki Gaurav has been working so hard and
it has inspired him.
It has inspired me.
And how Arun sir and Rajeev sir have been
helping me,
I think it is very personal for me.
And it is a very emotional thing for me.
But also at the same time,
I think, matlab yeh competitive space hai.
And for that, muskil bhi hota hai.
Hum baat karne hai,
India mein aisa kyu nahi ki hai humne aaj
tak.
For that matter, bahar bhi kisne kya kiya
hai?
Agar hum aisa bol rahe hain ki hum sab competitive
hai, toh same goal for...
I think waha pe thoda...
But more or less, same goal for the US guys
yaar.
Nahi, but
I agree with Gaurav.
You know something we don't know Gaurav?
US guys ke baare mein?
I'm just saying.
Toh basically kya hai ki, abhi tak nahi ho
paya, ab ho gaya.
Acha, okay.
Just asking you personally.
Yeh achieve karne mein, kya kisi ko bhi chase
karne mein
aisa laga ki koi off chal raha hai?
Nahi na?
All you had to do was just one call?
Yes.
And just one message?
Surprisingly smooth ha?
Surprisingly smooth.
Simple reason, main aapko batata.
December ke mahine mein humare paas content
nahi hota.
Yeh reality hai.
Sachme hum log struggle karte hain.
Sancheet, iska matlab yeh keh raha hai ki,
agar maine phone karke bola hota,
March, April mein, ya phir Diwali ke pehle,
sabse peak season mein, tu nahi aata tha?
Nahi, nahi.
Main toh aata.
100% Gaurav nahi hota.
Gaurav nahi hota.
I think unka matlab scheduling problem hai.
Exactly.
Not a matter of main nahi aata kyunki.
But hum sabki dates collide karte hai.
Aur infact, jab tech ki baat karte hai, aaye
din tech aati
hai, aur seriously hum logon ka peth bhara
hai.
Honestly, content hi kameeth nahi padti nahi
hai, toh thoda aisa lagta hai ki, yeh theek
hai, kamaayi bhi ho rahi hai.
Main honestly bata raho.
Ki mujhe aisa lagta hai ki, ho rahi hai kamaayi?
Nah, merko ho rahi hai.
Main samjha nahi, kamaayi?
What do you mean?
Matlab.
Ajit toh kamaayi karta hai.
I only want them to say something.
Devinder and Tamil.
So, first of all, yeh bahut badi cheez hai
ki, we have achieved something like this,
that all of us can come together and speak
freely.
Toh yeh bahut hi badi cheez hai.
And I appreciate the efforts that you guys
have put in.
Pehle kyun nahi hua?
Iske multiple reasons hai.
It's very evident that the tech community,
all of, like,
I'm not saying ki hum log, but bahut saare
aisa content creators hain that they don't
get along very well.
And that is the reason it creates a tension
between all of us.
Toh wo bhi rahta hai.
Competition, as you said, is another thing.
For us, specifically, language is also, thoda
sa barrier ban jata hai ki, hum ek audience
ko address karte hain.
Look at your Hindi, man.
Main toh shock hoye ja rahe hoon.
Main dar gaya hoon, yaar.
This is fantastic.
Main Rajasthan se hoon, toh Hindi toh...
Au phir toh phir.
Ragh ragh mein hain.
Yeah.
Toh, ab humein yeh bhi lagta hai, kahi baar
jab hum collaborate karne jaate hain, ki humari
audience, bahut
saare audience,
South India se hai.
So, they might not understand if we change
the language all together, or if we try to
collaborate with a different
content creator who's creating similar content,
but in a different language.
So, that becomes a barrier sometimes.
Aur aisa nahi hai ki humne collaborate nahi
kiya hai.
We have collaborated multiple times, but this
sort of collaboration hasn't happened.
But this is something big.
Tamil, what about South?
Matlab, and you guys represent,
Shaz and Tamil represent.
Hello!
You forgetting your own person?
He's tracking Tamil.
What is this?
What is this, Arun?
Okay, Arshad.
Office mein baat karte hain, iske baat karte
hain.
Nahi, nahi, mujhe bolo, yeh South India mein,
yaar Tamil tech creators mein, aise hi hain,
yaar situation is
different.
Even we collaborated before itself.
I came to your studio,
I collaborated for a video,
Gaurav ke saath ek video kiya tha maine,
Sherlock se mil nahi paya, so unse hi nahi
kiya tha maine.
Jab, maine try kiya tha, har baar try karta
hua main,
amesha.
No, not you,
I'm saying, generally, jaise hum baat kar
rahe the, humare ecosystem kya ho rahe the,
South India tech people…
Nahi, usme yeh hi dikkat hai, because most
of the time, kya hota hai na, sabko beech
mein competition hi hai.
Pehli cheez, most of the things happen only
in North India.
Device jab,
South India ko aana hai, vohi mushkil tha
pehli, aap thoda thoda aaja tha.
That is the main fact.
So, getting the device…
Is it only devices or something else beyond
that?
Whatever it is, the recognition, recognition,
only recent past, maybe the last three years,
we used to get lot of recognition, and the
whole India is getting online plug-in.
Scale to…
Scale now we are getting, but before, if you
come, even now, people think me that
I'm from Chennai.
Even if you're not in Chennai, we can do the
content.
That's how it is.
We are in Pune.
No, no, no.
For South, if I'm from Tamil Nadu,
I'm not from Chennai.
And previously, what used to happen is,
Phone Erna, or C4 Tech, they used to be in
Chennai.
And the devices, jo bhi aa raha hai, sirf
un log ko hi milega.
So,
mere ko kya milega?
Kuch bhi nahi milega.
Us time pe, me Gaurav, jab inne Dubai se video
jab kar raha tha, we can talk, hell lot of
things about technology even without the device.
That's what I got to learn from watching these
videos.
Then I started doing those.
That's the biggest thing for me
Again, you have not answered my question
Your enmity, you tell me
Enmity, competitiveness, our Hindi
No, no, I do understand
See, I follow each and everyone
Literally everyone, I've subscribed to them
I started my channel looking at your inspiration
and everything
But the problem is that the regional
You need some kind of a difference when you're
doing videos For me, it's like I create some
characters like
Different companies as a character
Then, you know, that's how I picked up my
channel But
again, his question is not getting answered
You guys are talking about you Is there better
camaraderie between all of you?
I don't know what, I can direct you
No, not with all, let me be frank
I'm putting that out there
Not with all, let's just get an answer
Recently, what happened?
I had a conversation with few of the creators
earlier
So with the new kind of creators coming in
And new guys are getting the views and everything
There is a chance
Either you have to collaborate with them
Or you're just be on your own So which one
you have to choose?
So what do you choose?
I just be on my own
So this is what I'm trying to say
That is the main thing The tech community
is first choice,
be on your own
I'm very glad you've done this
Even though you're saying it was very smooth
and everything else
I still do believe that the amount of effort
That has put into get this together Hats off,
I don't think
very many of us would have taken this on
It's a very difficult task
Because while people saying yes
Is only one very small part of putting it
all together
And I would really really hope that after
this
The collaborations and that sort of cocooning
Where we all go into our own little box breaks
So we keep using the word out of the box in
tech Let's also do out of
the box content with each other
Not be
But I'll answer your question which is like
Is there some kind of a clash?
Yes there is
There is
Okay Okay That's done
Now coming to both of you
Here also right now you've said that you know
We should work together and going forward
Still that competitiveness is going to be
there
Still there is going to be that
Who gets the first device?
Who gets the first video?
Why didn't I get it?
I saw the video
No matter how much you do
I mean even with everyone
If I didn't get the device and Gaurav got
it
Then I'll call and ask
Why didn't I get the device that Gaurav got?
This is what we
It happens
It happens right?
No it doesn't
That is Shlok
Yes 100%
Okay so I think
If there is competition
If you look at it in a healthy way
Then it should be there
And there is nothing wrong with it At the
same time We all know that we all co-exist
Yes It's a fact
And we don't want to hurt anyone
If I have to make a video with Shlok Then
I know for sure
If I say anything
He won't say no
I know
And I think like I said
When he called
When we spoke
Gaurav you are talking about inclusiveness
We are talking about
What the point he has brought is Okay now
let me ask you You will see that Shlok got
a device
And you didn't get it
Call him
We will do it together
Listen I'll give you an example
Samsung Galaxy Note 8 or Note 9
I forgot the exact device
I think Note 8
In which was the yellow S-Pen of golden color
It was a blue phone with a yellow S-Pen Note
Note 8
Samsung launched in New York
Okay I went to New York for Global Impact
I remember two people with me
From YouTube side
I don't know about the other media people
Ranjeet and Bharat
From IGN
We three went
Now I was part of the Samsung Global Program
and all So I got the phone with full box and
everything
In New York
For the video
Before launch I got the hands-on system
And because I was a part of the Samsung Global
Team After that I went to Korea and all that
happened
Ranjeet and Bharat didn't have that access
to the device Now I didn't talk to Bharat
at that time
I was aware
I mean I knew him
But we never talked
I used to talk to Ranjeet
So Ranjeet got the device
And just the device
No box nothing
And that too for a limited duration Just for
1-2 hours
Do whatever you want to do hands-on
I still remember
There was a place here
There is a walk in New York
Which is built on a railway track
Okay okay
Yeah It was just opposite the Samsung office
I still remember the exact same thing I saw
Ranjeet's face
And he was like
What should I say now
Just a phone
And I have a box
So basically you wanted to make a video
So what did I do
I told Ranjeet
I said do one thing Who knows that I have
unboxed the same box
I said what happens in the box
That's the cable charger
I said I will make a video
You keep the phone
You unbox it again
And I did that
Excellent And here we have a very fine example
Nothing phone
Yeah We had a similar thing When I asked for
help Everybody has been ready to help
And this is with everyone And I keep asking
And I didn't get the nothing phone personally
I don't know if it was a challenge
Or I missed it
But I asked Arun for the phone
And he also
I mean
He was getting a loss
In giving the phone
If I am honest
I think
Look Shlok, honestly
Sharing a device today
For that matter
If we talk
It's not like
Let's say I only have access
Or you only have access
And they will have it
If not today, it will happen tomorrow So the
main point is If you say no, let's say
Does not
End the world for that person
You will get the access
Why not put together
I want to ask a question
There is a brand discrimination here Like
Is there a level playing field
For everyone
There are small creators
At what level is that
And here is
At your level you are talking about this
Imagine a smaller level
I am proud to say
This is a very good conversation
Because this is more or less
A congregation of the top creators
Top creators
This is a little
Let's bring it down to the reality
No, no, no
We were not there before
When You know, 3-4 years back 5 years back
We were small
At that time Gaurav was big
We did not have it
And we know that situation
But was there a struggle or not
It was a struggle
That's what he is talking about
Is there a level playing field today
We are talking about
There can't be a level playing field
Level playing
Ranjeet Trophy player
Will not get selected in the IPL
He will have to work hard
We can do examples of cricket and everything
else There is always going to be
Someone that is going to be
Now moving forward
At one time you were not as big You were not
as big
There was a struggle period Today a brand
Knowing that it is the biggest creator Has
created a level playing field
For them
But is there a divide
As he said devices are available in North
India Not in South
Are all these things still relevant
I think this is an important one
Because this is going to be watched by all
brands Could we make life a little bit better
for everybody By bringing forward some of
the challenges
In this sense
What is a level playing field
Numbers for brands
I am talking from brand perspective
Now there are about 10 YouTubers
Who are more than 5 million subscribers
They should go
Now level playing field
Still does not happen that 8 out of 10 people
go Why?
Because brands
Also have their biases towards certain things
It's not even bias
I will say if it's my company
I have this water bottle
I will give it to whoever I want
This is what I am also trying to say out here
I completely agree
As a brand it is completely their choice
Brand is not out there
To create a level playing field in the content
But why did nothing discriminate
To the South entirely
Very important question to ask
Let's not get too specific
It can't be North-South
But it happens
It happens a lot
I think
He made a point also
North India has more access
Delhi has more access
Like you said
Let's not go into a specific incident
But it's not one specific incident
I have heard about it many times
There is a stage 1 and a stage 2
For everything to be sent out
And eventually
The reality of the business that we are in
Which is content creation
Where views matter Who watches your video
matters Are you not interested in the number
of views
When your video goes out after 1 hour After
12 hours You do look at it
You don't ignore it
If you are going to get a device
About 2 weeks after
If you are going to send out All their unboxing
and reviews How do you expect everybody else
To get the same number of views I think there
is that
It is understandable But it is a brand prerogative
First access, that is the reason why Because
the one who will post it later
Is not going to get it
Is our space all about first access Let me
be very very clear
It is all about views
But sir, first access brings views
I bought the device earlier
I don't even get devices from the company
I buy it from the market
We have done it too
That's what I do
What I like about what he is saying
Is that
Uniqueness There is a uniqueness in the content
That also brings the views
I know many people globally
Who still buy devices
And their videos are fantastic
Views can be 5000, 4000, 10,000
But still
The production quality and the interest
Is clearly visible And he is buying the device.
I'll give you my own example.
You must be assuming that I get side devices.
I shop for 8-10 lakhs every month just to
buy devices.
And I think we all have it.
We are not talking about shoes and clothes.
I'm not talking about that.
So this thing, I mean somewhere...
But you bought the iPhone.
Bro, leave this.
I don't think anybody will think about that.
I'll give you my example.
Even today, let's say there is a brand which
is not operating in India.
Or if it is, then I don't have access to it.
I'll buy it.
Hoping that one day, we will have connects.
We don't have it today.
And I think all of us have done that stage
before.
But we can't do it for each and every device
that is launching.
That's where the problem comes.
It's about the level then.
Today, when I started YouTube.
When all of us started this journey.
We all started at one level.
In the beginning, we talked only about devices.
Then we went to events.
Then we get devices.
So there is always a level 1, 2, 3.
I will agree with him completely.
Because even this IBTR for that example.
We have taken this risk.
Because getting all this together, putting
all that effort.
We don't know whether we are going to get
views.
But we have to do it.
You have to take that risk.
Like you said, we can't buy all the devices.
No, you have to.
And if it works, good.
If it doesn't, it is a risk.
Same I would say for me also.
Because when I started.
When I was making videos.
Everybody was popular.
I think for 3.5 years.
I made videos without any phone.
And I didn't have money to buy a phone.
So what I used to do was.
If a phone launched, I would make a video
without the phone.
That's it.
This phone came out.
These are my opinions.
That's how we started.
At that time, opinion videos were also very
popular.
My first video that went more than 10,000.
Was OnePlus 5.
Where I made an opinion video.
And that's how it started.
But that was the first video.
And at that time, it was very popular.
I started from Dubai.
There was no access there.
And I did those.
So you know what.
I want to segue into that.
I want to ask a question.
If a new creator wants to start today.
You can make opinion videos.
If I don't get devices today.
Today is the time where.
Unboxing videos.
Are on their way out.
There is nothing on the box.
You actually take a look at it.
Right.
I think the most boring thing now for an audience.
Is unboxing.
It's boring for us also.
I don't disagree.
Unboxing is fun.
Opening the box is very exciting.
Shlok is your unboxing.
It is the most exciting thing.
Unboxing today.
Forget about the phone.
If you unbox anything.
It will get you all the eyeballs.
But I am saying.
Unboxing today is the same as it used to be.
We used to do it earlier.
It's exactly the same.
I have seen them do this.
I have seen Arun do this.
The kind of excitement that they bring to
the videos.
Is crazy.
I agree with that.
But I am saying that we are now reaching that
stage.
Where the audience.
May not be sharing the same excitement.
I will tell you why.
When I agreed with you.
Unboxing as a process.
Why is unboxing fun?
What Shlok says.
It is.
Every time you open a box.
There is something new.
Something different.
The emotional connect.
That is not important.
The excitement of seeing a new thing.
A new phone.
A new design.
Unboxing a car.
That mystery.
I will give you a great insight.
About all our videos.
I will tell you who watches our unboxing videos.
Let's say you unbox a new iPhone.
I am someone.
Who wants to buy the iPhone.
And I have ordered it.
It's showing me delivery in 2 days.
For 2 days.
I will watch 5-10 unboxings of iPhones.
I know they are going to be the same.
I have done this.
It's my emotional thing.
I will watch Sanchit's.
I have to buy the Steam Deck OLED.
I have been looking at every single day.
When it shows me it's out for delivery.
I will still watch those videos.
For that excitement.
Validation.
I will go one step ahead.
Once I buy a phone.
Even after that.
I am watching on my Vivo.
I am watching on that phone itself.
It's an emotional thing.
I will tell you the part.
That I think has changed.
When unboxing as a concept came.
At that time.
For the viewer.
For us.
For everybody else.
There was a lot of mystery.
And unboxing was magic.
Because no one.
Including you when you got the box.
You didn't know what is going to come out.
The way marketing is today.
With all brands.
How much of it is still a surprise to you.
Almost 90% of the reveal.
Has already happened also for you.
And for your audience.
Then why are people watching millions of videos.
India has a population.
It won't be exciting for us.
100% Initially.
We put a camera over the head.
Opened the box.
We evolved.
We changed the camera.
We added expression.
Unboxing has evolved to a completely different
level.
Only the smell of the box.
And everything else.
And then you just close on the fact.
That you are just opening a box.
And you are describing.
This is a good box.
It has an emotional feel.
While it is fantastic.
The marketing.
If you look at the brand strategy today.
Their marketing.
That is based on a reveal.
Of 90% of everything.
Because they are trying to make sure.
Let me just finish this.
A brand today.
Is trying to make sure.
That their product.
Is coming after 2 months.
Somebody is not making a purchase decision.
They want you to wait 2 months later.
For their product.
And therefore they want to start revealing.
A lot more.
Even for brands.
That used to be very secretive about everything.
Today.
Whether it is done conspicuously.
Behind the scene.
Under the table.
Everything gets revealed.
Agreed.
In short he is saying.
2 years ago.
It is not that.
It is Shlok.
Doing the unboxing.
Shlok speaking.
Arun speaking.
Arun dropping the phone.
Gaurav doing.
There are channels on YouTube.
They don't say anything.
There is no face.
Getting millions of views.
You have to understand.
It is the only claim.
Dal rice can never be boring.
It is a point.
Yesterday we were shooting a product.
And we were taking a lot of shots.
We had to peel off a lot of places.
My team is telling me.
People love to see this shot.
Peel off and all this should happen.
Whether it is significant or not.
Because that attracts a lot of audience.
And the connection.
Which can relate.
That adds a lot of value to the video.
But B-Bomb doesn't do unboxing.
When you are testing a new product.
Peel off.
You guys have cracked the Instagram code.
Kitchen appliances.
Teach us.
Like we were talking.
We get a lot of products.
Because we get a lot of products first hand.
You get it or you buy it.
I am coming to that.
The products we cover.
90% of the products are bought by us.
So we are spending a lot of money.
A lot of research that goes behind it.
A lot of your products are from abroad.
Do you guys do that?
Unique items.
There was a Lyric speaker.
I think it was 1.5-2 lakhs.
We had to purchase it.
There was a Nike self-lacing shoes.
That we bought for 55,000.
It takes 1-2 months for them to arrive.
So do you reach out to the companies.
Or you just buy it?
Reach out is a lengthy tedious process.
So we buy it.
It's a tedious process.
It's a long process.
It means there is a lot of money behind it.
To buy that.
When he looks at that product.
He knows that when I make a video on it.
It will get a lot of views.
It's a business.
It's an investment.
Into the future.
The question that you had.
Sorry, carry on.
When we started building Instagram.
We have very clear intentions.
That Instagram is a different platform.
YouTube is a different platform.
So we treat them very separately.
Yes, we make content.
On both the platforms.
Like there is one product.
The content will go on both the platforms.
But they will be done in their own separate
ways.
There is no cross-posting.
Sometimes they use two different videos.
Rupesh is for YouTube.
And Akshay is there for Instagram.
So the idea is when we started building Instagram.
We made sure that we are going to invest.
This much amount of money.
In building this.
And in that strategy we were clear.
That we will not accept any paid campaign.
So that was our strategy for the first one
and a half years.
Jab tak hum 1 million hit nahi karenge, uske
baad, yes, obviously, but abhi bhi agar aap
dekhoge, toh frequency bahut kam hai, because
our approach is audience first.
Agar audience ko hum bahut zyada bombard karne
lagenge, paid content se, so they might not
start liking it.
So it's always to add value to the audience.
So Ishaan, your question, so coming back to
it, this is a great point, your question was
very different from where this discussion
went away.
Your question was, if a new person, who's
never done this before, is just starting his
channel, is unboxing the
video, and my answer was, not for that person.
No, he did not ask about unboxing, he said,
he just said
new creator, only you put that unboxing thing.
I'm going round this thing, one tip that you
want to give
to a new creator, starting with
Rajiv.
I think I'm going to go with exactly what
he said, because that is really my entire
spirit and philosophy, jo maine
pehle din bhi shuru kiya tha, when I started
what was not happening anywhere in the world,
which is a television show on tech, right,
the
strategy remains the same, the tip remains
the same, agar aap alag nahi kar sakte, passion
ke saath nahi kar sakte, and you're only going
to follow someone else's success, you are
100% going to be a failure.
Find the passion, and you have to be dramatically
different.
Inhone ek strategy banayi, bahut clear strategy
hai, we'll
buy it, we'll not take paid campaigns, we
have something where we'll do things very
very different.
They understood the platform that Instagram
is very different from YouTube.
Understand what you are doing, do not be a
sheep or a herd, ke uski shlok ki badi achi
unboxing hai, he does this and
he drops the phone, ye ek weighing machine
rag dete hain, ke achar iske itne gram hai,
Gaurav does this way of, if
you are going to take
bits and pieces and segments from all the
others and you want to then create your own
personality, you're going to
be a split personality with nothing happening.
The strategy cannot be different today, content
will always be king, queen, prince, ace, everything,
it's not going to change, the strategy must
be that.
Gaurav, aapta hai?
Yaar, mujhe lagta hai, internet is a youth
stage, aur sab
ke liye audience hai saamne, wo aaj nahi hai,
ho sakte hai ek saal baad aayegi, hum, on
a beginner level to be honest, main bolta
hoon kisi ko bhi, don't invest ek x amount
ko,
kyuki wo return
karne ke chakar main dimaag mein rehega na,
ki main ne itna paisa lagaya, main ko chahiye,
chahiye, chahiye, don't do that.
Log camera kharitte hain, team lete hain,
kuch dharwat nahi hai aaj ki date mein, all
you need is your phone.
You did it alone for so long.
Mainne shuru ki 100 video apne phone mein
banaya thi, woh front camera se, why front
camera, because rear mein uska preview dikhega
nahi, to selfie se banaya hai main, anyway
chalo.
Aaj ki date mein, you just need to start,
aur platforms
like Instagram, YouTube, short video bahut
zyada rewarding hai, and it all, kind of you
know, requires just you being consistent.
Aapko 100 din tak target kar lo, main 100
din tak 100
videos har roz post karunga, usme se 10 video
definitely
viral jayenge hi jayenge, and you don't need
anything,
aapko box nahi chahiye, phone nahi chahiye,
kuch nahi chahiye, you just want to talk
to people, just talk about anything, kuch
bhi topic hai,
aapko baat karni hai, that's all.
You know, this is beautiful, it just ties
up with what I
wanted to say, patience, because
I have been the most patient person when it
comes to channels.
You know, when I started Trakin Tech, first
1 year, we went only from 0 to 3000 subscribers
in 1 year, when I was
posting, me and Prateek were posting 1 video
every day, matlab nearly
August 2016 se leke, May end 2017 tak, 10-11
mahine, continuously daal de hai, aur humare
3000 subscribers ho gaye, kabhi bhi ek video
10,000 ke upar nahi gaye, but I knew someday
we are going to crack it, and then 1 video
jo 1 plus 5 ka hai, I still
remember that, wo gaya, and then we just took
off.
So my thing is, unique raho aap, consistent
raho, har roj
video daalna hai, ya hapte mein ek daalna
hai, ya mahine
mein ek daalna hai, jo bhi decide kiya hua
hai, wo karo consistently, and be patient,
results will appear.
I'll give a very fine example, we had started
another
shorts channel, Wittipedia naam ka entertainment
pe, you know, we had given them 6 months,
even after me knowing, me being
mujhe pata hai ki itne saare channels hai,
ki nahi hoga,
mein bola 6 mahine hum log karenge, agar nahi
hota hai, toh we are going to dismantle, we
are not going to put much
effort.
Every day hum daal rahe hain uske upar videos,
6 mahine ke baad, it was what, hardly 2000
ya 3000 subscribers ho gaye, we dismantled
the team, 2 mahine chale gaye, because host
wo gaye rahe, liye the bahar se, 2 mahine
ke baad suddenly
1 short went, that
in that 15 days, ek short viral jaane ke baad,
we went 400k subscribers, in 400k, 4 lakh
subscribers in 15 days, aur
mere paas abhi team nahi hai, toh,
Anson ko wapas bola, nahi wo log chale gaye,
toh main wohi
bol raha hoon, so patience.
Look, I feel, I agree saari cheezon ke saath,
I think consistency zaruri hai, I think saari
cheezon hai, but mere khayal se, ek cheez,
jo ek creator ko successful manauti hai, wo
hai ki, jo maine ghari hai, merle work ghari
hai,
ke bhai, main apni audience
se kabhi jhoot nahi bolta, main jaisa, jo
cheezein hain,
hoon, and ya, light aayi hai aur coffee aagayi
hai, toh
aapke aachanak se, continuity, continuity,
continuity,
there was a power cut, humare bottle ke colour
bhi change ho gaye, green to blue, so,
okay, go ahead,
But ek cheez maine notice kari di, ki jab
sab bata rahe
the, kisi ne algorithm ki, tags, title aise
dalna,
thumbnail aise lagana hai, kisi ne koi baat
nahi kari, and
I think, I also agree, ki ek doi bande, ek
jo person video banara hai, ek jo person video
dekh raha hai, agar aap us audience se dil
se connect kar sakto, aur usko kuch valuable
de sakto, toh aap video chalegi, aaj nahi
toh, kahl nahi toh, parson ek saal lakh sakta,
do saal lakh sakta, kabhi na kabhi toh chalegi,
aur main bhi, starting mein,
mera bhi bhi tha, ki main call-in mein baata
tha, na paise the, kuch bhi nahi tha, mobile
se hi maine bhi video banayi thi, jaise hum
sabne start kara tha, and tutorial banara
tha, main toh mobile mein yeh aise karlo,
software mein yeh karlo, thod tej
rahega, aise ek saal banaya, and woh dheere
dheere pehle,
10-10-20-20-100-100 views aan lagaye, toh
fir bad gaye, toh mera bahut simple hai ki,
agar main kuch audience se dil se connect
karke kuch de paa raha hoon, and main honest
hoon, toh grow hoonga,
and maine jitte bhi YouTubers ko dekha, jo
kuch actual acha kar rahe hain, woh apni audience
se bhauti zyada connected hai, toh mere ke
aata hai, woh sabse aad important hai, toh
tu aise kahe raha hai ki, thumbnails aur titles
important
nahi hai, nahi,
but woh change hote rahata hai na, woh constant
nahi hai, toh titles are very YouTube specific
thing, why do I feel
like everything, that I agree, it's a very
YouTube, content creation, could be Instagram,
but content creation I agree completely, I
was
just saying, it is like saying ki, yaar app
banane ke liye
wali exercise karlo, are khaan acha khao exercise
karlo, apna ban jate hain, kya baat se kuch,
sauce nahi, all
right, haan matlab mujhe aise lagta hai ki,
isme ek knowledge dene se better hai,
toh ek raw thought share karta hu, jab bhi
hum audience ki baat karte hain, hum bol jate
hain, woh insaan hi hai,
jaise ki, agar hum ek apne apartment me rahte
hain, society ki baat karte hain, toh mujhe
aise lagta hai ki, jo insaan baate achchi
karte
hain na, impact full baate karte hain, ya
phir logon ke hit me baate karte hain, woh
hamisha achcha maana jata hai, kisi bhi society
me, toh ye thought maine apne aapme built
in kiya, abhi jab recently meri video nahi
chal rahi thi,
jab maine thoda comeback
ka socha hai, toh mujhe tha yaar, toh achchi
baatein hoti hain na, woh society mein kabhi
khatam nahi hoti, aur society hi hume dekh
rahi hai, toh, aur YouTube pe aap popular
kyun ho gaya, apni baaton ki wajah se, toh
mujhe aise lagta hai ki, maine bohot
kaam kiya, apni speech ke upar bhi, pauses
kab lene chahiye, impact kab dalna hota hai,
toh jaise ki, society
ka example ek bohot acha rahata hai ki, humein
log hi toh dekh rahe hain, achchi baatein
karoge, 100% log dekhenge, aur agar aapka
kisi cheez
mein passion hai, jaise mera tech mein, mujhe
pata hai, kisi bhi time baatein karalo, uski
baatein mein karunga,
log sunenge, toh mujhe se lagta hai ki, yeh
bohot basic cheez hai ki, mere hisaap se baatein
achchi karne wale log jo hai, chalte hai.
Okay.
Shaz.
You tell no?
No, no, no.
You're the creator.
Don't be a moderator.
You're not a moderator.
No, no, no.
I'm not.
I'm genuinely not moderating.
None of us are talking till Ishaan doesn't.
Yeh nahi ho raha hai.
I don't have anything to tell people.
Because, I'll tell you, mera toh main journalist
tha yaar, tech journalist mein, usse yaha
main kya hoon?
But I'm going to, I'm going to ask you.
I'll keep quiet too.
Both of us are similar.
So then I'll keep quiet too.
No, no, no.
Listen, har ek ka experience and I have a
feeling that you and me have more to contribute
to this conversation kyunki hum log do platform
se aarein.
So tell me, what do you think is the content
creator that,
jo aapka question tha, answer it.
I mean, ek toh pehle define kar lo apne aapko
ki, content creator banna hai ki, you know,
you wanna do.
So I think that journalism still has value,
mereko honestly waise lagta hai, wo ek cheez
hai.
Doosra yeh ki, I completely agree with the
whole consistency bit.
Because mereko toh, usse, because I've seen
that myself, kyunki main toh abhi, I'm starting
fresh.
Like for example, you know, Arun and I immediately
had a conversation ki, Tamil chalu karna hai,
me bolein, tikka chalu kar dete hain, let's
start it.
And the only thing
was, consistent rao, bas wo hi kiya, aur kuch
nahi.
Acha content kiya, consistent rao, like you
said.
Talk to the people.
That's the same, I mean, all of the answers,
just almost, I have nothing new to add but
all of this is helping me in
building what I want to build right now.
Bas utna bolunga.
Wo, maybe will help you also to build what
you want to build.
Aishwarya, I want to ask, and this will come
as a surprise but, do you think journalists
nowadays are overrated?
Nahi.
No, not, yeah, yeah, of course.
But the best part about journalism is...
Journalists right now is that they have platforms,
multiple platforms.
I feel that in a lot of places it has happened
that they
have also come on YouTube, right?
Whether, whatever beat they are covering now.
Okay, so if you have to say that YouTube creators,
the content creators on YouTube are on top
or the journalists are on top?
There is a reason why I am asking this.
In which perspective are they on top?
What's your perspective?
The perspective to look at is the societal
perspective.
Forget yours.
What is the societal perspective?
It's looking fun, right?
I want to see.
Because you are a journalist, you are a content
creator now.
And also, we expect a diplomatic answer.
No, I am not going to become a diplomat, not
at all.
See, what is the problem of a journalist?
He studies from school, right?
Then he is told who, what, how and when to
follow.
So maybe in that, they are not connecting
with the people that the content creators
are.
Okay, tell me one thing.
See, I have noticed it.
Why do tech journalists hate YouTubers?
Exactly!
He is the one who made me do it.
And I have got a very cold vibe from these
people.
Whenever I go to an event, they give me such
a cold vibe.
I think he is laughing but I don't know why.
Okay, I will tell you.
Let's do one thing, let's finish this flow
first.
Then we will take the next question on this.
Okay, come on.
The one thing is that, don't do this for the
money's sake.
Everybody wants to start a YouTube channel
because they will get monetized.
That's what they all want to make.
Okay, I want to make some money out of it.
No, if you have genuine interest, let it be
tech or
whatever.
If you think that you can put it out there
in a very, you know, in a different and unique
way.
And inconsistent.
Then I think it's a good option.
If you are doing just for the money, then
I don't think
this is...
It's not a job.
But why is it not a job?
It shouldn't be one.
Because it's not that specific.
But why is it not a job?
Why is it not a career?
Why is it not a profession?
It's not a job.
It's a career, it's not a job.
I don't see any difference in those two.
It's a career but not a job.
People are only looking at the monetary thing.
They are just forcing them.
You should look at the monetary.
I am not really understanding the it's a career
not a job.
Don't do it for money.
Money, no matter what you do in life.
It will come, it's a by-product.
That's a given.
What's the problem with those people on YouTube?
Those who think that YouTube gives lots of
money.
And if they do it after thinking about it.
That's what I am saying.
They will always be behind the mind, always
thinking about money.
That's what I am saying.
And at that time, when they realize that they
are not going to make money.
Then they will be demotivated.
And they will lose track.
They should know that if you invest 2-3 years
in it.
There is a high chance that you will be successful.
And money will follow.
But if you think that he has earned this money.
And I will also earn it.
I will do it.
There is no such formula.
That's what I wanted to convey.
But that's for every business.
Every job, every profession.
There is nothing different that we are saying.
In YouTube, the journey is not linear.
In content creation, it's always exponential.
Arun said that he has 3,000 subscribers in
11 months.
That was the path.
And then...
I just want to say something out here.
Hold on to this exponential point.
Because I am going to ask a question on this.
Correct.
Most of it is already covered.
But two things that matter the most.
Obviously, you have to be consistent.
And if someone is going to start today.
I think short videos is the way to go.
That gives you an entry barrier.
Platforms reward.
Obviously.
On YouTube, you just have to play with the
algorithm.
You have to be consistent.
You have to follow a schedule.
That you always have to follow.
And on Instagram, you have to make content
that is share worthy.
That works.
And second thing is, you have to pick a niche.
That comes to you naturally.
Because all of us sitting here.
We didn't choose tech.
Because tech is the most lucrative.
We chose it because we are desperate.
We chose it because we are definitely interested
in it.
Naturally, it came with us.
Because of this, I think these are the two
points.
If you fake it, it will show.
You have to have real passion for it.
There was a question that was asked at one
another.
Can you fake it till you make it?
Not in the current content creation.
It shows.
People are too smart here.
Not in any aspect.
Any aspect.
One tip.
Almost all the points are covered.
Second point is, don't think.
Just act.
Most of the time, we just keep on thinking.
Whenever we.
Stop this video now.
That's what usually happens.
We overthink a lot.
Sometimes.
Because we see a lot of creators doing wonderful
jobs.
Covering most of the things which we dream
of.
Then we suddenly go.
We don't have anything.
What do we do?
Then we plan for something.
Then suddenly we see the same thing.
Which was done by some other people.
It's not about doing the thing today or tomorrow.
It's about just act.
Alright.
We have answered all the questions.
On the topic of exponential growth.
I want to pick that point.
Do you consider yourself.
Are you a celebrity?
No.
Let me put it in a nicer way.
How do you feel when some fan comes.
Comes and talks to you.
Takes pictures with you.
What is the difference between your.
Stardom and a celebrity stardom.
That an actor or an actress has.
Like a Bollywood actor or actress has.
It's more of a brotherly connection.
What happens in a celebrity.
If there's a movie star.
It's always a one way communication.
The person will go, watch the movie.
And come back.
He's commenting.
But he can't hear anything from the front.
It's always one way.
The content creators.
And their followers.
It's always a two way communication.
Because we address them.
It's somewhere happening.
A two way communication.
Second thing.
The relatable vibe.
He's like us.
He did this and that.
And now he makes videos.
The way people approach us.
It's very comfortable.
He won't get stuck.
He'll come and talk to us.
It's very simple.
It's very friendly.
You're absolutely right.
You know what happens.
I'll tell you the reason.
Everyday they're watching us.
We watch the news.
Regularly.
What happens with movie stars.
They watch one or two movies a year.
It's very indifferent.
But when they meet.
And they literally faint.
The die hard fans.
These people.
Tell us about the die hard fans.
Best fan interaction.
This is a long time back.
One and a half year back.
One guy literally came on the road.
In one instance.
He fell down from the bus.
Because he had to walk.
And second.
One guy fainted.
I was on the bike.
And then he was like.
And then he fainted.
For just a minute.
Day before yesterday.
They could not even type the number on the
phone.
Phone doesn't unlock.
Camera doesn't open.
I'll tell you one with me.
Which I thought was an incredible incident.
In a public bathroom.
I am there.
That person is there.
We are in the act.
We are both.
He is in the public bathroom.
He turns around.
He sees me.
He just went completely nuts.
He took the selfie then.
Thank God at the right angle.
If it was a typical selfie angle.
That would have been a problem.
I thought.
He saw Rajeev.
And he turned towards Rajeev.
Shaz you wanted to say something.
Like I said.
The celebrity thing.
They come and say.
My phone is broken.
What can I do?
Go to a service center.
I think.
This is a very interesting point.
That we connect.
We are not on top of a mantle.
We are not on a big platform.
It is not like that.
It isn't like that.
It is a good connection.
I think most of the times.
Besides a selfie or a conversation.
I think most of the time.
We are also asked for advice.
Which phone, which TV, which laptop.
That's become part of our lives.
And that is because what Arun said.
We are there every day.
Telling them the same things.
They just come to us.
And that video will continue with them.
I think celebrities.
If I were to look at it.
From an audience standpoint.
I think celebrities.
Have a higher status.
Their job is to build perception.
For example.
I went to watch a cricket match.
I bought an expensive ticket.
But I was thinking.
How many celebrities.
Can buy a ticket.
But they can't come to a normal stand.
Because they have to build a perception.
That yes, we are on top.
I think it is important to build.
Because.
To watch
A person
You have
Then you
Once a year.
So I think the perception. ...is that it's
inaccessible for a celebrity.
So, the scarcity there...
...increases the perception and aspiration.
I think the exclusivity makes them the celebrity.
Exactly.
It's the status.
Celebrity, obviously, they are higher but...
...I was talking about...
Not necessarily higher, to be honest.
Content creators are failing big celebrities...
...on your date.
That's very obvious.
our video.
has to open YouTube.
a celebrity.
to buy a ticket.
to drive.
to come to a hall.
to sit in a crowd.
become their dad.
I won't take names, but I've had experiences...
...where I've overshadowed people.
Nearly.
It's a reality.
I'm not kidding.
Who made celebrities?
And then people.
Who is making us?
You talk about Bollywood, politicians...
...people who are famous...
...in multiple ways...
...as long as you are...
...top of the hill.
In any field...
...it's a similar experience.
I'll tell you a small story.
Like everyone was saying...
...celebrities are not approachable.
They are YouTubers, everyone agrees.
I'll tell you a place.
DC Chowk in Rohini.
My car is parked there.
And so many approachable people understand
us... ...obviously, because we all share a
brotherly vibe.
He came in the car.
You are Sanchit.
When he wanted to meet me, he showed his hand.
I won't tell you the car's experience.
He gave me a good enough...
...five to six second pose.
And I was like this at that time.
What should I do?
And then he didn't take a selfie.
He didn't take any selfie.
He just called me white for a long time.
And that's it.
And then...
I'll tell you.
I was like, okay.
Listen to my car experience.
It's about Dubai.
And...
Deepak.
The three of us went out for tea at night.
I'm driving.
Porsche Panamera.
Carry is sitting on the side.
We went to a place in Dubai.
It's called Disco Chai.
It's an official name.
We went there and had tea.
The person who was serving us...
...was from Bangladesh.
He was 22-23 years old.
He was a subscriber.
He took a selfie with me.
Then he saw Carry.
He left.
Then he came back.
Can we take a selfie in front of a car?
We said, okay.
Carry and I were standing in the middle.
He took a selfie.
We started drinking tea.
He was standing there.
He said, can we take a selfie inside the car?
I said, okay.
He wanted a selfie in my car.
He sat in the car.
Finally, he got a photo.
He was sitting in the back.
I was in the driving seat.
Carry was sitting next to me.
We're back.
That's good.
Gaurav, tell us something.
Back after 10-15 minutes.
He said, can I sit in the back?
You two can sit in the front.
Then he said, Gaurav sir, can you take a photo?
He gave me his phone.
He said, he'll never get a selfie like that.
There's a car.
I'm in the driving seat.
I took a selfie.
He's sitting behind us.
This is inside a Porsche.
We left.
We discussed.
I said, if he didn't ask, he wouldn't have
got a photo with us.
He wouldn't have got a photo in the car.
He wouldn't have got a selfie.
Why did he ask?
Because he had that comfort.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have got a photo.
Here, he took 3 good photos.
I'm sure he'll tell a big story around to
his friends.
This is the difference of approachability.
Thank God, he didn't say, drive the car.
I would have driven.
As long as I'm free.
As long as I have time.
It doesn't matter.
It's only because he was asking for it.
I'll tell you.
I was at the airport.
A guy came running.
He was using a OnePlus phone.
Zen mode.
In Zen mode, you can't do anything.
He took out his phone.
I was free at that time.
I took a photo from my phone.
I asked, what's your email?
He got the photo.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have got the photo.
Just because there's approachability.
Everybody who's watching the show, remember,
if you meet Gaurav, if he has a car, make
sure you take it.
It's happened many times.
All the time.
Open offer now.
I'll come to that.
Tamil.
Specifically asking him.
Trolling is anonymous.
We've all developed a thick skin.
I don't know.
I'm just presuming.
We continue with our work.
When your peers roast, when your fellow YouTubers
roast, there was an incident with a Tamil.
I would want him to talk about that.
Recently that happened to me.
Where to start?
We've been in the space for a long time.
Most of us got the roasting, trolling, everything.
What we do is, we just ignore and we cross.
That's what we do.
If time and again, you're getting the same
kind of thing, people will start hate you
for the thing which you're not
doing.
That's where you'll
feel uncomfortable.
It happened to me too.
Four years ago, a man said something wrong
in my name.
He uploaded 3-4 videos.
The real face of...
The Tamil version of the video about TG in
Hindi will be uploaded on my channel.
It used to happen.
Someone is making fun of someone who's doing
the video in Hindi and getting some views.
They're following the same thing in Tamil.
I know this and I ignore it.
But it comes to a point where I have to show
my identity
card telling this is my name.
Tamil Selvan is my name and this is my identity
and I don't have to fake it.
This is where it started.
There's a story ahead.
There are a lot of things.
It added up.
Recently what happened is
I saw a video someone was making fun of two
other channels.
One was mine and someone's channel.
Up to a point, I was not worried about that
particular
thing because over the past few years, I came
through a lot
of stuff.
I ignored that one.
Then all of a sudden, I got a lot of negative
things.
Then I thought, what do I have to do?
Either I have to ignore and move on or I have
to speak whatever is in my mind.
Because there are a lot of pressures
I was building for the past few years without
talking
anything.
Because YouTube, we all have our passion,
profession, whatever it is.
I mostly don't often spend time with my friends
and everything.
Most of the time, it's in my YouTube channel
itself.
Comment section, Twitter, everything is there.
The pressure got up to me and suddenly, whatever
that comes into mind, I shot a video.
But I haven't uploaded that.
I didn't upload that video.
I kept it as it is.
I didn't.
Then I stopped it.
Then I came to know that the other person
who was in that video because I initially
texted him bro, this is the thing
that is happening this guy, this particular
channel is
talking about both of us.
What we have to do?
Because I don't have experience in facing
this kind of pure roasting.
What we have to do?
He said, simply ignore.
That's it.
Ignore and move on.
I said, okay.
I used to do that.
I will do that again.
But that other guy went on and commented on
his channel telling that, okay, from now on
I'm your huge fan.
I'm your follower.
Then all the TV channels, all the other YouTube
channels, all the comment section filled with
hate of this particular guy is the biggest
YouTuber.
He apologized
and he commented, you are so rude and you
are not even saying anything.
That pressure got into my mind.
Then I shot the second video not even thinking
anything whatever that comes in my mind, I
shot the video.
That's where I was little bit out of the way.
Whatever that comes in my mind.
I re-edited, but by that time we had some
other issues as well but I committed my subscriber
that I will be uploading the video on Sunday.
Every Sunday I will be uploading a video.
I know the video is not 100%.
I don't have the time to check because the
video has to go live.
So, first thing is
I have pressure from inside.
Second, the day is also I have to upload the
video.
Then I went on with the video.
Once the video is live,
I switched off the phone and everything
I went to sleep.
Suddenly, the next morning, even without seeing
the
comments, I realized that what have I done?
You made a mistake.
I immediately wanted to take the video out
and give
something for my viewers.
This is not me.
This is what is in my mind.
I wanted to say this and I said it like this.
I was thinking.
Then few other people were telling you don't
need to go and
do this.
Just work on it.
Then it started biting.
now we are facing the backlash.
What is the backlash?
Two years back?
No, no, right?
No,
six months.
Six months.
What is the backlash you are facing?
Negative comments in each and every video.
Every video.
I talk about Ratan Tata, I see the negative
comments.
I make a review, telling the phone itself
is not good for
that money, it's not value for money and people
started commenting you are getting some x
amount of money from this brand and you are.
How do you come up from that?
How do you all come up from that?
Yeah.
Let's talk about, he is not spoken, Sanchit
is not spoken,
which I am very surprised about, Sanchit.
What is happening?
No, no, when he told his story, it obviously
happened to me too.
It has happened.
Obviously, when fellow creators say it, it
hurts a lot.
But the best part is what happened to me.
First, I developed full hate within myself
for a month, no doubt.
But then, in the starting days, Shlok and
I used to talk a lot when YouTube started.
He told me that if you hate a creator, you
will never be able to learn from him.
What I did was, when there was a lot of build-up
inside, hate, I said, let's convert it into
actions.
Let's try to work on all this negative energy.
What will happen if you sit quietly in the
corner and show anger?
So now I have become a toxic trait for trolls.
If I don't get hate, I don't get motivation.
I look for it sometimes.
Gaurav, Gaurav.
I will tell you a story about Sanchit.
I think it was 2017 or 2018.
YouTube did a competition.
The YouTube community in India was a little
weak at that time.
I mean the online community, YouTube's community.
The overall community.
Yes.
So there was a
YouTube program where they collaborated with
me.
And they invited for entries.
Okay.
If you want to go on a community post, you
have to upload.
Like if you are a YouTuber, just to make sure
that the YouTube community's blog post gets
a little active.
Okay.
So got some, I think, 3-4 thousand entries.
We shortlisted.
And I had to pick two winners with whom I
will collaborate.
So it was a plan that we did with YouTube.
So there were two winners.
One, I picked Sanchit.
One, I picked Samreen.
Young girl was doing some sketch videos.
So we are watching Sanchit right now, where
he is.
And the other one, I think Samreen has a lot
of millions of followers.
And I remember we shot a video in the hotel
room.
After 2017.
That's a great statement.
We shot a video in the hotel room.
Amazing statement.
Imagination.
How did you feel that time?
We shot a video.
How did you feel?
It was very crazy.
It was discussed in my entire college that
Technical Guruji has made a video with
Sanchit.
So it was crazy.
It was a very crazy moment.
In fact, I also told in my JoshTalk that how
Technical Guruji had a very big, important
part in my life.
I will always be thankful to him.
Recently, Carry Mena TV.
Carry is younger brother.
What is that?
What happened there?
It was so much fun.
Let's have some fun.
Let me show you something.
Let me show you what Carry had messaged me.
Okay.
I think we spoke the day before yesterday
We spoke
the day before yesterday.
One second.
See this.
Let me show you.
When Carry uploaded it, he said, Hello Sir.
I made a small parody of yours.
I hope I was able to get close to your character
and you don't take negative.
Oh.
Really enjoyed playing your character and
got to learn a lot.
He sent me the link of the video.
I was on a flight at that time.
I replied to him.
Let me show you.
Hello brother.
How are you?
I just saw the video.
I was on a flight.
I was coming from New York.
I was changing my flight.
I just saw the video.
I was sitting in the lounge and everyone was
laughing.
I was wearing a laptop.
It was solid.
It must have taken a lot of effort.
Carry is saying, Thank you so much.
It means a lot.
We are having fun.
When the iPhone 15 was launched, we planned
something together again.
But at that time, I was traveling and you
couldn't shoot.
The thing is, there are two things.
If someone is really attacking you for no
reason other than
just to bring you down, it's a different side
altogether.
In Carry's case, we are people from the community.
We are having fun.
At that time, I say, see how he is, how he
is,
how I am.
It's fun.
So the parody he made, I mean, I am seeing
attention to
detail in all the characters.
And people have liked my character the most.
I am enjoying it.
Any thoughts Shlok on roasting?
I also align with the same thing that there
are two types
of criticism.
One is where there is no meaning to it and
they just want
to bring you down.
And sometimes there is a way where either
people are making fun of us or we have done
something wrong.
So a consumer or a viewer may get angry.
They may abuse in anger.
But it is our job to understand that whether
he is trying
to forcefully insult us or he has a problem
and he is commenting on us.
So I think, like in the case of Carry.
The good thing about Carry is that I don't
know about
others.
I mean, if I call him now, he will say, hello
brother, how
are you?
He has that image.
What you see on camera and what you get behind
the camera is a very different thing.
Yesterday or day before yesterday, I did a
reel post on Instagram.
Vishal, the guy who wrote Carry's sketch.
Deepak told me yesterday that he forwarded
it to the group.
And he tells Vishal that you should take the
writing fees from Gaurav.
He is also using your dialogue.
He is having fun.
Now, even with IBTR, till now, there will
be so many preconceived notions in people's
minds.
Immediately after looking at this, it is going
to change.
Because behind the camera, a lot of things
are different.
A lot of things are said in front of the camera.
Even between tech YouTubers.
But actually, they might be very good friends
and it might be planned.
Or it might be said that I am going to talk
about this.
Before going ahead, let's talk and do it.
Can I say a small thing?
It's a very small thing.
I mean, I tell you.
If you all align with Shahid, I am telling
you what I think.
This YouTube is a new thing.
It's a very new thing.
And if you look very carefully at your deep
inside, it is a
very lonely journey.
I mean, if I go to my friend, I tell him that
I didn't get
so many views today.
This topic was made.
I was talking on AI.
People didn't like it.
Someone will understand a little.
If I talk to you, talk to Shlok, talk to Gaurav,
talk to
someone.
You will immediately understand that this
was your shortcoming.
If we do the same work a little closeness.
So when there are talks, it makes you feel
a little relaxed.
It doesn't make you feel a little lonely.
So I think that in fact, not only on the collaboration
camera.
We should also talk to each other.
Because you don't know right now.
We have no idea what are the side effects
of YouTube.
You are so new.
So I feel that there is still a lonely journey
of tech YouTubers.
I feel so.
Not tech, but any creator.
Any creator.
Actually, there are side effects.
I mean, we saw what Lilly Singh was also going
through and everything.
So that's there.
You guys also went through some sort of controversies,
right?
Oh yeah, yeah.
I was hoping for the next question.
No, no, I didn't know.
No, I addressed it.
It's okay.
No, no, there are a lot.
Yeah, it's the same.
Oh, sorry.
No, I didn't know that either.
No, no, yeah.
The thing is, like you mentioned, there are
two types of trolls.
One is obviously in a fun way that CarryMinati
has done.
Which is his job.
Which he does.
And the second is to bring someone down.
So what happened with us is that each one
of us were working with a certain brand.
And we were working with them for such a long
time.
It was quite clear.
Entire tech community was working with them.
But one tech content creator did not get to
work with that brand.
And that pissed that person off.
Because of that, he wanted to retaliate in
some way or the other.
We just caught in the crossfire.
And it happened that a lot of negativity that
came from that video completely shattered
us.
I'm not lying.
We were completely devastated.
We were thinking, what did we do wrong?
Because that was what was happening the entire
time.
And so it happened.
And then we thought, what should we do?
And we did make a video.
But later we realized that we shouldn't have.
You shouldn't have.
I also, I generally don't see videos.
That time I had seen that.
And I don't.
And the best part to let go this is that you
should, like I
was talking with Sanchit off camera some time
ago, that if everyone is working on their
own and minding their own business, so the
other person should not get in the way to
bring someone else
down.
Because at the end of the day, we all have
a different
style of working.
I might not agree with anyone else's style,
but that is
their style.
I don't get in their way.
Similarly, I do not want someone else to get
in our way.
So that has happened with us at that time.
So those 3-4-5 months, whatever they were,
that was one of the worst periods of our YouTube
journey.
And like Sanchit just mentioned, YouTube is
very lonely.
And I couldn't share that problem or discuss
it with anyone.
No one would understand.
And obviously I can't be able to, I won't
be able to
discuss it with fellow YouTubers as well.
Because we don't interact that regularly.
We don't interact.
It was a lesson learned that whenever something
like that happens, don't take any action.
Just go on and mind your own business because
that will be useful and that worked for us.
But I think one of the most important things
if you notice,
all the people who have spoken so far, everybody
has at the end of it said there was a lesson.
I think trolls, negativity, absolutely agree,
there are two types of negativity, but I think
the comment section is your greatest learning
tool.
Enemy also.
Koi aur nahi aayega aapko guide karne ke liye
better because as you said, kabhi galti ho
jaye and the people flame you for it, you
learn from it and become better.
He is six months down the line, he is a much
better, where they have gone after the lesson
they have learned.
Wo jo ek aapka six months of loneliness tha,
at maybe your worst period, but see where
you are today.
Most of it will come from that six month journey.
Kitni learning thi, kitna lesson tha.
You never fail, you either learn or you win.
I think this is a very important thing.
It's not that never fail, a lot of times there
are
instances where things like this have happened.
The channel has gone down, views have gone
down and the key going down and it never comes
up.
Aise hua hai.
Either thing is, I'll tell you honestly, ignore
kar do,
that is the best.
If someone's trying to pull you down, it simply
means you stand above them.
Yeah, yeah.
You're important enough for them to want to
pull you down.
My point was, ek bar wo jane ke baad, how
do you come up, especially for an established
person.
Ek baat sunna hai, Devendra yeh cheez hui,
wo phase nikla, let's say kal yeh cheez dubara
ho jati hai, now you are in
a better position to deal.
Much better, yes.
Toh ek baar ka experience tha, but now it's
a learning for
a lifetime.
Correct.
Exactly.
Toh I think, jo agar sunn raha hai koi isko
abhi, jisne wo sakta hai aaj tak yeh phase
nahi kiye hai, toh usko already pata hai ki
kya karne, kyuki hamare experiences hain.
Toh I think, ignore karo, side nikalo, aagey
badho, that's
the best way out.
And that's the learning jo idhar se idhar
se aari hai.
Jaise abhi aapne bola ki, jab itna phase down
jata hai, toh usse bahar kaise nikalna hai.
Toh ek simple sa funda hai, jo ham apne 10-12
saal ki journey mein apply kara hai hamne,
and that is always go back to the basics.
Absolutely.
We just go back to the basics.
If you go back to what you were doing and
jis cheez ke liye aapko logon ne, they have
given you the love, you go back
to that again, do it better, with the learning,
I think
Arun, you come back.
But I'll tell you again, yeh jo basics hai
na, yeh basics
bhi because of algorithm change hote rehte
hai, and I don't know how many will understand
this, but YouTube pe, jo 6-5-6 saal chal raha
tha, basics, ki yeh yeh aapne karna chahiye,
wo agar abhi
aap apply karte ho videos ko, your videos
will not work.
But Arun, I'll tell you the reasons why.
Because wo basics ho gaye alag, because everyone
else has probably gone up, wo basics abhi
basics rahe nahi, basics have gone to a different
level.
So according to me, you have to keep evolving
and understanding.
But that's the basics.
That is true.
Understanding is the basics.
I am not saying ki jo basics jaise aap kar
rehte hai, waise
hi karte hoon.
Pehle hum text karte the, phir hum videos
pe aaye, uss time jab hum videos pe aaye,
kuch content creation, influencer, kuch bhi
nahi tha.
We just did it because humein laga ki kuch
gap hai jo hum fill kar sakte hain.
So we tried, we wanted to do different kind
of videos and that worked for us.
So our basics was to always evolve, like he
said, ki evolve to karne hi padega, ab short
videos agar aa rahe hain, agar aap short videos
nahi banaoge, that means you are harming yourself.
Usse kisi ka kuch fayada nahi hone wala, ki
aap ussi pe gogi, nahi mai to long videos
hi banaunga, kyuki mere ko to long videos
hi banaane aate hain.
Short videos is not my thing.
That is not my thing.
Pivoting is part of being.
So basics is that you should always be with
the trend.
Kahi baar agar ahead of the trend ho toh,
toh sab sahchi baat hai.
Be the disruptor or you will be disrupted
is a basic.
And I think Shlok, what Shlok has done with
the overlays, I think he is with the curve,
ahead of the curve, I must say.
Jo next category after content hai, that is
definitely
product and he has built a really nice product.
Yeah, yeah.
Or not one, multiple products.
Toh wo ek jacket hai.
Yeh jacket kisi ki hai yaar?
Yeh badhi achi jacket hai.
Badhi achi jacket hai.
Yeh monetization mein e-commerce, that's also
going to be huge, right?
I was coming to this, like how do you see
it
as a business?
I think this is a great topic, even I am going
to get into
this.
Main apna waise is pehle purane wale topic
mein apna opinion deta hu.
Kyuki I feel ki sometimes ignoring is not
enough.
Kyuki mereko aisa rakhta hai ki market mein
jo cheez jada boli jaati ho, sach ban jaati
toh agar ek banda kuch bol raha hai and wo
das bandon ko inspire kar deta wo same cheez
bolne ke liye, toh cheez sach ban jaati, agar
saamne ala banda reply na kare.
Mere kyaal se…
Off camera hai.
Yeh hi wali baat mein abhi aapko bolna chahata,
jab baaki log bol rahe the ignore ka, I completely
agree with you.
Mere zaap se theek hai, agar matlab it does
not make sense aur koi usko wo nahi dera hai,
tawajjo nahi dera hai, toh
it is okay.
But agar if it, I see it becoming a thing
and mereko lagta
hai ki nahi yeh galat hai, toh main toh fight
karne ke liye ready, main apna stand lene
ke liye, main laddi pe chal
rahe ho.
Aap gali mein chal rahe ho aur kuttey aapko
attack kar rahe hain, ek tarika yeh ki aap
ruk ke her ek pe patthar
pekhoge, patthar katham ho jayenge surat-darbaad
ho sakta hai aur kuttey bhadte ja rahe hain,
second option is aap unko biscuit fekho, toh
kuttey aap ke beeche pooch laate bheyenge,
toh my thing is ki agar aap ignore na karo
aur agar aap jawaab dere ho, toh bhai that's
what they want, they want more attention,
that's what they want, toh wo cycle ban jayega,
ek hai ki kutton ko jawaab dena,
ek hai ki jo actual reality hai, wo logon
wo dikhana, bhai
but wo kab tak karoge wo toh batao, but mere
kya se, at the end toh ignore karna hi padega,
at the end toh ignore karna padega, but did
you answer to the guy who had, I remember
this story, I
don't know how many people remember but jab
e-commerce brand launch ki layers launch kiya
tha, wo coding ka, arre
na aapko simple 3 baat, main flight pe tha
and you asked me ki maine reply karna chahiye
ya nahi, we were going to US
or somewhere at that
time, na wo simple story azaat hoon, ek hua
gaya hum website bana rahe the, website mein
mockups hote hain, sari cheezon hote hain,
wo publicly available hota hain, and
code jo hai, aap google ka code copy karo,
koi aapko kuch bolega nahi, kyu hi it is
not copyrighted ya koi ispe patent attendant
toh laga nahi, humne ek developer hire raha
tha, usne halka halka code idhar udhar utha
liya, and ek jo competitor tha, kyu hi hum
market mein agar ghus rahe hain, skins ki
hum market mein jaa rahe hain, toh
of course jo pehle jo competitor uski market
jaayegi, toh
wo humko bhai publicly aake ki, haan yeh kar
diya, yeh copy karta, yeh karta, wo karta
hai, manager wo theek hai bhai, haan hogi
hogi galti, theek hai koi baat nahi, but uske
baad like wo humare
upar ek legal notice bhai ne vej diya, maine
poore check
kar waha hai ki bhai yeh isme kya hai, yeh
toh basic cheez
hain, mockup toh publicly available hota hain,
sari cheez hain aisa kuch, it is not, it is
legally okay to do it,
yaar Instagram ne bhi
toh stories copy kari hain, humne aisa kuch
khaas copy nahi kar raha tha, humne website
bhi change kar di thi, but uske baad we filed
ek, humne wapas legal notice bheja, ki hum
defamation file karenge, agar aap jo aap cheez
kar raho, publicly kar raho,
uske baad then he stopped, kyunki usko bataegi,
usko jisko actual solution chahiye hota hai
na, wo publicly halla nahi bachaata, and mereko
wo cheez bhagi ki, of course, yaar aap kahin
bhi kisi market aap jaoge, log peeche kheechne
aa jaate hain, toh
it depends ki kab reply karna hai, kab nahin
karna hai, so
you replied basically and you took it forward
and, ab wo
uska kaam ban chuke, wo baar baar kuch kuch
naya lata rhta hai, main dekhta rhta hoon,
usko maza aa gaya aise hi humein, but even
I only
feel like you have to give a reply because
we don't have to bottle up our mental health
also, because, yaar taste wise, taste wise,
agar wo nahi, if he does, no I myself roster
companies, so I, he is doing it hot, I do
skits based on
you know, what are
the, no he is way of thinking, it's a controller,
yeh bahut difficult to understand, ki troll
ne sach bola hai mere baare mein galat, ya
phir wo faalto bol raha hai, agar aap realize
kar gaye apni mistake, toh shayad wo aapki
sabse greatest learning ho
gaye, aap curve hi badal raha hai, but I agree
with Gaurav ki like, bhai at the end toh ignore
karna hi padega na, haan haan, mada, otherwise
it is going to affect you, let's go back to
the question that we are all waiting for,
what you are doing, journey
kaise hai, e-commerce, if it's the big one,
do you believe that, does it take you away
from your core, sabse bada question hi hai,
ki jo, jis cheez ne aapko banaya hai, kya
usmein ab aap utna hi passion aur time daal
par rahe ho, content creator?
It,
mere kya haal se toh, 100% it is the future,
100% ek product ko agar aap distribution jo,
mada hum essentially videos bana rahe hain
hum sab log, agar aap ek accha product ek
aise cheez aap le aao, jo aapki audience isme
interested hai, it is a billion
dollar business, I am, main usko bilkul kam
nahi kar raha, agar audience fit sahi hai,
jaise
I have talked to physics wala, he has built
a billion
dollar business, Unacademy ke founders bhi
start unhoni YouTube se kar raha tha, kaafi
saari India mein log hai,
jino ne business banaya hai YouTube ko leke,
bas mere kya haal se dikkat hi ho jaati
hai, usually jab log start karte hain, wo
product ko for granted le leta hai, unko lagta
hai ki, manlab,
We can make a product and the audience will
buy it.
I think to build that product, whether it's
a physics
product or my own reference, it took us 3
years to make a skin.
It took us 3 years to learn clothes,
I have a whole industry to learn.
And if I remove the layers from TechBurner,
because there
is no distribution of TechBurner, but layers
in itself, no
one else in the market is able to beat that
product.
I am saying globally.
No one else is able to make a product like
that.
Same thing that we are making in clothing,
H&M, Zara, all the international brands, the
price point at
which we are making jackets, no one is able
to make it.
So I think if the product is good, then it
becomes easy to leverage that thing.
But the reputation you have made, what you
do today, the
way you have got love from people, credibility
from people, when you make a product and your
jacket goes out, have you not got criticism
that it has become commercial?
Number 2, now you are not making yourself
vulnerable, that people will start saying,
I bought a jacket, it turned out to be useless,
my button
came off.
I am not saying this is the truth,
I am saying I keep getting asked this question.
Is this vulnerability in your mind, at the
back of your
head?
100%.
I mean, when things are going on so publicly,
and
negativity spreads more quickly.
Now, if there is a slight delay in delivery,
if it is of
one person, then it will create more noise.
The thousands of happy customers, lakhs of
happy customers,
they just put up a photo and stay happy.
But negativity spreads.
But in our case, because the audience showed
so much trust, this has not happened.
There was a very positive response.
And I am personally very happy.
And I feel very grateful that our community
shows so much love.
But, in my opinion, it is obviously your intention.
If it is your intention to provide genuine
value, then the customer in front of you feels
it.
So, there is no problem in that.
How do you change your audience into a community?
This will be very important.
Because, there is an audience that watches
your videos, and there is an audience that
will buy your clothes.
Right?
So, how do you change that?
Or, you know, how do you build a community
in general?
Even B-Bomb has done it.
How do you build a community?
In my opinion, there is no rocket science.
In my opinion, the product is very simple.
If you show it well, it will sell well.
But, I will actually call it the opposite.
That, I felt that when I didn't start this
brand, that if I
do a promotion, then I am selling to the audience
of Techburner.
They will feel weird.
This is my question.
But, it was the opposite.
When we built our product, we shared the whole
story, people got more connected with us.
That, this guy is doing something, he is trying
something.
And, the more we share, that we are doing
this, we are
doing this, we are doing all these things,
we are planning this, people get more attracted.
And, I didn't expect this.
I thought it was the opposite.
That, if we sell, people will go away.
It has become very commercial.
But, when we started showing, people started
coming closer.
More people came.
And, this happens every time.
I mean, whenever we share our story, of layers,
of
overlays, people get more connected.
Maybe, it is an inspiration.
Maybe, they see that we are working hard.
We are just selling to earn money.
But, I don't know what it is.
But, I try that our products that we are making,
are strong.
And, your time management, are you still being
able to put
in the same amount of time that you used to
do before, in content creation for Techburner?
No.
This is not possible.
For a lot of people, that's what's missing.
I think, for everyone.
I mean, we all work so hard.
You are also running so many businesses.
We all do different things.
And, everyone has less time.
But, earlier, I wasn't able to give that much
time.
Earlier, I was a beggar.
But, there is a difference.
Earlier, the optimization was not that good.
Now, things are optimized.
I think, with time, we used to do it in 8
hours.
Now, we can do it in 1 hour.
So, if we have 1 hour today, it's enough for
the earlier editing comparison.
I think, that's done, over time.
Here, it's also about team building.
You have to build teams also.
That's the most crucial part.
I mean,
I think, it's your role now to build the best
team.
That also reduces loneliness.
Team building, reduces a lot of loneliness,
which I felt.
Over time.
I don't feel lonely at all.
I, because, it is a, on-term journey.
I feel,
I might be alone, but I am not lonely.
Yeah.
I enjoy it.
I am alone, but I don't have a problem with
being alone.
I think, community building, if it happens,
community is built, then, it happens for a
short time.
Let's say, 5 years, 6 years.
I feel, community, is a fear.
Like, I have a self-opinion.
I have made a new theory.
Maybe, I am wrong.
Tell me.
I am learning.
I think,
I have made a new theory.
It happened after a while.
It faded.
A legacy, what does it do?
It works quietly.
I mean,
I am working.
I am doing the same work.
I am improving.
It's been many years.
Come, see, go.
Bro, I will give you an example, for content
creators.
Our audience, every year, people move away
from it.
The one who was watching us till yesterday,
he got a job.
He is not watching you now.
He was in college.
He was watching you.
And the new guy, who got a new phone, he will
start watching you.
So, the crop, will always, it won't be like,
it's been 10 years, and he is watching you
since day 1.
No.
And if it is like that, then his interest
may be, earlier
it was more.
Now, he watches you sometimes.
What is the difference?
So, the crop will always come out, and the
new crop will come.
But what is the difference in what you said?
When you build a community, that is a term.
And a legacy, it eventually comes to, the
legacy is about community.
So, what is the difference?
I wish,
I could name drop a bit, but I won't do that.
For obvious reasons.
I have seen, those who have cult following,
after a time, just as a general statement,
I am giving someone's name, let's talk about
vloggers.
He had a community.
Means, I will say this, if he said, today
at 12,
I am coming here,
India Gate, everyone comes.
But, over time, that cult following, goes
like this.
But, if there is a vlogger, who is doing his
work, quietly,
and like this, means, he is not doing community,
community, he is not giving a name.
So, I have just noticed, that, the line of
the creator
increases.
May be I am wrong.
But, I feel that, he is banning his followers,
in such a
way, that, do more community, community, cult
following happens.
But, you are right about one thing, till date,
in history,
you, from the time, humanity has come.
This is absolutely right.
Cult following, it's called a cult, because,
it is for a
period of time.
There is no such thing, as cult following
forever.
This is absolutely right.
According to me, two things, like, I was listening
to everyone, so, there are two types of people,
one type of people, who know you, and, one
type of people, who want to become like you.
So, like, when a person, is young, or a child,
so, may be,
he wants to become like you.
When he grows up, then he realizes, no, I
don't want to become like him.
I want to become like Shahrukh Khan.
Or, I want to become like someone else.
So, the people, who,
So, the people, who want to become like you,
or, the things you are doing, they want to
do something like that, that,
is your, actual, follower base, community,
or cult,
whatever you want to call it.
And, the people who know you, okay, they know
you, but, may be, they want to watch your
videos sometimes.
So, I, personally, look at it, by dividing
it into these
two.
If you are doing something different, something
strong, then, there is a question here, this
community, is it same, for, YouTube also,
for, social media, is it the same?
I mean,
Instagram, Facebook, everything is different.
Everything is different.
In fact,
I also want to ask, because, we have,
Rajivji here, you know, as a medium, you have
been, on every platform, including TV,
YouTube, social media, social media, you are
doing very, very well.
How is it different, working, with, community?
I mean, how do you build a community, on each
platform?
Is it different, or, is it the same?
No, actually, there is a lot of difference.
First example, the same person, who follows
you on YouTube, and, who follows you on Instagram,
he comes with a completely, different psychology,
when he, opens Instagram, and, when he comes
to watch you on YouTube.
It could be the same person, but, he comes
with a very,
different psychology, of what he, what he
wants to consume, on a different platform.
When he turns on the TV, with what mindset
did he turn it on?
When he turns on the radio, and he is going
home from office, to, you know, somewhere
else.
This, community expectation, from the same
person, he can have four different expectations,
from you.
Number one,
I think, this is a very important, realization,
for all of
us, but more important, for all those people,
who will now come up.
That you, don't think that, your YouTube following,
has
become very good.
So, you will go on Instagram, even if you
have, pivoted
very well, but the person, is not expecting
you, to do the
same thing.
You know, you open Instagram, you want immediately,
you may have only, one, one and a half minutes,
you want, either
just entertainment, you want your mind to
be, you didn't
search for it, it was delivered to you.
I will also add a secret to this, that I,
like I also, when
I go, one day I went to the bank,
I was at work,
So I met a girl there, she took a selfie with
me and all
that
And she didn't even know what a tech burner
is
She didn't even know that I make long videos
She just saw my video on Facebook
And the 3-minute video that we cut and put
on Facebook
She just saw that video
And then I went and checked
That our Facebook audience
The YouTube Shorts audience
The YouTube audience
The Instagram audience
All of them are 60% different 60% audience
is different everywhere
And a lot of people don't even know that we
make long videos A lot of people don't even
know that we do tech reviews
A lot of people think that I just upload photos
It is like that
You have to have a long-format video
Even for Shorts and for Reel
You can't just put whatever you made for the
Reel
You have to put a little short
If you take for granted a platform's community
or following You will not be able to build
anything ever again
So Arun, the answer to this thing is that
Community building is per platform
It is not
If I take my TV audience
It will definitely come
It will get some initial momentum
Because people are like, I have seen this
on TV
But the rest of it
Has to be organically built
And it is for that platform only Right As
an entire
I have so many platforms
I don't use the word community Which platform,
Gaurav
Which platform do you think is more relevant
Or probably the platform of the future
Next What is the next big thing
Let's hear it from everybody
Let's start from Arun
What's the next big thing?
Reels is going to be the big thing for me.
It's been 3 years.
What's the next big thing?
It will continue.
It will continue for sure.
Because they are already working on EIS and
a lot of stuff.
So, it will continue.
I think Instagram Reel is doing pretty well
right now.
But I don't see it as a long-term thing.
I think people will get bored eventually.
But we don't know when that will happen.
Let's hope it doesn't happen.
We are working so hard.
Exactly.
But, yes, next.
I'll answer.
Oh, sorry.
I think the next big thing is going to be
Metaverse.
And that is what I believe.
Something big is going to happen.
But it will take time.
It's not like it will happen tomorrow or the
next year.
YouTube Shorts will co-exist.
But, yes, one thing that I see as a platform
is that the shoppable experience, social commerce,
will increase with the help of Shorts, with
the help of Reels.
And I'm seeing that, as of now, there are
links in the description.
So, TikTok has been testing this in other
countries.
As soon as I wear a T-shirt or an overlay
coat on the
video, if I tap on it, from there only I can
buy anything.
You know, you actually answered the next big
thing already.
So, take it back.
That without it looking like it is commercial
e-commerce, great content, without making
you say, buy this, do this,
you will have to do it organically.
But that is where the future really lies.
I'd love to hear from you.
MetaQuest, I don't think it's going to take
long.
Even I, in three to four years...
How many of us have used MetaQuest 3?
If you use it, you immediately come to know
that is what is going to really appeal to
the audiences in coming two, three years.
Photos are still messy.
So, not a lot of people...
Who does all this mess?
You can see the potential.
I disagree.
I was taught as a kid to sit a little further
away and
watch TV.
The small TV, 30-inch TV, sit a little further
away and
watch it.
A small 30-inch TV.
What is a 21-inch TV?
I had a 21-inch TV.
You know, the eyes are here.
4K, 4K, two TVs with the eyes here.
Put the headset on and watch.
I don't find it healthy.
It's a matter of health too.
See, again, this is the difference between
Gen X, Gen Y, Millennials.
The people who are 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17
years old have these two.
They will be on it all the time.
Because you don't have that baggage.
I disagree.
I don't think it's healthy.
It's healthy.
That's a different topic altogether.
AI, is it healthy or unhealthy?
It's different.
I'm saying that there has been a lot of testing
even for,
you know, beyond Gen Z also.
Right?
The thing that is humanly very awkward, no
one does it.
Why do 3D glasses fail?
Why do people not want to watch 3D movies?
Even in the cinema hall, we don't...
To strap on something, to keep something on,
that is not generational.
But everybody is expecting the Apple Vision
Pro to change things.
Exactly.
I completely disagree.
I feel that it will be the biggest failure
for Apple.
I used PS VR to make that video in 25 days.
I vomited three times to make that video.
That's what I'm saying.
I've been doing it since then.
You're using it while you're standing and
moving.
It's a different thing.
If you're watching a movie while sitting,
it's a different thing.
If you are moving, content around you is moving.
For example, FPV drones, you can't fly it
while standing.
A FPV drone pilot will always fly it while
sitting.
Because if he flies it while standing, he
can see that I'm flying.
He can't feel the gravity.
So there's a disconnect.
It's the same thing.
But if you do it while sitting, it's a different
thing.
There's a test I'm talking about for 12 to
15 year olds.
95% of them said after 15 minutes.
The wow factor.
Oh my God!
The world I've gone into.
After 15 to 20 minutes, would you buy it?
Would you want to do it again?
94% said no.
But the harsh reality is, whether you like
it or not, there will be a change in the future.
Yes.
But is this the future?
Is this the future?
It's not in perfect form.
Please understand.
It's in its third generation.
It will be much easier.
You'll be wearing glasses.
You remember the Google Glass?
It was back in 2011-2012.
I think something will happen.
If it comes in contact lenses,
I see a future.
I think it makes reality happen.
Vision Pro.
And even nowadays, like the iPhone is coming
up with special videos.
I feel Apple,
I don't know if they have a plan, but what
if they've come up with a different platform
where you can load special videos so that
it will be more lively.
Maybe that's something which can be looked
at.
You'll still have to wear it.
Yeah, but maybe like what Guruji said, what
if it's like a glass?
Eventually, it will go that way.
Yeah.
It can't be that big.
It cannot carry that.
I remember my first VR experience.
It was with Samsung S7.
When S7 and S7 Edge came, the Galaxy VR, where
you had to put your phone.
The phone had a quad HD screen.
So comparatively, it used to be sharp.
And at that time, it had all those different
theater modes
that it will create a virtual theater.
I think it was in 2016.
It was fun.
And today, when I tried
Apple Vision Pro in June,
I had a 45 minutes in-depth session.
It was night and day.
I mean, there's no comparison from any VR
to Apple VR.
Google Cardboard to Apple VR.
Exactly.
Google Cardboard, where your phone is connected.
It's the same thing.
The phones used to be so big.
And today, they're folding.
Basically, things will change in the future.
It would be like a normal glass.
This has a camera.
This has a speaker.
In this, you'll see the position and everything.
We're going to move forward with smartphones.
Whether it's 5 or 10 years from now.
Exactly.
What is the one future tech that you are seeing
future in?
I mean, AI.
Variable technologies.
Humane.
Humane kind of things.
Maybe you...
I don't think it's a replacement for a smartphone.
That's very clear.
You know, the next big thing can be, but it's
not a replacement for a smartphone.
We're talking about two completely different
devices, right?
Even though,
I did a video on Instagram.
The death of the smartphone.
Got millions of views.
I showed it to Humayun.
But the point of it is that if you are really,
really
truthful, that's not a smartphone replacement.
No, but sir, eventually, what my opinion here
is, today, we have a mobile phone that does
all our work.
At one time, we needed a calculator.
We needed Walkman.
Digital cameras.
Multiple things.
Today, phone is capable to do everything.
166 standalone devices replaced by a smartphone.
So, phone is the hub.
When we go to a brand's presentation, they
always show their chart.
This, this, this.
Phone is in the center.
Four things.
Smartwatch, this, this.
This is the thing.
Today, the phone is capable to do everything.
But if you don't have a phone, you forgot
your house, then you are handicapped.
You can't do anything.
So, this still is a hassle that I have to
carry this device with me.
If I don't have this, then I'm nothing.
Right.
I have to charge this.
I have to see this.
The future would be where we can replace this
with something that is in me.
Exactly.
Or with me altogether.
Yeah, yeah.
You guys are like into things going inside
your body?
Yeah.
Not at all.
It can be a chip.
No, no.
I would not prefer that.
But, but.
Irshad.
Put it nicely.
You know.
Those are not called wearables.
They are called insertables.
And just by the name itself,
I think it's weird.
I think.
I don't want an insertable in me.
I mean, maybe a smart band that I'm wearing.
Projecting things.
Or a glass or something.
I mean, eventually something that is with
me.
Flawless.
I mean, without even me having to think about
whether I'm keeping it or not.
It is part of me.
And it will happen.
Exactly.
I'm with him.
Tech.
We don't have to carry the tech.
In this, I have a challenge.
Right now, the biggest problem is that if
I have an image in my mind or if I have some
information in my mind, if I want to put it
in my mobile, then I just have fingers.
I will have to type with my fingers or I can
speak with my
voice.
I think the next big thing that will come
because I have the same problem with the watch.
I have the same problem with the eyeglasses.
I think the next big thing that will come
is that it's a little weird to put a chip
in the brain.
But there are such technologies that have
come now.
Neuralink has also come.
There are a few more things.
Which directly interact with our brain.
I'm telling you.
Think of an example.
We have smart homes now.
Alexa is on.
Light is connected.
I will tell it.
Alexa, turn on the light.
It's a good thing.
But still, I have to say the best would be
that I just have to think that.
I think that's the future.
And it will happen.
It will happen in 10 years.
In 10 years.
We are ready for that.
No, no.
It has to happen.
And this is a possibility.
In medical terms,
I think nanotech and everything will be better.
But I feel something which is connecting.
A part of a tech connecting our brain cells.
I'm not.
I mean, I disagree with that.
Maybe that might be the future.
I think that will be the future.
The voice will be better.
This, that, everything.
There will be telepathy.
100%.
That's what I was expecting.
So think about it.
I will send you a love letter.
Not having to carry the tech is what we are
going towards.
This is going to happen.
And one thing I also feel like the way AI
is coming and right now.
we are simply using the generative AI to help
our day-to-day tasks.
But in the future, I think maybe if smartphone
companies are able to implement it nicely,
then everyone would have a personal assistant
of their own, tuned to their habits,
their tasks, everything.
And it's possible that in 2024, AI could be
a big buzzword or marketing term for smartphones
to come.
2023 was the buzzword and marketing term for
AI.
2024 will be the result of that.
I think so far, the person who is using AI,
yes, it's great that this person is right.
But in 2024-2025, the job of the person who
is not using AI will go.
It will go, 100%.
And this means that AI will become a need.
And at this time, it is so powerful, I can
show you a video.
But what exactly are we supposed to catch
up with AI?
I think everything will be replaced.
Every single thing.
What is the thing which we have to catch up?
At least get to know how to use AI.
But why?
You need to be in the…
But why do we need to walk to AI?
There are people…
So that to you, okay.
You said, but why?
Okay.
If you are using AI, you are able to do what
you do right now.
You'll be able to do it 10x better, 10x faster.
But if you are not, then like he was saying,
next year, the person who is doing it will
be 10x better and 10x faster than you and
you'll be left way behind.
But what exactly are we looking at?
I'll show you one thing.
It's a tool that can be used…
No, see, that's the whole point is that if
you start
saying, which tool?
You look…
See, this thing is not going out only to us,
content
creators out here.
It's going out to the rest of the world.
Here, many different people will come from
different professions.
The point is not which.
The point is, what do you do and which AI
is applicable to you?
When you wake up in the morning and you go
to sleep at night, you do 7-8 core tasks every
day, right?
Out of those 7-8 core tasks, how many can
now help with AI?
Right?
Okay.
From imagination to your thinking to your
scripting to coming up with an idea.
But like I said, that scripting part is like
it's some…
A computer is generating that idea for you.
I'm not saying it's perfect right now.
But it's not perfect.
But that's not the point.
Computers are generating ideas.
How is it doing?
Large language models, basically they are
trained to think like humans.
So, the way we have got education, the computers
have been trained, they have been given large
data set.
But do you think that the time will take…
Let me tell you an interesting thing.
It will be clear to you.
When humans heard about fridge for the first
time, all the industries thought, make a fridge.
There is money in it.
It will be in everyone's house.
The one who earned the most money was the
one who had cold beverages.
Coca-Cola, Maza.
The one who used that fridge, cooled it down
and put it
back in its place.
So, AI is that thing.
AI is a fridge.
The one who will use AI to make tools, that
will work.
The second part, which is a layer up, that
AI needs a lot
of data.
So, I am telling you, the biggest companies
in the future,
will be more rich, will have more data, and
crazy things
will come out.
This is a reality which we should understand.
Even we don't know what AI is going to be.
We can only talk, but AI is that fridge, from
which we
don't know what by-product is going to come
out.
This is a fact.
Now, will you keep a cake or a drink in that
fridge, or a
healthy salad?
That is on you.
Or maybe beer.
According to me,
AI will change the entire content industry.
We won't have to make videos.
And it is possible,
I will show you one video.
And,
This video.
This is,
100% AI.
Pixels.
This is not me.
Neither is it my voice,
nor is it my video,
nor have I written the script.
All these things are AI, and it is possible
right now.
And, I am telling you, right now,
I just have to input my face into a software,
and it will make a video for me.
I have a friend, Varun Maya.
He has an AI page, and 70% of the videos are
AI.
And people don't even know.
People don't even know that he is talking
about AI.
The voice is also mapped, the person is also
mapped.
I am telling you, if this is happening right
now, 100 years from now, what will happen
after 5 years?
What is the end game of this?
What will happen after this?
What are we supposed to do?
If you don't have to do anything.
Yeah, what are we supposed to do?
But sir, raw conversations won't survive like
this.
This is not possible.
Point of view.
Okay.
Now, AI is trained on large data sets.
They don't have emotions.
One second.
Intelligence.
There is no emotional intelligence.
Creativity, emotional intelligence, that humans,
and they bring perspectives.
Like, what we are discussing right now, everyone
has a different perspective.
AI, it has been trained on large data.
It is a data set.
There are no emotions.
And most of our decisions, which we make,
are emotionally done.
At least 30, 40, 50%.
But you can bring a lot of that emotion with
the prompts that you choose.
So now, when we are talking about video, when
we pick it up, the emotion that we feel, that
AI can never give.
That's why your personal point of view will
always be important.
I think AI, so just I got to know yesterday,
there is an AI
named Delpy.
So what it does is, it analyzes all your Twitter,
all your Facebook ID, whatever the data, you
put on, in your mind.
Because the same thing, whatever you have
said so far, personally.
In your point of view, it analyzes everything
and it is available 24x7.
It replies to the comments or it replies to
the tweet of
our audience in such a way that we used to
do that.
You know Arun, you can give a prompt saying
that if we give this phone to Arun Prabhu
Desai, what would be his first
six emotional reactions?
Exactly.
And you will be very surprised it will be
the same six.
So I can quiz you at that time.
Okay.
I will ask you six questions from your AI
generative model then I will ask you, five
of them will be the same thing.
Let me tell you, this again, in fact, goes
to prove my
point.
What you put on social media, on Twitter,
is it what you
are?
You put your, what you want others to see
about you.
Okay.
Not you in particular.
You are talking about that only.
Exactly.
You will put AI outside only.
Most of the time online.
You will put AI outside.
But see, like I said, the data is still being
collected.
Yes.
And it is going to collect for another five,
so I think it
will get perfect.
Another five years.
No, no, no.
Not at all.
It's like,
I would give an example, that AI is like a
child.
Whatever you teach that child, it will learn.
Exactly.
And you teach it that if someone abuses you,
you should get angry.
Or if this happens, you should do this.
Like we teach a child to walk, to get angry,
to eat this,
not to eat this.
You can teach the same thing to AI.
It takes ten years to teach to a child, and
five minutes to teach to AI.
You scan a PDF of the whole book and send
it to it, to read it and deliver it to me.
And that book learns it.
And you give that photography book to the
AI chart board, and that photography will
learn it.
You tell it to generate a photo, it will do
it.
So if we, basically what AI is, whatever data
you feed it,
it does it.
You cannot feed emotions.
I am saying that too.
Its emotions are different.
Yours are different.
Mine are different.
Because that has come from how we have been
brought up.
Our experiences as a whole, that the people
who are sitting now, mine, every person sitting
here today, my thought process is different.
You thinking about everyone else is different.
It cannot be the same.
It is with the individual.
And you cannot teach that to AI.
But Arun, your question, you are seeing this,
you are now putting two different things together.
Your personal life and the life that you have
outside.
We were talking about can we make a video.
No, I was talking about emotions.
Can you make a video that is completely trained,
like he is speaking, completely trained on
every single thing you have ever output to
the world.
Not personal, not what you are thinking of
us right now.
Whatever you have shown your personality outward
to the public till date, that can be trained.
I am giving you this guarantee that if you
will say after
that training that Arun is sitting here and
we have asked your training six questions.
What would be your six emotional reactions
for the public?
They will be pretty accurate.
Then my question is do you have to promote
such a thing?
No, it is not about what we are promoting
or not.
It is going to be there.
See, he said like about the AI tool, but if
this is the
thing, like if it can generate the emotion
or it can
replicate what you are outward persona.
Personality, your personality.
There is a big difference between generating
emotion and outward persona.
How can it have that emotional intelligence?
It might take.
The emotional connect might take some time.
Maybe it takes.
But who is going to get emotional intelligence?
It might take some time.
Okay.
See, how do you get emotional intelligence
from outside?
What is important is what you are going to
get emotional intelligence from?
You might get emotional intelligence from
How are you going to feed your emotional intelligence,
which you have built
over the last 20-30 years with experience?
Even with the AI…
There is a whole field called psychiatry,
right?
That is
also part of AI, right?
And what you are talking about, that is our
formative
years, my 20-30 years as a human being.
But that formative years is also part of psychiatry.
This
is a very, very dense topic to get into.
Yeah, okay.
Let's leave it at…
See, I like the generative AI, whatever we
are using at the camera processing and all
those…
That is fine, that is harmless.
But I am like thinking about what will be…
If you unlock this thing…
Everyone is worried about it.
It's just not you.
Everyone
is worried.
Shloka is shown as just a deep fake, very
simple, straight forward.
I have shown it to you already.
What about…
I have seen it somewhere else.
But whatever is in the past… And to
talk about just the… To do the deep
fake that he showed right now.
Actually, what a deep fake.
It's like I have fed all the information in
my body language, where I move my hand like
this, move like that, give expressions like
this.
So, I fed all the information and in a deep
fake, the face changes.
No, no.
This is my whole… For instance, there
is a legal case of Bruce Willis.
There was an advertisement of a Russian Vodka
of Bruce Willis.
You can all see it online.
He never went to Russia.
He never shot for it.
His thing.
Approximately 1000 hours of video was actually
fed in.
That he has a tick here.
When he says this word, his eye
moves like this.
The whole thing was fed in.
And the whole ad deep fake,
they have never paid him for it.
Nothing.
It happened in Russia.
Very dense legal thing.
So, that is… And you know, there are
now contracts that are being given to people
in Hollywood.
So, this whole thing that is coming…
In every which way, AI is coming faster than
you can respond to it.
AI will take our job.
I have full confidence.
Like, either it will be us who do it or it
would be someone else.
I think it's like saying that which website
will be popular
on the internet.
Internet is the thing that is going on.
So, AI is the
framework.
Now, which website, which prompt, which…
That is not the point.
Because new ones will keep coming.
New ones come every 2 weeks.
So, it's like the framework you have to learn.
By prompting, I mean you learn to tell AI.
Learn to talk to
AI.
Or feed AI what you want it to do.
A lot of people have a problem with that.
A lot of people are in English right now.
Prompt engineering.
How to get a job.
Exactly.
There are… I have seen and I have read
about it.
There are some people who put up an e-book
with brilliant chat GPT prompts.
And they have been making millions of dollars.
Just by telling and teaching people how to
use AI in a better way.
If you know your prompts right, you can get
really good results.
Yes.
Sir, give it to me.
Give me the link.
Sir, I don't have it.
Everyone thought that the lower level jobs,
AI will finish first.
But the opposite happened.
Creativity finished first.
It's shocking.
I spoke about this that day at that event.
It's so shocking.
And really, we are at the red spot right now.
There is a lot of investment in the lowest
level.
Because in that, you need…
In the everyday mundane jobs, you need robotics
to actually close that action.
If you are a blue collar worker, if you are
making…
There is a point.
Did you see Tesla's new robot video?
It is crazy.
It is like an actual human.
That balance panel.
There is a coffee shop in Dubai.
Something about that.
In Dubai festival city.
And it is not there since today.
It has been there for the past 2-3 years.
There is zero staff.
Do you know what happens there?
You go.
It's a huge platform.
It's such a big platform.
There is seating on the edges.
You go and sit on the stool.
There is an iPad in front.
There is a menu.
You order.
You are ordering.
You pay.
In front, there is a barista.
He is a robotic arm.
You can see the robotic arm in front.
He opened it.
He poured milk.
He is doing all the human actions in the robotic
arm.
He will do everything.
He placed his order on the tray in front.
He knows that he has come to you.
You drank coffee.
You left.
There is no one in the entire shop.
There is a cashier.
For that matter, there is not a single person.
So… Gaurav, look at its investment.
Robotic arm and other things.
But it is one time investment.
Generating AI is only software building on
more software.
Sir, it is very expensive.
Sir, it is needed for that too.
But it is done for easy rounds.
But it is easy.
This is a fact.
Yes.
Okay.
But an interesting thing that we can take
out for the viewers.
What we are talking about is for someone to
start content creation now.
You think you don't even need a studio.
You sit in a chair at home.
AI has made the studio.
There is a camera.
There is less light.
AI has enhanced the light.
There is noise in the voice.
AI has removed that.
So, for someone to start the content creation
journey today.
Using all the AI tools.
Yeah, even I support that kind of AI.
With one click…
Listen.
So, with one click…
With one click, you have made captions.
With one click, your script is ready.
Translations.
Everything.
So, I think the struggle that we did.
Anyone can be a creator.
5 years, 7 years ago.
AI will be dubbed.
That struggle has reduced today.
If you are smart enough how to use AI.
This could be a good thing.
One more thing is clear.
AI is the next big thing.
We have talked so much about this.
I have said this from the beginning.
Always going to be AI.
But AI will be the biggest thing.
It will be smart.
Okay, guys.
We have to take a break for 2 minutes.
2 minutes.
So, it was a deep conversation actually.
So, let's come back to a little, you know,
rooted topic.
Smartphones.
Right.
Something that we covered day in and day out.
You know, we ran on that.
So, how is 2023?
How is 2024 looking?
Have the prices become aggressive?
Are we going back to pre-COVID days?
When, you know, shocking prices from POCO
F1 were there.
Are we going back to that?
That is not going to happen.
Not going to happen?
But it seems like iQOO.
With 12.
The new 7 Pro that came.
It was very creative.
With iQOO 12, I feel again.
That that part of it is starting to come again.
Because if someone takes a brand lead.
Others have to follow.
And I think with hygiene coming into technology.
Where everything is more or less becoming.
You know, very easy to put together.
Or wow factors of smartphones have become
lesser and lesser.
I think price aggression will come back.
Yeah, because I feel the same.
Because, first of all, smartphone adoption
has plateaued.
I mean, there is no growth in the market.
The 153 million peak that we took in 2019.
That plateaued to like below that.
And there has to be some sort of impetus.
To rise, right?
For the market.
Basically, you can never play on price.
In a longer run.
You can never do it in any business.
If you think that I will become aggressive
in price.
And I will make the market.
You can't make it.
You will make it today.
But it won't be long lasting.
Biggest learning, Xiaomi.
Showed how aggressive it is.
No one buys a Xiaomi phone for 25,000.
It doesn't sell.
No one buys a Xiaomi phone for 70,000.
But you can be aggressive at each category,
right?
No, no.
But I am just saying that.
If we are aggressive at iQOO 12.
iQOO 12 is good.
But the problem is.
iQOO 12 is selling a phone for 50,000 today.
Let's say they are very little margins.
It is possible that they can take a loss.
For some duration.
Just to establish themselves.
But they can't repeat it for 5 years now.
Okay.
So, the price game can never run long.
You can't wait for.
Here I have a point.
I am not talking about.
Undercutting.
Or having less price.
Selling at a loss.
I don't think so.
The thing is.
All the issues.
Because of which.
The smartphone's price has had rocketed.
They are gone.
Those issues are resolved.
But they were removed long back.
No, no.
It was till mid-2022.
It was oversupplied.
Yes.
Not oversupply.
A lot of stock was left.
And this particular time.
They have removed it.
All the stock.
So, a new stock will come.
But.
The issues.
Or.
Earlier they used to demand more from outside.
Now India is manufacturing.
A lot of things which were there earlier.
I think in the days of 2019.
We will see such days.
Without pricing.
Yes.
It's not one brand who will do it.
Correct.
I will tell you honestly.
Just think through.
Give a basic thought.
We used to see a phone for 10,000 or 15,000.
4 years back.
And we used to think.
We are getting so much in that phone.
Don't know why.
As customers.
And even as ourselves.
Whenever we.
The standard rate of inflation.
We also think.
How can a mobile phone be for 10,000 or 15,000.
We always want it to be for 10,000.
How can we get it?
Inflation is happening in the world.
It is existing.
What we are getting as an advantage is.
The technology is getting better.
At the same time.
So, we are getting some things at a lower
price.
But at the same time.
Price will increase eventually.
Everything is increasing.
Biscuits are increasing.
Water is increasing.
Everything is increasing.
Inflation is there.
6-7% inflation.
But technology has always been anti-inflation.
The laptops that used to come.
And the exact laptops.
I am not talking about the same specs.
I am talking that same category.
You are obviously getting it better.
Because production improves.
The overall quality of what you are doing
improves.
Economy of scale kicks in.
I think it's fine.
The phone for 10,000.
You were getting 625.
Now you are getting G85, G90.
No, no, no.
I am not talking about that.
I am not talking that the price of the same
spec comes
lower.
I am saying because technology improves.
Becomes better.
Do remember that.
The amount of hardware that is made.
You are seeing improvement in the phone.
There is a lot of difference in their manufacturing.
If you have an OLED TV.
TV that comes in at a particular price point,
a much better
one will come at maybe 80% lower a little
later.
Why?
Because production and economy of scale became
better.
So when you are actually, I am now predicting
that in 2024,
you are going to see a lot of the things that
went wrong in COVID, the oversupply.
Why did the oversupply come?
They actually have invested far more now to
get things done.
So the actual advantage of that will go to
consumers.
You will get better products at a lower price
in 2024
without undercutting.
I'll ask a simple question.
Tell me what's your answer.
Samsung S24 Ultra is launching in January.
If the world goes from one place to another,
can its price
be lower than the S23 series?
But when you talk about the highest flagship,
that is not
what is happening.
No, no.
But I am just saying.
I mean, when Apple Airpods 3 will come, will
it be cheaper
than Airpods 2?
No, I have a question.
I have a thing.
Let's say we all are going to agree something
like S23 is a good phone.
Like this year we got a release.
Do you think that someone can, I mean, with
the software support and the performance,
I am pretty sure that in 2025, S23 is a good
phone.
So if there is a chance that if that phone
is available in
a very low price, I think people can buy it,
right?
Yeah, I mean.
I mean, technology is that.
That is fine.
Fine.
But all I am saying is, the reason for the
price to go up,
I mean, the iPhone will start to be made in
India.
But if someone says that iPhone 16 is being
made in India completely, can its price be
lower than the current price of iPhone?
But both your examples are at the highest
one.
This is at the highest level, but that is
not really the
topic we are talking about.
Alright, alright, alright.
What we will do is, a mid-range normal phone,
okay, which in the last year, and in the last
year, it was available
for Rs 25,000.
Today, you will get a better phone in every
aspect, whether it is display, performance,
everything.
You are going to get it for less than Rs 25,000.
Are you saying that we are not getting better
phones
because you said that the price is going to
increase.
The price is increasing.
If you are getting more phone for the same
price, even today.
You will get more phone for less price is
what we are saying.
If the technology is enhanced, then it's obvious.
If you compare the phone from 3 years ago
with the phone from 3 years ago, then it's
also enhanced.
No, not that.
We have seen that with time.
In the beginning, there was a fingerprint
scanner in a phone for Rs 50,000.
Today, you can get it in a phone for Rs 10,000.
You know, whatever.
So, technology always trickles down.
What brands do is, if they are selling an
expensive item, they will earn all their maximum
profits, and then they
will introduce a lower tier variant of them.
I don't understand what both of you are saying.
Are you saying that phones are getting expensive?
He has something to say.
I would say, I would break it down.
According to me, the company that was trying
to sell at a low price, it doesn't have a
profit to experiment and make a new thing.
That's what you told me.
You can't play for a long time at a price.
I agree.
You can play by reducing the price.
But the market now is that you can't give
better specs at a lower price.
You have to do higher price, better quality.
I will give you something that you will immediately
relate
to.
The jacket you are wearing now, maybe you
bought this fabric from a Japanese supplier.
Now, the Japanese supplier you have, he has
invested maybe 1 billion dollars to make something
much better at a lower price.
Much better.
He has invested a lot.
You will give that advantage to your customer,
right?
A better product at a lower price because
you are being enabled to do it now.
First of all, someone should make it.
No one can make it.
And because we are making it by doing a lot
of research,
that is one of our incentives.
Because in skins and everything else, we have
invested crores, then we are able to make
it.
Someone else has to make it, he has to invest
crores.
I am talking about you.
Your input, this fabric, you import from Japan,
that guy,
that supplier has improved his production
and material and he can now give it to you
at 10% lesser and it is 10%
better.
Now you will buy the product from him, right?
But we won't reduce the price, right?
That's the thing.
Because… The market will go down.
The market will go down.
The customer will not get that advantage.
We won't introduce that as a… We won't
introduce Overlace as a cheap brand.
No, we are going on a different topic.
It's not about…
Let's keep the atmosphere light.
What do you think about bank offers?
What is your take?
One of the biggest game changers of 2023.
Not bank offers, the no-cost EMI has been
one of the biggest game changers of 2023.
But it was there earlier also.
No, no, now it is true no-cost.
Earlier it was a very fake one.
They used to make mistakes in calculations.
Today a lot of people come to me.
They used to say, you know, tell me in 30,000
rupees.
Now people's question has changed.
And they say, you know, at a budget of 3,000
rupees a month, which is the phone to buy?
So, the psychology of buying is changing.
And that is a huge game changer.
Huge game changer.
That's why iPhones have been sold a lot.
That's why.
What an amazing scheme this is.
No doubt, there will be bank offers, credit
card offers, no-cost offers.
I think all this has given a lot of benefit
to India.
In general.
But let me throw one more question out.
Because I find it very interesting that when
I get replies back.
In 2019, iPhone total market share was less
than 1%.
It is approximately now at about 7%.
Massive.
I mean, if you show any other brand that they
have increased 700% in 4 years.
Right?
But where is the growth?
Is it in the…
Like this year, did the iPhone 15 make this
growth happen?
Or is it the iPhone 11 and the 12?
Always last year.
But… Is that good for a brand?
But… Okay.
So, I will tell you one thing.
And I think you all will agree on this.
The iPhone which has increased by 1% or 2%
and has now gone up to 5%, 6%, 7%.
It will increase more.
Yes.
It can never decrease.
I will tell you the reason for that.
Everyone wanted an iPhone.
Everyone wanted it.
They were not able to buy it at one time.
Or there was a barrier of starting price which
was very high.
Should I give a contradiction to this?
No, listen to me once.
Why did they want it?
Because someone else did not have it.
Because it was a good phone.
iPhone is a good phone.
I mean… iPhone is a good phone.
There was also a reason that there was an
exclusive thing.
But sir, we felt that it has sold a lot.
Listen to me.
But when you see tier 2, tier 3, that aspiration
is still
there.
It is still there.
I am saying that it is still there.
People who do not have it still want it.
They want it.
Every year we see that the price of old phones
goes down.
Old phones are still good for another 3-4-5
years.
The way because the iPhones are made.
And at the same time, people's salaries are
increasing.
People are changing new jobs.
Money is coming into the market.
So at the end, they will buy the same thing
which they
wanted to buy.
So by doing this, more new people are going
to join in this.
But there is no drastic change in technology
also when it
comes to phones.
It's just a big thing.
It doesn't matter.
See, okay.
I mean the latest ones which have been released.
Today, almost all the phones in the market,
they are good enough phones.
There was a time when there were bad phones
and good phones.
Okay.
Today, for every phone, if let's say not you
are the
target, someone else is the customer and they
are happy
with those phones.
iPhone is also good.
Samsung is also good.
All these are good phones today.
So if you come to nitpicking, you will find
15 shortcomings
in every phone.
No one is perfect.
But it's a good phone.
It gives you a good experience.
And that's the reason people want to buy it.
Because it's a good phone at the end.
Samsung is also good for that matter.
No, iPhone is more affordable now actually.
That's what I am saying.
So because of it, because of it being…
So now let's paint a scenario that the aspiration
tier 2,
tier 3 is because you have it, I don't.
I aspire to it.
When iPhone will be in the 20% market, what
will be the aspiration?
Sir, there is such a big market in the US,
it is still sold.
Because the phone is good.
But sir, our population is very big.
Dubai, Dubai, there is no carrier in Dubai.
Take it, it is sold there too.
Basically, let me tell you one thing.
Let's say something is good, genuinely good.
If its market share is 80%, then you will
not stop buying
it.
Thinking that its market share is 80%, that's
why you will stop buying it.
No, but its aspiration decreases.
No, but still you will.
But the population is very big.
No, no, no.
I am not…
Listen, if in India, Apple has got 20%, then
they will be
in trouble.
Sir, it will happen.
It will happen.
You will get 20% soon.
You won't get it today, you will get it after
2 years.
But I agree to what he said.
There was a time when people used to see Apple
as a very
premium product.
We wanted to acquire it.
But now the thing is that, let's say, everyone
has it.
But everyone has the access to buy the phone.
So I feel the market is more like, you know,
people that have a mid-range phone.
They are the ones who are going to look up
to all these flagship phones.
I actually did a reel on this exact emotion,
where earlier, 5 years back, if you bought
an iPhone or if you are using it, everyone
is looking at you.
And then…
It was quite funny, I saw it.
But the point is, that is actually happening.
But still, I also agree that the iPhone sales
will increase.
No, I am not saying that it will increase.
I am saying that it will increase by 10-15%.
I said that if there is a good product in
the market, and we all use it, will I stop
using it just because…
But its wow factor will decrease.
Sir, it doesn't matter.
The wow factor of the phone is never less.
I feel…
We made it.
No, sir, we made it.
They want to say something for the longest
time.
One of the benefits of the iPhone is that,
let's say we are using any iPhone for 2 years,
its resale value is much better compared to
any other Android phone.
And in the Indian market, that is very important.
That is very important.
But why is it so?
For the same aspirational reason, because…
Okay, what you can afford the other person.
Because till date, as sir has mentioned, buying
an iPhone was an aspiration for many people.
So, there is a scarcity in the market of seeing
an iPhone.
Now everyone is using the iPhone.
Do you see 2024 or 2025, iPhone will have
the same resale value as before?
There is a huge room for growth, I think.
There is a huge business now, which is refurbished.
And already in the refurbished market, iPhone's
prices have dramatically dropped.
Second thing, in this Diwali, there is also,
you know,
there is all these analysts that work now.
A very interesting thing came out through
these analysts, in corporate, the most wow
thing to give to somebody, big corporates,
like someone is working with a huge company,
they are sending 100 iPhones as gifts.
Lowest number of iPhones were sent this year.
Do you know what replaced it?
Folding phones.
Because the wow factor of folding phones was
very low.
And tomorrow, Apple will get a fold.
No, no.
It will be worth 4 lakhs and people will buy
it again.
What happened now, 2023, there was a shift
to the wow factor of folding phones.
Alright, one question, now we are talking
about iPhone's sales.
In India, how many people buy iPhones for
the software, hardware optimizations, the,
you know, really good looks and good camera?
And how many of them buy just because it has
that brand value?
It is because there is an iPhone, that's why.
So what will be…
Should I answer?
Yes.
There are a lot of people who change their
new iPhone on day one.
There are a lot of such people.
There are a lot of people who will change
their iPhone after 3-4 years.
But there are a lot of people who don't care.
What is the percentage?
Listen, listen.
There are a lot of people who don't care if
the iPhone is worth 2 lakhs, 3 lakhs or 5
lakhs.
They don't care.
They are using the iPhone and they will buy
it.
Maybe they are on the ecosystem.
No, no.
They don't care about the ecosystem.
They may not even use 5% of the iPhone on
their phone.
All they are doing is just phone calls and
WhatsApp.
But just because they have the money.
They just have to have it.
They have the money.
They have to have it.
They buy it.
They will buy 10 pieces of iPhone on day one
and gift it to their family.
Those who have to have it, still continue.
This is number one.
Number two.
Those people who are coming in the creator
space.
Because iPhone is such a robust device.
Those young guys.
They will buy a phone and they know that this
is the phone which will be able to do multiple
things in once.
I can also edit on it.
I can also shoot on it.
The camera is also good.
Everything is good.
Instagram works well for example.
They will get that.
In today's date.
The people who are buying only because of
the Apple logo.
That number is less.
And what happens is.
Earlier also when there was a number where
only the Apple logo was flexing.
Till the point he actually bought that phone.
That thought will be there.
But once they start using it.
Then it's no more.
Their next phone will be iPhone only.
I will add one more thing.
I also agree.
I think the person who drives the purchase.
I will break down a secret of the iPhone ad.
That if you ever give an ad of iPhone.
In that, a normal person will not use it.
They will show that a person is going.
Climbing a mountain.
Coming down 50 meters in the sea.
So I think he drives the sale of a product.
That is when professionals start using something.
Now you will see.
In India or in the whole world.
All the cinematographers are using the iPhone.
All the gamers.
No matter where they get sponsors.
But they are actually streaming on the iPhone.
So all the professionals.
It is visible that they are using the iPhone.
All the DJs have MacBooks.
They don't need a screen.
And the normal consumer.
Follows this audience.
Follows the professional.
Have you worn a watch ultra?
Are you really the target customer for watch
ultra?
No.
You are not the.
Where are you going to climb the mountain?
I don't know about you.
I said it.
But okay.
The watch is targeted for extreme sports.
Athletes.
Normally like that.
Since the launch of watch ultra.
All the people I have met.
Who used to use Apple watch.
Till yesterday.
Series 6, 7, 8.
Whether they are the target customers or not.
They are all on ultra now.
Majority of them.
And the simple reason is.
Because this is.
Battery is also broken.
Battery is one of the biggest reason.
Battery is the biggest reason.
To whom ever I have spoken.
But 3 raise 1 is nothing.
Apart from battery.
The reason is.
Because this is the most expensive Apple watch.
This is the latest one.
They need to have it.
And that's the reason they have it.
I have seen people.
Which one are you wearing?
I have seen.
I am wearing a Rolex.
Which one are you wearing?
Rado.
AP.
And I am not wearing a smart watch right now.
This is a very strange situation.
Forget that.
My point is.
I have seen.
I have seen people.
I will ask you an example.
I will ask you a simple question.
And I will tell you my reaction to it.
When Samsung launched Fold in India.
Or when it was launched in the world.
The idea was targeting towards professionals.
Businessmen.
Who will work on the go.
This this this.
Okay I agree.
To a certain extent.
Some people who actually do business.
And they need a fold phone.
And they used the phone.
Their life is changed now.
And I will tell you.
If we get the data of Samsung.
If we can tell something from Samsung.
In Delhi NCR.
All the people who have money.
They have kept 2 folds.
And they have no business.
They don't do anything in the phone.
I have seen this.
They have kept 2 folds.
In Pune too.
And in Pune too.
And Samsung.
The sales that Samsung got in India.
Of the folds.
They have got it from them.
Very few people from business.
But the one who had money.
The one who was able to buy.
He bought it.
No no.
Leave it in Delhi.
Same thing is there in iPhone.
It is there in folds.
They show you how to climb a mountain.
How to swim in the sea.
I am saying.
They have kept their watch.
And they are tracking their steps.
So.
In my opinion.
The professionals and top tier people.
Those who are using.
Noravrandha follows them.
So it is the same thing.
After listening to all your talks.
After summing up.
What I felt.
I will tell you.
Because you really got to learn.
One thing is understood.
Apple is one of the super lucky companies.
If the aspiration ends.
In my opinion.
Lucky.
Let's take an example.
The aspiration is over.
Everyone has an iPhone.
But.
Their foundation is so strong.
That the ecosystem has come.
Maybe you will buy airports.
Their sale is increasing.
Subscriptions and multiple things.
Subscription has come.
Then.
MacBook.
As you named it.
It became popular among the creators.
We have seen.
The product becomes popular.
In the middle of the community.
So.
If it is in the middle of the creators.
Then he will buy a MacBook.
And Atom is also good.
Yes.
FCP.
Final Cut Pro will buy.
I think.
Apple.
Yes.
Lucky word.
I agree.
I used it wrong.
The foundation they have built.
Their branches.
That is very solid.
It will be strong.
I will give you an example.
Poco community.
Xiaomi community.
Any brand.
Realme community.
iQoo community.
All the Android communities.
Today.
If Xiaomi's product.
Becomes popular.
Then.
All the Android communities.
Today.
If Xiaomi's phone.
Is coming in the bracket of 10,000 or 15,000.
Redmi Note.
Something.
Which used to come at one time.
All those community members.
They are joining in.
They are using the Redmi phone.
They are a part of the community.
You tell them tomorrow.
Take this.
Your iPhone.
They will leave the community immediately.
They don't have that brand attachment.
Just because.
In today's date.
Given his scenario.
His situation is.
His affordability is till there.
He is doing that.
The day.
He is able to afford an iPhone.
He will buy a second iPhone.
He doesn't have any attachment to Redmi.
I would disagree.
To some extent.
Brand loyalty.
You get this.
I would just say.
Like premium customers.
Vivo.
Redmi is not premium.
I am talking about Redmi.
I am talking about less than 15,000.
Yes.
In a less priced point.
But like some Vivo customers.
And I have seen many Samsung customers.
Samsung and Apple.
Are on a level.
Oppo as well.
Oppo and Vivo.
Very strong this time.
I was talking about.
This budget range.
Ok.
One question.
If we shift from the iPhone.
Then.
Which brand according to you.
Which brand.
Is the most popular.
Now.
I mean.
Which is most popular.
And according to you guys, and it might be
controversial, which brand first?
And we are going to talk to Bebop and Tamil.
Which brand in 2023 do you think did the best
brand of smartphone?
In Android, no?
In Android.
To make it interesting, it has to be one.
If we say that, then you won't know.
OK, so for me, it may be iQOO for two reasons.
One, when you see at the budget segment, iQOO
predominantly in the market only to sell the
performance.
But this time,
what they did is, with iQOO Z7 Pro, it might
be a rebranded smartphone, whatever it is.
But in a particular price segment, they launched
the smartphone with a good processor and also
with good cameras.
So in my video, most of the people who are
asking about the budget segment smartphone,
I recommend that one.
And to a far extent, the software is not refined
before.
But iQOO 12, they changed it, maybe not 100%,
but at least by 40% or 30%.
They improved a bit.
So that's what I personally feel.
What about?
We have to name one, huh?
Yeah, that's when the fun starts.
You can also say none, so that's fine.
If you don't know.
It's not like there's no one.
But one thing, like,
He's making fun of us.
Now, the thing I'm notifying,
I read a lot of stats, and I come to realize
that, like
inflation, like we were talking about, in
smartphones, so usually the inflation number
that the government shares with us, which
is 6-7%, but in smartphones, in India, it
was 12%.
So I'm not expecting the smartphone prices
to go down in the coming year.
I'm only expecting them to go high.
But at the same time, I'm also feeling that
the smartphones that will come, they will
be a little lean.
They will not be launching every other month.
Their product...
They will reduce the portfolio.
I feel that way.
The question was different, by the way.
Yeah, yeah.
You made me go crazy.
Say yes, man.
I am calculating the percentage right now.
I was about to ask him what was the answer.
So, I am coming to that.
One word answer.
It should be a one word answer.
Explanation later.
So, for me, I think OnePlus Open is a standout
device for me.
And with that regard, it's OnePlus for me.
Yeah.
Same here.
OnePlus.
Why?
Because one thing is that they have this green
line issue.
The software issue which has been rapidly
happening with a lot of customers.
They rectified it and they gave a proper explanation
on why.
And again, with their product range, OnePlus
11 and the Open looks very nice.
Even the pad is also good.
OnePlus.
So, the one brand that stood out for you is
OnePlus?
I cannot stop using the OnePlus Open.
It's that good.
Also, I mean, a lot of the...
Sometimes a single product can define a whole
year.
Yeah, yeah.
Define a whole year.
Because we were all waiting for it as well,
right?
For OnePlus' first foldable.
Did it sell?
Yes.
I'm not sure about that.
I'm not sure about the numbers.
From a techie's perspective.
So, I'm not sure about the numbers, but okay.
So, two things I liked about the OnePlus Open.
The approach of OnePlus towards the Open.
One, they didn't make it like they launched
a foldable for Rs. 80,000.
It's premium.
They launched it at a premium price in India.
We know that Samsung will launch it for Rs.
1.5 Lakhs.
So, they also have one for Rs. 40,000, number
one.
They didn't play on the price bit.
They know that they need to establish that
as a premium product.
Second thing, they went all out with marketing.
Go to airports, go to premium places, you'll
see Open all around.
So, okay, you can't expect results straight
from the first year.
But it clearly shows the trajectory ahead.
That in the coming years, they will be there.
And I think it looks good from this point
that they will have a certain solid line-up
in the foldables.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, I wasn't finishing my answer.
It's that OnePlus also not just the Open across.
Like, they refined their line-up or they,
you know, made it better this year with the
Nord CE 3 and the Nord 3.
11R, I think.
11R was a fantastic device.
So, you know that at every segment, there's
a OnePlus phone to cater to every audience.
So, even if you don't like the phone or not,
as a reviewer, people are buying it.
I saw so many OnePlus Nord CE 3s, it's not
even funny.
Even at airports and the Nord Buds 2R.
So popular.
So, OnePlus is actually getting the audience
to acknowledge their devices and buy it.
So, they've done a good job.
And I think they will continue to do a good
job if they continue to keep it this way.
And if they could just kind of do a segregation
between Open.
Just answer my question.
Who has improved the most?
Which smartphone brand impressed you in 2023?
Simple.
OnePlus.
OnePlus, for sure.
Alright.
For me too, I found one thing very interesting
in OnePlus this year.
Like, I tried OnePlus 12.
It is all an experiment.
I mean, all the things, like, the alert slider,
they removed it first.
Then they put it back on the right side.
Now they put it on the left side.
And in its software, they sometimes put the
aperture slider up.
So, every phone is like full of experiments.
And there were a lot of issues with it, like
the green line issue.
But some experiments have been done.
Like, OnePlus Open was, in my opinion, a very
risky product.
Yeah.
Because it would cost Rs. 1 lakh.
And to launch it at that price.
So, in my opinion,
OnePlus showed the guts to experiment, and
I would give it to them.
Because OnePlus Open is genuinely a good smartphone,
but it is not there yet.
There is no actual proof of concept yet.
Which brand is it?
OnePlus.
It's the same.
It's not there yet.
I had two, but I have to pick only one.
But I would say,
OnePlus and Motorola.
These were the two brands that, in my opinion,
they did very, very well.
But, OnePlus is the winner because of that
OnePlus Open.
When OnePlus 11, 11R, all these came, and
if you see the 10, I mean, the ones before
2022, those two years, OnePlus launched shit
phones.
But this year, 2023, whether, all the series
you look at
it, whether it is Nord or Nord C, or their
11, 11R,
excellent phones, but, best thing,
OnePlus Open.
Wow.
And that's why,
OnePlus is my brand.
I can copy the video of Babar Azam from Pakistan.
There's a video that has gone viral, where
Rohit Sharma says a long answer in English.
And Babar says, yes, my answer is also same.
Yes, same, same.
So, OnePlus, the reason for that is, again,
was OnePlus 7
Pro or 7T Pro?
It had a pop-up camera and a curved screen.
Both 7 and 7 Pro.
That was the last amazing OnePlus.
We saw the deviation in 8, 9, 10.
But this year, and it clearly showed, that
was the
beginning, 11, 11R, everything is going well.
Nord C, I'll give you an example.
I was in BITS Pilani, Hyderabad campus.
I must have taken at least 500-700 selfies
there.
And 80% was using that, lime color, what color
is it?
Lime color.
Lime color, CE3 light.
I mean, I'm seeing that every other student
has CE3 light.
CE2 light was the highest setting.
I said CE3 light is also going to be the highest.
For that matter, even Nord 3T light.
3T, amazing performance, good package.
Open, they have nailed it.
So, I think, acknowledging the faults, what
went wrong over the years, and coming up with
a solid lineup,
I think OnePlus.
And I remember speaking to OnePlus guys in
2022, and they had told me that, you look
at 2023, the lineup we have, you will change
the thought process about OnePlus.
So, they have done it.
Yes, sir.
Tell me.
So, I think everybody has already said quite
a few interesting things.
You know, OnePlus seems to be…
Wait a minute.
Let's score them.
IQ got one.
OnePlus, OnePlus, OnePlus, OnePlus, OnePlus,
OnePlus, OnePlus, OnePlus.
Why is OnePlus written on the bottle?
But my answer is not OnePlus.
So, edges are different then.
The middle, the middle.
So, acknowledged OnePlus.
Motorola, you said, was fantastic.
I think Vivo is another company that is doing
some great work.
Don't be diplomatic.
You only said, don't say two, and now he said
three.
You've already done all this.
It's done.
But I'll give a very, very contradictory answer.
Another company that has really impressed
me this year is another company that is pushing
innovation at price points that are not possible.
They are opening up markets.
It's making people imagine, and that is techno.
I was about to say that.
It's a very unusual thing for a company to
have the guts to be able to take so many risks.
Whether you look at folding phones or flip
phones, they want to be premium also.
They want to bring in things in very different
ways.
I like the guts of that company, and I'd love
to see what they do in 2024.
Because the people who never thought of buying
a folding phone, at least they still may not
be buying it.
I don't know what they are selling.
The people who have never bought a folding
phone, I don't think they'll buy a techno
phone.
I bought that.
You bought it?
Bro, look at its hinge.
But I had a poster.
It's been a while, the hinge is moving.
I had a poster.
Sales of the folding techno phone.
With that techno folding.
I saw your video and bought that techno folding.
And he was very happy with it.
So I'm actually surprised.
I work with a lot of analysts who only track
this.
And they track it through various sources,
including from mobile networks, which phone
is latching on.
So they have all these numbers, instead of
just fake numbers from brands.
They've actually sold very well.
And the fold has sold more than their flip.
Yeah, even I like the Camo series.
Yeah, that was nice.
Okay, I think...
The last question, and I want to close off
with...
Something very interesting.
I mean, we all review phones, so we get phones
to use.
But I'm pretty sure that we're also buying
gadgets of our own, right?
I'm not so sure.
I just want to double check that now.
Starting from Rajiv, what's the best and the
worst gadget purchase of 2023 for you?
Best and worst, huh?
Best and worst, one-one each.
So I'll tell you, I'll give you a guess.
I think everybody has enough time to think
about it.
So I think I bought...
One of my best purchases has been an LG OLED
TV.
I'm very surprised at just how good they are
getting this technology and at prices that
I could not even imagine, right?
Absolutely fantastic.
And because I was in a very big hurry, and
I was very excited by it because I've been
using it for years, my disappointment one
was the new Sony XM5.
Oh.
It's still a great product.
It's just that I still feel that the previous
generation is better.
The overhead ones?
No, no, no.
You should have kept it to smartphone.
Did you buy it and which one was the worst?
Both have been bought.
I said I was in a big hurry, so I actually
bought it from abroad.
My worst...
To be honest, I can't remember it and I can't
highlight it.
But the best I know is the DJI Osmo Pocket
3.
Yeah.
Amazing, cute little camera.
Handheld, inbuilt gimbal, it's a one-inch
sensor.
Comes with a mic that's automatically paired
with the camera.
It's a good thing.
Are you using it regularly for content creation?
No, so I haven't used it much till now.
But I think if I have to carry just one camera,
sometimes you can't carry a big DSLR for vlogging
and stuff.
Right.
And if you use an iPhone, you have to use
a rear camera, use a wide angle, low light
is not that good sometimes.
You know, it has its own complications.
So this small gimbal which you can attach
a small tripod, it will stay in one place,
you know, self-tracking and all those things.
So I think it's a good camera.
And, yeah, the best has happened, but the
worst is not coming to my mind at this time.
Yeah.
I have not bought too many things.
Honestly, only the one I remember and which
I think was excellent was the MetaQuest 3
which I got from the UK.
We forced you to get it.
Yeah, yeah.
Perfect, correct.
Yeah, so that's all.
I don't have...
I haven't even purchased the rest yet.
I have bought a bedsheet for around 2-2.5
lakhs.
And what happens in that, it is 8-sleeve.
And the world's top...
Nowadays, he has gone into bio-hacking.
Health, fitness.
We haven't talked about that yet.
Health, fitness of creators.
It is a bedsheet that changes the temperature
of your body so that your sleep improves.
Elon Musk.
Top athletes.
A lot of billionaires.
They all use it.
And when you hear it, you'll think, what is
he sleeping on?
But that has improved my sleep a lot.
And I think sleep is something that has a
huge impact on life.
So my best purchase so far is the same as
of this year.
Send me the link.
Yes, 100%.
I have a question.
It's not sponsored.
No, no, no.
Does he have an app or not?
I haven't used his app much.
He has an app.
Okay.
So do you do any preset?
Or you don't have to do anything?
I just set it like that.
I'm asking the question because
I have a lot of trouble getting up.
Okay.
I can't get up.
I mean, I enjoy sleeping.
And my deep sleep becomes very deep.
So I thought if he has an app where you can
set an alarm kind of thing that at 8 in the
morning, you can make it completely cold.
I'll answer.
Then the eyes will open or something.
What does it actually do?
No, no, no.
I'll answer.
Absolutely.
So you can actually, it's called a silent
alarm on this.
Okay.
It vibrates.
Vibration is a new term.
No, no, no.
It does it with temperature.
It increases the temperature.
It's very slowly.
Changes the temperature enough.
It's a good thing if there is something like
that.
If I have 150 alarms on my phone,
I can't open my eyes.
Worst?
I don't purchase worst things.
Say worst ever.
If you want to say, even if you buy it in
2022.
It was worst for us that I bought a RED camera.
And I think the whole set-up cost me 10-15
lakhs.
But it's so tough to use that we used it in
5-6 videos.
So it's worst for us but it can be good for
someone.
Not fitting in your routine.
The workflow.
Got it, got it.
Okay, okay.
Next, I'll tell you.
Best, I felt,
I enjoy audio products a lot.
I spend the most money on audio products.
Like what?
So there is a Sony soundbar.
Sony HT-A7000, I think.
I bought that.
And the surround sound experience that I get
from that soundbar.
I went crazy.
I have it at home.
I do it a lot.
I enjoy it a lot.
With the rear speakers and...
Exactly.
3.1?
No, no.
7.1.
It's wireless.
The one you picked up for the...
The same one you picked up.
Same one.
So I also have the same one.
Same one, same one.
HT-A7000.
How much is it for?
I think 1-2 lakhs.
2.5 lakhs for the whole setup.
Rear speakers and the woofer.
Okay, it has rear speakers too.
I can add everything.
I can add as many speakers as I want.
Crazy experience.
White, white.
I mean, I'm satisfied.
But he's talking about soundbar.
If I don't buy the soundbar...
No, no, you can get a soundbar plus those...
Yes.
I thought it only comes as a package with
the two speakers.
No, four speakers and soundbar.
You can fit it anywhere.
You just have to give power.
Sony's naming convention.
Coming back to this thing.
I think the A9s were the ones with the four
speakers setup.
And there was the A7000 with the soundbar.
Soundbar and...
Subwoofer comes with it, right?
Subwoofer comes with it.
When they said XM5, headphones or earphones...
Subwoofer package.
But if you're asking about a particular product,
then...
It comes in a bundle.
You have to say something.
I mean, it comes in a bundle.
I bought the whole bundle.
And I'm very happy.
Should I talk about the worst?
It's the exact same setup and...
How much did it cost?
2.5 Lakh.
The second worst I can recall because as such,
I'm telling you all the time.
I just bought it.
Recently, to make a video,
I bought a Blackberry passport.
Oh God!
Why did you make it?
Don't say that.
I used to use it.
And it was a very strong phone.
Today, it's experience is bad.
Because today...
It was from the time of iPhone 6.
And I was comparing it side by side.
I thought...
There was so much wrong in it.
I was using it at that time.
See, I used to text.
And in that, the keypad is all touch sensitive.
You're typing.
It used to give you three options in predictive
text.
One here, one here, one here.
The area where you swipe on the keypad, that
word will come.
And I used it like crazy.
Its screen...
It's I think...
1440 by 1440.
Like a square.
Square.
So, today...
I...
It's my phone.
That's what I said.
Of all time, which I bought in 2023, what
problem did I face in the keyboard?
That literally, they removed the letters and
put a space bar in between.
That means,
I have to bring a learning curve.
If I have to start using the keyboard, then
I have to get used to that my space bar will
be in between the letters.
Where there should be a B, there is a space
bar.
No problem.
And when I saw other things, that phone only
asks for learning curves.
It says, first learn how to use it.
But...
In that,
BBOS, which has a passport, in that, if you
swipe to the side, at the same place, there
are WhatsApp threads, chatting threads,
Facebook threads, and email, and text.
Everything is on one side.
But I heard that...
It was such an amazing thing.
But I heard that
APK didn't work.
It used to work at that time.
It used to work in the beginning.
When the transition happened, there was a
solution by
adding Amazon's app store.
But only to a certain time.
You know what happened to my passport?
I'll tell you my incident story.
My passport was...
It's a square device.
From the bottom, it has a sharp edge device.
I kept it on the table like this.
And it fell like this.
This was the distance that it fell.
And the screen was...
It was worst product.
Otherwise, it was good.
So, obviously,
I also don't buy a lot of tech.
I don't have lakhs.
But, what I picked up recently was a backbone
one.
It's a controller that you attach to your
phone.
I mean...
I'm very interested in gaming.
So, I don't get time to play the PS5.
So, even in iPhone 15, you can play all the
games.
I mean, Resident Evil is already out there.
So, I wanted to play that.
And a lot of Indies that I wanted to play.
So, best purchase ever.
Because I got a good 50% off.
I got it for 5000.
I was damn happy.
Worst purchase was an audio product.
I'm an audiophile.
So, I spend money on audio products.
So, there was a
Fiio FH5.
So, it was such an impulsive purchase.
It was so bass heavy.
I didn't like it at all.
I don't know what to do.
Which one?
Fiio FH5.
It's an audiophile.
How much is it?
I got it for about 19-20 thousand.
And this backbone controller?
Is it Bluetooth or you have to connect it?
No, it's a it's like a type C one.
Right?
So, it gets it attaches to your thing.
Your phone.
Any phone.
But he keeps playing that.
So, yeah.
I love it.
Okay.
I have two best.
One is just like he said, the pocket the pocket
3 DJI.
And another one is
TWS which is called
Moondrop Space Travel.
It costs around like 25 dollars.
I think you can import here also 3000 rupees
or something.
Very good stuff for that price.
Worst will be
Sony Xperia 1 Mark 5.
That phone.
Okay.
You bought it?
The problem
He buys a lot of it.
The problem with Sony in my experience the
last Xperia 1 Mark 1 2, 3, 4, 5 is that they
are having good hardware.
But Sony didn't learn computational photography.
Yeah.
So camera sensor is good.
Everything is good.
But when you click photos there was no night
mode.
Now there is night mode.
So what Google,
Samsung, Apple have been doing over the years
Sony didn't latch on to the computational
photography.
And that's why the photos and videos are very
bad.
Alright.
B-Bomb.
The best purchase is actually
we bought a speaker for one of our videos.
It was lyric speaker.
Whatever you play
Hindi, English, Punjabi anything.
It will start the lyrics and lyrics will come
in the style
of the mood of the song.
And it's a really nice thing.
And I kept it in my home and I enjoy it.
It's a nice motivational starter.
Worst actually there will be a lot of worst.
Team actually purchases a lot of stuff.
They don't tell me the worst.
That is for sure.
So I am not sure about the worst but that
was the best.
The storeroom is full of worst products.
Yes, it is.
Alright, Tavel.
So my best tip would be two things.
One is hardware side.
I bought a new
Insta360 for 360.
Just take it in your hand and you can cover
everything.
You don't have to like for vlogging every
time take out the phone or the camera and
talk.
You can give the voice over suggestions.
Enjoy the moment.
That one.
And the second thing is software.
After paying a lot of amount for
Sony Resolve for one time that was the best
decision and
the best software for editing.
Worst?
Worst is a smart ring.
I bought it for 10k and it is not worth it.
Which?
Vodka.
I thought something from abroad.
Sleep tracking was not on to the point.
Because we used to wear it.
The least thing
No, this was my engagement ring.
That was the best one.
Sorry guys,
I am going to interrupt.
Should we do a do a thumbnail
I will have to leave.
Thank you so much
Thank you for coming.
This was fantastic.
Thank you.
Great, great.
Great initiative.
See you.
Bye Shlok.
Bye bye.
Take care.
Good to see you.
We will sit and chat for sure.
Okay.
Thanks.
Great initiative.
Lots of hard work.
Good to meet you.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
We'll catch up again.
Nice to see you.
We'll also sit and chat at some point.
Definitely, sir.
Good meeting up.
Best of luck.
I wanted to ask this question.
How do you guys take care of your health?
So, I really want to know.
Because, 2023, for me, I have focused on health
like crazy.
Because, till last year, I was just going
mad literally, working, working.
But, since I started focusing on health, it
helped me in my work as well.
I find myself getting even more free time
now.
I don't know how.
My productivity has increased.
What has happened?
My mind is in a better space.
But, what about your health?
What is your...
In my opinion, because I have been part of
this biohacking community and all.
Till now, we used to think that we have to
live for 60-70 years.
It's like, okay, let's live.
We'll grow old.
All the people I have met, who are part of
this community, who are working on top tier
technologies, age reversal.
A few years from now, or the technologies
that are still there, you can live for 100-150
years.
I mean, you can live through them.
And, it's not just that you'll be able to
live.
You can live like a 30-year-old healthy person.
80-90 years.
And, I think...
You can have an active lifestyle.
Hiking.
Cycling.
And, So, what you're doing?
You're doing something like that?
Yes, 100%.
There are a lot of machines.
There are a lot of things.
Like, it is diet.
There are machines.
There are technologies.
Like, for example, right now, it happens that
most people are deficient in something.
And, as I'm doing scientist research,
I'm finding out that everything is because
of a deficiency.
If you're not eating properly, your pancreas
doesn't function properly, and you develop
diabetes.
If you're not eating properly, eventually,
you develop cancer.
And, research has been done, clinically proven,
that if you keep eating certain things throughout
your life, you won't develop diabetes, you
won't develop cancer, and you won't get sick.
And, there are supplements.
There are supplements for everything.
There are supplements for treatment.
I was just looking at it.
You were eating so many...
How many tablets do you eat?
Supplements.
I...
Tablets are like...
It might sound a little weird that I eat 20-22
tablets a
day.
But, those tablets are like, turmeric powder,
neem powder, Okay.
There's some fish oil.
So, it's a very basic supplement type.
They're not medicines.
But, they are.
They're supplements.
And, they've developed a lot now.
They've refined a lot.
And, the second thing is that there are such
technologies that you can use in your body
while exercising naturally.
For example, there's a body suit.
If you wear that and work out for half an
hour, it is like working out for 4 hours.
So, if you wear that and do normal work, you'll
basically have a workout session.
And, there's a machine, it's called a sculptor.
In that, there are electrical simulations
in the body.
So, if you put it on your stomach, within
half an hour, you can do around 20,000 push-ups.
And, the body basically does this.
The body has electrical signals.
So, the muscles contract, and contract, and
contract.
It happens very quickly.
And, it hurts.
But, all these things work.
Because, I did 7 sessions of the sculptor.
And, my abs got a little better.
And, Only in 7 sessions?
Yes, 7 sessions.
But, it is painful.
We all want to see your abs.
It's not there yet.
No, no, no.
But, as soon as it comes,
As soon as it comes, first of all, for you.
But, I'm getting that moment from the Nayak
movie.
I'm like, he's trapped.
But, it is like an experiment.
It might work, it might not.
So, you're doing a lot of biohacking.
And, health.
So, you're focusing on that.
Yes, there are some other people with whom
I'm connected.
And, they're on the same path.
Now, I think, as far as I'm concerned,
I have a lot of faith in science and this
community.
And, the output I've seen for my body, it's
very positive.
So, I'll do it and see.
And, we'll know.
We'll know.
And, videos are coming.
Yes, videos are coming.
I did something in between.
I saw the thumbnail,
I didn't see the video.
That's testing.
Testing.
Basically, I think, it's a very simple philosophy.
To improve health, even in an uneven business,
the thing you can measure, you can improve
that.
So, if you take a blood test, you can measure
vitamin D, A, B, C, whatever comes, you can
measure everything.
Similarly, if you measure your lungs, your
stomach, your pancreas, you can measure everything
and you'll know that these things in your
body are bad.
And, if you track that and keep improving
it, so,
basically, your body will also improve.
And, as it improves, you have a biological
age, which is called the rate of aging.
If you live for a year, then most people,
if they're eating
bad food, if they're not exercising, they
reduce their age.
So, after living for a year, they're dragging
their lives
for two years.
So, if you reduce that, 0.5, 0.3, so, basically,
your rate
of aging, if you live for a year, so, basically,
in that year, you only spent three months.
So, if you live for a year, then your one
year will end.
So, you can live for 150 years.
A lot of biohacking going on here.
And, I'll add one more thing to this, that,
sitting in
India, we think that all these things are
not common.
That, in 70 years, who is tracking and whose
abs are there?
But, there is a country like this in the world,
there is a country in Okinawa, Japan.
There, it is common that 80-90 years old people
have blue zones.
Blue zones.
And, tracking and living a very healthy lifestyle.
So, this is possible from the beginning.
But, by breaking it down, scientifically,
yes,
scientifically, it is being given.
And, I think, this is the future.
And, people will live for 150 years.
But, it takes a lot of money now.
Okay, I have a question for this.
So, you told me your diet is the main thing,
right?
So, do you prefer foods that are only like
raw fruits and veggies, that thing?
Or, what are the impurities that we usually
have in our daily, day-to-day foods?
Like, in flour, even in that,
what do you do with that?
So, I have a lot,
I mean, we can't do anything about it.
We do what we can.
That's why I am asking.
Because, you went to Chennai and did all the
testings and everything.
They can tell you that you eat half a kg of
this, of
fruits, or 100 grams of this.
Those things you can.
But, the impurities in your food, which we
can't see directly.
But, it is like, do you have any solutions?
Of course, in living in this society, sitting
here, we
might have smoked 5 cigarettes.
Because, this is Delhi.
So, we can't do anything about that.
For that, you can shift.
Maybe, you can shift to Kerala.
There, the impurities will be less.
So, that is what
I will also do.
You are planning to do.
He is planning to shift to your city.
I am planning.
I think, to what extent you can go to, that
depends.
For example, there is a guy named Brian Johnson.
He doesn't leave his house.
He cooks his own food.
He does everything himself.
So, what is the use of cooking at home?
But, he experiments on himself and does it
for us.
No, I just wanted to know.
Because, he is the king of biohacking.
He understood the whole technology.
You come up in farms.
You stay where there are a lot of farms.
So, you must be getting pure.
No, no, no.
Impurities is all the way.
Because, even while seeding itself, they use
the pesticides and everything.
They grow the fruits.
Do you do any exercises?
Nothing.
Nothing?
And, you stay fit like this.
No, I was not fit.
Like, when we met 4 or 5 months ago, you told
me about it.
Before, when we met in China.
After that, when I came to Pune.
Because, that's what
I was about to speak actually.
Physical health and mental health.
Both are big things for creators.
So, I keep on running in the morning and day.
In and out.
Because, I have to oversee everything.
Until you have a good team, you have to do
everything.
Which we usually do for the past 8 years.
Then, mental health with all the negativities
happening around you and a lot of things that
is going around you personally and professionally.
So, managing these things was my priority
this particular year.
Going forward, it will change.
Because, after having a lot of discussion
and a lot of
I got to take a lot of things in my mind.
Awesome.
Kanchit bhai.
So, I have a lot of perspective about health.
Especially, creators.
What are you doing?
I will tell you what I am doing.
I will give context behind it.
Shlok told the tech side.
I will tell the emotional side.
I have this problem that I have to take a
lot of stress in the initial days.
So, stress level increases and stress is also
mental obviously.
We don't know.
We seriously don't know what stress is, what
anxiety is,
what depression is.
All three things are different.
But, we think these are words.
But, it is not exactly like that.
There is a different story behind everything.
So, I was in stress and I was taking a lot
of milk.
Obviously, it is expensive.
After that, suddenly, I was not able to digest
protein.
Then, there were a lot of proteins like lentils,
chicken.
So, I was taking a lot of protein.
Then, I was taking a lot of milk.
Then, I was taking a lot of protein.
Whatever it is, I'm not
able to do it.
All this has happened to me within 3 years.
But what was my focus?
YouTube, YouTube, YouTube.
I'm busy with YouTube all the time.
So that was it.
I didn't
understand what was happening
to me.
I thought a bad phase of life is going on.
It will
be fine.
But then, there was a talk going on on the
podcast
of BRBicep.
I keep listening to the podcast.
Manish Pandey, probably a lot of people know
him.
He does a lot for creators.
He's your friend, right?
Hmm.
So he once said in a conversation to someone,
I think Ranveer Alabadia must have said it,
that creators
don't know what the side effect of YouTube
is.
We have no idea because everything is so new.
Some people get hit, some don't.
I was unlucky that I got hit.
Everything.
So recently I was watching a podcast of Ranveer.
Ranveer himself said that he suddenly stopped
digesting cheese.
I have become lactose intolerant.
Maybe Shlok had also said that he stopped
digesting milk.
I think stress is hitting creators.
But we don't realize it.
It's hitting in different ways.
I think so.
But I realized that I have a problem with
stress.
By the way, everything is fine after marriage.
Hahaha.
So, I mean,
Shlok is happy.
I'm kidding.
Anyway, stress management is something.
I just found out.
Maybe it will work in someone's life.
The thing I told you.
But yes, stress management is a process that
should be taken in life if you have stress.
I learned this.
I'm doing it.
Tell me, Gaurav.
Your muscles are very real in the middle.
I can still see it.
No, no.
I have taken a little break now.
But I think if we just follow the basics.
Basics means.
Do workout.
Half an hour, one hour.
Whatever.
You just walk or go for a jog.
Or lift weights or whatever.
Basically, there has to be a balance.
Between your diet.
Between your sleep.
And your workouts.
As long as you have those basics set right.
You are going to the gym.
You are sweating.
You are jogging.
And you are sweating.
I think it drains all the negative energy.
It freshens you up.
If you wake up in the morning and do workout.
For the rest of the day, you are completely
charged.
You will be charged.
Good thoughts will come.
You will do the work well.
It's a loop.
It's a positive loop that you go into.
As long as you are maintaining a balance.
I mean.
You are partying for a day in a week.
But do you know that the next day.
I will have to balance what I ate last night.
I am taking out the waste here for two hours.
So as long as you have a balance.
It should be fine.
I am not the person who will be like that
in any case.
I will lock myself in the house like a normal
person.
I am not like that.
Or for example, Shlok did his research.
I won't go that extreme.
I think as long as I am able to do the basics.
It's a good enough thing.
And at least to start with.
You have to do that.
The rest is on top of it.
By the way, I will share a few things.
Because we were talking about this.
So I had the same problem.
With a lack of some vitamins.
You get depressed.
I mean if you are deficient in some vitamins.
I think there are some vitamins of B.
For a period of two to three years.
You will get depressed.
You will get anxiety attacks.
And with vitamin D, you lose sleep.
For example, I didn't have any protein left.
With the supplementation of B1 and B12.
I am able to digest protein well now.
So I think.
I mean if we look at food a little consciously.
I mean it's not necessary.
You have to take a tablet.
It's in nutritional yeast.
It's in egg or something.
By supplementing all that.
If you are eating properly.
You can stop depression.
It's possible that anxiety attacks.
Stress.
If you can stop all these things.
I am saying what happens is.
Basically, in this creator space.
Because of the priorities set towards that.
Everything else takes a toll.
You won't be able to sleep on time.
Eating and drinking will be random.
You travel a lot.
Because of that, the routine is not set.
So it gets affected.
Whether you see it in a year.
Or in two years.
Or in five years.
Depending on how long your body can tolerate
that thing.
Sometimes you will get the result.
So I think because of the kind of burnouts.
You are facing.
Or you are too much engrossed into just your.
Like creating thing.
So I think a balance is necessary for that
thing.
As long as it's balanced.
To start with.
That should happen.
If that doesn't happen.
Then its negative will definitely happen.
Irshad.
Tell me.
I am seeing the journey.
Right in front of you.
He has lost something like 15 kgs.
Now he is on his way.
Yeah, so bad eating habits.
I mean because.
Eating happens due to stress.
You know.
Eat anything.
And never cared about health.
I obviously play a lot of cricket.
And like you know.
We started playing cricket in office.
Okay.
Yeah, so I have also ensured.
That the whole team on Saturday.
Every Saturday we play cricket.
So.
Very proper.
I couldn't run.
And I am like.
This is not me.
Like this is not me.
Like you know earlier.
So I had to like.
Take some changes.
Make some changes.
I didn't start with exercise.
Obviously.
I used to only play cricket.
But I started intermittent fasting properly.
And then I cut sugar from my life.
I don't.
I don't generally prefer sugar either.
But sugar is not required for your body.
Very good advice.
Yeah.
So it's not.
Sugar.
That's the best.
Both of us don't eat sugar.
Yeah.
I mean additional sugars.
But total I mean.
And then also like.
Protein intake and everything.
That's not been a problem.
But cutting carbs.
All those basic things.
Doing those basic things.
It's making a difference.
And now I have started.
Proper exercising as well.
Which is basically walking and running.
So it's helping.
So I was 110.
Now I am like.
What?
Yeah.
Now I am like 98.
I was 110 at one point of time.
I was like literally.
Into YouTube space.
I was like.
I was in a very bad mental state.
This is common.
Bad mental space.
Every YouTuber.
It reflects into your routine.
That's the problem.
You are not in your right mind.
You won't be able to sleep.
You won't be able to wake up the next day.
On time.
Your day.
So it's a loop.
Sir this YT creator studio app.
Which is showing you in real time.
Now 10 views have increased.
Now 20 have increased.
See.
Depends.
That's what I am saying.
Depends on how much you are using.
Then it is showing comments.
Then you know.
You are getting feedback in real time.
The audience is feeling bad.
Feeling good.
This is a very stressful thing.
Which can happen to anyone.
So I did.
Went for like a therapy session.
With a proper psychologist.
That kind of.
That was the initial thing.
Then after that I.
Does it help?
Yeah it does.
It does help.
How many sessions you had?
I had like a proper.
Help for you?
But I didn't.
I don't believe.
For me it works.
So it's fine.
So.
No it's about how we perceive it.
They will give their input.
Based on our.
Whatever saying we have.
But we need to act accordingly.
So it might differ person to person.
Yeah that is there.
So for me it worked.
And after that I decided.
I have to reduce my weight.
So.
No I heard a dietician.
I have a back issue.
I have a spine issue.
I have a slipped disc.
Okay.
So I can't work out.
Or lift heavy stuff.
Or run for a very long time.
So I have a dietician.
I'm still following a proper diet.
So that's how I reduced it to 98.
Still.
You are you are slim and trim.
So you do something for it.
Or it is all natural.
Multiple things.
I'm going to tell you that only.
YouTube studio.
Or YouTube.
The more stats we see on the phone.
The more anxiety there is.
And sometimes.
The game of views is going up and down.
So you don't like it.
So just before the shoot.
You were showing me a video.
And I told him.
I don't have YouTube.
I'm watching it on Safari.
Because I'm detoxing.
So the idea is simple.
I don't keep all these apps on my phone.
Because I'm so engrossed in the office.
YouTube.
Instagram.
Facebook.
Twitter.
None of the apps are on my phone.
So that is one thing that I don't do.
Like don't keep it in my phone.
I install it.
For fitness.
So there are various basic things.
On which we collectively work throughout the
office.
Like.
From this data I've got from internet only.
That if you walk 10,000 steps in a day.
So you can stay away from a lot of diseases.
So we have.
We are doing a step up challenge in our office.
So we are 35 people.
So 35 people are challenging each other.
And everyone has to complete 10,000 steps.
Every single day.
It's tracked on an app.
I mean a step up app.
It will be tracked on that.
And the winners will get exciting prizes.
So this is how we are promoting fitness.
In our office.
We should implement something like this at
our office.
This app.
Because I want.
It tracks through just the smartphone.
Or it can pair with an Apple watch.
Or a fitness band.
Or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
It can be paired with a fitness band also.
Or it can be paired with your phone as well.
Because the steps on the phone will be a little
inaccurate.
Because you either have to keep the phone
in the gym.
Now there's a catch in that as well.
If you do it like this.
Then also the step count will be there.
But we will give that benefit of doubt.
Obviously.
It's up to you.
At least if someone is doing it like this
with dedication.
Then it will be a little more impressive.
But yeah.
It's a good thing.
And people.
I mean all the team members.
They are taking it very positively.
And this is one thing we are doing.
But slowly and gradually.
We will amplify it more.
We have just started with walking.
Walking is the best exercise.
By the way.
You had also told in a podcast.
I used to walk 30,000 steps.
Yeah, exactly.
4 months straight I did that.
And I lost 30 kilos in 4 months.
Wow!
From 105 to 75.
You told me this in your podcast.
If I open my health app and go to the gym
for that duration the rings go around 10 times.
2000 calories burn.
2500 calories burn just from walking.
3 hours, 3.5 hours, 4 hours walk.
Walking is the best exercise.
You are always extreme.
This is in nature.
For me, it's either best or nothing.
As long as I am not doing it or if nothing
is involved then it's fine.
But the day I come in, I want to make sure
that I take the lead.
What a word of thanks.
I hope everyone enjoyed the conversation.
I am presuming.
There
will be takeaways for everyone.
And hopefully we can
do
this next year as well.
That's the idea.
This is just the beginning.
How much duration did you do?
3.5 hours.
3.5 to 4 hours.
I am getting a lot of blessings from my heart
for some editor.
2,000 to 4,000 GB data.
The editor is watching the video.
Minimum 3,000 to 4,000 GB data.
If there
are 8 cameras and 3 roles.
And RAW.
3 to 4 TB data.
That's
what I am saying.
All done.
Thank you
so much.
It was fantastic.
Thank you, crew.