in the short series we'll show you how
to buy and set up a burner phone by the
end you'll be a real james bond burner
phone pro you cannot use your regular
phone as a burner phone the imei and
imis numbers will give away your
identity and privacy select an
electronics retail store in a different
part of the city from where you live
that sells prepaid unlocked phones in
the us or canada visit walmart best buy
target or kmart you'll pay with cash if
you withdraw cash from an atm do so the
day before and from near your home
withdraw more than you'll need and do
not visit an atm in or near the store
you'll be shopping at before visiting
the store leave your phone and other
internet devices at home do not bring
them with you if your car is internet
enabled do not drive it to the store
take public transportation instead once
at the store purchase a prepaid
smartphone that usually costs between 60
and 120 dollars purchase a monthly pays
you go sim and traveler plan kit for as
little as 15 do not register the phone
or the sim in your real name or with
your real address have a fake name and
address ready turn on setup and test the
phone and sim in the store shut the
phone off and if possible remove its
battery before you leave the store next
part 4 how to use a burner phone
subscribe right now to take back control
of your privacy and become a burner
phone