Hello, friends!
Is democracy over in our country?
This is a very serious question.
Many of you will have a
simple answer to this question:
Obviously not.
We can vote for any political party we want.
The politician who gets the most votes,
comes in power,
so obviously democracy still exists in our country.
But this question is much deeper than that.
The things that I am going to
show you in this video today
will be very shocking.
After watching this video, you will be forced to think
about the real answer to this question.
Although, if you are someone
that considers PM Modi to be a god,
"He is our god.
We worship him."
"Prime Minister Modi,
he is God's incarnation to us.
He is not a normal human."
"This country's Prime Minister is the incarnation of Lord Vishnu."
"God incarnate."
Or if you are someone
who thinks that Modi's every action helps humanity,
if you're already in awe of PM Modi,
"Modi is my husband,
my brother, my father, my teacher."
"-Okay.
-What do you want to say?"
"Why do you feel like no one other than
Modi or Yogi can bring development?"
"I am in love with him."
In such cases,
it might be difficult for you
to open your eyes and look at the truth.
But for the rest of the viewers,
if you truly care about the country,
watching this video is immensely important.
It's not just about one incident,
but many such incidents
that are happening one after the other,
for the past few months,
for the past few years.
All those incidents point to one thing,
that our country is moving forward towards One Nation, One Party.
Eradicating the voice of the opposition from the media,
horse-trading of the MLA's,
the taking away power from the elected governments
by making new laws.
Weaponisation of investigative agencies.
Pressuring and imprisoning
opposition politicians through ED and CBI.
Interfering in state governments' work through governors.
Withholding funds from state governments.
Taking away the right of the citizens to protest.
And if someone protests,
welcoming them with tear gas and rubber bullets.
Using electoral bonds to hide their funding.
And even if an opposition candidate manages to win the election,
then committing election fraud
to declare themselves the winner.
I would like to tell PM Modi,
"Have some decency!"
Before talking about democracy, friends,
it is important to know what democracy actually is.
It is a basic concept
but most people have a major
misunderstanding of this concept.
Some people think that
if there are regular elections in the country
and you can go to vote,
then it means that the country is a democratic country.
But you know what?
Elections are held in North Korea too.
I am not kidding.
There are regular elections in North Korea.
You can also see 100% voter turnout in those elections.
But the only difference is that
if you do not vote for the official candidate elected by the government,
you are considered anti-national.
Your job can be snatched away,
your house can be snatched away.
And if it's just about the word democracy,
then the official name of North Korea,
the word democracy is included in it.
North Korea is called the DPRK by their government.
Democratic People's Republic of Korea.
But what is the truth?
This country is a dictatorship.
Similarly, Russia is also considered a dictatorship.
But elections are held there too.
The only difference is that any candidate
who competes against Putin
is sometimes disqualified for some reason,
or sometimes k!lled mysteriously.
So, one thing should be clear from this
merely having elections does not mean
that the country is a democracy.
Elections need to be free and fair.
Free means that the people have freedom
to vote for whom they want to
and Fair means that
different candidates and different political parties
have a fair chance of winning.
It shouldn't be that one party has a lot of advantages.
Recently, the Chandigarh Municipal Corporation held its Mayor elections.
For this election, Congress and the AAP had formed an alliance,
and had a total of 20 votes out of 35.
It was clear by the party votes that
this alliance would win the elections.
But when the elections actually took place,
what did the presiding officer do?
This is not a secret.
You can see the CCTV footage of what he did.
He declared 8 Congress and AAP  votes as invalid.
And this election fraud that took place here,
was captured in the CCTV camera.
In fact, he was caught looking at the camera too.
Look at his face.
The way he is looking at the camera,
it looks like he was caught stealing.
And what was the result of the election?
BJP claimed to have won this election.
Such an open election fraud
has probably never happened in the country before.
The Chief Justice of India said that
this is a m*rder of democracy.
Although in a historic decision, the Supreme Court
had to save this election,
the question is,
if there were no CCTV cameras here
or ballot papers,
would this fraud have been caught?
This is just one example, friends.
Before that, look at this news from 2021.
An EVM machine was found in a BJP candidate's car in Assam.
After this, the Election Commission had to order a repoll in this place.
But no need to talk about old news.
Look at this month's news.
February 2024.
Three unknown people went to the Saswad Tehsil office in Pune
to steal the control unit of the electronic voting machine.
Is this a joke?
Are our elections being conducted in a free and fair manner?
The Election Commission is an organisation
which is expected to conduct free and fair elections across the country.
But the Election Commission has been accused
of being partial and biased.
This accusation is very old.
Initially, BJP politician Narendra Modi had made this accusation.
You heard it right.
Before the May 2014 election,
Narendra Modi accused the Election Commission.
Although he won later elections.
But in the last 10 years,
the Election Commission has been accused so much that
Prashant Kishore said that
the Election Commission is an extension of BJP.
He says that he has never seen such a
partial and biased Election Commission.
That this Commission has always tried to bend the rules.
And tried to make the schedule of elections in such a way that
BJP always benefits.
The Election Commission has given very clear directions
that the Indian Army cannot be mentioned during political campaigns.
But before the 2019 elections, PM Modi,
shamelessly asked for votes
using the martyrs and airstrikes.
"I want to ask my first-time voters that
can your vote be dedicated to
the brave martyrs in Pulwama?"
Chief Minister of Uttar Pradesh, Adityanath, went on to
call the Indian Army as Modi's Army.
"And Modi's army sh**ts the terr0rists."
When a complaint was filed with the
Election Commission regarding this,
no action was taken for 21 days.
And after 21 days, the Election Commission gave its clean chit.
The rules are clearly written,
they are being openly violated
but still a clean chit.
It's not the only clean chit,
PM Modi has got such clean chits in at least 4 different cases.
Amit Shah compared Rahul Gandhi's constituency with Pakistan.
This is also against the rules.
But the Election Commission has given clean chits in this too.
In total, there are 7 such cases
in which Modi and Shah have received clean chits.
NDTV had also reported that
one out of three election commissioners,
had a dissenting opinion
in 5 out of the 7 cases.
It means that there was an election commissioner
who believed that they should not be given clean chits.
Later, it was found that the name of this
election commissioner was Ashok Lavasa.
Do you know what happened to him later?
His wife, son, daughter, and sister all got
notices from the government agencies.
The Citizen Commission on Elections in their report stated that
Ashok Lavasa was silently removed from the election commission.
Just think, this is an election commissioner,
is this a democracy or a dictatorship?
In a democracy, separation of powers,
independence of institutions,
is something you must have read about in school.
Our Supreme Court had given an order
to strengthen the independence of the election commission.
To have the Chief Election Commissioner and other Election Commissioners
be appointed by a three-member committee.
One of whom will be the Prime Minister,
the other will be the opposition leader
and the third will be the Chief Justice of India.
By doing this, it could be ensured that
the Election Commissioner who is being appointed
will be truly independent.
There will be no bias towards any entity.
But a few months ago,
the government brought in a new law
in which the government said that
the Chief Justice of India would be removed from this committee.
Instead, they added their minister to the committee.
So, in three-member committee,
two of them will be from the government
to appoint the Election Commissioner.
If BJP's intentions were clear,
then why was such a law passed?
Why does the government want to control
the appointment of the Election Commissioner?
This was later challenged in the Supreme Court,
but the Supreme Court did not take any action here,
saying that this falls under the separation of powers.
If the government is making a law,
then the Supreme Court does not want to strike it.
Even today, the Election Commission has set a limit on
how much money can be spent on an MLA election and an MP election.
In an MP election, the limit is ₹9.5 million.
BJP contested the election on 437 seats.
So, the total spending of the party
should not have been more than ₹4.15 billion.
But how much did they spend?
It is written on the website of the Election Commission,
₹12.64 billion.
how did the Election Commission allow this?
The Center for Media Studies also estimated that
BJP had spent ₹270 billion in the previous elections.
Which was 45% of the total expenditure.
If you look at the data of today,
electoral bonds worth ₹160 billion have been sold.
Out of these ₹160 billion,
more than ₹100 billion went to BJP,
₹15 billion to Congress
and ₹8 billion to TMC.
All these amounts surpass the spending limit of the election.
BJP leader Uma Bharti once said,
"Elections are a choice between bad and worse."
Which is true.
But think about it.
If a social worker who has dedicated his life to serving people,
how will he be able to bring ₹9 million to contest an election?
How will he be able to promote himself?
Especially when on the other side,
the party has billions of rupees.
The problem isn't limited to elections.
Even if an opposition party forms the government,
the government is then broken apart.
Here, countless allegations have been
levied against the BJP for horse-trading.
People have repeatedly accused BJP
of taking MLAs to some resort
and buying them with an unimaginable amount of money.
Are these allegations of horse trading true?
I cannot tell you because
I have never been to that resort.
But you can imagine,
all those MLAs in the resort won't be merely playing Ludo.
Investigative agencies are responsible
for investigating such allegations.
But if all the investigative agencies
dance to the tune of a single political party,
then who will investigate these allegations?
Now imagine what would be going on in the MLAs' homes.
The politician who buys these MLAs,
what would he say to his family?
Proudly telling them the good news
that he suppressed the voice of the people.
That he str@ngled democracy.
Hoping to be praised.
And the other MLA, who sold his soul for some money,
what would he tell his family?
Proudly showing the money he brought in.
By maligning the integrity of the nation by falling for horse-trading.
Celebrating his lack of integrity.
It's easy to get angry at such politicians,
but they're pitiful too.
How miserable they are,
how low they have fallen.
Horse-trading and luring politicians with money is just one way.
If an MLA doesn't fall for this,
the second way is to use the investigative agencies.
Using ED,
weaponisation of ED.
Last year 14 political parties had
complained to the Supreme Court
about how the government is using CBI and ED
against opposition leaders.
They said that they have carried out
more than 3,000 raids on political leaders.
If you compare it with 2014,
you can see a 4 fold jump in the number of ED cases against politicians.
And 95% of the cases are registered against opposition parties.
In response, ED said that their conviction rate is very high.
The conviction rate is 96%
because the trials in 25 cases are over
and there was a conviction in 24 cases.
But the truth is that from 2005 till now,
ED has registered more than 5,900 cases.
The trial was conducted in only 25 cases.
And the conviction was in only 24 cases.
That translates to only 0.5% of the cases being substantial.
Whenever an opposition politician is accused of corruption
and he joins BJP,
all charges vanish suddenly.
All cases against him are dropped.
Someone had even written a poem on him.
*Washing Powder Modi*
*lies and frauds*
*it hides everything*
*even serious allegations disappear in a blink*
When Himanta Biswa Sharma was in Congress,
he was accused in the Saradha Chit Fund Scam.
CBI called him for questioning in November 2014.
And since 2015, when he joined BJP,
7 more allegations of corruption have been filed against him.
One allegation is about a land scam,
another allegation is that he is running
syndicates in the silk and muga industry.
But since he joined BJP,
there have been no investigations on him.
By the way, the list of politicians who
went in BJP's washing machine is very long.
Many of these politicians were previously
mentioned by PM Narendra Modi in his speeches
as examples of corruption.
Calling NCP the Naturally Corrupt Party,
and asking people to never vote for them.
But as soon as these leaders joined BJP,
the investigations stopped
and the corruption scams were forgotten.
BJP leader Atal Bihari Vajpayee had once said
where someone has to rely on corrupt individuals to gain power,
he said that he wouldn't want to get near that power.
"If I get power,
I don't even want to touch such power with a tong."
But that era was completely different.
That BJP and today's BJP,
are vastly different.
Today when Nitin Ghatkari is asked about Modi's washing powder,
he answers with a smile that
BJP's detergent is eco-friendly.
It's important to win in elections,
and the winner decides what's right or wrong.
"BJP's soap is washing away everyone's scandals in a washing machine."
"It's an eco-friendly detergent."
Whom do you agree with more?
Present-day Nitin Gadkari
or the former PM Atal Bihari Vajpayee?
Comments below.
Even despite the lure of money
and the pressure of ED,
if an opposition politician doesn't join BJP,
the proceedings against them continue.
And in many cases,
they are put in jail without being convicted.
And they remain in jail for many months.
AAP MP Raghav Chadda said that
if Manish Sisodia, Satyendra Jain, Abhishek Banerjee, Sanjay Raut,
Farooq Abdullah, and Tejashwi Yadav join BJP,
all the cases by ED and CBI against them
will be dismissed immediately.
And people like Manish Sisodia, and Satyendra Jain who are in jail
will be released immediately.
Now, to imprison someone after a conviction is a different matter.
But here, opposition politicians are being
sent to jail before they are convicted.
The worst thing is that in the states where opposition governments exist,
they are not allowed to work there.
Not just one or two, but many states have
repeatedly accused the Modi government that
they are using governors to interfere in the state's day-to-day affairs.
They are preventing the state governments from working.
The West Bengal government has said this.
The West Bengal governor has been repeatedly blamed for this.
The Tamil Nadu government has said this.
The Delhi government has said this.
The Kerala government has said this.
Last year, the Kerala government even accused the governor
of delaying the bills passed by the state government for 2 years.
Delaying the bill's approval.
The state of Kerala even complained to the Supreme Court about this.
The Supreme Court said that the governors cannot delay bills like this.
That this is unconstitutional.
The issue between the LG and the Delhi government in Delhi
has been in the news for many years.
Over the last few years,
CM Kejriwal has repeatedly said that
they are not allowed to work.
The LG interferes in their work.
The Delhi government approached the Supreme Court for this
and the Supreme Court's decision was in their favour.
The Supreme Court stated that
LG should not interfere in this way.
The real power should be in the hands of the elected government.
But what did the Central Government do
after the Supreme Court's decision?
They brought a new law
to take away the powers of the Delhi government.
GNCTD,
Government of National Capital Territory of Delhi (Amendment) Act, 2023.
The Modi government used this
to transfer many powers vested with
the Delhi government to the LG.
"We changed the hospitals.
We made them grand.
We arranged for all the medicines.
They forced the officers to disrupt the flow of medicines.
They stopped the tests.
Last year, for three months, no tests could be run in the mobile clinics.
They stopped the payments to the laboratories.
They play dirty and are disgusting people.
By passing one order one day,
they removed the data entry operator
in all the government hospitals in Delhi.
Now there is no one left to register patients in the hospitals.
I ask them, what do you want to do?
Do you want to k!ll the people of Delhi?"
Think about it yourself, friends.
Even if you are a Modi fan,
forget about him for a second
and ask yourself sincerely.
If PM Modi was really worried about the country,
the people of the country,
would he have done such things?
Now some of you will think that
surely some opposition party has funded me to make this video.
But I am telling you the truth,
no political party has funded me.
The things that I am showing you in this video
represents the reality of the country.
If you are really concerned about the country,
then you should open your eyes after seeing these things.
News Laundry revealed an investigation report two days ago
that shows ED is used not only against other political parties,
but also against companies in the country.
At least 23 such companies which
hadn't donated any money to BJP yet.
Central agencies raid their premises
and a pattern emerges.
After the raid, those companies donated millions of rupees to BJP.
In total, these companies donated ₹3.35 billion to BJP,
which were subjected to IT or ED raid.
So, were these companies threatened to extort money?
Are our elections held in a free and fair manner?
Here, the media also plays an important role too.
Fair elections mean that the politicians of
the ruling party and the opposition
are given an equal chance to speak.
Both get more or less equal media coverage.
But what do we see in the media?
Day and night, 24*7, the media sings praises the government.
They praise the ruling party.
Or repeat their talking points.
"Every mother in the country wants her son to be like PM Modi.
and every son wants to be like Narendra Modi."
"Modi has the solution to everything."
"There's no one like PM Modi."
"Modi built the New India."
"PM #1"
Opposition parties may go on a Bharat Jodo Yatra,
to make promises to the government.
There was a time when on Doordarshan
the politicians of the ruling party and the opposition party,
debated on important issues before the election on the news channel.
Both had the right to defend their stance.
Can today Doordarshan do this?
Today, the BJP spokesperson doesn't even need to speak
because TV anchors have become BJP spokespersons.
Instead of questioning the government on behalf of the people,
they defend the government.
And they defend the government to an extent that
they might start to hold the youth
responsible for increasing unemployment.
And if you have elected an opposition party in the elections,
then they will start insulting the people.
"And the people have turned away
from the national issues and BJP.
They choose to vote based on
which party will give them free stuff."
NDTV was the last TV channel
which dared to question the government.
Ultimately, NDTV was taken over by PM Modi's friend, Gautam Adani.
Today, TV news has d!ed a silent de@th in our country.
The government uses tax money to
give huge amounts of money to these TV
channels for running 'advertisements'
and these TV channels work to suppress the voices of the citizens.
If the real news doesn't reach you,
will you be able to decide freely and fairly who to vote for?
Manipur was set ablaze for 77 days,
but there were no special reports on TV channels.
Recently, the CAG of India presented 12 reports,
which had a lot of irregularities
and instances of corruption
in government departments and ministries.
Under the Ayushman Bharat scheme,
more than 900,000 people
were using only 3 mobile numbers.
Millions of rupees were spent on the treatment of 3,400 patients
who were already declared dead.
When this CAG report came out,
the government transferred the CAG officers.
Have you heard this news on TV channels?
You haven't.
How will it reach you?
The second misunderstanding that people have is
they confuse democracy with majoritarianism.
Imagine that you are travelling in a car with 5 people.
One person in the car says that he wants to listen to loud music.
He convinces his friend and the driver
that they should play loud music in the car.
But you are travelling with your father who has a heart problem.
You say that loud music should not be played.
That person says, that all of you should
vote to prove that it's a democracy.
And three people voted that loud music should be played.
Your father and you, are the two people,
who say that loud music shouldn't be played.
Since the majority voted to play loud music
in a democracy, it would mean that loud music will be played in the car.
Is this really democracy?
No, this is stupidity.
To give you a small-scale example in real life,
then look at this circular from a society in Gurgaon.
"Dear Residents,
This is to inform you that
two wheeler not permitted inside our society
as per decision of the management."
It means that only cars will enter the society,
scooters and motorcycles cannot.
Look at the unabashed discrimination.
The management, the RWAs,
have been elected by the people.
So even if you don't like this rule, you would need to keep quiet.
Because the majority has consented to this,
they have elected the RWLO.
People who confuse democracy and majoritarianism,
must be thinking this.
This is not just about one society,
there are many such societies all over the country
where you will find such stupid rules if not stupider.
Look at this article from 2019.
A bank employee is saying that her sister didn't get an apartment on rent.
Because many RWOs blacklisted her
just because her sister was an air hostess.
Some societies say that they can't rent an apartment to an air hostess
because of their odd work timings.
Often, these RWAs make up any baseless rule they want to.
For example, in some societies in Noida,
entry and exit fees have been imposed.
Anyone who wants to rent an apartment in these societies,
will have to pay an entry fee.
And they will, of course, be required to pay the rent to the landlord,
but when they leave the society,
they have to pay an exit fee.
The majoritarianism at the local level in the country,
Some people think this about politicians and governments.
Once the politicians are elected and they are in power,
they can make any rule they want.
On the Preamble to our Constitution,
4 words are clearly written
Liberty, Equality, Fraternity, and Justice.
These 4 words are the cornerstones of democracy.
In fact, Dr. Ambedkar went one step further.
He said that these 4 words are the principles of life.
So, a majority vote doesn't mean that
you can take away someone's natural rights,
discriminate against them or make nonsense rules.
This is why we can say that some of the decisions taken by the government
go against democracy.
In the language of the Supreme Court,
they are unconstitutional.
Like just a few days ago,
the Supreme Court struck down the Electoral Bonds Scheme
calling it unconstitutional.
The court said that the government had made an arbitrary rule.
Why was this Electoral Bonds Scheme unconstitutional
and against the welfare of the people?
I have talked about this in previous videos.
So, it was a good step by the Supreme Court
even though the decision was a bit late,
but at least the took the right decision
in favour of democracy and the people.
But holding the government accountable
is not only the Supreme Court's responsibility,
but in a real democracy,
this is the job of the opposition,
media, civil society, and the citizens.
And for this reason,
mechanisms like RTI, Right to Information Act, exits.
Which gives us data about the government.
For the same reason, the media is called the fourth pillar of democracy,
so that it will hold the government accountable.
But what is the situation today?
Till date, PM Modi has held zero press conferences
where unscripted questions have been asked.
Accountability is at absolute zero.
Forget the press conference,
he doesn't have the courage to face one unscripted question.
When Dr Manmohan Singh was the Prime Minister,
he held press conferences or addressed the press at least 117 times.
The last time a proper press conference was held in our country
by the Prime Minister,
it has been more than 10 years since that day.
In that last press conference,
62 unscripted questions were asked to PM Dr Manmohan Singh
with more than 100 journalists present.
In a true democracy,
this accountability is the reason
which gives the citizens the right to protest.
If the managers elected by our country
are not interested in being held accountable under the RTI,
aren't comfortable with being accountable to the media,
then they will have to be held accountable by the citizens.
A positive example of this was recently seen in UP
when the UP government made a very strange and undemocratic rule.
They issued guidelines for coaching centres
that they should not conduct classes for girls after 8 pm.
If they do, action will be taken against them.
And what was the government's justification?
That it was necessary for the safety of girls.
But does this make any sense?
Instead of controlling the ones who are a threat to girls,
instead of controlling the problematic elements,
they tried to put the girls in cages.
protested against these rules.
And after the protest,
the UP government withdrew the ban.
This small incident shows
the power of the people in a democracy.
But what if the right to protest is taken away from people?
Recently, when farmers had to go back to the streets to protest again,
the government welcomed them with sharp nails.
In some places, roads were dug
to completely block the roads.
Then rubber bullets were fired at the farmers,
tear gas was thrown at them, using drones.
As if this was a war zone.
The photos of the border crossing made it look like
this was the national border with China.
Even there, there are no arrangements like this.
And in the news, it is being reported that
at least 3 farmers went blind
because of the rubber bullets fired by the police.
We will talk about the reasons behind this protest
and the demands of the farmers
in a separate video.
But for now, this doesn't matter.
The point here is that
the government treating citizens peacefully protesting like this,
Is this right?
Before this, there was the wrestlers' protest.
The police behaved similarly back then too.
This was the case in the last farmer protest too.
Numerous farmers lost their lives during the protest.
According to an article from 2021,
at least 600 farmers were killed in the last farmers' protest.
And these are the protests that you get to hear about in the news
because these protests have gotten bigger than a certain limit.
Apart from this, most of the protests that were held over the last few years
have never been talked about in the news.
Did you know about Kashmiri Pandit's protests that lasted more than 40 days?
About the government employees protesting against the old pension scheme,?
Or the protest in Hisar that continued for more than 400 days?
Against the closing of the Doordarshan Kendra,
Or the doctors' protest last year,
or the protest by the unemployed youth.
Don't delude yourself that this has nothing to do you,
since you are not taking part in these protests.
Because tomorrow, if you are subjected to any injustice,
if the government takes any decision
that goes against your rights.
And you go out to protest to defend your rights.
What do you think?
Won't you be treated the same way
these farmers are being treated today?
Are you special?
If the government is treating all the protesters this way,
then you won't get any special privilege.
Now this question that I asked you at the beginning of the video,
I would like to ask again.
Is democracy still alive in the country today?
Whatever your answer may be,
but one thing is for sure,
if the situation continues to deteriorate this way,
it will not take much time for us to fall
to the levels of North Korea and Russia.
Democracy will exist on paper,
elections will also be held,
but in the real sense,
democracy will have breathed its last breath.
Thank you very much!