Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, Sadhguru, did
you start participating yoga at a very young
age?
Sadhguru: What do you mean, when I was young?
I'm young, man.
When I was in the gym, for about seven years,
every day, I could run up a coconut tree.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Who showed you this
path?
Sadhguru: I told you, I've been a worm.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Maybe you're
like, totally free, free bird and...
Sadhguru: Hey, bird has bird brain.
Hmm?
I got a human brain (Laughter).
Instrumental music...
Sadhguru: A hungry man has no civilization,
has no morality.
Is that the world we want to create?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Let's talk about
organic farming.
Sadhguru: If the entire country goes into
organic farming, our food production will
come to twenty-five percent of what it is.
How many people do you think will die out
of that?
Instrumental music...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Hi, Sadhguru, can
you tell us about the place we are going to?
Sadhguru: Ah, we're going to the farm, where
they're doing tree-based agriculture.
Yeah, and you can see how the land has improved
in a... just a few years.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): I see a lot of young
people in the ashram.
Sadhguru: Only young people, only young people.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): From childhood, I
have heard people around me say that yoga
and spirituality are things that you should
pursue after your retirement or towards the
end of your life.
But at the Isha Foundation, I see so many
young people.
What is the reason behind this?
Sadhguru: Spirituality is not when you're
no good for anything.
It's (Laughs)...
At the very beginning of your life you must
do it.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But it is often said
that we should live the material part of our
life and explore spirituality at a much later
stage.
Sadhguru: See, that is because of the images
that they've created of spirituality, that
it is something that is anti-life.
Tell me, you can...
Anything that you have, let's say, your phone,
or your motorcycle, the more you know about
it, the better you can ride it, isn't it?
Why is that not true with your life?
The more you know about this human mechanism,
the better you can do it.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Sadhguru, I had one
this one question in my mind for which I could
never find an answer was - when I used to
watch Mahabharata, there was a saying that
everything is predestined and nobody can change
what is destined.
(Speaks in Hindi - not transcribed) On the
other hand, they would always say that, "Life
is in your hands, you should always work towards
_____ (Unclear), it is your karma."
So, I always find these two things as contradictory.
Sadhguru: No, no, no, nobody said that.
This is all losers... losers in life explaining
it like this.
Does Krishna look like a loser?
So, in his given context, he's doing everything
possible.
Well, a lot of things didn't work out as he
planned, but the thing is, he did his best.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, what do you have
to say about teachings that say that everything
is predestined?
Sadhguru: See, those things are said by losers
who have nothing to show for their life.
You don't want to accept your failures and
do better; you want to explain your failures.
Oh, explain it - you'll never know success
in your life.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, you mean everything
is determined by karma?
Sadhguru: No, no, no.
Karma means it's your action.
Yeah, when you say, "My life is my karma,"
you're saying, "My life is my making."
This is the most dynamic way to exist, but
now people have twisted it and made it, "Aiyyo,
karma."
Karma is not something that you inherit, kand...
ma...
karma is in what you're doing right now.
So, what life throws at you is not always
your choice, but what you do with it or how
you hit it is your choice.
Right now, there is a corner, that is the
way it is, but how you take the corner is
entirely yours.
Let's say somebody goes and crashes in this
corner.
Now, they say, "The corner was difficult."
That's not the point.
You didn't know how to take it, that's all
it is.
That's so with every aspect of life.
That's what karma means, it's your doing.
If you make it, it's you; if you don't make
it, it's you.
This is the only culture which has looked
at life like this.
Everywhere they're saying, "God - he is doing
everything."
If God is doing everything, why the hell are
you here?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, Sadhguru, did
you start participating yoga at a very young
age?
Sadhguru: What do you mean, when I was young?
I'm young, man.
You got old, hmm?
I started my yogic practices when I was eleven,
twelve years of age.
And also, by the time I was fourteen, fifteen,
I was in the gym, for about seven years, every
day.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Besides yoga and
flexibility, did you also do a lot of stuff
like weightlifting and strength training and
bodybuilding or going to the gym?
Sadhguru: Not that kind of gym.
I made sure that I were (was?) very lithe,
very strong.
I could run up a coconut tree, like that I
was.
So... so, for me strength and flexibility
were more important than bulging muscles.
So, I kept myself very fit.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): I also spend a lot
of time in the gym, working on myself.
Sadhguru: You don't have to s... you don't
have to say it, I can see it (Laughs).
Instrumental music...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, we are here in
this place for...
Sadhguru is going to tell us what is...
Sadhguru: Tree-based agriculture.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Tree-based agriculture.
Sadhguru: And what it does to the soil.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yes, for me it is
all same thing because for me...
(Overlapping conversation)...
Sadhguru: Yeah, because you're a A320.
You don't know what is soil, what is earth
(Laughs).
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): For me, it is same.
Agriculture means trees and plants.
Like, that's what we do in agriculture, right?
We plant trees, but what is tree-based agriculture?
Agriculture is all about tree, farming, plants.
Sadhguru: Hmm...
See, right now, the important thing is this.
What is happening to India's soil and the
world's soil is this, the organic content
is going away.
Because, year after year, you're taking out
the crop, you're putting lot of pesticide,
you're putting insecticide, you're putting
fertilizer, but no organic content.
Why organic content is, this whole process
of life happens because of microbial activity.
Even you, you're a bodybuilder, but sixty
percent, hmm?
Sixty percent of you is just microbes, you
know that?
Only forty percent is genetic material.
Sixty percent is just microbial life within
you.
So, the food that you eat, you cannot even
digest it without their help.
Similarly, here in the soil, whatever nutrients
that are there, the plant really can't take
it just like that.
It has to exchange with the microbes.
So, it has to catch carbon from the air, make
it into carbon sugars, pump it here, and trading,
okay, for what it wants.
So, this is a very sophisticated marketplace
in the soil.
A handful of soil has anywhere between seven
to ten billion organisms.
So, right now, what we have done is, using
the trees, the green, whatever the material
that is there in terms of leaf, we prune it
and put it back into the soil continuously.
And there are also some animals, with... the
animal waste also go into this.
See, now...
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): _____ (Unclear)
Sadhguru: ...it is not...it is not rained
in probably, you know, two, two-and-a-half
months.
But, you will see...
Come, you've never done this probably.
Just dig here, I'm telling you.
Is it wet still?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yeah, yeah.
It's wet.
Sadhguru: Look at that.
Look at that.
That's rich soil, all right?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): The texture is different.
Sadhguru: Because it's always covered like
this -- with leaf.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Is this how it is
supposed to be?
Sadhguru: Yeah, it's good.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): You don't see...
when you go to fields, you don't see, covered
with leaves.
Sadhguru: That is because they're killing
it.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No, but if the leaves
fall on the ground...
Sadhguru: They will sweep it.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): They will sweep it.
Why?
Because of the...
Sadhguru: No, because there are no leaves.
Where is the leaf?
There are no trees.
You're flying...
Do you...
Did you ever fly in India?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yes, all the time.
Sadhguru: You're flying for a (an?)
Indian airline?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yeah, yeah.
Sadhguru: Okay.
So, when you fly, probably for a pilot, you
can't look down.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): You can't look down.
Sadhguru: If you look down, you will see,
except Western Ghat and northeastern part
of the country, the whole country looks like
a brown desert.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Even this soil is
different.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Haan.
Sadhguru: It's full of life.
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Microbes.
Sadhguru: If you increase the organic content
here to eight to ten percent...
Right now, this may be around three to four
percent.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): This is three to
four percent?
Sadhguru: Yeah, eight to ten percent if you
make it, your irrigation requirement will
come down to thirty percent of what it is
right now.
That is, if you're using hundred liters of
water, thirty liters will do the same job.
If you raise it to twelve to fifteen percent,
ten to fifteen percent of water will do, irrigation.
So, just imagine, 84 percent of India's water
is used for agriculture.
If you bring it down to even twenty, twenty-five
percent of what it is, there'll be ample water
for everything.
Right now, we're just plowing the land, leaving
it open.
This is like, peel off the skin, stand in
the sun, you will be screaming.
Land is just screaming.
People don't hear, that's all.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, you're saying,
only solution is plant more trees?
Sadhguru: No, no, not only trees, there are
many ways to do it.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Okay.
Sadhguru: The important thing is; the ground
should be... not ripped open with plowing
and left open to the Sun.
Something should be there.
There should be grasses, there should be a
crop.
There should be some photosynthesis happening.
So, this leaf has come, not just from the
trees.
They put cover crops and just chop it and
put it right back here.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Okay, okay, okay.
Sadhguru: So, with this, the yields have gone
up significantly.
For farmers, within, let's say, five to seven
years, many farmers are earning 300 to 800
percent more income.
You must see, this is a small farm, it's a
recent one.
These are all just five, six year olds.
You must enter a farm which is ten, fifteen
years old, the water table has come up, soil
organic content has gone up, the nutrient
level in the food has gone up significantly.
They're getting a much better price in the
marketplace.
And above all, the farmer is earning 300 to
800 percent more.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Sadhguru ji, I have
a question.
It used to be, I'm saying, it is supposed
to be eight to ten percent, whatever.
We have, by our own way, made it down to three
percent, four percent.
But...
Sadhguru: No, no, not 3 percent, percent...
4 percent.
In India, 62 percent of India's soil, organic
content is below 0.5 percent.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): You're saying agricultural
land or...
Sadhguru: Agricultural land.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): _____ (Unclear) how
much...
Sadhguru: It's gone below 0.5 percent.
That means we are on the verge of desertification.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): How many years we
have?
Sadhguru: According to the UN, in the entire
world, there is only sixty to eighty harvests
left, that is anywhere between forty-five
to sixty years max.
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): _____ (Unclear)
Sadhguru: By 2045, it's expected we will be
producing forty percent less food than what
we're doing right now.
And our populations will be over 9 billion,
9.2 billion.
That's not a world you want to live in.
Your two children, they will be in that world
if you don't turn it around now.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But the question
was, let's say, 200 years back or 300 years
back, the content was okay... for...
Sadhguru: See...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): ...for farming?
Sadhguru: I'm telling you.
Not even that far away, even fifty, sixty
years ago, there was no farm in this country
without trees and animals.
Now, trees are gone, animals are gone.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): My...
That's my...
My question is, if everybody knows that, (Overlapping
conversation)
Sadhguru: They knew.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): ...that is more beneficial...
(Overlapping conversation)
Sadhguru: Not that they know, they knew.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): They knew?
Sadhguru: Now, we've forgotten.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But, why have we
forgotten?
If this is a more...
better way to...
Sadhguru: See, it's like this.
You're eating good food and you're doing well,
the doctor checks you up and says, "Well,
your calcium is not good enough.
Your vitamin B12 is not good enough, your
iron is not good enough" and gives you three
pills for a month, two months, six months,
something.
You took these pills and you felt really good.
Then you decided, I don't really have to eat.
It...
I just have to multiply the pills.
Instead of three, I will take thirty pills.
That's what we did to the land.
We put little fertilizer, everything burst
out.
We thought this is it.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yes.
Sadhguru: And farmers were advise... advised
like this.
Speaker: That's true.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Everything that happened
during the Green Revolution?
Sadhguru: Yes, it did.
But, we must also understand and appreciate
why that was done.
See, India was a country which was suffering
with famines.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yes, yes, yes.
Sadhguru: Millions of people used to die.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): We were importing...
we were importing wheat.
Sadhguru: Not only that.
Every other year there was famine.
Okay?
So, famines means, in 1942 famine, over three...
three million people died.
So, this used to be the reality of this country.
To offset that, to bridge that somehow, then
we went into Green Revolution.
So, it is like you're unwell, you took some
pills, and you got well.
But, then you should have improved your nourishment.
But, you just started taking only pills, thinking
it will make you well.
Those same pills are making you sick now.
So, we are not against fertilizer, not against
pesticide, not against anything.
The important thing is, organic content should
be there because, first thing is, right now
we are consuming the soil of the unborn child.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yes.
Sadhguru: We're eating up the future's soil.
So, putting life back into this is the most
important thing.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No.
I read somewhere that you should leave the
planet, if not better...
Sadhguru: At least the way...
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): ...in the same way...
Sadhguru: ...at least the way it came to you.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): ...it came to you,
or you received it from your ancestors.
But we are degrading the planet and then giving
it to our...
Sadhguru: Super degrading it.
I'm saying, just imagine.
Just imagine.
Where are you from?
Where you live?
Mumbai?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No, Delhi.
Sadhguru: Delhi.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Delhi, Kanpur.
Sadhguru: Okay, Delhi, Kanpur, wherever.
In your city, suppose, forty percent less
food is available in the shop.
Not that you don't have money to buy, there
is no food, forty percent less food.
That means forty percent of the people are
not eating enough, or they have no food to
eat.
What do you think will happen to your city?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Chaos.
Sadhguru: What kind of chaos do you think?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): The poor will die,
they will not get food.
Sadhguru: Really?
You think they'll die?
No, no.
When they see you, a well-built guy like you,
they'll slaughter you.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Yeah.
Sadhguru: That's not the way it's going to
happen.
A hungry man has no civilization, has no morality,
has no humanity left in him, isn't it?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): _____ (Unclear)
Sadhguru: We'll... we'll push the world in
that direction.
Today, UN agencies are predicting, by 2035,
there'll be dozens of civil wars in the world.
Is that the world we want to create?
But right now, if we act, we can turn this
around in the next twelve to fifteen years'
time.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Another question.
I was working on this project of rainwater
harvesting.
I went around with Jal boards of different
cities.
But then there's a problem.
Sadhguru.
See, my videos are watched by people around
twenty-five to thirty years of age.
Now, the best solution I could give them was,
it was costing them 50 to 55000 rupees to
build a system for rainwater harvesting on
their roof so that you can replenish.
But then they're saying ki, we don't have
50000 rupees to spend.
The problem, why it fails...
We make a video, people watch it, yes, there's
a problem.
They will say Sadhguru ji is right.
Sadhguru: No, no, no, I don't give such...
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But... but...
Sadhguru: I don't give that kind of solutions
ever.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, what...
what...
Sadhguru: Here I'm saying, this is not an
ecological plan for the farmer.
For the farmer, this is an economic plan.
But it has an ecological impact.
So, everything ecological we do is like this;
it's an economic plan.
Because if it's not an economic plan, it'll
anyway not succeed.
Okay?
They must make money out of it, then only
it'll succeed, and then only it'll sustain.
Okay, even if I had 50000... 55000, or 1 lakh
rupees, I spent it today.
Will I spend it every year?
Whatever is needed?
No.
It can only sustain if this becomes economically
very good for me, isn't it?
So, this is about marrying economy and ecology.
Otherwise, there will be no success at all.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): So, you're saying,
farmers who are on the ground, working on
their fields, they should bring this change
or a government policy change?
(Overlapping conversation)
Sadhguru: No, no, no.
Policy change is a must.
Because, see, today, this farm is good.
This is one generation of people.
Because we have worked with them, they've
made their farms like this.
But let's say, next generation comes, they
may do their own thing.
For you to see an example, for example, you
live in Delhi, the New Delhi is built in a
certain way.
Because if you have, let us say, 10000 square
feet of land, you can't build a 10000 square
foot building.
You build 6, 7000, allow some space for yourself,
your neighbor.
This is the law.
You cannot do it.
If you do more, they'll come and knock it
down.
But just go to Old Delhi and see, there's
no concept of a window.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Mhmm... mhmm... mhmm...
mhmm (Indicating agreement)
Sadhguru: One door entry, one door out.
All sides, there are more homes, there is
no possibility of a window.
All right?
Is that the way to build a building?
That happened when there was no law.
So, right now, if you have twenty-five acres
of land, you can plow every inch of it and
turn it into a desert in the next ten, fifteen
years' time.
Nobody will ask you, "Why are you doing such
a damaging thing?"
Because there's no law.
We need a law, that if you own agricultural
land, you must have minimum three to six percent,
this is minimum to keep the soil alive.
If you don't live well, that's up to you.
But you can't snatch away life from future
generations, right now.
Because once soil is gone, there's no life
left.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): But Sadhguru
ji, In that case farmers would say that, you
know, they will earn less, they're already
earning less.
Sadhguru: Arrey, I'm telling you, they're
earning 300 to 800 percent more.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Sadhguru: This is wrong education that we've
given them, right?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm, (Indicating
agreement) right.
Sadhguru: Tell me if the soil is rich, will
you earn less or more?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): More.
Sadhguru: If the soil is rich, will you commit
suicide?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): No.
Sadhguru: 300000 farmers have committed suicide
in India.
Speaker(Ritu Rathee Taneja) : Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Sadhguru: If the soil was rich, even if they
don't have money, if they can grow food for
himself and his family, will he kill himself?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): No
Sadhguru: Then why are we not looking at it?
In United States today, in the last twelve
years, fifty percent of the farmers have not
seen a single dollar.
Okay?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Sadhguru: And the highest suicide rate among
all professions is among the farming community.
It's not just in India.
This is because there is no strength in the
soil.
Your costs are going on because every year
you have to keep on increasing the dosage...
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sadhguru: ...of fertilizer and everything
else.
So, costs are just rising by the year, they're
not able to ta... bear that.
Otherwise, if you raise the food prices, other
people will complain, because... inflation,
they can't handle it.
So, the important thing is, soil has to be
rich.
Soil should be alive, because first twelve
to fifteen inches of soil is the source for
eighty-seven percent of life on this planet.
When you're born, you come out of it; when
you live, you eat out of it; when you die,
you go back to it.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Sadhguru: This is the only magical place in
the universe -- not on the planet -- where,
if you sow death into it, it bursts out with
life.
Tell me one other place like this.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
Sadhguru: Let's make it happen.
Save Soil.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But this is going
to take at least two to three years of transition
period where farmers will earn less because...
Sadhguru: No, no, why?
Why are you...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Straight away from
the next harvest they will earn more?
Sadhguru: See, because in your head it is
stuck, you must do organic farming.
This organic farming is a crime committed
by urban people.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Let's talk about
organic farming because...
(Overlapping conversation)
Sadhguru: No, no.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): ...we pay so much
to get organic foods.
Sadhguru: No, no.
I'm not saying it's not good.
I am saying, you never worked on the land.
So, suddenly you declare, "Organic farming."
Right now, if the entire country goes into
organic farming, without fertilizer, without
pesticide, without any of those things, our
food production will come to twenty-five percent
of what it is.
How many people do you think will die out
of that?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Sadhguru, that's
what exactly I want to ask ki, how to bring
this change?
Sadhguru:.
I'm telling you, institute it in the policy,
first.
If you...
Like, in the city, there is a law.
If you build a house, there must be so much
ventilation, so much space, whatever.
Similarly, if you own an agricultural land,
minimum three to six percent organic content
should be there.
Speaker: Mhmm (Indicating agreement)
Sadhguru: If that is there, you will use a
certain amount of chemicals and stuff to grow.
But, if you increase the organic content to,
let's say, six percent to eight percent or
ten percent, then your fertilizer and everything
will come down, your input cost will come
down.
Well, you may take two, three years to make
this re...
enrichment.
But that also can be offset very quickly,
within a year you can do it.
If the government is willing to give some
subsidy for enrichment of soil, you understand?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Right.
Sadhguru: See, in Tamil Nadu, we promoted
this in the last twenty-four, twenty-five
years, I've been telling the farmers, ten
percent of your land should be trees, which
will provide foliage for the remaining ninety
percent.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Sadhguru: If you don't invest that ten percent,
then everything will die.
Now, if you invest that ten percent, you think
you're earning less?
No.
In the remaining ninety percent, you earn
much more than what you were earning with
full hundred percent.
But we are not saying, "Don't use fertilizer."
As the soil becomes richer, the use of fertilizer
will naturally go down.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Right.
Sadhguru: So, we are not "anti" anything.
Okay?
This is not "Don't use fertilizer, don't do..."
These are things are said by urban people
who have never done farming.
Farming is a heartbreaking job.
Once there is no necessary, you know, inputs
to do that.
See, you don't have to do agriculture like
it's some kind of philosophy or a religion.
This is not what you believe in.
This is about making a practical solution
out of this.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Right.
Sadhguru: I'm just saying don't cut the golden
goose.
If I have to say it very simply, wait for
the eggs to come (Laughs).
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But, it's scary to
listen to the timelines what you have told
us.
2035 will be desert...
(Overlapping conversation)
Sadhguru: See, right now, we are partnering
with UN CCD.
That's a agency, UN agency for combating desertification.
Desertification is the biggest problem in
the planet right now.
Nobody's talking about it because there's
no money in it.
Everybody's talking about fossil fuels, automobiles,
coal, this one, that one because if you knock
industry, it spills dollars.
Here, you can't go and knock anybody, you
have to spend your life to make it happen.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Exactly.
Sadhguru: To convert about 125000 farmers
to... to tree-based agriculture in Tamil Nadu
and Karnataka, twenty-five years of our life
is gone in this.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): With no reward.
Sadhguru: Not that there is no reward.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No, to the people
who are volunteering.
Sadhguru: No, they don't look for a reward.
They want to do it.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Sadhguru: What's a reward?
We're alive, and we're happy, that's a reward
(Laughs).
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement) True.
Sadhguru: What other reward is there in life?
You want a crown (Laughs)?
Very uncomfortable, damn thing to wear, just
know that (Laughter).
Can you imagine a metal ring on your head?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): I always used to
wonder, that... in our epic...
Sadhguru: It's a terrible thing to wear (Laughs).
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): It is shown, it is
of gold.
Sadhguru: See, right now, you're wearing a
helmet, it's properly cushioned, everything,
that only irritates you after some time.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): After some time,
_____ (Unclear)
Sadhguru: Just a metal ring... metal ring,
you put it on your head and walk around.
That's the silliest thing to do.
So, we're not looking for a crown (Laughs).
Rich with life, it's reverberating.
The land, that's how it should be.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Mhmm (Indicating
agreement)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Sadhguru ji, where
do you do so much research?
Do you read?
Sadhguru: No, no, I don't do any research.
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): You have a lot of...
I'm not talking about what you tell about
spirituality, life.
But...
Sadhguru: Even the soil...
(Overlapping conversation)
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But this soil, tree,
seeds...
Sadhguru: ...this is because you know, for
six and a half decades, I have lived on this
planet.
Others don't live on this planet, they live
in their head.
I don't have anything in my head.
So, I live on the planet.
I'm like a worm.
You ask a worm, it knows what is the soil
condition, isn't it?
Do you think the worm in this soil knows more
about this soil than a scientist?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But it cannot tell
us.
Sadhguru: No, this worm can speak.
That's the only difference (Laughter).
That worm also speaks, you're not understanding
the language.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Yes, maybe (Sadhguru
laughs).
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But, it is strange
to see that what is affecting our life, what
is affecting our children, we are not...
Because nobody...
Sadhguru: See...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Even when I heard
about, I was talking to swami ji.
He told me about all that.
Desert... it's going to turn to desert and
the fruits and the vegetables itself, if the
soil doesn't have any nutrition...
(Overlapping conversation)
Sadhguru: It has nothing.
See, right now it's a fashion to eat salads
in America.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No, even in India.
Sadhguru: But for example...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): I eat salads.
Sadhguru: All right.
You?
You eat salad?
You've been eating a buffalo (Laughs).
So, in California especially, it's very fashionable.
But one important item...
This is the only thing which has been studied.
If you study everything, it'll all come out.
Lettuce, for example.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Okay.
Sadhguru: It has only ten percent of the nutrition
it had hundred years ago.
In 1920, if you ate it, what you got, today
you're getting ninety percent less.
You're eating trash.
This is what we've done to our food.
If you ate one orange in 1920, today you will
have to eat eight oranges to get the same
thing.
Can you eat eight oranges?
Even you can't eat.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But then people in
1920 must be starving.
You can't...
The amount of food you eat, amount of space
you have in the stomach, you need...
Sadhguru: No, if the food is rich, you don't
need that much quantity.
Right now, people are eating much more than
what they should eat because it lacks nourishment.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): I thought it is because
of the volume, it satisfies the hunger.
Sadhguru: No, no, that is also there.
See, what level of activity - physical activity
-- people were putting in 1920, and what level
of activity you're putting now is not even
ten percent.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Right.
Sadhguru: Everything had to be done with your
body.
All right?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Now we have machinery.
Sadhguru: So, we can think, it's like, you
know, in the petrol.
Whether you want to ride with a hundred octane,
or you want to ride with fifty octane, it's
a big difference (Laughs).
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): So, you know
what happened, Sadhguru?
One day, I was flying with another captain,
even I'm a captain.
Sadhguru: Oh, you're also a pilot?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Yes, I'm also
a pilot.
I'm with Indigo airline.
So, he told me about you.
And one day, I was on layover and then I actually
tried to do Isha Kriya.
Although I failed at it, but yes.
Then I started following your videos and your
ideology.
So...
Sadhguru: Hey, I have no ideology.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Not exactly
ideology, but...
Sadhguru: Simply, life sense.
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Haanji, life
sense.
But yes, like...
my father tells me this every time.
See, like... as a child needs a teacher to,
you know, guide in a certain way, my father
told me that a person needs somebody.
I mean, like, for me, it's you.
Sadhguru: See, flying an airplane, it's such
a simple, damn thing.
If you just pull it, it will fly.
But, if there was no trainer, you think you
would have?
You'd be dead, probably.
Isn't it (Laughs)?
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): Exactly.
That's what my father tells me.
Sadhguru: Any unknown terrain, if you want
to walk...
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Sadhguru ji, question
comes that, okay, so many people follow you.
You are the trainer who shows them the path.
Who showed you this path?
Sadhguru: I told you, I've been a worm.
I've lived on this planet, absorbed life.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No, but I've seen
so many of his videos.
He never answers this question (Ritu Rathee
Taneja laughs).
Sadhguru: Do I look like I was trained by
somebody?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): No, I don't know.
I'm asking.
Sadhguru: No, no, just tell me, looking at
me (Laughs).
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): I didn't feel
like.
I feel like, that maybe, you're like... totally
free, free bird and...
Sadhguru: Hey, bird has bird brain (Ritu Rathee
Taneja laughs).
Don't tell... call me a bird.
Hmm?
I got a human brain (Laughter).
Instrumental music...
Speaker (Ritu Rathee Taneja): (Speaks in Hindi
- not transcribed) It's very sweet.
Sadhguru: Yes.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Because the soil
has micro...
microorganisms, right?
It has more nutrition?
Sadhguru: Definitely, it has.
Really.
Those neat looking agricultural lands, lines
and lines, they are not good lands.
Unfortunately, we've advertised like that
-- that's how land should look.
No, this is how it should look - full of vegetation.
Instrumental music...
Sadhguru: Farmer is living a quiet, nice life,
with a house, family, settled.
Both his children are well-educated now.
All from the farm.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): But Sadhguru ji you
know, she is from Haryana, a farming background.
But, the main problem is, everyone is sending
their kids to cities.
They don't want them to be farmers.
Sadhguru: Unfortunately, yeah.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Even a... for...
Sadhguru: We have made some kind of a rudimentary
survey.
Not even two percent of the farmers want their
children to become farmers.
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): And even for... they
want...
Sadhguru: Yes...
That is a thing, just imagine in twenty-five
years, if this generation passes, where is
the food security for this country?
Speaker (Gaurav Taneja): Are you taking the
same bike, to ride in Europe?
Sadhguru: Europe, I'm riding a GT 1600.
Arabia, I'm riding this.
From Tel Aviv to Oman, I'm riding this.
Instrumental music...
Sounds of Isha music - Soil Song Lalale Lale
Lale...