Our gynae was an interesting person
The first time we met her,
She asked us “how long have you been trying for?”
“Why does it concern you?”
We got the desired end result.
So, focus on it.
It’s not like if we say it happened in first attempt
You would start celebrating,
“Well done Mr Ranyal,
you have exceeded all expectations.”
Which means we got pregnant 5 years ago.
That’s how maths works.
And these days you have to say ‘We are pregnant’
‘We are pregnant’
Technically only she was pregnant
I just have fat
But still I have to say ‘We are pregnant’
But if I make a mistake
Then only I am an idiot,
Its never like ‘we are the idiots’ and we are pleased to meet you.
That doesn’t happen
We went to a gynae post finding out about our pregnancy
Gynae did some test and told us ‘Good news, you guys are pregnant,
But don’t tell anyone right away.
We will do some more tests in 2 weeks
Post that you can tell people.”
We said okay, Fair enough.
She continued “one more thing,
Now you guys can’t have sex.”
I assumed she meant it only for the 2 weeks.
we are not that desperate
We already did a lot to get pregnant.
Gynae corrected us “No no no,
You can’t do it for the whole 9 months
And 2 months post that.”
Now it doesn’t sound like a good news
It feels like an above average news.
And I couldn’t believe that you cant have sex during pregnancy,
Because our primary source of sex education – English sitcoms.
In that people are doing it during pregnancy.
So I googled “Can you have sex…
Google gives options
The first option was
“Can you have sex in space?”
Who are these kids who want to be astronauts
But want to see if they will get action in space or not.
Second option, I’m not kidding
“Can you have sex post heart attack?”
Both the young and old have too many needs in our nation.
5th option was “Can you have sex during pregnancy?”
I read up all the research articles,
All of them advised against doing it in the first trimester
But recommended it in the second trimester,
Some of them even said you can lift each other while doing it,
Provided there is no physical injury,
If you can manage it.
So I went back to the doctor,
How dare you stop us?
Science says we can.
Doctor replied “Fine, do it then,
But if any complications arises, then don’t come back
You are a doctor,
Your entire profession relies on complication.
What kind of doctor wants only healthy patients?
And I know whenever I discuss this topic – sex during pregnancy,
It divides the room.
Because some people must be thinking “Why so desperate,
You don’t have any control?”
It’s not about control,
I should have the right to decide.
And this is all I have done in the last 4 years,
Whenever I meet a gynae, I ask them
“Do you allow sex during 2nd trimester or not?”
And I have noticed a trend,
That young doctor, who are less than 40,
They are allowing it.
Because they have read the latest textbooks.
Gynae who are 50+ do not allow it
They are dreaming of becoming a grandparent soon.
One of the gynae shouted at me “You shouldn’t even think about it,
Such impure thoughts shouldn’t enter your head.”
Impure thoughts?
You are a gynae,
Your practice relies on these impure thoughts.
if I were a gynae
I would encourage my patients to have more sex,
You get new diseases, I will cure you.
How else will I make money?
Our gynae was an interesting person
The first time we met her,
She asked us “how long have you been trying for?”
“Why does it concern you?”
We got the desired end result.
So focus on it.
It’s not like if we say it happened in first attempt
You would start celebrating
“Well done Mr Ranyal,
You have exceeded all expectations.”
Your horoscopes as well as your organs are compatible.
We got all the tests done in 2 weeks.
Everything was fine.
We told our parents, they got over excited with the news
This is the first time where I have enjoyed a process whose outcome my parents have enjoyed.
My dad started respecting me,
He called me and said “Beta Ji”
I got shocked by the ‘Ji’
so I said “Uncle, wrong connection.”
“it’s your dad, you idiot.”
“Yes , Papa Ji”
But we didn’t tell anyone except our parents
Because of this concept called ‘ Evil Eyes’
What great concept we guys have.
According to ‘Evil Eye’, if you are doing well in life,
Don’t show it, instead hide it.
Because someone will lay their evil eye on it and steal it from you.
Basically, it means, you can buy a Mercedes,
But don’t but it.
Instead buy an activa,
And overtake the same Mercedes from the left side.
Post the first trimester, we told our friends.
Amongst my friends, I was the first one to become a parent.
My guy friends didn’t know how to react,
Single guys don’t know how to act in front of a pregnant lady.
They have seen pregnant women asking for pickle on daily soap.
5 friends came home,
4 of them got pickle.
5th one got us ‘achari paneer’.
My daughter is 4 years old,
We still have the pickle from their first visit.
My friend went crazy, they started cleaning up post party
I went to the kitchen, one friend was cleaning utensils.
I wondered what was wrong with him.
He replied “We don’t want to trouble our beloved sister-in-law”
‘Beloved!!!’
This same utensil washing guy,
During a party before pregnancy, came to our house at 11:30 PM.
Brought 4 more single guys with him.
We didn’t even know them.
And then our friend left the party.
At 3 am, only those four guys and I were awake.
And then I realised that those 4 are not even talking to me.
People who don’t have kids can’t realise what a pregnant couple goes through,
Only people who are pregnant around the same time can connect with you.
Experienced parents have forgotten how difficult it was to raise a child.
Old people feel there is no difficulty in raising a child,
According to them, raising a child is as easy as snapping your finger.
Snap again and you have raised the second child.
If you have twins, you need to snap twice
They were saying anything.
During the 3rd trimester, we were scared about labour pains.
My dad is a doctor, he claimed there are no labour pains.
“What are you even saying?”
He replied “When I was interning at a hospital,
Pregnant ladies would deliver on the way
On their way to the labour room
They would deliver on the train,
They would deliver on the bus,
Some of the were walking towards the hospital and they delivered on the road.”
Did a childbirth ever happen in your hospital?
At least then you would have seen labour pain.
Our relatives would say “Pregnancy is the best time for couples,
It’s even better than honeymoon.”
I wonder what they were doing on their honeymoon?
Pregnancy is not the best time,
I was nervous throughout the pregnancy,
Once I had to calculate 7 multiplied by 4,
I couldn’t remember the answer.
I don’t even remember the table of 7, how can I be a father?
Worst is I couldn’t even remember the table of 4.
Modern couple fight the most over –
What to watch on TV?
Now my wife is pregnant, she had all the control
I put some serious drama, she rejected it saying
“This is too serious, my child is getting sad.”
I changed it to an action movie,
She rejected that too “It has too much violence, it’s impacting my child.”
Now it’s only ‘your’ child.
Isn’t it ‘our’ child?
Next, I put comedy on TV,
She rejected that too, “It’s not making me laugh.”
“It’s my video
Have some shame.”
“I can’t lie to my child.”
Our gynae was the best gynae,
There were some complications in the last trimester,
Everything is fine now, don’t worry.
Our gynae started my wife’s maternity leave one month before delivery,
She would call us for tests during the day.
Now I have a lot of free time,
if she called us during the day, i was there
if she called at night, i was there
I wore shorts whenever she called us
She got concerned after 3-4 appointments,
that I have never seen him wear
So she asked me one day “What do you do?”
I told her “Standup comedy”.
She got even more concerned,
“I hope you can pay the hospital bills.”
“My wife earns a lot, don’t worry.”
The day of delivery, we had a caesarean delivery.
I’m in the operation theatre, my full focus is on wife’s face.
After our daughter got delivered,
The doctor called me to the other side.
I went to the other side,
My wife’s abdomen was cut open,
The doctor’s is showing me the insides.
See this is your wife’s fallopian tube,
This is your wife’s uterus,
This is your wife’s large intestine.
“What are you trying to achieve with this?”
She replied “Now you can go on stage and say
I have seen my wife’s guts.”
You are thinking of jokes right now?
Seal up by wife immediately.