Position the camera.
Be ready.
Start camera.
Action!
Sir.
Gajendra spotted, sir.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir. Gajendra Sahu.
He is not an ordinary target.
He is the most wanted
criminal of this terrain.
Forests and the water bodies
are being ruined by him.
Industries are vanishing.
Hundreds of police officers,
military men
and thousands of civilians
died in an effort to nab him.
He is a high value target.
If he smells your presence there,
none of you would be alive.
You will all die.
(Chants)
That great soul isn't somewhere far.
He is right here in the green tree
that's growing in front of you.
That is His form.
He exists in the flowing river.
The mantra that he gives us is
the sound of that flowing river.
He exists in the pure,
fresh air that you breathe.
That is how He gives us life.
If we destroy any of these three things
would the human
kind be able to survive?
Will the next generation
be able to take birth?
Protecting them is the
gift that you give me.
The nature is the form that
the five elements.
It is the truest form of the almighty.
This is the truth.
Believe this and
shape your living accordingly.
May everything in the
entire world prosper.
(Chants)
Gajendra.
You've been wanting
to ask me something.
Go ahead and ask me.
Why do they bow to you?
Many practitioners of yogic lifestyle,
accomplished people
and extraordinary men,
walked the path of Dharma
and established this place of worship.
Their respect is not for this body.
They respect that place of worship.
I want that place of worship.
What will you do after you have it?
I am going to use the five
elements that you spoke about.
I will ruin the country that killed me.
You must never challenge the fate,
the one who writes our fate,
and the entire world.
The response they give you is something
you will not be able to handle.
Response?
Tell it to come.
No matter when it comes to me,
or in what form
or even if it comes in front of me
with a lot of strength,
I will take it on.
According to the will of the God.
Sir, you've been blessed with twins.
One of them is alive and
there is no movement in the other one.
What do I do?
(Chants)
Seer, you never set foot
in anyone's house,
you came to our house.
(Chants)
According to the will of the God.
Mr. Ramachandra, this one is nature.
That one is a natural disaster.
Cultivate your relationship with this one.
Cut the cords of this one from you.
You will understand at the right time,
try to understand.
(Chants)
Seer, as a father,
I cannot do anything.
If the mother knows,
she is going to die.
(Chants)
Lord.
Lord, the child you gave
to a gypsy like me,
it hasn't opened his eyes yet.
I don't know about his birth,
the destination he is going to reach.
So, I hand him to You.
I offer him to you Lord Shiva.
Hail Lord Shiva!
you gave me this
(Chants)
Supreme being of disaster.
You have taken a big decision.
And now, he is your responsibility.
Son.
- Father.
When you let go of working for Rajappa
and worked alongside with me,
look at how abundantly
the crop has grown.
I can't believe it.
- Yes, father.
God, shower your benevolence on us.
Break the coconut.
Let's start the harvest.
What's going on?
I heard you quit the job.
I was the one who held him back.
- Why?
That great man gave us farmland
when we didn't have any.
He also gave us seedlings.
We promised him that
we wouldn't get into fights.
Just because he gave you seedlings,
you obeyed him?
What if you don't have those seedlings?
You will be back to being dogs in
front of my house, isn't it so?
Cut everything.
Please don't.
Sir, please don't do it.
Father.
- Sir, please don't ruin it.
I beg you. Please, don't.
Oh no! They are ruining Narsu's crop.
Oh, my God! Oh Lord!
Wait, Nandi!
Keshav,
even though your blood is boiling,
you restrained your anger
because of the promise you made me.
Well done. You'll grow in life.
I am with you.
I'll take on the responsibility
of getting your sister married.
Hey,
you seem to be promising things
without knowing what we are capable of.
Hey,
are you famous to know you?
You are a small little creek.
If you mess with us, we are going to
sever your head off. Understand?
If you mess with us,
I will give you a terrible death.
I won't kill the one who followed me,
but will kill each
and every one of you.
Whoever fights with me,
I'll attack them on their chest.
Bow down to me and
I will spare your life.
What's this route, brother?
- This is a shortcut.
Oh, my God! Looks like
an action movie is going on.
We might get hurt. We need to
get away from here immediately.
Action movie?
Why are they killing each other?
Let's scoot.
What are you looking at? Get him!
What's up!
Are you going to kill me? Go on.
Why should I kill you?
I asked that young man
to work for me.
What's wrong in it?
When you are speaking to another person
learn how to conduct yourself.
There is a difference between asking,
'How is your father?' and
'How is your mother's husband doing?'.
Raja, I already told you to stop
with these factional fights.
Keshav has reformed.
But you haven't.
That is why I needed to
put sense into you.
It's easy to build enemies,
but it's difficult to win people over.
Try it.
I didn't hit you because you wronged,
I hit you to reform you.
A tree is like a vermillion dot
on the forehead.
If you cut it down,
there will be neither shelter nor
food or even existence of mankind.
Try and grow a tree with the very
hands that you used to cut them down.
Be the foundations of the society,
don't destroy it.
What work do you have here?
I am here to meet sir.
- Sir?
Sir, the situation is critical.
Bury her. Clean the room.
When I went to the police station,
I was told sir is at the guesthouse
and asked to come here.
Wow!
What's the matter?
My brother-in-law came home drunk
and beat up my sister, sir.
Why is that?
Because he is unhappy with my sister.
He wants me as well.
He touches me inappropriately, sir.
Is that so?
You?
- Yes.
Damn it!
He has to be fated to get
married to someone like you.
How fair-skinned you are.
You're beautiful.
Do you know something?
If I wasn't married,
I would have married you blindly.
Come on, sir.
My brother-in-law isn't as
nice a person as you are.
I wonder why the goats
always vote for the butcher.
On the way. Hang up the phone.
I am going to meet with
the District Administrative Officer,
when I am back,
we will settle things between us
and then,
deal with your brother-in-law.
You freshen up,
I'll finish the work and be back.
I will wait for you, sir.
Wow.
Good morning, ma'am.
Ms. Padmavati, what brings you here?
- I was recently posted
as Principal Secretary in Environment
and Forest department.
Please come.
I was trained under your mentorship.
I am happy to have the opportunity
of working with you.
It's your first posting,
a tough district,
a tough terrain and tough people.
Be little careful.
Sir, the District Administrative
Officer is asking for you.
Since this is my joining day,
let's just sign and
go to your guesthouse.
I am not that kind of a man, ma'am.
Oh, really? Then, what is this?
Don't believe her, ma'am.
She is a prostitute.
She came to you for help because
the guy she fell in love cheated her
and you raped her.
Ma'am...
You order her to be buried
though she was alive.
You are suspended.
- Ma'am, you don't know about me.
Shut up!
Officer, arrest him.
The evidence is right here.
Okay, ma'am. Let's go.
Let's go, inspector.
There's no need.
I am there for you. Don't be scared.
Good job.
Thank you, ma'am.
Who is the 'Uravakonda'
town concerned CI?
Sir, madam is asking for you.
Yes, ma'am.
- Your mobile number.
9866490050.
I've sent you a photo.
By the time I finish my
meeting with the minister,
I want that man before me.
We'll meet again, ma'am.
Hello, boys and girls.
You all know who we've
been waiting for today.
We request the central minister,
Mr. Bharat Reddy
and the District Administrative Officer,
Ms. Sharanya Bajpayee
who is taking charge today,
to come onto the stage
and say a few words.
I request them to come on the stage.
He won the MP election
from our region and
took on the responsibilities of
a Central Minister, Mr. Bharat Reddy
is with us today.
This generation knows me
as the MP of this region.
But the previous generations
knows me very well.
Once upon a time,
my family was prominent
in the factionalism of this region.
I am the only heir.
I would use my knife to get my way.
But there was a great man
who told me that
if I keep killing people,
I would be left with only graves.
He mustered my courage.
He took away the weapon from my hand,
gave me a pen,
helped me win the MP elections.
He made me rise to the position
of a central minister and
put me in front you.
He replaced the hands
that held dagger with a plough.
He placed books in the hands
of their children.
This is the result of such efforts.
But who did all this? A farmer.
He is the reformer of this region.
Here comes the roaring lion.
Greetings, officer.
You asked me to meet with you,
I will see you after the function.
Sorry, I was delayed
because of a small meeting.
Glory to you!
In any region, a wealthy person
is not the most respected man.
The most respected man is the
one who has good thoughts.
We've elected him
as the MP of our region.
But it was his effort that raised him
to the rank of a central minister.
You must have that sort
of a determination.
Hats off to him!
If children wrong,
the parents are blamed.
If someone does something good,
everyone asks him where he hails from.
That's because,
from our birth to our death,
we might have changed
hundreds of clothes.
But the only thing that doesn't
change is where we were born.
It is our identity.
It is our responsibility to protect it.
It is your responsibility.
I want to give you an example.
It's a story about a state in India.
In a small village in Mahabubnagar,
a girl child was born.
Her parents were farmers
but they couldn't even have
one proper meal a day.
The village did not have
proper bus connectivity either.
Every day, she would ride a bicycle to
her school that was 10 kilometers away.
She would study hard and clear
the Civil Services Examination and
is right now in front of you as the
administrative officer of our district.
You should be inspired by her.
Welcome her with loud applause.
Hats off to you.
Establishing educational institutions
is not that note-worthy a feat.
Children should progress,
that's a big deal.
It's not note-worthy that you take
with you a degree from here
that helps only you.
What's note-worthy is when your talent
is beneficial to the society.
Who is going to stop the cruelty that
woman are subjected to in the society?
You must be the ones to stop it.
Your way of life should be
the one that stops such acts.
Who is going to stop the people
who divide and create chaos
in the name of caste and religion?
You should be the ones to stop them.
Your way of life of life
should stop it.
All of you have
a responsibility for it.
Pure minds create
clean society and great future.
Thank you.
Sir, we've quit the path of violence.
We are going to follow you
until our death.
Come, ma'am.
If you called for him,
he would've come to the office himself.
You coming all the way here...
I misunderstood him.
I can't call him here
just to apologize. Let's go.
Brother, she has come.
Why are you standing here?
Come in.
Place your right feet
first when you come in.
These people take
their customs seriously.
Come, dear.
How are your parents?
- They are well.
I am Ramachandra.
She is my wife, Bharthi.
Come, dear.
Everyone come here.
Sit down, dear.
How is the girl?
- She is beautiful.
We liked her very much.
Mr. Satyamurthy, your daughter...
- Sorry, Mr. Ramachandra.
Girls of this generation
are very spoiled.
After the sun goes down,
wives take their husbands
to pubs and clubs.
My daughter isn't the
right fit for your family.
That is why I didn't send her.
Then who is she?
I am the District Administration Officer.
Forgive us.
His friend's daughter
came down from U.S.
She was supposed to come
to our house to meet Murali Krishna.
If they like each other,
he wanted to get them married.
We thought you were her.
Why did you come by?
I came to meet Mr. Murali Krishna.
I see.
He is outside with farmers.
Come, dear.
Manager.
- Sir.
I put down the surety signature
on farmers loan application form.
Okay, sir.
Give them whatever amount
they ask as loans.
Sure, sir.
I am there for them.
You are our Lord, sir.
I am one of you.
I am a part of your family.
Don't praise me and
distance yourself from me.
Let's go and have our meal together.
I shall call him.
- No, wait.
He is busy. I'll meet him later.
All right.
These documents need your signature.
Yesterday, I went to
Mr. Murali Krishna's house.
Thank you.
Very interesting character.
Not just him.
After meeting his family,
I felt their house to be the cradle
of good customs and traditions.
What's strange is that,
there are a lot more people
flocking around his house than
the District Administrative Office.
- Great.
You've made a lot of
observations in a single visit.
Ma'am, Mr. Murali Krishna
is here to meet you.
Mr. Murali Krishna?
Wait for two minutes and send him in.
- Okay, ma'am.
Greetings, ma'am.
Mr. Murali Krishna, when did you come?
Just two minutes ago.
What was the need to wait?
You could've come in directly.
Hello, ma'am. How are you?
I am well.
- Sit.
What brings you by?
- I am sorry.
I heard that you came
to my home yesterday.
The farmers from the village
dropped in at the same time.
I was occupied and
couldn't meet you.
It's not a problem.
But I met with your family.
I really enjoyed a lot.
What else?
Tomorrow, there is pulse polio
immunization program at our hospital.
If you could come over,
it would be good.
Sure.
- Thank you, ma'am.
It's at 9 o'clock in the morning.
I shall take leave.
- Okay.
Isn't it we who conduct
the pulse polio immunization program?
Why would he do that?
Not just schools and colleges.
He is the one who built
all the hospitals around the area.
Not just that.
The best facilities and
best doctors at free of cost.
All right.
You said you wanted some signatures?
Mine lease extension file.
Copper mine in Nallamala forest?
Isn't this a green zone?
Why would there be mining in it?
Exactly my thoughts.
By the time I came here,
all the permissions were granted
and the Mine began to operate.
I think something is going wrong.
Ms. Padmavati, I want a complete
report on the activities of the Mine.
And, keep it between you and me only.
By the way, the DSP is working
for the Mine owner.
What's the name of the Mine owner?
Varadha Raj. Varadha Mines.
What is it? What's going on?
He vomited blood and passed out.
- He vomited blood?
Oh, no. He's dead.
- Stop the work.
Why did you stop the work
For years,
we've been working in the Mine.
No matter where we worked,
nothing happened to us.
Here, as we go deeper,
the workers are vomiting blood,
itching and have
burning sensation in the eyes.
Father, why get into trouble?
- Shut up.
Until we know what's happening here
we wouldn't step into the Mine.
Anybody there?
Who are you?
My car broke in the forest.
I am hungry.
I see. We don't have bread.
Will you have rice?
I am okay with anything.
- All right.
Son, get the banana leaf.
Come in.
Did you eat?
My husband went to the city.
I'll eat when he returns.
You go ahead.
Wash your hands.
It's raining outside.
I don't like to owe someone
who fed me.
That's not necessary, sir.
- I will give you what I owe.
Why do you care
what happens in the Mine?
Listen to me carefully.
If someone complains of itchy eyes,
tooth ache, vomiting blood
or make excuses to stop the work,
I will call him and
his family to my place
the food of their funeral.
How are you?
- I am fine.
Please come.
- Sure.
The children seem to be disciplined.
"Happy birthday to you."
"Happy birthday to dear ma'am."
Thank you so much. Love you all.
- Happy birthday to you, ma'am.
Touched my heart.
Hello.
- Please.
Take good care of the child.
Thank you, doctor.
Help the doctor.
Happy birthday to you.
- Thank you so much.
You made my day.
Please come.
Are you just going
to give me flowers?
Is there no party?
We'll have lunch at my place today.
I asked for a party,
you invite me for a traditional feast.
What do you want, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Listen, I am not
an administrative officer.
I am just Sharanya and
you are just Murali Krishna.
Today, you must not deny
any of my requests.
Murali Krishna.
- Yes.
Let me tell you something.
I also befriend people I don't like.
My language might seem a little rough
but I am generous.
You're okay with it, right?
By the way, are you interested in me?
- What?
You've made me happy with the
way you introduced me on the stage.
You made me happier today
on my birthday.
Looks like you are trying to woo me.
Am I right?
You're look traditional in sari.
The way you walk is proud.
Your words are sweet.
I like them.
Put on the seat belt.
Life is very precious.
Sorry.
Stop.
What is it?
- Party.
Here?
Come on.
Get on.
Get on?
Perhaps it's not appropriate.
Do you think people would
recognize you here as well? Get on.
Sir! Sir, you are here.
She...
Even though I've got you this far,
you still seem popular.
Of course not. We are his fans,
we will never stop adoring him.
Sir, please let me message my
young friends that you are here.
They have come
with a lot of fun and fare.
Sir has brought his girlfriend.
No.
Brother and sister-in-law
at toddy field.
How is it, sister-in-law?
- Shut up!
Get on the tree. Go on, get it.
Sir.
There are plenty. Get me one.
She seems even more aggressive.
Is it appropriate
to consume alcohol now?
This is not alcohol.
This is medicine.
This is our tradition.
If you consume it,
your body is going to be cleansed
and your mind will cool down.
Didn't you do this in your childhood?
As a child,
he got into driving violence away.
Here, take it.
Hold it.
Sit down.
- Sit down? Where?
Just sit down.
Hold this.
You there, give me the toddy.
Do you have some snacks?
- What do you mean snacks?
I meant snacks.
Oh. You want snacks. Here you are.
Wonderful.
Lick it.
Not like that.
You must lick it like this.
It's wonderful.
How me your tongue.
Wow! How well you lick, sir.
Keep licking.
She is doing a good job.
The discomfort in your throat
will settle down.
Drinking toddy is an art.
I will show it to you.
Watch and learn.
Get up.
Give it to me.
Pour it. Pour it.
Sir.
This is the rare and
best quality uranium.
The capacity of this is
that we can generate power
required for the entire world
for a day with this sample.
But the radiation is very high
and very dangerous, sir.
You are going to be the pioneer
in the market.
No one can dethrone you.
Brother, someone’s come with a deal.
Jagajith Chauhan.
I have businesses all over India
and they are best businesses too.
I have my contacts
in every government.
The top to the bottom.
But, do you know why I am still here?
You have the best Mine in the country.
I want that Mine.
If you've been operating this Mine all these years
without the government's knowledge,
I can gauge your guts.
If you sell it to me,
you will be very happy.
If not, you are going
to be in the headlines.
National headlines.
What is this?
- Answer.
My hair.
You told me what you are.
I am going to show you what I am.
Who do you think is behind him?
A person who is hungry needs food.
A person who believes in God,
chases good karma.
That is the philosophy of this Ashram.
This is the path that
my teacher has shown me.
May you endeavors be successful.
If you tear up, I will wipe your tears.
If you are in difficulties,
I will be the one taking care of you.
If you are in trouble, I will save you.
I am here for you.
I am with you.
I am close to you.
Glory to you!
The sins committed at Brahma's
are destroyed at Vishnu's.
The sins committed at Vishnu's
are destroyed at Shiva's place.
The sins committed at Shiva's
are destroyed at your teachers.
The sins committed
at your teachers are destroyed
when everything turns into nothing.
May it be so!
Baba. Greetings, baba.
What is the reason for your anger?
Your worshiper has been insulted.
When you went and asked for the Mine,
he pulled out his hair and
placed it in your hand.
Is that it?
- Yes.
He threw his hair on my face.
- Is it him?
You are great, baba. It's him.
I want his Mine and I want him dead.
He must die.
How dare you go against Varadha?
I am the spirit.
He is my body.
That Mine is ours.
Good bye.
How are the Mine operations proceeding?
The contamination tanks are full.
Take the bore out and
send it all back into the earth.
A bore?
Reverse boring system.
- But it is dangerous.
Ten years ago,
we did the same thing in Bengal.
People died.
But that didn't affect us.
We did that in Bihar and Assam.
We will do this here as well.
If you don't understand what happened,
half of the people will die.
If they understand what's going on and
start questioning, all of us will die.
Varadha Raj, once upon a time,
this country gave me something.
I am going to return its charity
a hundred-fold. With your support.
Two people can earn a lot of money.
Their customs and traditions
might bring them closer.
But when their aspirations match,
it is indeed very rare.
But I could see that light
in our journey.
Let's walk together.
My parents might ask you to marry me.
Your parents might agree as well.
But your opinion is important for me.
Shall we get married?
"My beloved, I have chosen you."
"My beloved."
"I have started to dream about you."
"I have fallen in love
ever since our eyes met."
"I fell in love with you
at the very first sight."
"I have surrendered myself to you."
"You reside in my heart now."
"My beloved."
"I have chosen you."
"I have started to dream about you."
"You are my first love."
"You are my first acceptance."
"I can't think of anything else
other than you."
"You are my love."
"You brought happiness into my life."
"You are my evening."
"You are my world."
"You are the reason
for my life."
"My love."
"I have chosen you."
"My beloved, I have started
to dream about you."
"You are my world,
you are my happiness."
"You are my existence."
"I are always on my mind."
"I am fortunate to marry you."
"Be my life partner
in all my lifetimes."
"I have surrendered myself to you."
"You reside in my heart now."
"My beloved, I have chosen you."
"My beloved, I have started
to dream about you."
Greetings, baba.
My granddaughter
is now three years old.
I would like your blessings.
Go back.
Lord the destroyer.
What is the meaning of this?
Go! Go, fast!
- Yes, doctor.
Take all of them inside. Be quick.
- Take all of them inside.
Sir, you need to come
to the hospital immediately.
We have many patients.
Please be quick.
Come with me. This way.
- Calamity has befallen.
All right. Hold on.
I am looking into it.
Everything will be all right.
Look what has happened.
Hold it.
- Look what has happened.
Be quick.
Be quick. Take the stretcher.
We have more children.
Sir. What's going on, sir?
How can a just born be in such a state?
What happened, doctor?
- I don't understand, sir.
What?
We're unable to figure out
if this is a virus or poison
or some chemical effect.
Each of these patients
don't have just one organ damage.
They have multiple organ damages.
They are not responding
to any medication.
They are little kids, sir.
They are unable to take it.
What the hell is happening?
Where are you?
I am heading to the airport,
there's meeting in Delhi.
Start immediately and
come to the hospital.
Turn the vehicle around.
All these people belong
to the neighboring villages.
What happened there?
That is a tribal area, sir.
Viral diseases such as these
are pretty common there.
This isn't a viral attack, sir.
These people are tribal,
if don't practice good hygiene,
diseases...
Tribal?
Murali, calm down.
There is a small copper mine
in that area.
Do you think they would
be affected that?
That is not a copper mine, sir.
It is just a copper mine in name.
But Uranium is being
extracted from there.
Uranium?
My God!
Don't make unfounded
allegations, Ms. Padmavati.
It's a complicated matter.
Shut up!
Complicated? For whom?
For you or for Varadha Raj?
This is the report compiled after
procuring data for three years.
When ma'am talked about this,
I had started my investigation.
I took a lot of risk.
With the use of satellite sensors
and fiber optic probes,
we collected samples from the mines.
I knew that they would be
compromised here.
So, I got it tested
in a laboratory in Mumbai.
Do you know what they found out, sir?
Copper exists only up to
the depth of fifty feet.
Below that, all of it is Uranium, sir.
They extract it there, purify it there
and dug holes into the ground
and used reverse boring to send
it back into the earth, sir.
This horror is a result
of such activities.
These are just early effects, sir.
If something is not done quickly,
our region and our country
would turn into graveyard.
Mark my words.
Doctor,
arrange for medicines and
equipments required to save them.
Where is that Mine?
This is my empire.
I am going to turn it into ruins.
I am the other name for death.
- I am your death.
I am destruction.
- I am catastrophe.
You can't touch me.
- I will destroy you.
I am an animal.
- I am the lion that hunts that animal.
Come at me!
You meddled with the soil.
You killed the animals
that provide us with milk.
You meddled with
the life-giving waters.
You killed innocent people.
I will kill you.
Calm down.
Respect.
Respect?
Respect comes from behavior;
not by begging.
You have locked horns
with Anthapur Varadha Raj.
If you were born in Anthapur,
I was born in Anantapur.
If I decide what is wrong and right,
I never spare the one
who crosses my way.
I send the funeral food
of my enemy to his house.
With his head.
You will behead me?
Once I decide to step into the fray,
I am like a bulldozer without brakes.
I will crush you.
Whether left or right, top or bottom,
no matter from where
anyone searches you,
not an inch of your body
will ever be found again.
Come at me!
Mr. Murali, please.
Where would he and this mine go?
We will shut it down in an hour.
The situation at the hospital
is taking a downturn. Please.
If even a single life is lost there,
you will no longer be alive.
Listen to me.
The minister is with him.
The Administrative officer
has collected proof against us.
This isn't the right time.
Listen to me. Calm down.
Sir, he is someone
who does simple quarry mining
is using such a high-end equipment,
that means
that there is a bigger force at play.
Please give me some time, sir.
I'll bring all the information to light.
You must.
If not, a lot of future generations
will be lost.
As long as you are here,
I am not scared, sir.
Don't be scared.
I will make sure
not a single life is lost.
And also make sure that the Mine
doesn't operate anymore.
Murali!
Father, what happened to her?
She passed out while she was playing.
She hasn't opened her eyes until now.
Doctor!
Bharat.
'As long as you are here,
I am not scared, sir.'
Not a single person was left alive.
Not a single one.
Varadha, did the blood flow like flood?
The dead bodies and
morsels of meat scattered?
There was a loss in sense of direction
with the drums of death beating hard.
How do you know about it?
Do you think the one who created
it wouldn't know about it?
What do we do now?
We need someone to pin this sin on.
Leave it to me.
Krishnamacharya Perumal,
NIA, New Delhi.
The one who died
was a central minister.
The bomb blast occurred
at your hospital.
You are under arrest.
On what charges?
You, being the wife of an accused,
you have no rights to question.
And you are also under suspension.
To find out the truth,
you need to come with me. Shall we go?
You are going to arrest him?
Let's see you do it.
There are already a lot of lives lost.
Do we need one more?
Until yesterday, whatever happened
in the Mine was a secret.
Now, it's out in the open.
All those who let the secret out
and those who've supported it
and the villages that stand as evidence
should no longer exist.
Before the victims come towards us,
finish them all.
You killed the children and the elders.
What more can you do?
Kill us!
Highly advanced plastic explosives.
It's a small rural area.
This is the first time in the state.
I'm surprised.
The minister came
because you phoned him.
As per phone records.
He came to your hospital.
There is technical evidence.
Surprisingly, until then
you were with him.
But, at the time of the blast,
you moved to a safe zone.
How come?
Mr. Murali, I need to know
why you killed
the minister and
so many innocent people.
Silence will not change the truth.
If you don't say anything, believe me
all your routes and gates
will be closed forever.
No one can save you.
Ma'am, the condition is serious.
The child has been in an unconscious
state for a long time.
If she doesn't regain consciousness,
it is going to be dangerous.
We have to immediately
shift her to Delhi.
How can we go, doctor?
Look at how the police have
surrounded the entire house.
Mr. Ramachandra,
if Mr. Murali was here,
he'd risk his life to save the child.
We can't do the same for his kid?
Let's go.
Let's see who is going to stop us.
No matter what happens,
don't get down from the vehicle.
The Mr. Murali's wife is in the car.
Save her.
Go.
Move fast.
Don't be scared.
Nothing is going to happen to you.
I'll take care of it.
Hold the steering wheel.
Ma'am, the child...
Ma'am!
Janvi...
My child.
Sorry. I am sorry.
Janvi.
My child.
She is here somewhere.
Let's find her.
My child!
Lord!
(Chants)
Where else can she go?
Kill her and her daughter.
May you live long!
(Chants)
Who are you?
The one with sun,
moon and fire in his eyes.
The rider of the white bull, Nandi.
The one who wears a snake
around his neck.
The savior who protects by
destroying the Tripura demon.
I am Lord Shiva!
Who are you?
This body is eternal and abundant.
My form is never
ending and imperishable.
I am Shiva.
The sound of the conch that I
heard isn't an ordinary one.
The power that shook me up and
my throne is no ordinary thing.
The one that I saw
is no ordinary being.
Who is it?
'You must never challenge your fate,
the creator and the entire world.'
'The response they give you is
something you cannot handle.'
Tatva.
The throne has been contaminated.
Shift the base to Ananthapur.
Who is he?
(Chants)
He is alive.
What happened? Who did all this?
Answer me.
You want to know what happened.
The divine dance.
The divine dance of lord Shiva.
The one who killed them
is not an ordinary being.
It's Lord Shiva.
He didn't send you dead bodies.
He sent you a sign that he has come.
You have come to his notice,
he is destroyer of sins and
an ardent devotee of Lord Shiva.
If you play with the life of a child,
will the divine one spare you?
The third eye has been opened.
You will surely die.
Baba has moved Ananthapur.
Join him, I'll be there too.
I am saying this as
your younger brother.
Have faith in me.
Go on.
You defeated everything that
came in your way, but you lost today.
He is a definitely a powerful man.
I will find out who defeated you.
Until then,
keep the fire in your heart burning.
I will tell you who you
should burn in that fire.
The devotees are waiting.
Go perform your brother's last rites.
Who are you?
Adoration to Lord Shiva.
May you live long.
"Lord Shiva is present
in every particle of earth."
"Lord Shiva is present in the wind."
"Lord Shiva is responsible
for the burning fire."
"Lord Shiva is present
in every drop of water."
"Lord Shiva lives even in the sky."
"Lord Shiva present
even in the five elements."
"Lord Shiva is present
in the five syllables."
"Lord Shiva, protect everyone."
"Lord Shiva is the removal of obstacles,
an ascetic."
"Hail Lord Shiva,
You are furious."
"You are the Lord of the world."
"Lord Shiva, You are the Lord
of the universe."
"Ease our problems."
"The protector of the world."
"You are omniscient and great."
You had been to the hospital.
How come you came back immediately?
What happened, dear?
What happened?
What are these injuries?
How did you suffer injuries?
Then who saved you?
Baba.
Forty people died because of you.
We need to investigate,
come to the police station.
Her husband killed hundreds
of people using bombs
just to cover up the crime
that he committed.
He killed forty people
because they attacked you.
You look beautiful
even after getting married.
Mind your tongue.
I will say what I want to say.
If anyone intervenes,
I am going to cut his tongue.
You old hog.
- Sir, this is wrong.
They are a very reputable family.
She is an ex-collector.
Why are you physically assaulting them?
Your behavior is not correct, sir.
Is it?
Then, what's right?
Tell me.
Do you want me to worship them?
You want me to serve them biryani?
How will we know the truth?
How can we find out the truth?
The sage said that if you abuse a child,
God won't spare you.
Then, I won't abuse the child,
let's just kill her.
No!
What are you doing?
(Chants)
Is it this fellow? Is it him?
It's me.
(Chants)
The one who saved them...
- It's me.
The one the sage was talking about...
The one who killed so many people...
- It's me.
It's me.
(Chants)
Kill him!
I don't know if one can meet God
after performing a severe penance.
But when the lives of children
are in danger,
when innocent people are troubled,
Lord will definitely come there.
Baba.
All the sins that you've listed
out have happened right here.
Sit down.
All this happened right
in front of my eyes.
But God didn't appear.
How will He come?
As long as you resist,
God will never appear.
When you let go of your
ego, strength and pride,
and succumb to the mightiness
of the God,
and scream until your throat turns raw,
that God is your only rescue,
that is when God will appear to you.
God!
Save me, baba.
As a God, I command you. Let him go!
(Chants)
If you say a word,
it becomes a sound.
But if I say a word,
it becomes a command.
A divine command.
Baba, you are right. God is here.
Praise be with you!
May the entire population
of the world prosper.
Other than him.
(Chants)
Hey!
Praise be with Lord Shiva!
You are a pig that changed its
colors in front of a raging bull.
If you speak nonsense,
I will behead you.
(Chants)
There is another cruel man
named Varadha Raj.
When his name burns,
his life will burn too.
He is your son.
That day, it was decided
by Lord Shiva
that I must separate
your child from you.
Now, he returns to you
at the behest of your grandchild.
This is Lord Shiva's will.
What? Did God order you
to separate a child from his mother?
When you know everything,
is separating me from
my child justified?
Your son was born for a purpose.
He is the part of the creator
of the world, Brahma.
He was born from your womb.
As soon as he was born,
Lord Shiva severed your relationships
and called him towards Him.
What is the reason?
There is a brute that killed a great man
and committed the first wrongdoing
by questioning Tripurari.
He's played with the nature and
committed the second grave mistake.
He killed innocent children, people and
committed an unforgivable
third mistake.
That is why Lord Shiva blew the
divine conch and began the war.
No matter the reason for his birth,
I am the mother who gave him birth.
I want my son. That's my right.
I will ask him.
It's God's will.
Baba.
I am your mother.
You are my son, I birthed you
and I didn't know that.
Lord Shiva asked for you
and you were given away.
How unjust!
When a mother knows that
her child is in front of her,
how can she stop herself?
Look at me.
Turn around and
take a look at your mother.
You are my blood. You are my child.
SANSKRIT
In this lifetime,
Lord Shiva is my father.
That divine mother
is my only mother.
This breath, this voice and this body...
I am His slave.
This life is dedicated to Lord Shiva.
My next life will be
the command of Lord Shiva.
I would only get
to hear your words.
Now, I see that you've come here.
What is the matter?
(Chants)
Akhanda!
Do you know him?
He is Akhanda Rudhra Sikander Ghora.
He killed my teacher and
my followers ruthlessly.
He isn't an ordinary man.
He is a great transcendental being
who has kept the seven chakras
of the body in great control.
Even the five elements of nature
are under his control.
They are scared to touch him.
They bow to him.
Even the cold that
can harden the blood and
also the fire that melts the blood
can never touch him.
Time is their slave.
All the mantras are
merely their directions.
For the sake of the blessing that says
'May all the beings
in the world prosper'.
They can do anything.
and if need be,
they would even fight a war.
Prachanda, you know why I've
come to you and you tell me this?
I will kill him.
What are you scared of in this world?
- Death.
Death fears him.
When I call only ghosts answer my call.
When he calls,
the Lord of ghosts answers his call.
But why did we cross paths?
He was born for you.
He took up weapon for you.
This is the game Lord Shiva played
while taking the shape of a small child.
I am indebted to you.
I will leave only after
I solve your crisis.
Believe me.
It's your turn.
- Come on.
What's wrong.
- Darn it.
What you are doing
in the temple is wrong.
It's God's fault not ours.
He didn't give us job,
doesn't matter where He is.
You have to find a job yourself.
God failed to give us a job.
That's true.
We don't need a barren land and God.
Do you want them?
No.
All of you will be punished.
Punished? Who is going to do that?
Aghori!
We need one more person,
come and join us for a game.
I don't know this game.
- Then, what do you know?
I know tiger hunt.
- What did you say?
The tiger and the goat game.
In this game, who is the tiger
and who is the goat?
The ones in a group are the goats.
The one who is alone is the tiger.
Looks like the tiger is here.
Looks like it's going to pounce on us.
Fine, we are goats and you are a tiger.
Now, show us your game.
May your heart's desire come to fruition.
I don't know this game.
Who is that?
- What happened?
He is beating us.
Who are you?
Gora!
I am Akhanda Rudra Sikander Gora.
Destination is Kailash mountains.
I enjoy skulls.
My weapon is Trishul.
My duty is to destroy evil.
I am a soldier.
I am Lord Shiva's soldier.
So? Why would you hit us?
I didn't hit them
because they were gambling,
I hit them
because they removed the God's idol.
You should've knocked sense into them.
Why did you beat them?
Are they kids that
they need to be educated
with offerings of chocolates?
If you mess with divinity,
I will break your jaw.
You keep threatening us
with the trident.
Are you going to kill us?
Why would I need to use the trident
to kill an idiot like you
An idiot?
This is our village, our temple,
it's our wish.
We will do what we please with it.
Did you build this temple?
- No.
Then, how can you destroy the temple?
Do you know how much effort goes
into the establishment of a temple?
Do you know how much
energy comes out of it?
Be it be chanting, prayers,
the divine texts,
the Vedas, Dharmas, the treatises
on beginnings and decorations,
the rules that dictate the worship...
All these are joined together
and the structure is built.
That is when it becomes a temple.
Do you know the value and the glory of
the idol that sits at the temple's core?
To erase the pain of the people
and make them happy,
it is the God Vishnu Himself.
Goddess Sita preaches
the tenets of Dharma.
Lord Krishna comes
to preach life truths.
Lord Shiva comes to preach
the tenets of the soul.
Lord Anjeneya comes to give courage.
Lord Ganesha for auspicious beginnings.
Goddess Lakshmi
for wealth and prosperity.
Goddess Saraswati for knowledge.
The mother Goddess comes forth to give
the power of all the Gods in the universe.
The idol of Gods have been installed
in the temple for your protection.
How dare you disrespect them?
Stop it. You are right.
But, the science has developed so much.
Why are you giving a lot of
importance to an invisible God?
When you fall ill, where would you go?
To the hospital.
Why is there a temple in the hospital?
The doctors pray to the God
by asking for His guidance
while operating
to save a person's life.
Why is it?
So that they are successful in treating
the patient by the grace of God.
And the scientists who you hail,
the very ones who launch rockets
from Sri Hari Kota,
ask for His benevolence and guidance.
Why is it?
It is because God would help them
fulfill their mission.
God is the father of all creations.
Nature is the mother.
And science is their child.
This is truth. Learn it.
Ask for God's mercy,
don't challenge Him.
Please, ma'am. Please.
Sir, please.
No, it's not possible.
Please come, ma'am.
Please, ma'am.
Sir...
We know.
Wait.
Get in.
If there is a blast in the hospital,
it should lead to the death
of all the people of all areas.
But people from only one area died.
- Yes.
I had asked you for the enquiry report.
Where is it?
It is ready..
- Good.
The people who were admitted
in his hospital
were affected by the radiations.
The reason for it is Varadha Mines.
But that is not correct, sir.
I personally visited the site
and investigated it.
There are just copper mines there.
There is no possibility
of any presence of radiation.
Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
Hello?
Yes.
Is that so?
Remove the cameras.
I am not clear on whether you
are a farmer or a criminal.
Just now, I was offered
100 crores to kill you.
That is a big amount.
It's double my weight.
Anyone else could have gotten
the exact same call.
They say that society is
protected by God and gun.
God might not be tempted
upon listening to this offer.
But anyone with a gun
would be tempted.
I came here to close the case.
Don't take this so far that
it would end with you being killed.
What exactly happened?
Same bloody old silence!
They won't tell me why
you should be killed.
And you don't tell me
who killed them.
Who will tell the truth?
Who is going to tell the truth?
(Chants)
Hail Lord Shiva!
Sir, the operations in Varadha Mines
is not regarding copper mining.
It is regarding dangerous
uranium extraction.
I have all the necessary
proofs regarding this.
Mr. Murali Krishna
might bring this truth to life
and that is why
they are trying to kill him.
Sir, I will be there
with the files in an hour.
I need to meet with
Mr. Krishnaacharya.
They say wars took place
because of woman.
You opened your mouth
and many children died.
And he is in custody.
Thousands of people
are buried in the earth.
Someone disturbed me
by killing my brother.
I want to kill him
but you are intervening.
Hey...
- Mother!
No!
Get up. Stop me. Come.
- Don't beat him.
Let go of him.
- Mother!
Please don't beat him.
Let go of him.
I beg to you. Let go of him.
I am your enemy,
Let go of my son.
Please don't beat him.
Let go of him. I beg to you.
Bring her son here.
Look.
- Mother!
No!
You can't lock horns with me
because you have the support
of the government and the people.
Go and do what you want.
Take the kid away.
Come on.
Hail the supreme God.
You know where he was born
and what brought him here.
You also want to know
how he is going die.
That is why I brought you here.
If a deer is attacked by 25 cheetahs,
they would pounce on it, all at once.
When they keep tearing the bone
and flesh off the body of the deer,
what will happen
to the life of that deer?
What will happen if there is
a lion in place of that deer?
Up until then, that vengeful lion
kept a lid on the emotions of anger
pain, revenge, lust, arrogance.
Once it opens its eyes and
throws its fiery gaze around.
(Chants)
Imagine if Lord Shiva
turned himself into a bow,
with Lord Vishnu as the string and
wore Sri Hari as his armor
and begins the war.
How would that look?
I am Varadha Raj.
You fool. He is Lord Shiva.
He is going to die.
He will come.
Call him.
- He is here.
(Chants)
Akhanda.
Mother!
Don't cry, mother.
Get up. Don't cry.
Mother, look at me.
He showed you my death.
God is going to show you his death.
Look there!
(Chants)
I have a Mine.
I am arrogant.
People have faith in me.
I have a teacher,
I can do anything I want.
If you mess with mother earth
and woman,
your root chakra will be destroyed.
Your sacral chakra will be destroyed.
(Chants)
Your solar plexus chakra
will be destroyed.
(Chants)
Your Heart chakra
will be destroyed.
Your throat chakra will be destroyed.
(Chants)
Your third eye chakra
will be destroyed.
(Chants)
Your crown chakra will be destroyed.
Hail Lord Shiva!
Offering it all to Lord Shiva.
(Chants)
A lot of you people have died.
Do you want to lose more?
Gun down. Gun down.
What is the meaning
of this veneration of death?
This isn't about killing people.
I cleaned up pollution.
Polluting has become
a passion for every loon.
That is why I had to clean it.
Dust cleaning.
In another word pest cleaning.
Killing of the germs.
Why are you walking away?
He was indeed a criminal.
You must hand him over to us.
How could you kill him?
What are you going to do
if I hand him over?
I would've put him in prison.
You would just put him in prison.
I put him into hell.
The one who pollutes the earth and
troubles women has no right to live.
We will not spare him.
We will kill him.
We will chase him and kill him.
If a child misbehaves,
the mother beats it.
Do you think mother earth
would stay quiet?
She asked me to kill him
and that is what I did.
Order, sir.
In one shot, I'll finish him.
Hey, no. Wait.
What are you doing?
- Tamed dog.
You are dog
that's been domesticated.
You can only bark,
you must not growl.
You have a young daughter and
she needs to complete her education.
That is why I'm sparing your life.
Go away.
As an ascetic,
the Hindu religion says
that non-violence
is the highest moral virtue.
Correct yourself.
That is just half the sacred
verse used to control aggression.
Do you know
what Haindava Dharma says?
SANSKRIT
Do you know what it means?
Non-violence is the highest
moral duty of mankind.
So too is violence in the
service of the highest Dharma.
That is exactly what happened.
From now on,
if a man crosses his limits,
this is exactly what's
going to happen to him.
Sir, no matter what you say,
according to law, anyone who takes away
another person's life is a criminal.
that doesn't apply to me.
Doesn't apply to you?
Are you not a human being like us?
Never!
Your world and
my world are not the same, officer.
You've studied the justice system.
I believe in Dharma.
Both are not same.
You keep searching for God.
I live together with God.
Both are not same.
Your family is your world.
For me, the entire world is my family.
Both are not same.
You search for life.
I search for death.
Both are not same.
You people cannot hold a piece of ice
on the palm even for 30 seconds.
We are people who brave the cold and
live in those eternally cold mountains.
Both are not same.
If you face a problem,
you beg for God's graces.
We put an end to that problem itself.
Just like this.
Both are not same.
You chant mantras for the life of man.
And if that very life is in danger,
we fight wars.
A very horrible war.
"Hail Lord Shiva! Show Your powers.
Erase everyone's problems."
"Lord Shiva, kill the evil."
"You win the battle
and do Your duty."
"You are Lord Shiva,
You have mercy on us."
"O Lord, the religion is in trouble."
"O hairy one, You ease the problem
and follow the tradition."
"You are immortal."
"You save Your devotee
and punish the sinner."
"You are immortal."
"You erase the evil from Earth."
"You kill the demons."
"There's army of demons,
kill them with Your trident."
"Be victorious."
"Don't spare anyone.
Kill them with your trident."
"You are immortal."
"You save Your devotee
and punish the sinner."
"You are immortal."
"You erase the evil from Earth."
Baba.
The child.
(Chants)
Call for the expert of mantra and
tantra, Kedari Agori Baba, from Kashi.
Some evil spell has been cast on her.
Baba!
While I was searching for his strength,
I found out about his weakness.
I made a move that's going
to result in his death.
Until now, weren't we
at the receiving end?
Now, when we hit back, he must die.
Deploy.
No matter in which corner your
strengths lie, deploy them.
This is the final opportunity.
Deploy your strengths.
You've invested yourself
in this relationship.
They've invested in your weakness.
Don't you know that our journey
is antithetical to relationships?
My destination is Lord Shiva.
What if the mission that
you wanted to give life to,
asks for your life in return
as a sacrifice?
Let's do it.
Get everything ready
for the fire sacrifice ritual.
Akhanda.
The most powerful force
that can change the impossible
into possible in this world,
that can command the coming
together of nine planets
and command the constellation of stars
lies in this fire ritual.
I have made this weapon to
save lives.
This is a very powerful veneration.
It can change the destiny
written by Lord Brahma.
This is the only way to save lives
from the Lord.
But the end result
is that Supreme Lord's.
(Chants)
Akhanda.
you need to chant the mantra
until the ritual is over.
You are the protector of this ritual.
Yours is the will,
the accomplishment is Lord Shiva's.
Begin!
(Chants)
Gaja,
he is right now locked as a prisoner
to the Shiva Panchakshari mantra.
Until that child's life returns,
he can't stop chanting
nor can he turn his head.
Even if Lord Shiva calls him,
he will not get up.
Why are you hitting him here and there?
Hit him on the head.
Brugu...
Gaja, he is at the last stage
of chanting of the mantra.
You must distract his focus from God.
Go!
Akhanda.
The ritual is over.
The child is awake.
(Chants)
Everything is over.
He is not human now.
It's Lord Shiva.
We need to stop him.
Surround him.
(Chants)
He carries river Ganga on his head,
fire on his forehead,
poison in his throat.
The nature carries
the entire world in its womb
and you mess with it?
Will you kill the child
who is the form of God?
You dare touch the third eye?!
(Chants)
Father.
Son, let bygones be bygones.
Please stay with us now.
(Chants)
Sir, please. Please listen to me.
Baba.
Baba, where are you going?
When will you come back?
Everyone is sad that you are leaving.
Aren't you sad?
I don't desire anything.
What about me then?
The very moment I was born,
Lord Shiva cut off all my ties
to relationships and affection,
friendship and enmity.
Did he break your relationship
with me as well?
Mother said that
your soul lies in me.
If you leave,
it will leave with you too.
You shouldn't say that.
Don't leave me and go.
Don't go.
I want you.
If you go away, what will I do?
Don't go.
I am giving you my promise.
If you are in difficulties
or destruction,
in fear or in pain,
or if you face death,
no matter where I am or
in what condition I am,
I will be there before you.
This is my promise.
(Chants)
Baba.