Hello, my name is Anpu and welcome to my YouTube channel and today
I wanted to you know introduce the Indian accent to you, and I am very well aware that there is a
big variety of
Indian accents, and not just Indian there is a Sri Lankan, Pakistani, and you know all over a South asia,
there is different accent, but I want to to introduce to you the South Indian accent. You know
I am very interested in accents
And I you know if you ever interested in learning the Indian accent and perhaps you have a you know at acting role
Where you have to learn Indian accent this video will cover the basics of the Indian accent
So without further ado let's get straight into this video
Let's just address the elephant in the room
You were clearly judging me on my Indian accent weren't you?
You know I'm also passionate about like you know identity and racism, but that is not the topic of today's discussion
Today's discussion is about the Indian accent and if you follow as few simple steps and a few simple rules
You'll be able to master the Indian accent. You know really easily
Let's start off with the t sound so the t sounds something like this
[tur]
[tur] not [t]... [tur] ... so your tongue is actually further back in your mouth
so for example if you want to say the word 'but', in the Indian accent it's 'but'
'But'...okay, so not 'but'... 'but'... so let's try
dot
It's not dot it's not
Okay, so I'm really exaggerating the t here
so try and practice that sound yeah, and
Then [tone] it down a little bit so dot yeah it
It it
It so in the sentence don't try it becomes don't try it
don't
Try it
so once you've practiced that the next sound practice is the L sound so
Let's take the word table for example
When we say the word table, we don't actually pronounce the L in table
You've got the t sound which we talked about earlier and this L sound so practice to start not teh
t and
Then it becomes
Peru
not table table
So can you put the you know groceries on the table?
please the next sound is the w sound so British people will pronounce w as work and
so the word water
turns into vodka
Okay, so the w turns into a V and
Then the t in water is the sound that we practiced earlier
and
Then the R is what the last sound is what we're going to practice. So art isn't rough. It's rough
so var Dad
Var det another one could be pizza beep done
Peter I
spoke to be Dead on the Phone I
Spoke to Peter on the phone
Alright, so I'm sure you can hear that difference there
and I've tried to break down the particular sounds that sound different, so go away and practice that and
You know I might do a part two
So hit like on this video if you found that video useful and you know this this video is not intended to make fun out
[of] any accent, you know
It's purely educational
and
You know this video is all [about] if you are wondering one Indian accent sounds like and how exactly to do one I hope this
video helped Subscribe to my channel to stay in touch with
my latest videos I make videos on any life London life and
Traveling as well. I hope you have a fantastic Christmas, and I'll see you in the next video. See you later
[I] even see you in the next video and
Take care of yourself. Bye
allow it
Allow it man, [it's] please don't laugh into in it leave him alone you white white. Why are you messing them around for love it?
Stop it. That's a bait
Okay