Gentlemen, look at this.
This is not doll,
this is beauty of Kashmir.
Look carefully.
And impose right price so that
she don't feel bad.
Say sir.
- Rs 5.
Rs 5 for this sir.
Say, Rs 5 for this sir.
- Rs 7.
Rs 7 for madam.
Say sir, Rs 7 for madam.
Rs 10.
Rs 10 for sir.
Say madam, Rs 10 for sir.
Rs 20.
Madam's Rs 20.
Say, sir. Madam's Rs 20.
Say gentlemen.
- Rs 30.
Sir's Rs 30.
Say madam. Sir's Rs 30.
Say madam. Rs 50.
Madam's Rs 50.
Say sir. Madam's Rs 50.
Rs 70.
- Sir's Rs 70.
Say madam. Rs 70, one, two...
Rs 80.
Madam's Rs 80.
It's good that due to...
their stubbornness some poor
person is getting good.
Madam's Rs 80. Rs 80, one, two...
Rs 100. Sir's Rs 100.
Sir's Rs 100.
- Come on, why are you insisting?
Say madam. Sir's Rs 100.
Rs 100, one.
Rs 100, two. Rs 100, three.
Take it, I was...
I was just kidding.
Shame on you.
Idiot, he is always after me.
And keeps staring at me.
I just go to his friend,
Rajan and complain.
Oh God!
Look, Mr Rajan.
Your friend misbehave with me.
Either you make him
understand or I will...
How beautiful this place is!
But not more than you.
Looks like you are here for
the first time.
My name is Rajan. What's your name?
Why shall I tell you? Nothing.
Shut up.
I was feeling like slapping him.
Stupid! What does
he think of himself?
But the boy is handsome.
I consider even talking to
such people as an insult.
What is this?
Dance.
- Dance?
This is called dance.
With whom will you dance there?
With a girl.
A big twist is going
to come in my life.
Have you ever danced in your life?
So what? But today
I'll beat everyone in dance.
Twist, twist.
Come on, dance there.
Bansi, Asha.
Rajan, Jyoti.
Look Madhu, those boys are dancing
so well. Aren't they?
I'll be back. I also go.
Tomorrow we will go to Char Chinar.
I heard it's a very nice place.
Yes, of course.
Excuse me.
What?
I mean excuse me.
Let's go on the field.
What do you mean?
I mean together...
let's go dance.
I am prepared to dance today.
No one can beat me in dance today.
Bansi.
Yes dear.
Today I am also
in very terrific form.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Don't you feel ashamed?
Where is the manager?
Bansi, let's go from here.
Please, forgive this idiot.
One, two, three, four...
Who are you?
Actually, I am looking for two girls
who lives in another room.
Get out.
- Actually madam...
that if... - What are you doing?
Get out. - Sir, listen to me.
Get out.
- Listen to me, sir.
Room no. 10.
God, I hope that girl is inside.
What happened?
Did you check the room?
Yes, a zero and a one.
I mean room no. 10.
Room no, 10...
You go inside.
I'll guard.
Go inside.
"I came for you, leaving the world."
You.
- Oh, God!
Who are you?
Who gave you permission
to come here?
Oh, God!
Bansi.
Where are you going?
Wait.
Stop there.
Oh, God!
Have you seen the condition
of my face because of you?
Because of me?
I got insulted because of you.
My eyes can never be deceived.
Oh, shut up.
First you slapped cake
on our face...
and now you are knocking the door.
The keys are with me. Stay inside.
Let's go and ask at the counter.
Look at us.
Sir, does Asha live in room no. 10?
393.
- What do you mean?
She left this hotel
this morning itself.
What happened to you?
Mind your own business.
I told you that
she lives in room no. 10.
No, it's not possible.
She might be staying
in some other hotel.
Let's do one thing. Change our
clothes and search for them.
No, you go alone...
and I am going to Jyoti.
Char Chinar.
Bansi.
I made a fool of Bansi.
He must have gone to Char
Chinar looking for us.
What are you doing?
- I did not do anything.
Oh, it's you.
Hey! Earthquake in Kashmir?
Now say, who made fool to whom?
You. How many have
I told you to not follow me.
Who came after you?
I am standing in front of you.
Really?
Oh, God!
You are such a nice guy.
Why do you trouble me?
I am innocent.
And handsome too.
No, I am not handsome.
Oh God! Oh, my waist!
My waist! Where is my room?
My room.
Oh!
Hey! take us to Char Chinar.
Oh dear!
Sail the boat little faster.
Hello.
You liar.
I say stop the boat.
I say, stop the boat.
What do you think of yourself?
Great.
Madam, I took you here safely.
"Everyone has seen moon, what would
I give to it. I saw you."
"I saw you, I saw everything."
"Everyone has seen moon."
"There is anger in the eyes."
"But the heart agrees in the heart."
"Now whatever the world thinks."
"Now whatever the world thinks,
why should I know. I know you..."
"I know everything.
I know you, I know everything."
"Everyone has seen moon."
"My heart adores your lips."
"If there is someone as
beautiful as you..."
"why should I adore her,
I adore you."
"I adore you, I adore everything."
"Everyone has seen moon."
"My heart called you..."
"Now what's there with God?"
"What should I ask for? I asked
for you, I asked for everything."
"Everyone has seen moon."
"Everyone has seen moon, why should
I look at it. I saw you..."
"I saw everything.
I saw you, I saw everything."
"Everyone has seen moon."
What is this?
I am shivering with cold.
That's why I am giving
a little heat.
And what's that?
This...
I am knitting sweater.
For whom?
For my wife.
Like the Gorkha people.
But how do you know
that it'll fit her?
I am making 36 size.
It is a common size.
Whichever girl will fit this
sweater, I will marry her...
and make her grandmother
to my grandchildren.
Really?
You forgot about Jyoti?
Hands up.
Jyoti hit me on my waist so hard...
that my waist is paining.
And I came into the room.
Listen to me.
You also give up.
Asha will not accept you.
Where are you going in
this cold weather?
Take this blanket.
Asha's stubbornness
and indifference won my heart.
Today she have to believe
in my love.
Where are you going?
Listen.
You are here again?
Look, how beautiful the weather is!
The other side of lake...
that mountains covered with snow...
sound of two lovers singing...
a poet was right...
this air, this ocean, this moon,
I wish to spend my life here.
You realize
the beautiful sight of nature...
it's strange.
Why?
Am I not a human?
You are human
but do not have humanity.
I want to say something.
Please, why are you bothering me?
For God sake, leave me alone.
I hate you.
Your indifference can kill someone.
Maybe you never thought about it.
I don't want to listen anything.
If this is your wish then I swear...
I'll change this hatred into love.
Today you are rejecting
my feelings...
keep in my mind...
one day the same feeling
will not let you sleep.
What was he saying?
Don't talk about him.
Looks like, he intend to sit
downstairs all night.
Go and tell him, he'll get sick in
this cold weather.
I don't care.
Asha, it's not good to hurt anyone.
Lest it happen that you start
loving him. - Please, Madhu.
What are you watching?
Nothing.
I know, you are saddened
by not seeing Rajan.
Sad that too for Rajan?
Yes.
Because your pride is hurt.
You must have thought that
he is still here.
Yes.
Madam, your letter.
Whose letter is this?
Prakash has send the letter...
Dad is not well.
We have to leave today.
Dad.
Asha, my dear.
Hello, uncle.
- Hello. - How are you?
My health deteriorated suddenly.
But how could
I die without seeing my daughter?
Dad, what are you saying?
Don't worry, dear. Until you
get married, I'll not die.
This is my wish.
Dad, where is Prakash? He didn't
even come to the airport.
Oh, may be he must have gone on
a visit somewhere.
Dear, Prakash served me very well.
He is very close to me.
He has everything...
but no parents.
You are there.
Yes, dear. My friend's only son...
he was 10 year old
at the time of his father's death.
Asha, what are you thinking?
Nothing, dad.
Looks like you must
be missing Kashmir.
Madhu, how was Kashmir?
It was great, uncle.
And you?
It was nice.
Okay, Asha, I am leaving.
Mom must be waiting.
Okay, dear. Asha, go with Madhu.
And take rest.
Bye, uncle.
God bless, dear.
Okay, Asha,
say my hello to aunt. - Okay.
And don't forget to come tomorrow.
Okay, I'll come.
Good night.
Asha.
Hello, Prakash.
Asha, I have decided to quit my
profession of doctor. - Why?
What? Is this what you call life?
I was just coming to receive you
when a patient arrived.
Nice excuse.
I don't make excuses
and that too from you.
Excuses are made from strangers.
What have you brought from Kashmir?
Memories.
Memories of beautiful scenery.
Your face looks like you
have lost something.
To gain beautiful memories,
you have to lose something.
What did you do in that time?
I didn't feel good after you left.
I was feeling lonely.
Why did this happened?
I think you need a partner.
A life partner.
I will get my life partner.
I am living in that hope. When
I get it, you will definitely know.
May God bless you.
I'll be happy for you.
'Your indifference can also
take someone's life.'
'You might never agree.'
'If this is your decision,
then today I also swear...'
'I'll change your hatred into love.'
'Today you rejected my love...'
'keep in mind, one day this feeling
will not let you sleep.'
What are you thinking?
I know, what are you thinking about.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know, Madhu.
Madhu, I used to hate Rajan.
But now, I keep
on thinking about him.
He was so passionate about me.
But I hurt him.
I don't know, where and how he is?
Can I not meet him again?
You have to move on.
This is better for you.
Happy birthday.
- Thank you. Come in.
Happy birthday, Rajan.
Thank you, Dr Sharma.
Hello.
May god bless you with 1000 lives.
Where is my gift?
Here it is?
- What's this?
See it yourself.
What is this?
Stethoscope.
I thought, it would
be useful for you.
I can hear heart beat without it.
Then leave your profession.
Why?
Only a poet or
a lover can hear heart beat...
without stethoscope not a doctor.
Come, meet my friends.
Keep this.
Dr Pintu, this is Pintu.
Miss . Asha. - Hello.
Mr and Mrs Mihir Chandani.
Mrs Asha. - Hello.
And he is my best friend...
Rajan.
Yes.
Asha, Rajan...
- Happy birthday, Dr Prakash.
Oh! thank you Dr Vijay.
They want to meet you.
Yes, of course. Excuse me.
Meet my Bhanu. Dr Prakash.
Happy birthday. Thank you.
Waiter. Bring the drink, please.
Please have some.
You too.
Excuse me.
Why don't you dance?
Please, Asha.
Come on, Raju. You have no idea
how good Asha dance.
She'll be very good
partner. Come on.
Please, excuse me.
I'll check on guests.
What are you wondering?
I am thinking
how my dream came true.
Asha, I fear if this reality
turns back into a dream.
Rajan.
I know, you hate me.
But still I want to
meet you for once.
Can you do this favor for me?
I...
- Please, do not refuse.
I want to say something to you.
I will never forget this favor.
I promise,
you'll never see me again.
I'll meet you.
Really?
Excuse me, what's your size?
Shut up.
Excuse me.
Sorry, wrong number.
Wrong number!
But I made a correct size.
But God made me a wrong number.
It's okay.
I'll wear this ladies sweater.
'What didn't I become,
beloved in your love?'
'I'll kiss you.
I knitted sweater for you.'
This is not mine. You were giving...
this to some other girl a while ago.
No, I made this only for you.
I searched for you...
please wear for once, Jyoti.
You want me to wear it?
- Yes. - Okay.
Hey!
What did you do? Get out.
"How cruel are you murderer? How
you broke my heart, oh, oh."
"I keep saying cruel."
"I say, I say..."
"I kept saying, my heart is cruel."
"My heart is,
my heart is, my heart is..."
"Oh heart keeps coming here."
"It is hard to count."
"Recognise yours... Recognise...
which heart is yours
among these hearts?"
"Which is your heart?"
"Take all these hearts,
keep it on your foot."
"You tell them all
the name of girls."
"Who yearn, yearn, yearn, yearn."
"Who yearn on your name,
guess that's..."
"my heart. That is my heart."
"Which heart is it?"
"No."
"Oh, my mother."
"Your poor heart, roam around."
"I do not want your yearning heart."
"Listen."
"Listen, taker him. Listen,
taker him, he is rogue."
"Your heart it is.
Your heart it is."
"Fall in love with someone."
"My heart is the leader of all, try
to do election." - "Will see."
"Let's go."
"Wait, wait, wait..."
"Let's take vote
and see which heart is best."
"My heart it is. My heart it is."
- "Your heart it is?"
Asha, remember that night in Kashmir
when you rejected my love.
I sat under your room all night.
With the hope that
you'll believe in my words.
My whole body was numb
from the cold.
Then I fell unconscious.
When I opened my eyes,
I found myself in the hospital.
Raj. - I searched
for you whole day and night.
Asha, if you don't
believe my love...
then go to those valleys where
everything will witness my love.
You will see your name everywhere.
The name which has become
an important part of my life.
Hoping that at some point of life
you will pass from here.
And by chance
your eyes will fall on your name.
So maybe you will recall
that someone was crazy...
whose love you rejected.
That's all, Rajan.
I got my punishment for hurting you.
I came far away rejecting
your love...
but I couldn't forgot about you.
The indecisiveness of heart
and mind took away my sleep.
Away from you I realised...
that I love you.
I used to cry for you.
Asha.
Rajan. Asha.
I'll not talk to you.
Wow, the pot calling
the kettle black.
Neither anyone is pot nor kettle.
I am waiting for half an hour.
You are lying.
I am waiting here for an hour.
One hour?
You?
- You?
Who are you?
- Who are you?
I mistook you as Jyoti.
I mistook you as Deepak.
Sorry, sister.
Sorry, brother.
Sister, can I get your address?
You are calling me your sister...
and asking for address
at the same time?
If I'll not have the address
how can I come at 'Rakhi'?
Madanpura Simit Chal.
This is near to my house.
My address is Chauki
Mohalla Grass lane.
Okay, sister.
- Okay, brother.
Bye-bye.
Jyoti.
Sorry.
No need to say sorry.
What do you do?
Bansi.
Don't you feel ashamed of
talking to another woman?
Jyoti.
- Shut up.
Jyoti, what should I do?
I see your face in every face.
Your beautiful eyes...
your soft cheeks...
you little nose...
and...
My Bansi.
Yes, dear.
I always miss your face.
Have you ever eaten 'Pakoda'?
'Pakode'? Yes.
This nose of yours...
your cheeks...
and this eyes.
I miss them all.
That means, I am very handsome.
No, you aren't.
Stop this nonsense and listen to me.
Yes. - You have to meet
my father tomorrow.
I'll not meet your father.
Then I'll also not meet you.
Mom, where are you?
What happened? Mom, look who's here?
Who?
Hello.
Are you Asha?
Isn't it?
Yes.
Oh! so she is the one...
for whom my son used to be so upset.
Did not sleep whole night.
Mom, don't say in front of her.
Otherwise she'll be on cloud nine.
Why not? She is
the Goddess Laxmi of our house.
You'll stay happy only
if you'll pamper her.
Oh, God!
Okay dear, you sit here.
I'll be back.
Miss. Laxmi, come here.
No.
Oh! you are showing tantrums
from now only.
Okay, I'll come to you myself.
What are you doing?
I'll call aunt.
You don't have to do that,
I'll call her myself.
Dear, put it on.
I was waiting
for this day for long time.
Mother, I'll put it on her.
Okay, take it.
Miss. Laxmi, give me your hand.
Mom, she is so shy in front of you.
I will put it on her finger
at the temple of Goddess Laxmi.
Come, Asha.
Hello uncle.
Come, dear.
How are you now?
I am tired of lying
down on this bed.
It is just for few days
after that you can relax.
I am a heart patient, who knows...
when the heartbeat will stop?
Prakash, I want to say something.
Yes.
Dear, I want you to marry Asha.
Uncle, you're making me
feel embarrassed.
You have already done
a lot of favors to me.
Does anyone do a favor to his own?
Dear, you are the son of my friend.
It is my duty to take care of you.
I always considered
your father's respect as my own.
I have faith in you.
That's why I want to marry
my daughter with you...
I want to feel relieved.
I don't know if
I am worth it or not.
But I promise you,
I'll keep Asha happy.
Prakash, you gave me relief.
Dad. Hello Prakash.
- Hello.
Dear, you are late.
I am sorry, dad.
I got late at Madhu's house.
Okay, go and have dinner.
Okay. Let's go Prakash.
Okay, uncle.
I'll come again tomorrow.
Bye, uncle.
- God bless you, dear.
Madam, I have kept
the food on table.
Asha, I am leaving.
First have some food.
No, Asha.
- I'll not listen to you.
You have to eat with me.
Please, Prakash, come on.
Come on.
Thank you.
You go.
Wow!
Take this.
- Hey! that's it.
Take this 'Paratha.'
No, that's it. - What are you
doing? Aren't you hungry?
What else should I serve you?
What are you looking at?
You seem to be so happy today.
Yes, Prakash. I am so happy today.
Today, I have taken
the biggest decision of my life.
What?
Won't you tell me?
I want to say it.
If I'll not tell you then whom?
Because you are the one who...
I feel shy.
Please, tell me.
Not today. Some other day.
I'll wait for that day.
I have waited too.
My friends...
my sisters...
make me so perfect in love...
that Jyoti should not have
any complains.
Okay then tell us
whatever we taught you.
Okay, I'll tell.
Your eyes are so beautiful!
Wow! your nose is so cute.
Wow, your silky hair.
You are my love.
You are my darling.
Bansi. What is this?
What happened?
If this is
the situation before marriage...
what will you do after marriage?
After marriage, I'll do nothing.
I was doing all this
for your benefit.
What's my benefit?
Jyoti, I don't know how to love?
I was just learning.
Am I not there?
Ever since we have met...
have you ever talked with love?
Have you?
Have you ever given a chance?
OK, let's talk.
What to talk?
You are angry.
Bansi.
Yes, dear.
What is this?
Why is your nose flickering?
Oh God!
You ruined my mood.
This is my style to love.
I don't know why my nose flickers
while making love.
Yuck!
"I am falling in love with you."
"Oh God! Oh God! Oh God!"
"My heart started to
agree with you."
"Darling, darling."
"I am going crazy."
"My eyes have told your stories."
"Your love
and loyalty did the magic...
even the butterflies are in love."
"My heart called."
"What? What? What?"
"I am falling in love with you."
"Oh God! Oh God! Oh God!"
"Give me your foot step...
since when
I have been waiting in your way."
"Give me your foot step...
since when
I have been waiting in your way."
"How will I say my heart is yearning
to come in your arms."
"My heart called."
"What? What? What?"
"My heart started to
agree with you."
"Darling, darling."
"When loneliness surrounds
my heart...
then I came to know that
I love you."
"When loneliness surrounds
my heart...
then I came to know that
I love you."
"We are in falling in love...
with each other then tell me
when we are getting married?"
"My heart called."
"I am falling in love with you."
"Oh God! Oh God! Oh God!"
"My heart started to
agree with you."
"Darling, darling. Darling,
darling. Darling, darling."
Doctor, can I come in?
Rajan.
You.
Are you alright?
Why? Is only patients allowed
in your clinic?
Here friends
and patients both are allowed.
But you are one of those friends
who meet once in a year. - Okay.
And what about the day
I came to your party?
That's strange.
How come you came today?
According to me you should
have come after an year.
I don't accuse you.
How can you spare some time...
from your girlfriend
to meet your friend?
Tell me, who are you in love with?
Prakash, that Rajan is changed.
I love someone.
You fell in love with
every beautiful girl.
No, dear.
For the first time I have understood
the pain of the love.
I wish you had also loved someone.
Ask this heart, since when it
has been waiting for someone.
Really?
Prakash, who is she?
Rajan, you'll be surprised.
Even after
I know that she loves me...
I never confessed my
feelings to her.
You lost here.
See that before you express
your love to her...
she becomes someone else's.
Friend, we should not wait
in case of love.
No, Rajan.
I trust my love.
My love can't betray me.
Hello, Prakash.
Hello.
Asha, I...
Don't talk to me. I was waiting
for last 30 minutes.
And you don't care.
I am very sorry, Asha.
I'll never repeat.
Then let's go.
We can still watch movie.
Yes, Bansi
and Jyoti are also going with us.
Let's go. I am sorry, Prakash.
I am taking your friend with me.
Asha, you go.
I'll be there in a moment.
Okay, come quickly.
- Yes.
Wow, man...
I am very impressed.
You won her heart
in just one meeting?
What do you mean?
What do you think,
that I met Asha in your party?
No, my friend.
I met Asha first time in Kashmir.
And it was love at first sight.
To be honest, Asha taught me
the true meaning of love.
And I realised that love is
the most beautiful reality of life.
Rajan, as a friend,
I never asked you for anything...
but I am asking you today...
You have no idea, this house has
done a lot of favor to me.
And you know well,
Asha is so innocent.
Don't cheat her ever.
Please keep her happy.
This will be a favor on me.
Prakash, you will not trust
my loyalty if I say...
you will know it at right time.
Go, someone is waiting for you.
Uncle.
- What's the matter, son?
Uncle, I can't marry Asha
as per your wish.
Prakash.
I am sorry.
What happened, dear?
Asha loves someone else.
Love?
Who is he?
Rajan. I know him.
He is my friend
and belongs to a good family.
I can assure you...
Asha will be very happy with him.
But, Prakash...
I...
If Asha is happy it makes me happy.
You haven't talked to Asha
about me. Have you?
I was about to talk to her today.
Uncle, do not let Asha
know about this.
She'll feel bad.
I'm leaving.
Prakash.
- Prakash, I am so happy.
I feel like
the whole universe is in my favor.
Asha made my life beautiful.
It was you, who helped me
to get my love back.
Now you'll not have any complaints
that I don't see you.
You are really selfish.
Will you only come for Asha?
You are selfish too.
You know everything about us.
But you didn't tell anything
about your love.
What about her?
There is only sadness in my fate.
Prakash.
You were right, one should never
wait in the matter of love.
She loves someone else.
How do you know?
I can see it in her eyes.
May be you have a misunderstanding.
No, Rajan.
After betrayal I realised...
that time doesn't wait for anyone.
Who threw this garbage?
Who's there?
There is a silver spoon
in this garbage.
This is my spoon.
Oh, when I was asking about garbage,
you were not responding.
And as soon as you heard
about spoon, you came.
Come down.
Sorry.
Can't you see me?
Do you consider me a dustbin?
Come here.
I am sorry.
Come here. I'll not spare you.
Okay, I am coming.
Hey, come.
Why did you called me downstairs?
My bad. I had only seen
your face from here...
not your body.
You can go back.
My anger cooled down.
Why will I go back?
Why? Hey, talk with manners.
Don't use your hands.
My anger is very bad.
I'll not spare you.
You'll hit me? Oh, God!
Hey! Don't hit me.
Look, I'll call cops.
I'll call them
and you'll get such a beating...
that you'll call
your mother out of pain. - Shut up.
Why are you beating me?
He is hitting me.
He hit me really.
I will go and complain to my mother
that this bastard hit me.
Wait, stop there.
Asha, so sorry.
I can't make it today.
Yes, with Bansi.
Bansi.
What happened to you?
There was a serious fight...
I teach him a lesson.
Whom?
My enemy, he was thinking
himself a don.
I also taught him
a lesson by beating him.
Well, you know Jyoti...
that I don't raise my hands
on weak person.
But he was not agreeing.
Then I got angry
and I slapped him hard.
And again I hit him.
And again...
- That's it.
I understood.
- No, you didn't.
And at the last I swindled him
like an airplane.
And threw him.
And then I counted, 1... 2... 10...
and he fell unconscious.
I wish my father had
seen your bravery.
I can show that at any time.
Where is your father?
Why aren't you satisfied from
what happened earlier?
Who are you?
- Dad.
Dad.
So he is your Bansi?
You can't marry him.
- No, dad.
Please don't break my heart.
I am sorry.
Dad, forgive him.
Not at all. He is a coward.
Get up.
- Dad.
Dad, look...
I knew that you are Jyoti's dad.
So how can I fight with you?
If you want to know about
my strength...
then you can test me.
Then lift the weight.
- Okay.
Lifted.
Not her, I asked you
to lift the weight.
Weight, oh okay. Oh, God...
give me strength.
Come on.
Come.
I can lift it.
I did it.
You have guts.
Isn't is?
Now, tell me when can
I come to marry?
I'll feed the procession...
but who'll feed Jyoti?
I mean, what do you do?
I play flute.
And love others.
'Keep lighting the light with
the light." - Shut up.
Listen careful,
until you find a job...
you are not going to get Jyoti.
Understood? - Yes.
Yes, I got it.
Couldn't happen.
Couldn't happen again.
What are you thinking?
Asha, do you know,
Prakash also loves someone?
Not possible. You must have
had some misunderstanding.
You told me himself about it.
And you'll feel bad after hearing...
that the girl loves someone else.
Who could she be?
Asha, do you know
any girl known to Prakash?
Prakash loves someone
and I don't know?
From childhood till date
he has not hidden anything from me.
There's a lot of difference between
childhood and youth.
Asha, I feel sorry for Prakash.
He was so sad.
I'll go to him today. He needs me.
Who will support him other than me?
Who will understand his grief?
Prakash.
Asha.
Come.
I came here to fight with you.
You are angry with me?
I never expected from you that
you'll hide something from me.
What?
About your love.
What if I complain you
about the same?
Many times
I wanted to tell you about Rajan.
But don't know, could not tell you.
Do you remember, I told you
that I will tell you later?
And I said that
I will wait for that day.
Now, I have no complaints.
But I have.
Who is she?
Asha, please.
I don't want to recall her.
May be you misunderstood her.
I misunderstand her.
I feel sorry for that girl...
who lost your love.
How unlucky she is!
I am unlucky.
She got her love.
Prakash.
"The way I am laughing after
swallowing the tears of my sorrow."
"No one else can do this."
Hey!
What?
I am saying you to eat these sweets.
And pack what's left.
We will eat tomorrow.
I don't want it.
I am not hungry like you.
He always asks to eat
at other's parties.
But never said, Jyoti, come on,
I'll take you to Taj.
Jyoti, hotel's food is not healthy.
And there's no discrimination
in my heart.
I consider other's place as mine.
And my house is already mine.
Keep this sweets with you.
We'll eat it tomorrow.
I don't want this.
- Hey!
Dear, meeting you,
gave me peace of mind.
Dear, I am really happy today.
Happy birthday, Asha.
Thank you, Madhu.
Hello, uncle.
- God bless you dear.
Hello, Madhu.
- Hello.
Prakash hasn't come yet?
He might be busy with patients.
Okay dear, I'll take some rest.
No, dad. You can't go.
Dear, this is your party.
Madhu and Rajan is already here
and Prakash might be on his way.
There's no use of me.
Okay.
Rajan, I'll go.
Where are you going?
Who will look after the guests?
You are looking really pretty.
Prakash.
May you live 1000 years.
And each year will have 50000 days.
That's it?
Where is my gift?
Gift?
Asha, I had kept the gift for
a long time.
I thought I would surprise you.
But it's strange...
I lost the gift.
You have the gift, Prakash.
Your voice. You can surprise
not only Asha but everybody.
No, Rajan, I cannot sing today.
If not today, then when?
Please, Prakash, for me.
You swear on your lover.
Click her picture and keep it here.
Nothing can be better gift.
"If time used to be faithful..."
"you would have been mine."
"Like everyone else I also..."
"would be loved by you."
"If time used to be faithful..."
"There is already some sorrow
in my destiny."
"And some loyalty is also less
in your nature."
"Otherwise I would have not lost
the game I won."
"If time used to be faithful,
you would have been mine."
"If time used to be faithful."
"I could not even tell my partner
that I am also thirsty"
"There was glass in front
and I could not even take that."
"I wish I had not been betrayed."
"If time used to be faithful,
you would have been mine."
"If time used to be faithful."
"I am suffocating still I am alive."
"I am ashamed of my life."
"I would have died if I would have
been dependent on memories."
"If time used to be faithful,
you would have been mine."
"Like everyone else I also..."
"you would love me."
"If time used to be faithful."
Prakash.
You and the guest probably
didn't like my gift.
I am sorry.
Asha, that day the girl...
Prakash is
in love with had come to the party.
I appreciate that he made a picture
of his love with his voice.
And I came to know.
Rajan, why didn't you
show me the girl?
At that time, I did not considered
it appropriate.
Don't worry. You know that girl.
Who is she? Is she Madhu?
You.
Rajan, you are very doubtful...
and jealous too.
How can you say that...
the girl he loves is not you?
Because I know Prakash very well.
If he loved me, he would definitely
tell me about his heart.
When you doubted on him...
then I want to say something.
Before you came in my life...
if he had expressed his love...
then maybe you would
not come in my life.
If Prakash would have been
in your life...
then would you be very happy?
I would be sad.
Rajan, the place and respect...
I have fore Prakash is
way more than my love.
Maybe you will not understand this.
I want to look
at Prakash with the same respect...
not as my lover.
This is my wish.
Asha, I am sorry.
I misunderstood the relationship
of yours and Prakash.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
I just thinking...
If you don't mind,
can I ask something?
Yes.
Will you tell me the truth?
Do you love me?
Asha.
Sorry, Prakash.
But Rajan is doubtful
that you love me.
Do you feel the same?
No.
I can never think wrong about you.
Rajan could not understand the
relationship between you and me.
I feel sorry for that.
I respect you more than my love.
This feeling is support of my life.
I told this to Rajan also.
Asha, what if Rajan is right?
I would feel very sad.
My vision would have been shattered.
I will never let that happen.
I respect your feeling.
What is your name?
Rusi.
Who Rusi?
Rusi, I mean Russia.
What's your name?
I got it.
Rusi Bandukwala.
Okay.
- What's your father's name?
Mr Rastam.
What's Rastam's father's name?
- Mr Patau.
What is Mr Patau's father's name?
- Mr Palam.
And I don't know
the name of Mr Palam's father.
Have you got any award for a song?
Yes, Golden Jubilee.
Golden Jubilee?
I have worked at fifty places during
the Golden Jubilee.
Tell me the name.
- Yes, I am telling the names.
Laila's messy hair.
Majnu's tears.
Farhad's heart with the work.
That's it.
Show me your acting.
- Okay.
My dear Jyoti...
you are my love.
I love you.
I can't show you
that by tearing heart...
but I can show by tearing my coat.
How true is my love!
Enough, leave me.
Hey!
- Sorry.
Sorry. Wait.
Have your seat.
Your seat.
Sir, I got this...
Hello.
- Yes.
Bansi, you?
Hey, is he Bansi?
- Yes.
You lied to me. Get out of here.
Hey take him out.
Get him out.
- No, wait.
I'll go on my own.
Thank you.
Okay, shall I go.
- Yes.
Get out.
- Sorry.
You also go.
Go after him.
But dear, why do you need
to go abroad for studies?
You are already successful.
Dad's last wish I should get my
degree from Oxford University.
I consider it my duty
to fulfill his wish.
Well done, dear. You go.
May God bless you with success.
And it's just a matter of 1 year.
Till then Asha will also
become a doctor.
Yes, it is right.
What are you looking at?
You.
Rajan, how will
I live 1 year without you?
Why are you thinking this?
Darling, we have 1 month left.
Come on, let's dance.
Prakash, do you remember...
you introduced me to Asha in
the same place a year ago?
I thought you are so innocent.
You couldn't even realised from our
face that we have already met.
Rajan, I am not so smart like you.
Why would I doubt?
What kind of love is that
which can be expressed on face?
Anyone can see your face
and tell about your feeling.
really?
Okay, how are you going to abroad?
What do you mean?
I mean, by plane, by car...
by steamer,
by motorcycle, cycle, horse car?
How can I go on horse car?
I am going by plane.
If you want to enjoy
the journey then go by steamer.
You'll be able to see many
more cities along the way.
Wonderful idea.
What say, Asha?
Asha, I am very happy today.
How good it had been...
if Prakash's love would also
have been with him!
I feel sorry for Prakash.
Such a big house, loneliness...
but I'll not let this happen.
Rajan, after you come back, you'll
see his life partner with him.
I'll change his life...
that you'll be shocked.
Asha, promise that Prakash will
not be alone when I return.
Yes.
That's it, now I am tired.
No, one more dance.
Okay, sure. Not with me...
but Prakash.
Come on.
Come on. Why don't you dance?
Maybe you don't know
that Asha dances very well.
No, Rajan.
Let me see.
I love watching both you dancing.
Sometimes I feel,
you should ask me for something.
Today, you ask something from me.
If I ask, can you give?
Ask me.
You'll be shocked.
You are panicking as if
I am asking for your life.
I was just kidding.
Do I have to ask from you?
I have the right
on everything you have.
What say, Asha?
Dear, how long will you ship reach?
It will take almost 15 days.
Dear, tale your garland.
Mother, you keep this with you.
Asha, will you forget your mother
after Rajan's departure?
This is not possible, aunt.
Take care of mother and Asha.
Sure.
Go, dear.
Take care of yourself.
We will be restless
till your return.
Prakash.
Mother.
Hello, uncle.
Uncle, hello.
Prakash, come.
How are you?
Dear, I am fine.
Please try to explain
my crazy daughter.
What happened?
She didn't had her
dinner last night.
Now when I called for breakfast
she is saying her head is hurting.
She is furious on everyone.
Isn't this craziness?
She have to spent
a year without Rajan.
Go and make her understand.
Take her somewhere out so that
she feels better.
Go dear.
Okay.
You came again.
Hit me again.
Maybe your anger will cool down.
I am sorry, Prakash.
I thought... - Okay.
You have made your this condition
in one day separation?
How will you live
for 1 year without Rajan?
I am not feeling well.
How will you feel good in
a closed room?
Go and get ready. We are going out.
No, Prakash. I am not feeling good.
Are you not coming?
No?
No. No?
Okay, I'll go. Leave my ears.
Okay, get ready.
I am waiting downstairs.
What are you thinking?
Are you missing Rajan?
No.
I was thinking about you.
Prakash, will you listen to me?
I know what are you going to ask.
With someone else I... Isn't it?
Yes, Prakash.
You'll get tired alone in
the journey of life.
Without a life partner...
life feels like a burden.
What if you lost your love?
Someone else will bring
love into your life.
And your life will be full of joy.
And you'll start loving your life.
How do you know that
I don't love my life?
Your grief and your feelings...
how can I not understand?
I wish you could understand.
No, Asha.
I cannot even think
about someone else.
Let's go.
It's getting late.
Hello.
Come, have a seat.
Thank you.
What's your name?
My name is SIDT Swamy.
Why have you come here?
For your job.
You had given an advertisement...
that your daughter wants
to learn sing and dance.
Yes, for my daughter.
Yes, I am a teacher.
Okay, which ragas do you know?
I know a lot of ragas.
I know Pawamanipu Raga.
I know Naedimalli Raga.
I know Haritalmattum Godimaharaj.
You have knowledge about
great ragas. - Yes.
Okay, then sing a raga for me.
Okay.
(Other language)
Hey, wait.
- Yes, sir.
Lower your volume.
This is my office.
I am sorry, sir.
I was lost in singing.
Okay. You are hired.
Thank you, sir.
Take this card and visit my
house tomorrow morning.
I'll introduce you to my daughter.
Daughter?
- Yes, for teaching song.
Song? Yes.
Mr Subramaniam.
You are going to come...
You?
What happened?
Do you know him?
- Yes.
You have no idea...
this man is a fraud.
He only scams.
I'll not spare you.
He is my daughter's teacher.
I called him at my house.
He'll run away with my daughter.
Go and call the cops.
If anyone does this, he should
be handed over to the police.
Yes, of course.
I'll go and call the police.
You guys wait here.
Go quickly.
- Yes, go.
Will you become the witness?
- Yes.
Oh God!
He went to call the police now whom
will we hand over to the police?
Hello, dad.
Dad, you are always busy
reading newspaper.
Dad!
Dad.
But isn't this possible
that some people...
Yes, please.
Regarding Nilkamal.
Sorry, sir.
No sir.
I am very sorry, Mr Prakash.
Thank you.
No one can do anything.
Yes, dear.
Even mothers can't do anything
against God's wish.
But Asha...
I am going to her.
May God give us
the strength to bear this sorrow.
Rajan.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I'll tell you.
Do you know, why I have come here?
The way you were looking
at the sleeping pills...
and talking to Madhu about death.
You are torturing yourself.
And now you want to hurt us
more by committing suicide.
Yes, I want to commit suicide.
I don't want to live.
What do I live for?
Asha.
Get out of my way.
Who are you to stop me?
Prakash, this misery is
not bearable for me.
God has done so wrong to me.
Dad's voice echoes
in my ears again and again.
I always miss Rajan.
I feel as if
he is calling me for help.
This loneliness haunts me.
And I feel suffocating.
I feel like,
I should do something to myself.
My head is hurting.
What should I do?
Asha, I can feel you.
If every person starts committing
suicide to get rid of sorrow...
then what will be left
for the person?
Life is a gift of God.
You can't end your life like this.
And you have a aim in your life.
You are going to become a doctor.
You can establish a hospital.
By giving free treatments to poor
and helpless patients...
you can forget
your sorrow and grief.
Asha, everyone lives
for themselves...
you live...
for those helpless people
who needs you.
This can give you a new life.
And I have faith...
that one day you'll feel
the need of yourself.
You have a very bright
future Dr Prakash.
Thank you, sir.
Mr Prakash.
- Bansi.
Can you give me
a job in this hospital?
Bansi, what will you do
in this hospital?
I will give vitamin M to patients.
Vitamin M? Yes, Vitamin M
which means entertainment.
Entertainment for patients.
There is no happiness in this world
other than happiness, Prakash.
But Bansi...
- No but and if, Miss. Asha.
If I'll not get this job,
I can't marry Jyoti.
And if I'll not Jyoti,
I can't bear this.
And if...
if...
- Okay.
So can I join from tomorrow?
- Yes.
Then, I am happy.
I am happy.
Sorry, deduct
it's money from my salary.
I am happy.
How many times have
I told you to wear nice clothes.
I am ashamed to go with you.
I feel ashamed to go with you.
I mean, Jyoti
why you pay attention on clothes.
Just focus on my heart.
You used to call me stingy...
look, today I spent Rs 8. 12...
and bought this ring...
for our engagement.
You keep this ring with you.
And listen carefully.
- Yes.
I will not marry you until
you do your makeover.
Did you get it?
"Oh don't go in attitude,
don't go like this."
"The intention of passers
by will change."
"You are so beautiful,
just after looking..."
"no one gets burnt in jealousy."
"Oh don't go in attitude."
"These days you have
a lot of pride."
"You are young
and God is also kind on you,"
"If I got crazy,
what's so strange about it?"
"What happened to
the person who spoiled you?"
"I love your tyrannical attitude,
innocent face."
"Oh don't go in attitude,
don't go like this."
"The intention of passers
by will change."
"Oh don't go in attitude,
don't go like this."
"Alcohol is a little nectar
and a little poison."
"When they are mixed,
your beauty is made."
"The respect of the people
of the city is in danger."
"Oh my, darling,
my life is in danger."
"I love your tyrannical attitude,
innocent face."
"Oh don't go in attitude,
don't go like this."
"The intention of passers
by will change."
"Oh don't go in attitude."
My mother called me...
and I am here. Come dear.
Have a seat.
How is Asha?
Mother, your Asha is very magical.
Every patients she treats...
gets cured.
Prakash, I want to say something.
Have you ever thought about Asha?
I didn't get.
She has become lifeless.
She is serving people all day...
just to run away from her sorrow.
But for how long?
I know, mother.
But what can I do?
You can change her life...
by becoming his life partner.
Mother, you know everything.
Still you are saying this.
You are also aware of everything.
Her sorrow.
And who else other
than you can understand her?
Don't you want Asha to be happy?
Mother, I can do anything
to see her happy.
My happiness lies in her happiness.
But would Asha...
Asha can't refuse her mother.
Hello, aunt.
- Asha.
Come, you remembered
your mother today.
Okay, mother.
I have some work in hospital, I go.
Okay.
Asha, come and sit.
I want to say something.
Mother, I know everything.
I can't even think of it.
Asha, life of a woman is incomplete
without a life partner.
What if life partner is separated?
Life doesn't end.
You have to live.
No, mother.
I can't do this.
Without love,
one's heart is always incomplete.
Your heart needs love.
Love!
It is not in my fate.
Dear, what about Prakash?
Don't associate him with me, mother.
Asha, he is the one
who can take away all your sorrows.
His happiness lies in
your happiness.
Mother.
Please, think.
I'll think about it.
Did mother told you
about me anything?
Yes, the same thing she told you.
You tell me Prakash,
what should I say to mother?
Asha, maybe
I can't give you the love...
the happiness
that you ever wished for.
But yes, I'll always try
to understand you.
Seeing you happy...
is the desire of my life.
Do you remember...
that one day I was also
at the same point of life as yours.
And you said, that
I'll get tired alone in this life.
What if you lost your love?
Again someone will come with love
in your life.
And you'll get your happiness.
And you also said that life feels
like burden without love.
Asha, mother loves us.
That's why, she wants this.
Still, if you are not happy with
the decision...
then you can say.
I'll make mother understand.
Whatever mother said...
is right.
Do you remember,
one day you asked...
about your gift?
That time I had nothing more
than my sorrow.
Today it's your birthday.
But you didn't asked me for gift.
Asha, this is not a gift.
It is my soul.
This is all the feelings of my heart
that I am presenting to you.
You'll definitely miss
the passed time.
That memories is unforgettable.
That is the part of our lives.
Whenever these moments comes...
I'll try to understand
your feelings.
My love will never hurt you.
Prakash.
- Yes, Asha, I promise you.
Rajan's ring is irreplaceable.
I'll never try to remove the
memories of Rajan from your heart.
Today I want to share
a secret with you.
Maybe I would not tell you
in my whole life.
Because I knew that it'll hurt you.
But this is true Asha.
You are my love.
Rajan was right.
I never expressed my love.
And I have always adored you.
Even after knowing...
that you love Rajan.
Prakash.
Asha, I am sorry.
I broke your trust.
No, Prakash.
My trust is not broken.
Today, your respect has
increased in my heart.
In that point of life
where you are alone...
I'll support you.
Isn't my daughter beautiful?
Mother.
No.
I am very happy.
My wish has been fulfilled.
Aunt.
Please fulfill my wish as well.
Please pay attention in my life.
Until when I'll be single?
Hey!
Doctor, Rajan.
Do you know him?
He...
How does this happen?
How is the case?
He met an car accident
outside the hospital.
He is out of danger.
But he lost a lot of blood.
Taking him to the special room.
I'll be there.
No, Asha.
Asha, please.
Be brave.
Excuse me, doctor.
I want to handle Rajan's case.
If you don't mind.
Not at all, Dr Prakash.
Thank you.
I'll go for a change.
Prakash.
Where is my ring?
With me.
Prakash.
Asha, it was all fortune
that brought us to engagement.
I don't believe in such bondage.
The bond is of heart
and emotions not about the time.
You are free.
Asha, I never came in
the way of your happiness...
nor will I ever come.
My happiness lies in your happiness.
Being a mother...
my tears roll down when I miss him.
I don't know why
I feel that Rajan is not dead.
He'll come back.
You are giving false
hopes, isn't it?
You can't see tears
in mother's eyes.
I am not giving false hopes, mother.
I got to know that some people
survived in that ship.
I feel like Rajan also survived.
You are joking with your mother?
If he would have survived...
he would not have made me
cry for three years like this.
Mother, he is back.
Prakash.
Mother, our Rajan is back.
Our Rajan is back, mother.
Rajan is back?
Rajan is alive?
Yes, mother.
Where is he?
Mother, he is in the hospital.
Hospital?
He met an accident.
He has lost his memory.
He lost his memory?
No need to worry, mother.
He will be fine soon.
Prakash, take me to him.
Come.
Rajan.
She is your mother.
Why are you crying?
No...
I am very happy.
I got back my son.
What happened, son?
Tell me, dear.
I am not feeling good.
I am with you.
Mother.
Let him sleep.
Come.
What are you thinking, mother?
I am thinking, son...
my Rajan is back...
now what about my Prakash and Asha?
What, mother?
Everything will be fine.
Asha and Rajan will get married.
And your Prakash will enjoy
in their wedding.
Mother, Asha will be the bride...
and Rajan will bring
the wedding procession.
I can't come
in wedding procession...
don't mind.
I have to bid farewell to Asha.
Except me...
who will be with her?
Son.
God bless you, son.
You are so kind.
You are still a child.
Mother.
- Yes.
Why do you worry?
There's nothing to worry, dear.
What can make me
happy other than this?
I am fine.
Take me home.
You want to go back home?
Okay, I'll ask Prakash.
Take this medicine.
Now I'll see patient 9 again.
Prakash.
- Mother.
Dear, Rajan wants to go back home.
Better.
Don't try to remind Rajan
of old things.
He should have any problem
that affects his condition.
Okay.
2... 4... 2... 9... 4... 5... Jyoti.
Jyoti, there's a news good for you.
Yes, I mean the good news.
In the hospital, all
those ward boy working here...
I have become
the president of their union.
Just get sick
and come to the hospital quickly.
Then you'll see the,
my vitamin M is more affective...
than any doctor's medicine.
Hello.
- Wait a minute.
Jyoti, darling,
if you can't fall sick...
then your harsh father...
send that idiot here.
So that I can fix him.
What? Hey!
We are waiting for so long
and you are avoiding us.
Jyoti, darling.
An elephant has escaped from
a Kamla circus.
I'll call you later.
Who told you my name?
My name is Kamla.
What has happened to you?
Donation.
Donation is the name of sickness.
Hey! I am not sick.
I have come here to give donation.
- Donation for what?
Hey! Shut up.
(Other language)
I am tired.
Asha, we have so far from
our destination.
Now in order to reach...
the destination we have to cover
the same distance.
Isn't it?
Yes, Rajan.
This is the distance between us
and destination.
Look at this, Rajan.
Here it is...
there too.
It is everywhere.
Do you remember, Rajan?
You wrote my name here?
You told yourself.
Me?
Yes, Rajan. Do you remember?
Please, try and recall.
No, Asha.
I don't remember anything.
I am feeling dizzy.
"I swore, a night came, my dear."
"You also wanted to be
someone... to be..."
"Now everyday comes from there..."
"the sound of someone crying."
"I swear, it came..."
"When I miss you,
spring becomes restless."
"Like me in
this season raining clouds cry."
"Says morning, you'll meet..."
"this night is to cry together."
"I swear, it came..."
"I asked for blessings
but got some pain and loneliness."
"Despite being near, you are far."
"The meeting clarinet cries."
"It remained
the desire of this heart..."
"for the fulfillment of desires."
"You also swore one night
for being someone."
"Now everyday comes from there
the sound of someone crying."
"You swore..."
What do you think about it?
I am not sure.
There's one way, by which
he can get back his lost memory.
But there is also
the fear of one thing.
What?
Rajan was away for 3 years.
We don't know what happened in
that time with him.
Maybe something had happened...
after knowing
which you can lose him again.
I feel like,
we should know about that.
Where was Rajan in
these three years?
What happened?
And as far as losing him
is concerned...
it is my fate.
Prakash, I want my love.
Not a statue.
To whom I have to tell about
our relationship.
We have to repeat that car accident.
I am sure this shock...
of fake accident will definitely
bring back Rajan's memory.
I'll drive the car.
Do you think, I'll kill Rajan?
Sorry, Prakash.
I really thought this for a moment.
I am ashamed...
that I thought this about you.
The person...
- It is not your fault.
You are tensed.
Asha, we will not tell
mother about this.
But we will take her permission...
that Rajan will stay with us.
Prakash, what did you do?
I was not wrong.
What are you saying, Asha?
Nothing has happened to him.
Did you see
the fear on Rajan's face?
I am sure, Asha, that...
this incident will help Rajan
in recalling his memory.
Dr, Sharma, take him.
Look Rajan.
Who is here?
Rajan.
I am not Rajan.
Who are you?
Rajan, do have any idea,
what are you saying?
Look, try to recognise.
I am your friend, Prakash.
Look at Asha.
Your love...
- You guys are misunderstanding me.
I am not Rajan...
but Ramesh.
I can recall.
That car...
accident...
bright light.
The darkness in front of my eyes.
This hospital.
For how long have I been here?
3 months.
3 months!
Oh God!
My mother must be waiting for me.
My sister...
what must they be thinking?
What if... No,
I want to go back home.
I will go back home.
Please, lie down.
I promise...
you'll go back to
your house tomorrow morning.
Trust me.
Asha.
You are feeling ashamed of calling
me your mother, isn't it?
Look, you are mistaking me.
I am not that who...
You can deceive Asha and Prakash...
not your mother.
I know, why are you
doing this, Rajan.
I told you that I am not Rajan.
Look in my eyes.
Now say that you are not Rajan.
Say that I am not your mother.
Yes, I am not Rajan but Ramesh.
Swear on me.
Swear on me and say...
that I am not your mother.
Am I not your mother?
Say.
Mother.
Yes, mother. I am your Rajan.
I don't know how
I survived the accident.
When I realised that I am alive...
it was too late.
My friend and love had changed.
The day I came back...
'Isn't my daughter beautiful?'
'Mother.'
'I am very happy.
Today my wish got fulfilled.'
I could not bear it.
I wanted to go away from here.
I wanted to run away from myself.
I was dead for all of you.
I wanted to die. No.
I kept on running
and I got hit by a car.
After that I lost my memory.
When I woke up I saw Prakash
and Asha in front of me.
My fate brought me
back in the same situation.
I don't want to come
in between Asha and Prakash.
That's why, mother. I changed
my name from Rajan to Ramesh.
Didn't you think before
changing your name...
that how will your mother survive?
How will you stay away from us?
How was you living when
I was not here?
Asha and Prakash was your own.
Is there difference between me
and Prakash in your eyes?
Speak up, mother.
This is right.
I'll go away from their lives.
Rajan, don't you care about
your helpless mother?
You want me to live with
pain and sorrow?
I won't let you go.
I'll tell everything
to Asha and Prakash.
Don't do this, mother.
You have to support your son for
the happiness of Asha and Prakash.
No, Rajan.
Mother, you swear on me.
If you'll not listen to me,
I'll die. - No.
Before someone listen to us,
go away, mother.
No.
Prakash.
Well done.
I expected this from you, Rajan.
You want to go away from
Asha and my life.
Why? Just because we are engaged?
But did you even try to know
why did this happened?
You could not bear this?
And what hasn't she suffered
for you, my friend?
You could never imagine.
The oppression you have done
on Asha by becoming Ramesh...
I'll never forgive you for that.
Rajan, she ate poison
because of you.
Prakash. - Yes,
mother, Asha ate poison.
No, this can't happen.
Prakash, please say
that Asha is safe.
Say, Prakash.
Asha will be safe.
Rajan, Asha only loves you.
I am sorry, Prakash.
I had a misunderstanding.
Where is Asha? Take me to her.
Hi, what did you say?
Don't talk to me about Bansi.
Otherwise I'll hang up.
Jyoti, ever
since you got angry with me...
my eyesight is getting weaker.
You are lying again.
Don't talk to me.
Jyoti, don't say this.
Otherwise I'll go crazy
just like Romeo.
The people of your neighbourhood
will laugh at me.
And your dogs will bark at me.
Yuck!
Okay, I am sorry.
Sorry.
Okay, listen,
I'll give you a good news.
Dad has agreed.
Am I dreaming?
No, this is true.
Where is that great personality?
Where is his feet?
Here it is.
Yes.
Who says heaven lies only in
the feet of mother...
What are you doing?
I say that heaven lies in
the feet of father-in-law.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
Help me to get up.
Okay, get up.
- Yes.
Have your seat.
Father-in-law, I have an idea.
What idea?
You also come.
Father-in-law, Rajan
and Asha is getting married soon.
Why not both of us get married in
the same wedding alter?
Not a single penny will be spent.
Even the alter is free.
Alter is free?
- Yes...
no penny will be spent
and the alter is free as well.
Isn't Jyoti your daughter?
- Yes.
You just buy 15 piece 'Suit'
and 'Sari' for her...
and 25 piece suit for me.
Not a single penny will be spent.
Alter is free.
- Yes, alter is free.
Buy me a motor.
Motor?
- I mean a bike.
I will take your daughter on
a trip on that bike.
No penny will be spent
and the alter is free as well.
Isn't it, no penny is spent.
- Yes, alter is free.
What say, father-in-law?
You make all the arrangements
and I'll do the rest.
No penny will be spent
and he told the cost of Rs 10000.
But dad, alter is free.
Yes, it is.
Alter is free.
"My heart called. What,
what, what?"
"I am falling in love with you."
"Oh God! Oh God! Oh God!"