Stop! Stop!
Switch off! Switch on!
Start!
Stop! Stop! Once again.
Switch off! Switch on!
Start!
A guitarist like you
will not be able to turn this handle!
Jaggu!
- Coming, brother.
You can't even turn the handle,
give it to me.
Get up!
You eat 50 breads with the cream!
Still you don't have strength!
I do eat but...
- I think there's a problem with the car.
What?! Is the dynamo clean?
- Yes.
Carburetor?
Engine?
- Yes.
Battery?
Armature?
- Yes.
Hen?
Harmonium? Tabla?
- Yes.
You are just bluffing!
Why isn't the car starting?
Why is the car not starting?
I think one of us has seen
a woman, early in the morning.
Have you?
No. I saw myself in the mirror.
But Mannu may have.
Me?! When you are coming down,
I just saw your face.
Does that mean, I have?
Look that girl is watching us.
No wonder the car is not moving!
Till the time she keeps staring here,
the car is not going to start.
Get rid of her. Chase her away.
- Yes.
You go.
- You go!
Why me?
- You go.
Should I go?
- Please do so.
No one needs to go.
Let's use our old trick.
The car will now start and speed away!
- Yes, it will!
Come on.
- Let's go.
Come on. Start!
Hail Lord Hanuman!
The car's gone!
- It's gone!
Come on brother. Catch it!
"Move aside."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
"The greatest truth of all is this.."
"..come what may
success will be ours."
"The greatest truth of all is this.."
"..come what may
success will be ours."
"In a tattered state it may be,
it's fine as long as it's mobile."
"True or untrue it may be,
"In a tattered state it may be,
it's fine as long as it's mobile."
"True or untrue it may be,
"Turn to the left
and turn to the right."
"Move aside."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
"A matter so trivial,
the world failed to fathom."
"As long as man moves on
every treasure can be won."
"A matter so trivial,
the world failed to fathom."
"As long as man moves on
every treasure can be won."
"What is fame? To move on
is the name of the game."
"What is honor? To move on
"What is fame? To move on
is the name of the game."
"What is honor? To move on
"Turn to the left
and turn to the right."
"Move aside."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
"Always stay together like this."
"United we stand,
Divided we fall."
"Always be together like this."
"United we stand,
Divided we fall."
"If problems are strewn your way
with a brave face, challenge it."
"If huge hurdles block your way,
together move it aside."
"If problems are strewn your way
with a brave face, challenge it."
"If huge hurdles block your way,
together move it aside."
"The one who fathoms this
achieves success."
"Move aside."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
Jaggu, fill oil in this.
- Yes, brother.
Mannu, fill oil.
Sir, has our car been repaired?
It's in top condition!
We'll win the race this year too!
Really?
Yes, clean the car
and check the oil.
Certainly!
Sir, I need a holiday tonight.
Why?!
Raman Circus from Madras will be
showing good exercises tonight.
Some of my friends are going.
I also need Champion, our car.
Indeed! Who'll do the work?
I've changed the fuse, filled oil
and cleaned the cars!
Very good! Very good!
How awful! Mannu!
- Yes?
Come here.
- Okay. Move aside.
Look at this!
It's a lovely picture.
Did you put it there?
- No. - Then?
I did.
- Why?
Our driver Vithal gave it to me.
He told me it was lovely.
I put one here. I'll put the other
with a swimming costume, there.
I'll smash your head! Jaggu!
- Jaggu sir.
Coming, brother.
Look at this disgusting picture.
- Awful!
Have you ever seen a woman's
photograph in this house?
Have you?
- No. - No.
If I wanted to put up such a picture,
wouldn't I have done so?
Yes. But why didn't you?
Because I don't want anyone
in our home to befriend women!
Nobody should befriend a woman.
What if a woman comes
here with a car?
Suppose it's an emergency?
That's a different case. But burn
this photograph with Mobil Oil!
Mannu, burn this photograph
with Mobil Oil.
Mojha, burn this photograph
Boss, can I get an off?
- An off?!
Why did you put the picture there?
I got slapped!
I'm sorry, it won't happen again.
May I take Champion?
Go.
I'll burn this first.
I've got a holiday!
You've given Mojha a holiday?
- He wants to go to the circus.
But who will stay here at night?
- You will.
Why should I?
You gave him an off, so you will stay.
The day you give him an off,
I'll stay back.
No, I won't stay.
- I won't stay either!
I won't stay!
- I certainly won't stay!
I won't!
I'm a deep sleeper. So if a
customer returns, don't complain!
That will bring us disrepute.
It'll fetch all of us a bad name.
Think about it.
Let's toss.
- Okay.
Fine?
- Absolutely.
Heads I win, tails you lose.
- Okay.
Ready?
Look.
- Tails.
You lose.
- Damn!
Heads I win, tails you lose?
Who's it?
Who the hell is it?!
Why is he knocking at this hour?
Hey! Why don't you tell me
who you are?
Just you wait!
What are you looking at!
I thought it must be a ghost!
- What!
It's the middle of the night.
I was sleeping so peacefully!
You were sleeping?
- Yes.
You were sleeping?!
- Yes, I was.
You were sleeping with the
'Day and night service' indicator on?!
Is the indicator on?
I will complain about you!
Idiot.
The indicator has been turned off.
Now you also buzz off!
Come and complain in the morning.
I wonder where she came from!
The girls nowadays are such a pain!
Excuse me!
You haven't left yet?
Please open the door!
I'm in big trouble.
Very good!
My car has broken down.
Get it repaired when you
come to complain tomorrow!
Please! I said that in anger.
Please open the door.
I am a girl. You ought to help me.
I ought to help you, indeed!
Have you cooled down, madam?
Absolutely? Sure?
Where is the car?
Parked on the road.
The road?
Where is the driver?
- I, myself, drive.
No wonder!
It had to break down!
Come with me.
Come here.
Start.
Once again.
I can't figure out this way.
Pardon?
- I can't figure out.
Then?
- I'll have to open the bonnet.
Go ahead!
How can I open it here?
I need light.
You mean, the car has
to be taken to the garage?
Obviously!
Who will push it?
- That's a good question.
I can't see a soul in these rains.
You're right.
I don't spot a soul.
You push it!
- What? - You push it.
I knew it! If you can disturb
my sleep at midnight, you can...
Just shut up! Take care of
the steering wheel. I'll push!
Really? Let's go.
Push, madam.
Come on! Push harder!
Very good!
"A stormy, rainy night it is.
Look at the trouble it's brought.."
That's enough.
It will take some time.
Go and sit somewhere. Go!
Oh dear! You're drenched.
There aren't any dry clothes here.
My coat's over there,
you may wear it.
Pardon? No, thank you!
Your wish.
Even the car is dripping wet
just like madam!
Where was the misfire?
Oh, so you were misfiring?
Look, there's a flask kept.
Bring it here.
Me?!
- Yes.
Fetch it yourself!
So you won't go?
I am not your servant!
Is that so?
Even I'm nobody's servant.
The work will be done
only after the flask is brought.
Careful! It will break.
It's hot tea. Just gulp it.
I don't drink tea.
- No? Thank God!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Please remove a
cigarette from my pocket.
My hands are dirty.
Remove it.
Match stick.
Where is it?
- It's not there?
Anyway, the cigarettes are wet.
- Serves you right!
She's shivering with cold but
her head has not cooled down yet!
"A girl, drenched to the core."
"Wide awake in the dead of night."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"A girl, drenched to the core."
"Wide awake in the dead of night."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"Flames of anger burn
from deep within."
"Seething with rage she comes."
"Flames of anger burn
from deep within."
"Seething with rage she comes."
"Fretting and fuming
on a lonely, rainy night."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"A girl, drenched to the core."
"Wide awake in the dead of night."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"Swaying hither and thither."
"Seeming so lost."
"With all the zeal
she set out on a night so stormy."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"A girl, drenched to the core."
"Wide awake in the dead of night."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"Soaking wet from head to toe."
"She's as crazy as can be."
"She stands, bends, walks, stops
and set out on a night so dark."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
"A girl, drenched to the core."
"Wide awake in the dead of night."
"Met a stranger
with not a soul around."
"Is it something very wise to do?"
Start the car, madam.
That's it!
Sorry for the trouble, madam.
You had to wait long.
I have never seen
a man as strange as you.
Well, you have now. People say
I am a bit mad. What do you think?
You, and mad?
You could make a sane man go insane!
That's nice!
My charges!
She's gone!
Cheat! She got the work done for free!
How will she get away now?!
Why is he sleeping here?
Hey, Mannu! Wake up.
Why are you sleeping here?
What's the time?
- It's 9 a.m. Why didn't you go home?
A girl had come last night.
I'm waiting for her.
What is he talking!
- What rubbish!
Fool! Which girl are you waiting for?
I mean, it was an emergency case.
Emergency.
- Emergency.
She had come to get her car repaired.
But why are you waiting for her?
She left without paying.
Did you use any spare parts?
- Did she steal anything?
No, but my hard work went to a waste.
She left her bag behind.
She will surely come back.
It's a nice bag!
What were the charges?
- Five rupees and twelve annas.
Then take five rupees and twelve annas
from this bag..
..and debit the amount
from the company account.
Very well, brother.
- What's wrong?
How can I open the bag
without the girl's permission?
Nonsense! Obey older brother.
- Take it.
You open it, brother!
This is not being decent.
How can I do it?
Absolutely.
What nonsense you talk!
You open it.
- How can I?
I never touch a girl's bag.
- I say, open it!
I'm doing it at your behest.
Otherwise I don't even touch it.
A bullet!
- A bullet?
There may be a revolver.
Hold this!
It's a lipstick, not a bullet. Look.
It looks just like a bullet.
- Empty the bag.
There's not a single penny.
She made a fool of you, idiot!
Cheque! I'm sorry.
A show for an invitation!
An invitation for a show!
She will surely go for it.
Return her bag and ask for
five rupees and twelve annas from her.
Fine. But I have never seen her.
He's at fault, so he should go.
I understand. You go.
All right.
You also come along.
- No way! I keep away from girls.
Let's toss.
Toss? Alright.
Heads I win, tails you lose.
Hey, you've understood now!
Fine, I'll go.
This is a stage pass.
Please go over there.
Ms. Renu.
Excuse me, is this yours?
- Yes.
But it's in Ms. Renu's name.
- She's the one I want to meet.
You can't go in without work.
I have important work with her.
- What work?
I want to recover
five rupees and twelve annas from her.
Five rupees and twelve annas!
Have you gone mad?
Step out!
- If I don't take my money...
Wait out until the show is over.
- I can't wait. I...
Watchman!
- What will he do?
Yes! Where will she go now!
I'll surely take
five rupees and twelve annas from her!
O' God! It's 12:15 am.
Bye, Sheela. I must leave.
It's very late.
If the car breaks down again like
last night, I'll be in trouble.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Come in the morning itself.
You have to spend the entire day
with me. Have lunch and...
Will you come with me for
shopping also? - Yes.
And to roam around?
- Yes.
Pray that my car runs fine.
- Yes, I will.
Good night.
- Good night.
"I'm a melody of the stars.
A tale of the springs."
"Cast your eye on me
and drive yourself crazy."
"I'm a melody of the stars.
A tale of the springs."
"Cast your eye on me
and drive yourself crazy."
"Beauty unleashed you sure are.
The love of my life you sure are."
"But five rupees and twelve annas
is what you must pay me first."
"Five rupees and twelve annas."
"Else, brother will thrash me."
"Forget about the money."
"And seek my heart instead."
"My darling, what did you say?"
"Let alone my heart,
seek my youth instead."
"I can become a Romeo for you.
I can chant your name all day."
"See for yourself an example of it."
"My blood gets shed for you.
My heart gets broken for you."
"This is the punishment
your lover gets."
"This ardent thing called love
is a feeling, so wonderful."
"Cast your eye on me
and drive yourself crazy."
"This ardent thing called love
sure is a feeling, so wonderful."
"But five rupees and twelve annas
is what you must pay me first."
"Five rupees and twelve annas."
"Else, brother will thrash me."
"Leave behind your woes,
create a melody instead."
"And sing a song of my beauty."
"O' my darling."
"Continue to make such requests."
"A song I can sing for you.
A melody I can create for you."
"See for yourself an example of it."
"Tread slowly and deliberately."
"Tread slowly and deliberately
in the garden, O' bee."
"A great admirer of art you are."
"Excuses galore you can make."
"Cast your eye on me
and drive yourself crazy."
"An excuse so good, it sure is.
A great admirer of art I am."
"But five rupees and twelve annas
is what you must pay me first."
"Five rupees and twelve annas."
"Else, brother will thrash me."
"Fall in love,
devoid of any worries."
"Money is nothing
but a fleeting possession."
"O' my darling, it's true."
"Everything is an illusion
except your love."
"I can become a recluse for you,
and wander the jungles so dense."
"See for yourself an example of it."
"Your sack is going to burst apart.
So beware!
"Your sack is going to burst apart."
"The love of your life I am."
"Come and embrace me."
"Cast your eye on me
and drive yourself crazy."
"The love of my life you sure are."
But first pay me...
One, two, three, four, five."
"Five rupees and twelve annas."
"Else, brother will thrash me."
This looks like a garage.
But how did I get here?
It's 2 O'clock. O' God!
I'm badly trapped!
Hey, who's in there?!
Hey, Ramu! Where are you? Get up!
There's a thief in the house!
Get up, Ramu!
Who is it?
- Who is it?
- Who are you?
Who is it?
Oh, it's you!
Where is it?
Here's your bag.
And please show me the way out.
Who are you?
Didn't you recognise me?
You had come to my garage last night.
I had repaired your car.
Oh yes!
Then give my five rupees
and twelve annas.
But how did you get here?
- You brought me along?
What!
I was sleeping in your car
and you didn't even see me.
In my car? Are you in your senses?
No, I'm mad.
Or I wouldn't take the trouble to collect
five rupees and twelve annas.
Where is he?
Where has he gone?
What happened?
- There's a thief in the house!
Where is the thief?
- I don't know.
You don't know? Do you think
he went this way? Come on.
Show me a place to hide.
There's none!
They will thrash me.
- Good!
You come at midnight to ask for
five rupees and twelve annas.
If you open the door,
I'll tell all of them.
What?
- That you brought me here.
What! I brought you here!
Yes, you did. Open the door.
I'll tell them everything.
Renu! My dear, open the door.
Renu!
I'm coming, father.
- Open the door.
Listen... wait.
Open the door.
Wait. Let me hide.
Renu! Renu! Open the door, Renu.
Yes, father.
What's the matter, father?
Are you all right?
Absolutely fine.
Then why did you scream?
Me? I didn't scream, father.
But I heard you.
I didn't hear anything.
I did see, though.
You did?
- Yes. I had seen a dream.
Dream!
- What is this pistol for?
There's a thief in the house.
There's no one in my room.
I was sleeping peacefully.
How would you know then!
He must be hiding somewhere here.
No, father.
Father, you have woke up just now.
You heart is beating so fast!
- Is it?
You got scared.
- Scared my foot.
I'll shoot that thief!
Move aside. Let me take a look.
Why don't you come out?!
There's nobody here, father.
I wonder where he's gone!
What a problem...
You'll break the legs.
- Legs?
The bed's poles are very weak.
Father, I think
he's hiding on the roof.
I'll shoot him!
On the terrace.
- Okay, I'll go there.
Lock your door. And don't worry.
Chaubey! Pathan!
Everybody come with me!
Get out!
I'm going. Let me catch my breath.
My back is broken.
Get out!
Thief! Thief!
After that, I remained in the
midst of beggars for a long time.
I could leave only after the cops
came and took the corpse away.
The story is very good!
I have surely read it before.
Indeed! Had you been in my place,
you would have known!
The question that now arises...
- The question that now arises..
..is that as per the law, you
should tell the cops everything.
But it was the police
who took the dead body away.
Yes, it could mean more trouble.
That's why I'm quiet. However...
You couldn't get five rupees
and twelve annas. - Right.
I couldn't. So what?
That's why I say,
stay away from women!
Don't repair their cars.
You can't please them. They are cheats.
Yes, all of them are.
Wrong! Not all girls are cheats!
How do you know that
this girl isn't a cheat?
She will pay us.
Did she say so?
- Yes.
When?
- At 2 O'clock at night.
She'll come to pay at 2 a.m.,
and we'll keep waiting!
I mean, she told me that
she would come this morning.
At what time?
- At 10 O'clock.
10 O'clock?
- Around 10-10:30.
Rubbish! I shouldn't have sent you!
You get excited seeing girls!
I get excited?!
- Go and do your work!
Go and do your work.
How often have I told him not
to get excited on seeing girls!
To concentrate on his work!
- And you should play!
No.. I am also doing my work.
Mannu! - What is it?
- Nothing.
Are you angry with me?
- No. Why?
May I ask something?
Did you actually fall on the girl?
I told you I did.
You did? In that case,
the girl is very nice.
How do you know?
Wouldn't she have handed you
over to the police otherwise?
How does she look?
Very beautiful!
- Really?
Manu. Manu.. how old is she?
60 years!
What! She's old.
Don't joke. How old is she?
Damn! She must be
around 20-22 years.
20-22 years! Very good!
Hey! What are you doing?
- Nothing. Introduce me to her.
In front of brother, you scold me!
And now, ask me about girls!
I'm dead! Help me, sir!
Help!
Hey, why are you hitting him?
I asked him to paint my car black
but he painted my face instead.
I'll hit him!
Stop it, you fool!
You wanted to fight with me.
Get up. Fight.
Brother!
You act smart with children, huh?!
Mojha accidentally
sprayed paint over his face.
He beat him so badly that the
poor chap began to see stars!
I thrashed him...
- You can't thrash him, you musician!
But you! You eat 50 'rotis',
yet lack the strength!
Brother, I did try.
But he is strong.
Why don't you show your might?
Come on.
Brother, knock him out!
Come on!
- Really?
Brother, just one powerful punch
on the right side.
Come on.
Very good!
Upper cut!
Do you see stars already?!
Now I will make you see stars!
Ask him how many stars
he can see!
1.. 2.. 3.. 4.. 5.. 6.. 7.. 8.. 9..
- 10!
Send him to the hospital.
- The hospital?
Yes!
Heave ho! Heave ho!
Ready?
- One! - Two! - Three!
It's 10:30. He said she'd
bring the money at 10:30.
My foot, she'll bring!
There's dirt in the carburetor
and the brakes aren't proper too.
Pay your previous dues first.
Only then will I do the next job.
Previous dues?
- Yes. Five rupees and twelve annas.
But I have come here
for the first time.
Really?
- Yes.
Manu! Jaggu!
- Coming!
Look, you can fool Mannu
but I'm very smart.
Who's Mannu?
I don't know any Mannu.
So you don't even know Mannu?
- No.
He had repaired your car and was
at your place at 2 last night.
Brother!
- Shut up!
He came to my place at 2 a.m.
What do you think I am?
What do you think we are?
Do you expect us to work free for you?
Pay up or I'll call the police!
Brother!
- Quiet you fool.
Will you pay five rupees
and twelve annas?
This is some compulsion!
- What! Didn't he work for it?
How much was it?
- Five rupees and twelve annas.
That's what I'm asking for.
- But, brother...
Five rupees and twelve annas.
Here, take this.
Return four annas.
And here is your receipt. Keep this.
What a problem!
Return me four annas.
Hello.
- Hello. Mohan Brother's motor garage.
Yes?
- Is it Manmohan?
No. I'm his older brother.
Could you please call Manmohan?
There's a girl for you.
I'm his older brother. He's busy.
I am calling from
Mr. Kishanchand's bungalow.
Manmohan had repaired
my car earlier also.
When?
- Day before yesterday night.
At 2 a.m.?
- Yes. It's broken down again.
So, you had to pay five rupees
and twelve annas?
That's right.
Damn! I charged some
other girl for it. This is...
I'm sorry. I wasn't talking to you.
What work do you have?
My car has broken down again.
- Fine. I'll send somebody.
Are you convinced now that I've
come here for the first time?
I'm extremely sorry. Please sit.
Your car will be repaired.
Here.
- Thank you.
Why didn't you tell me?!
- You never gave me a chance!
It wasn't the same girl
but her bag looked so similar.
That's where even I went wrong.
Well, never mind.
Go to Peddar Road and repair
Kishanchand's girl's car.
Girl!
He can't collect the money,
so it's no use sending him!
I never visit a girl's house but
since you order me, I'll go.
Mojha!
Listen.
Clean the carburetor of her car.
Repair her brakes too.
Repair everything.
But don't charge her.
Why?
- I messed up. And insulted her.
The engine is fine.
I wonder what's wrong.
I'd repaired it this morning.
I think there's a problem here.
I wonder what's wrong.
Who are you?
- Why have you come here?
Someone had called for me.
- Who had?
I don't know.
Perhaps it was one of you.
Sheila..
- I don't know who he is!
Mister, you've come
to the wrong house.
How can that be? This was the
address given over the phone.
Are you from the garage?
- That's right.
But the one who had
repaired my car..
..is my younger brother.
Why didn't he come?
- What could he have done?
He's only a mechanic.
I am an automobile engineer.
Well, Mr. Engineer, how long
will you take to repair the car?
I'll have to look at it first.
Go ahead.
Renu dear!
Repair the car quickly.
- Very well.
What's wrong?
If you would step aside,
I'd be able to work better.
Go ahead.
Please hurry up!
Hey, don't!
There's nothing wrong with it.
Then, there must be
a problem with the plug.
The plug is fine. The battery is charged.
I've checked everything.
There may be a problem beneath.
- Beneath?
Yes. Take a look.
Okay.
Why are you staring at me?
- It's nothing.
There's a black mark on the face.
Black mark?
Wipe it off.
- Me?
Yes, wipe it off.
Hey! Why are you so nervous?
I... I... I'm not nervous.
Please get me a glass of water.
Water? Fine, I'll get it.
But at least go down and check.
I'll go right now.
- Quickly.
Hello. Mohan Brother's motor garage.
- Yes.
Whom have you sent?! He's still
not been able to repair the car.
He's had 10 glasses of water!
What!
- Yes! Please send Manmohan.
All right. I'll send somebody else.
Don't worry.
Thanks.
Mannu... come here.
- Yes.
Jaggu can't repair the car.
So you go.
No. I have work to do.
It's beyond him.
He's had 10 glasses of water already.
10 glasses of water!
- Yes. Go there.
I'm taking the car.
- Okay.
Hasn't the car got repaired yet?
- No, it hasn't.
Is that car yours?
That one? It's ours.
It looks very strange.
Strange? It's a racing car!
A 1921 model.
May I take a look at it?
- Sure!
Excuse me. My elder brother had
come from the garage. Where's he?
He's beneath.
- Beneath?
Brother Jaggu!
Hey, what's the matter?
I am stuck! Please get me out.
Has the girl gone?
- Yes, she has.
But how did you land there?
- Don't ask! She pushed me in.
How?
- I'll tell you later.
Have you got the car?
- Yes, I have.
I'm leaving.
And listen.. you only recover five rupees
and twelve annas. I'm going!
Brother Jaggu!
- I'm going!
Good God! What an escape!
"I am fortunate for having
being able to escape."
Hey! Where are you taking me?
Who spoke? There's no one here.
Where are you taking me away?
You!
- Look ahead! There could be an accident!
What's happening?!
Listen!
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Please wait!
Please listen to me!
Please wait!
I'm tired. I can't run anymore.
Fine. Then sit in the car.
In the car? But how can
I sit in the car with you?
Why not? Am I a tigress?
Well, I don't know that.
But you surely are something!
Come on, just get into the car.
Come.
Where do I have to go now?
Drop me home.
- Your home!
Dear God, what trouble
have You landed me in!
What!
- No! I was talking to myself.
Let's go.
When did you come?
- A while back.
You didn't even inform me.
- I was repairing the car.
Is it done?
- Yes. It was an easy job!
Your brother couldn't manage.
He was nervous.
- Why?
He's a bit afraid of girls.
I was worried the whole night.
I kept running everywhere.
At the end of it, I got so tired.
Why has the
police inspector come here?
Because a thief had
entered our house last night.
Have you told them?
He didn't steal anything.
He only ate 3 bananas and 2 apples.
I suspect he was a member
of a gang of murderers.
What!
- Yes.
A famous jeweler named Lalchand
was murdered nearby last night.
We found his
dead body on the road.
Before we could get there,
the rogue escaped.
It's possible, one of the gang
members had entered your house.
Good God! In that case,
search the place well.
Because the hoodlum
has seen my house.
Don't worry. It's a murder case.
I'll take special care.
Thank you very much.
In the meantime, I'll go and
keep the jewelry in the bank.
Is the car all right?
- Yes, daddy.
Wait. Let me first
interrogate your driver.
But you've held the driver and
my other servants in custody.
Then who's he?
Who are you?
- Well, I am...
He is the mechanic.
He had come to repair the car.
Indeed.
Have you come here before?
Never.
I'll question your servants at home.
Investigate well.
Inspector, the hoodlum must be caught.
Renu, who will drive the car?
- I will.
I have the jewelry with me.
What if the car breaks down again?
Let's take him along.
- Yes, I'll come.
Come on.
- Let's go.
Your car doesn't
knock now, does it?
No.
- How can it?
My adept hands, and fail?
No company has made such a car!
Race... Faster!
Accelerate some more!
Faster, indeed!
Suppose there's an accident, then?
Since the time the thief entered
our house, I've been jittery.
Did a thief actually get in?
- Am I lying then!
What did he steal?
- That's most surprising.
He didn't steal a thing.
How could he? He didn't come to steal.
He wanted to take Rs.5...
What happened, son?
- What's wrong?
You were talking about Rs.5?
- Nothing.
I think he was a
blessed saint, not a thief.
No wonder he ate 3 bananas
and 2 apples... 5 fruits in all.
What do you think?
I think he is crazy.
What's happened to you now?
Nothing, daddy. My foot slipped.
Be careful, child. Let me keep
the jewelry safely in the bank.
What a pain!
She wants to drive, indeed!
Why did you talk about the thief
in front of daddy?
You were about to say everything.
You are really mad!
You haven't seen madness yet.
You must meet my brothers first.
I pale out in comparison!
The one who came this morning
and had 10 glasses of water...
He is my second brother,
Jaggu brother.
An electrical engineer.
But he's ignorant about electrical works.
He does discuss girls but gets
jittery when he faces them!
And what about you?
Me? I'm the opposite.
What?
Girls are afraid of me.
You know the state
you were in last night!
Don't laugh. You're too much!
Should you have done that just to collect
five rupees twelve annas?
I had no choice.
Had I not come, my eldest brother
would have thrashed me badly.
And specially, bills of girls!
No way!
Why? What wrong have girls done?
I don't know.
But yes, he does hate them.
He even hates their pictures.
He instructs us not to talk to them,
not to repair their cars.
And was he the one
who sent you to collect..
..five rupees twelve annas at 2 a. M?
Obviously.
Hey! Where are you going?
To drop you to your garage.
- Please don't that!
If my elder brother sees me
with you, he'll kill me.
Give me the money,
I'll get off here.
Mannu, I'll pay the money
only to him.
And I will also see
how much he hates girls.
That's your problem.
But please let me get off here.
Please stop the car!
Look...
All right. Drive on.
What happened?
- Nothing.
It's 12 O'clock. He won't be
in the garage now. Drive on.
That's it.
Thank you.
Done?
- Yes.
"I was there, and so was she.
She was there, and so was l."
"I was there, and so was she."
"The ambience too were lovely;
you know what I mean."
"Reached a place I never meant to go;
"It means I am in love!"
"I was there, and so was she."
"The ambience too were lovely;
you know what I mean."
"Reached a place I never meant to go;
"It means I am in love!"
"How I got lost in her words."
"I'll tell you about it
but let me catch my breath."
"How she got lost in my words."
"I'll tell you about it
but let me catch my breath."
"Messages aplenty
were conveyed through the eyes."
"I'll tell you about it
but let me catch my breath."
"I was there, and so was she."
"The ambience too were lovely;
you know what I mean."
"Reached a place I never meant to go;
"It means I am in love!"
"Mannu, love has struck you
but what about me now?"
"Two eyes fluttered so fast.."
"..when she turned behind
to look at me."
"As though she was telling me,
'Listen to me, young lad.'
"When I turned behind
to look at her."
"Two hearts then began
to beat so fast.."
"..when both of us turned behind
to look at each other."
"I was there, and so was she."
"The ambience too were lovely;
you know what I mean."
"Reached a place I never meant to go;
"It means I am in love!"
"Mannu, love has struck you
but what about me now?"
"Just a little."
"Just a little slowly she pulled."
"Then her sari,
just a little slowly I pulled."
"From sheer nervousness then,
Our hands we pulled."
"I was there, and so was she."
"The ambience too were lovely;
you know what I mean."
"Reached a place I never meant to go;
"It means I am in love!"
Is it true?
All of it is a lie!
When Renu gets married,
you'll long to eat such food.
You're absolutely right.
My dear, have you
heard of King Hardayal?
Why?
- He is coming home tomorrow.
- To meet you.
His younger brother,
Prince Prakashchand..
..will be returning
to India in some days.
He may be!
Hardayal says that
the boy is brilliant.
He looks good,
and is good-natured too.
Maybe.
I think he's worthy of you
in every respect.
What? So, were you
discussing my marriage?
Obviously! Uncle wants you
to become a princess.
So, have you fixed the marriage?
No, my child. How can I fix it
without your consent?
Meet Prakash first.
If you like him,
then give your consent.
But what's the hurry, father?
If your mother were alive,
she'd have got you married 4 years ago!
Father, I will not
marry a prince.
Meet him first.
I'm sure he will have all
the qualities that I dislike.
He may not have them either.
All rich people has false pride.
But you don't.
- Well said!
Explain to your friend.
I'll go and have a digestive pill.
You must be thrilled,
hearing about the prince?
You look as though
you're really angry.
I am!
I understand.
- My foot, you do!
"Uncle wants you
to become a princess!"
Fine. I'll tell uncle
that a prince won't do.
He should get you married
to a king instead!
You talk of marriage all the time!
Why are you after me?!
Why don't you
get married instead?!
O' God! I always keep dreaming
about it! When I'll get married?
Shall I tell you?
Marry the prince.
Nonsense! Even I don't like him.
Whom would you like?
- I like someone round.
Round?
- It'll be nice, won't it?
And he should be
a little dim-witted too.
Why?
Because nowadays the shrewd boys
will not be in your control.
I want a hen-pecked husband.
Very good.
I think you already have
some dim-witted boy in mind?
There are many.
In fact, it's getting difficult to select.
It's your turn now.
Shall I tell you?
Not now.
Who is disturbing me?
Excuse me, I'll just come!
Good morning, ma'am.
Where is everyone?
- It's the day off. No work today.
Where is Mannu?
- All of them are sleeping.
They are still sleeping?!
- They will wake up at 12.
Just shut up!
What impertinence is this!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I have important work with Mannu.
Go upstairs and take a left.
Mr. Mannu is sleeping there.
Oh I'm sorry! Come on!
Hey!
Wake up.
Did anybody see you?
How did you reach here?
Just the way you reached my house.
I got there by mistake.
- Even I got here by mistake.
If my brothers see you,
I'll be in deep trouble!
Are they also yet sleeping?!
Yes. Now's the chance,
so please leave!
I came to pay
five rupees twelve annas.
Forget the charges! Please go!
Why? When you'd come to my place,
you had created such a racket!
Today I will surely pay
five rupees twelve annas.
I'll be dead!
Help! Help!!
Help me, Mannu!
What happened?
- Something disastrous!
A lad... I mean, a lass
barged into my room!
Which lass?
- The petrol lass.
The petrol lass?
- Yes. She has barged into my room.
Excuse me.
I'll take the tea. You may leave.
Tea.
I knew you would
surely come someday.
I've been waiting for you
since so long.
Are you asleep or awake?
Tea.
What's the time?
9 O'clock.
You woke me very early.
Break my knuckles.
Come on!
You aren't doing it right!
Never mind.
Massage my back.
- No!
Why not?
Jaggu! Mannu! Mojha!
Why are you shouting?
I had come to pay the bill.
Which bill?
- For repairing my car.
Who are you?
- I am Renu.
Renu? Who's Renu?
Where are you from?
Jaggu, there's a girl in my room!
Run! Go to sleep!
Don't move.
- I won't.
Please move away. Jaggu!
Mannu! Get up! There is a big blunder!
- What happened?
There's someone
named Renu in my room.
Renu is a girl!
- A girl!
I don't know her.
- Me neither.
But how did
a girl get into my room?
Which girl?
- Who's the girl?
She's here to pay her bill.
But how did she get into my room?
How did she get there?
- Mannu, you know everything!
Do you know her?
- No! Yes, I do.
She owes us five rupees twelve annas.
- Oh, so you've called her here?
Why should I?
She must have come on her own.
How can such a big girl
come here uninvited?!
Exactly.
All of you seem troubled
because I'm here.
No. But you could have
paid the bill at the office.
I was sleeping and you came
upstairs. It's a holiday today.
Please listen to me.
- Sorry.
I had gone to your office.
But even there, a boy was dancing.
Even there?
She went to pay her bill at
the office and Mojha was dancing!
What audacity!
Bring my boxing gloves.
Forget it.
- How can I?
Excuse me. I have some work.
May I take Mannu along?
I don't like my brothers
going out with girls...
Whose picture is this?
- I found it in his room.
A girl!
- A girl's picture!
Show me!
- Let me see!
Give it here. It will tear.
But how did a girl's picture
reach my room?
It was on your bed.
- Fine. But on my bed?!
It was under your pillow.
- I know. But how?
Shall I burn it with Mobil Oil?
There's no need. I want to...
Take him along. I'll find out how
a girl's bed reached my pillow!
I mean, how a girl's picture was
found on my bed. I'll find out.
What's brother saying?
Mannu.. let's go.
Okay.
Everybody's gone?
I'll go to sleep!
Come out.
Madam, where have you brought me?
Stop being so formal.
- Sorry.
Hold the basket.
How is the place?
It's beautiful!
Madam, you...
- You're being formal again.
You mentioned that
you had some work?
I don't spot any car here.
So what will I repair?
Can't there be any work
other than repairing cars?
What else can there be?
- There can be many other jobs.
For instance?
- Will you be able to do it?
I can do anything.
Think about it.
- I have.
Suppose you can't?
- I'll concede defeat then.
Let's lay a bet.
- What?
If you lose, you'll have to
carry the basket, the entire day.
Basket?
Do you accept?
- I do. Tell me the job.
Let me think.
- Okay.
You see that?
Yes.
What's it?
- A hen.
Go and catch it.
- The hen?
Yes.
- That's no big deal!
Hold this.
"How's the gentleman feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
"How's the gentleman feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
"Soft breeze begins to blow;
your sari flutters to and fro."
"Let go of it and watch
the white and dark clouds."
"Soft breeze begins to blow;
your sari flutters to and fro."
"Let go of it and watch
the white and dark clouds."
"Your eyes convey messages
so conflicting."
"How's the gentleman feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
"Foolish girl, have you wondered
why we ever met."
"Foolish boy, why does every word
you say make my heart beat fast."
"Foolish girl, have you wondered
why we ever met."
"Foolish boy, why does every word
you say make my heart beat fast."
"Your eyes convey messages
so conflicting."
"How's the gentleman feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
"Should I spend every single day
with you this way?"
"I fail to fathom a thing
so how do I tell you anything?"
"Should I spend every single day
with you this way?"
"I fail to fathom a thing
so how do I tell you anything?"
"Your eyes convey messages
so conflicting."
"How's the lady feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
"How are you feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
"How's the gentleman feeling?"
"How do you think I'm feeling?"
"So zealous you appear."
"I was swept off my feet
so I slipped."
I win.
It was such a lovely day!
Time just flew!
I will always remember this day.
Let alone this day, I will
always remember this night too.
Why?
Only I know how much brother is
going to box me, once I get home.
Let's go. It's getting late.
- Are you so scared of them?
No, I'm not!
But I have to be scared.
Well, they love me very much,
and even I reciprocate that.
So I'm afraid that I may
do something to upset them.
Wow! What cool breeze!
Yes. What cool breeze!
What a beautiful place!
It's a lovely place!
So let's sit here for a while.
No! We'll get late!
No problem.
- You just don't understand.
It's 7 O'clock.
- Who cares!
Elder brother will...
I'll be in deep trouble!
Mannu, you haven't
understood a thing.
I understand everything!
- What do you understand?
That girls nowadays are lazy.
Once they sit, they don't get up!
Please hurry up. Please.
Mannu.
- Yes?
Nothing.
Mannu.
- Yes?
What are you thinking about?
- Nothing. But why?
It's nothing.
There's surely something.
Tell me.
Hey, tell me.
Shall I?
- Yes.
Mannu.
- Yes?
I'm getting married.
Married?
So you're getting married?
With which fool?
Not with a fool
but with a prince.
With a prince? That's obvious.
I think... you are a bit jealous.
Jealous? Why should I be jealous?
Girls do get married. And then,
I am glad you're marrying a prince.
The wedding will be held with splendor.
There will be feasts.
And... and...
And even I'll come.
You're happy?
I ought to be happy.
Of course, we won't be
able to meet this way then.
We won't have
the freedom to go out.
Is that all?
What else can there be?
I will get married and go away
to another man's house.
Aren't you feeling bad at all?
Yes... No.
No?
- No.
Not at all?
Not at all.
Renu.
Renu. Renu.
Mr. Kishanchand, if you give
your consent, I'll be at peace.
You have approached us with the
proposal. So how can I refuse?
But I must ask Renu once.
Sure. But I've already approved
of Renu for my younger brother.
Thank you.
I consider myself fortunate.
Exactly what I wanted to say.
We received many proposals
from royal families.
But all the other girls
paled in comparison with Renu.
By the way, when will Prakash
be returning from abroad?
Very soon. God willing, even you
will be as happy to see him..
..as I was, on seeing Renu.
Why not? After all, he is
your younger brother.
I'm not praising him
because he is my younger brother.
But because
he is a brilliant boy.
Renu, come here.
Meet King Hardayal Singh.
Hello, Renu!
Do you like the design?
Why did you bother?
Does one go empty-handed to fix a
marriage? It's only a small token.
Take it, dear. You tell her.
Take it, my dear. If that's what
he wants, how can we refuse him?
Thank you.
Father, may I...
- Yes, you may go now.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
In spite of being the daughter
of such a wealthy father..
..she is so gentle and coy.
They will make a good pair.
Can't you make out how changed
Mannu is from how he was at dawn?
No.
- Take this.
He's become a bit fat.
Rubbish! What are you thinking?
- Nothing.
You'd laugh over dinner daily...
- You'd create a din.
What's wrong?
I told you, it's nothing.
- Tell us what happened!
I told you, it's nothing!
- He says, it's nothing.
He's playing with fire!
Exactly! With fire?
- Yes!
I'd warned you not to
get involved with rich girls.
Exactly.
- You shut up!
They never stand by you. Continue
this way and you'll sulk forever!
And not eat.
- You eat your food!
But I disagree.
- About what?
That every rich girl is...
Mannu, you still
haven't seen the world.
Have you?
- No.
It's for your own good. Women are
the root cause of all troubles.
We should stay away from them!
Then why do you keep a
woman's picture with you?
I wasn't going to hide about it
from both of you.
I thought I'd tell you
at an opportune time.
You asked why I keep that picture.
It's because I loved that girl.
She was also
a beautiful and rich girl.
But I was an ordinary man then.
Therefore, she jilted me
for a man as rich as her.
The trauma of it still hurts.
If not for both of you,
I may have taken a drastic step.
Perhaps even killed myself.
I only want to say that I don't
want you to get hurt like me.
You will not be able to bear it.
Eat your dinner.
"I'm yours."
"Come and see for yourself."
"If you're not convinced
then ask my heart."
"I'm yours."
"When two hearts meet.."
"..what can the world do, my love?"
"..the world will burn
with envy, my love."
"When two hearts meet.."
"..what can the world do, my love?"
"..the world will burn
with envy, my love."
"If you wish,
walk a few steps with me and see."
"If you're not convinced
then ask my heart."
"I'm yours."
"Come and see for yourself."
"The unbridled joys
that love can bring."
"Hearing about it
will make you so oblivious."
"The unbridled joys
that love can bring."
"You will begin to fathom."
"The unbridled joys
that love can bring."
"Hearing about it
will make you so oblivious."
"The unbridled joys
that love can bring."
"You will begin to fathom."
"Let your heart be restless
just the way mine is."
"If you're not convinced
then ask my heart."
"I'm yours."
"Come and see for yourself."
"The one who truly loves you.."
"..cannot be afraid of sorrows."
"will never whimper a protest."
"The one who truly loves you.."
"..cannot be afraid of sorrows."
"will never whimper a protest."
"If you wish
tear apart my heart and see."
"If you're not convinced
then ask my heart."
"I'm yours."
"Come and see for yourself."
Fantastic!
Shut the door,
and don't let anybody inside.
How come you've returned so soon?
Rajasaheb, Ramlal has been
arrested with the diamonds!
There's no need to worry.
Sit down.
The diamonds were fake.
- What!
I didn't know. I was scared...
Prakash! You still don't know me.
I think of the future.
So, did you suspect that
Ramlal would get caught?
I didn't suspect, I was sure.
I wanted to see how shrewd he is.
Now that he's in jail, we know
that he is of no use to us.
Suppose he reveals about us
to the police, then?
No. He wouldn't dare.
Why?
Because I have promised
to look after his children.
Whether he gets
imprisoned or divulges.
Rajasaheb, you are very far-sighted.
Anyway...
Look at this picture.
How is she?
Extremely beautiful.
She's a golden goose.
She's the only daughter of a rich father.
Have you heard of Mr. Kishanchand?
He can buy many rich men like you!
Yes, but he suffers from
blood pressure problems.
You seem to be plotting a new scheme?
I've already plotted.
From now on, you are my
younger brother, Prince Prakashchand.
Really?
Only for this job.
Acting!
No problem.
What do I have to do?
Get married.
To her?
- Yes.
You are abroad now, and will
return after a couple of days.
You will then be introduced to Renu.
Within a month, you'll have to
impress Renu and her father so much..
..that they will not consider
anyone else but you..
..as being worthy of her husband.
Okay. Then?
- You'll get married!
I understand! Then, Renu's
father will suddenly die..
..and all his wealth
will be mine.
Not all, only half of it.
So be it.
As far as I know, you have
tried such a scheme earlier too.
Indeed. I did get 7- 8 lakhs
from Kamini's father.
Did your father-in-law also
have a blood pressure problem?
No. He was a heart patient.
What are you thinking?
It's nothing. I was wondering..
..why you make such schemes when
you have wealth in abundance?
Prakash, once you acquire wealth,
you will understand.
It's the wealthy
who lust for more wealth.
The hungry need only food.
And if we don't usurp their
wealth, someone else will.
After all, we aren't the
only intelligent men around.
Rajasaheb! Madam has
escaped from her room!
How?!
She attacked the woman who
went to her room with the food.
Move.
- Let me go!
Leave me.
- Kamini!
How did she come downstairs?
All of you leave!
Let me go!
Kamini! You're getting more and
more insane by the day! Come on!
I am not insane! Let me go!
All crazy people say that.
No, I am not crazy.
- Come on, Kamini.
I won't go there! I'm scared!
- Go to your room.
I hate you! Leave me!
- Come upstairs!
Come upstairs!
- No!
No!!
Come on.
- Let me go!
Get up, Kamini!
- No!
No!
- Come on!
Leave me. I am not crazy.
Leave me.
Sit down quietly!
Why should I?
I am not afraid of you.
Kamini!
I don't fear your threats anymore.
You can't silence me anymore.
I will tell the world
that you are a murderer.
You poisoned father to death.
Kamini! Do not forget who I am.
I can never forget that.
I can never forget the manager
who betrayed us.
Wretch! My father was ready
to get me married to Brijmohan.
But you held me captive that very day
and poisoned my father.
And when I refused to marry you,
you claimed that I was crazy.
I can never forget the atrocities
inflicted on me since 10 years.
I will surely seek vengeance!
Kamini!
- Leave me! Let go of me!
She's getting madder by the day!
It isn't safe to keep her here.
Lock her in her father's empty house.
She can scream there
as much as she wants to.
Okay, boss.
Well, you've been
introduced to each other now.
Sit and talk.
I'll go and meet my solicitor.
Bye.
Goodnight, sir.
- Goodnight.
Your house is extremely splendid!
Pardon?
- Thank you.
You are quiet again.
What do I talk about?
Well... about anything.
All right.
Your coat material is good.
- I beg your pardon?
Did you like it?
I bought it abroad.
I can see that.
- What?
Made in England.
You aren't mocking me, are you?
What! Do you think
I'm so impertinent?
No! You appear quite interesting.
Whatever Rajasaheb told me about you
was nothing in comparison.
Ms. Renu, what are your hobbies?
Riding.
- Very good.
Swimming.
- Excellent.
Especially, motor driving.
Marvellous.
Even my hobbies are the same!
I've brought my new car.
What do you mean?
Let's go for a drive.
Let's go out somewhere.
My friend will be here at 8:30.
But it's only 8 O'clock now.
We will be back in half an hour.
Come on.
Please.
Hey, you look so uncomfortable.
Relax. Sit comfortably.
We should get to
know each other, right?
You are absolutely right.
You're very sensible.
You're no less.
Thank you.
One won't find a sensible girl
like you in the whole continent!
Have you searched?
Even if I tried,
I wouldn't find one!
I hope you don't mind the speed?
How fast can you drive?
I'm driving at 60 kms/hour.
I can take it up to 80.
I can drive faster.
You're very smart.
But if you want to see how fast
I drive, come tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
- Yes. At Juhu airport.
A motor racing is going to be held.
Even I have enlisted my name
for motor racing.
If you come, I'll surely win.
You will come, won't you?
Yes, I will have to come now.
Or you will not win!
Mannu, your work is over.
Then why are you waiting here?
For no reason.
- Really?
I know why!
- Why?
What's the use of sulking?
Go and meet her.
I won't!
You are hopeless! Come back in a jiffy.
Brother will never know.
You will tell him everything!
- That's the problem, Mannu.
I can't keep things to myself.
I try to please brother and you.
You are the youngest.
I love you so much. It's such a problem!
Brother is coming.
It's such a problem!
- What's the problem?
Nothing as such... Renu's phone...
Hadn't I warned you?
- Brother!
Did I say a thing?!
It must be Renu.
Hello, Mohan Garage.
Renu? Wait.
It's some other girl.
Hello. Pardon?
Whom do you want to speak to?
Jagmohan? It's your call.
Jagmohan? How can that be?
Which girl would phone me?
Hello.
- This is Sheela here.
Sheela!
- Sheela?
Chevrolet.
What are you saying?
An emergency case of a Chevrolet!
It is an emergency case
of a Chevrolet.
Hello! I's an emergency
case of a Chevrolet car!
Hello?
- Let me talk.
Which Chevrolet car, and whose?
Emergency? What are you talking
about? What's wrong with you?
Nothing.. what's wrong with your car?
My car?
My car is fine, gentleman.
But are you feeling fine?
Pardon?
You had said that
you would take me out?
Yes, I did.
Move aside!
What are you doing today?
We are very busy today,
so I will not be able to come.
Why don't you come to the car
race tomorrow at the airdrome?
Meet me there. I'll repair
your car... your Chevrolet there.
You will meet me, won't you?
Very good. Please do come.
Brother Jaggu, what kind of
an emergency case is this?
Emergency is emergency.
Hey!
- You!
We could have come together.
I didn't know you were also coming.
I had to come for Mr. Prakash.
But what are you doing here?
My round, chubby man is here.
- Where is he?!
Do you see that old car?
That's him near it.
Hey! So, even they are here?
That's fantastic!
Hail Lord Hanuman!
Pay your respects.
Best of luck.
Brother Jaggu!
Look, what's happened!
- What's wrong?
Push it.
Hey, move back!
Hey, my cap! Give my cap.
Here, take your cap.
Mannu!
The first prize this year
goes to Manmohan Sharma.
Hip Hip Hurray!
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
Renu.
Thank you.
How are you, Renu?
- So you did recognise me?
How could I not?
- I thought you'd forgotten me.
How can I?
I thought you were angry and
would call once you calmed down.
Even you could have phoned!
- I could.
But then I feared that
you would get more furious.
I am crazy, am I not?
- Yes. No!
Renu, well actually...
I've not been able to understand
you and your moods.
Well, you talk that way!
- I promise it won't happen again.
But please don't get angry.
Hold your ears once again.
- Here!
Mr. Prakash, I suppose
I wasn't lucky for you.
Mannu won the prize instead.
- Manmohan.
I forgot the introductions.
Manmohan... He's Prince..
Prakashchand.
He is the prince
about whom I'd mentioned.
Prince?
Glad to meet you.
Let's go. We're getting late.
Okay. Bye, Mannu.
- Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Renu!
I was looking for you,
and you were here.
Renu, this is important!
- What is it?
Let's go somewhere else.
Excuse me. I'll be back soon.
- Let's go.
Renu, has your marriage
been fixed with this prince?
Yes. Don't you like him?
I may be mistaken, but he's
the prince of which realm?
How would I know!
Are you blindly marrying him?
- Yes. Why?
No! Please don't marry him.
I had told you the other day
itself that you're a bit jealous. - No.
However, you had disagreed.
But it's turned out to be true.
Yes. No, you don't understand.
I do.
I think I had seen him dumping
Lalchand's body the other day.
Yes.
What are you saying, Mannu!
- The truth, Renu.
The same looks, the same style.
And the same hairstyle.
Enough, Mannu! Water!
Water, please!
Coca Cola.
Renu.
Renu, are you all right?
Are you sure?
Absolutely, Renu.
I never forget faces all my life!
Mannu, let's inform the police.
- Okay.
No, wait. If you're wrong,
we'll get into trouble.
So what do we do?
- What do we do?
I know! We should become spies.
Yes!
- Good idea?
He's looking our way.
- Who?
We must follow him on the sly.
Don't move your hand so much.
And we must find out
what exactly he does.
You'll be with me, won't you?
- Of course.
All right, as soon as I
get a chance, I'll phone you.
Won't your brothers object?
- In this matter, I don't care!
Very good.
Don't feel nervous.
- Ofcourse not.
Bye, Mannu.
- Bye.
Spies!
I am a spy.
What's happening?
Brother Jaggu, in love?
Well, won't you
introduce me to her?
What are you doing here?
Let's go home!
Your friend?
You befriend an ordinary mechanic?
What's wrong with that?
But I certainly
do not approve of it!
However, I like it.
- But I don't approve of..
..you joking around with
an ordinary mechanic in public.
I didn't know
you were so petty-minded.
And I didn't know
you were so shameless.
Shut up.
Who are you to say such things?!
Your future husband!
Future husband! But you aren't!
And you never will be!
Why were you introduced to Renu?
Well...
- For business.
And not to fall in love with her.
You can get plenty of girls
but not a rich girl like Renu.
If you do want to fall in love,
then it will be done my way.
You will get Renu,
and I will get the wealth.
Well, Mr. Kumar,
learn from my experiences.
Wow! It's beautiful!
But, son, such expensive gifts...
It's not my fault. Rajasaheb has
personally chosen it and sent it.
This is not fair.
I'll speak to him about it.
It's a gift,
so it can't even be returned.
My dear, please accept them.
Sir, the car is ready.
- Please keep these upstairs.
Renu, sit with him. I have
some important work to attend to.
Okay, bye.
Please sit.
- After you, please.
I think you're angry with me?
No, I am not. Why?
I apologise for whatever
I said after the car race.
I came here to say that I'm sorry.
Sorry?
I didn't take it to heart at all.
Really? And I was worried sick,
wondering what you'd be thinking.
How sweet of you!
Permit me to leave now.
Are you leaving already?
Yes, I have some important work.
Please sit for a while.
I surely would.
But somebody is waiting for me.
Won't you stay
even at my request?
Let me go today.
- Fine.
Then I'll assume that you're
the one who's angry with me.
How can I be angry with you?
Then sit down. Just a minute.
Please.
Thank you.
Hello? Mohan Brother's Garage.
Who's speaking?
Renu! It's a girl? I'll be dead!
Sir, there's a girl on the line.
A girl?
Hello?
Renu?
- He's here.
He's there?
- And he wants to leave right now.
Don't. Keep him engrossed.
I'll be there in 5 minutes.
Come soon.
- I'll be there in a jiffy.
How will I know?
I'll park my car a little away
from your house and honk twice.
Okay?
- All right.
I'm sorry, but I'm getting late.
"Hey you!
Please wait awhile."
"What's the hurry?"
"Thorns of separation
will prick me all the while."
"Hey you!
Please wait awhile."
"What's the hurry?"
"Thorns of separation
will prick me all the while."
"Twilight descends
and you get set to go, beloved."
"For my sake
don't go away from me."
"Twilight descends
and you get set to go, beloved."
"For my sake
don't go away from me."
"My love, don't be so unjust."
"I'm a girl so delicate."
"Hey you!
Please wait awhile."
"What's the hurry?"
"Thorns of separation
will prick me all the while."
"I want to tell you so many things,
so let me say it all."
"This heart full of love holds
many things, so let me say it all."
"I want to tell you so many things,
so let me say it all."
"This heart full of love holds
many things, so let me say it all."
"Wait awhile, my love,
let me come to my senses."
"Since the time you've come,
I've been a little lost."
"Hey you!
Please wait awhile."
"What's the hurry?"
"Thorns of separation
will prick me all the while."
"Just think,
what I am receiving for loving you."
"Just think, my love
a thousand deaths I die."
"Just think,
what I am receiving for loving you."
"Just think, my love
a thousand deaths I die."
"Wait awhile
don't break my heart."
"But a man who spurns love
will never give this a thought."
"Hey you!
Please wait awhile."
"What's the hurry?"
"Thorns of separation
will prick me all the while."
"Hey you!
Please wait awhile."
"What's the hurry?"
"Thorns of separation
will prick me all the while."
You're interesting!
I'm not sure you'll give me a place
I deserve in your heart.
You're getting late.
- No, I'm not.
Even if all of the beautiful
girls in the world beckon me..
..I wouldn't be
willing to leave you now.
No?
How sweet.
But you'd said that you
have some important work.
Yes, I did have work but
that work can be done tomorrow.
No. I don't want your work
to suffer because of me.
Your work is important.
Don't bother about me, I'll wait.
You are asking me to leave?
- Yes. No!
I mean, I hope there are
opportunities like this again!
And that I get
a chance to stop you again!
How sweet, Renu!
How sweet of you.
You are so nice!
I just don't feel like going.
Even I don't want you to go.
Okay, bye.
- Bye bye.
Renu.
- Yes?
1Stop saying my name
and say something!
Do you think he suspects
that we're following him?
Suspects? How's that possible?
Look! He's driving slowly now.
- You too slow down.
We must keep a safe distance.
If he turns, he'll recognise us.
You shouldn't have come with me.
- Why?
He can recognise you from afar.
- But how can he, in this car?!
You're beautiful and it is
hard to hide a beautiful face.
That's enough.
He can recognize you too.
How?
- He's seen you at the car race.
Oh yes!
What are you doing? There will be
an accident. Please don't honk.
What to do? He'll recognise me!
You make me also nervous!
Renu... look at me now.
He won't recognise me now.
Even I cannot recognise you!
Don't laugh or we'll get into trouble.
Do one thing... Don't laugh!
Change your appearance.
How do I do that?
I have an extra set of clothes.
Wear them.
How can I wear your clothes?
Don't joke! We'll be in trouble.
Please go.
Don't laugh!
CPV65!
Renu!
- Yes?
Have you worn them?
Hurry up. Don't laugh!
Renu!
Don't look behind!
I've worn the clothes.
Hey, you'll cause an accident!
Come in the front.
What are you doing?
Hey! He has stopped the car.
You also do the same.
Okay.
Mannu, he's entered the lane.
What we do now?
Let's follow him.
- Okay.
Don't! If he comes back,
then it'll be a big problem.
What do we do then?
- What do we do?
We'll wait here.
- All right.
What's wrong?
- Someone is following me!
Police?
I don't know. But we should be alert.
Where is my disguise?
I'll get it.
I'd like to know who they are.
The car looks familiar.
Is everything in there?
Where is it?
You go and stand next to my car.
I'll disguise myself
and see who they are.
We have to unload the goods.
I hope the plan doesn't get foiled.
Don't worry. I'll tackle
them in a jiffy! Be ready.
Okay. And then, we'll go there.
It's been so long
but he still hasn't returned.
I don't think he will come now.
What!
His car is here.
Why won't he come?
Renu, it's possible
that their hideout is here.
Yes!
They must be surely
having a meeting.
Let's inform the police soon.
- Come on!
Police. Police.
Police.
Mannu, he is an insane.
What's happening?
Renu!
What's wrong?
- The tyre is punctured!
Oh no!
Hey, the car is leaving!
You haven't slept as yet?
Where were you?
- I had gone out.
I asked, where were you?
- I had some important work.
You go out with a girl at 1 a.m.
And tell me, it was important!
A girl?
- Didn't that girl phone you?
And hadn't I asked you
not to go?!
Then why did you go?
Answer me!
Our opinions about girls
do not match.
Look at the way he talks!
- Mannu, speak politely!
You back answer me!
- No.
I'll smash your teeth!
You can smash my teeth
but you can't snatch my freedom!
So you won't heed me?
- Not if you're wrong!
I'll box your head!
- Please don't fight.
Bring my boxing gloves.
- Gloves!
Wonderful sport!
I won't fight!
- Indeed! You're only a kid!
You're afraid! You can
only roam out with girls!
Brother! If you challenge me,
I will surely fight!
Gloves.
- Gloves.
Since you are a boxing champion,
you will use only one hand.
Give him the gloves!
Mannu, don't lose this opportunity.
Use both your hands.
I'm going.
So, kid, are you ready?
Ready.
- Ready.
Mannu, brother knows the rules.
Let me explain them to you.
Below the belt is a foul.
Come on shake hands.
Ready?
Start.
You threw brother down!
Wow! Very good!
Will you meet that girl again?
- I will!
Now say, will you meet her?
Very good.
I'll be dead!
You dare hit the referee!
You're disqualified! He hit me!
Not here. He's over there.
Two.. three.. four..
Greetings.
- Greetings.
Please take a seat.
- You sit.
Please sit.
- You sit. I want to talk to you.
What's your name? I forgot.
Renu.
Renu, please try to understand
whatever I'm going to say.
Okay.
You know, we are 3 brothers.
I have raised both of them.
They have always respected me
but today he didn't heed me.
I'm talking about Mannu.
And you are responsible.
Me?
- Sit down.
You are wealthy
and want to enjoy life.
But I don't want you to
enjoy at my brother's expense.
What?
- Listen to me first.
He is immature. His life could
get ruined... Let me finish.
Therefore, I want you
to stop meeting him.
That's it.
Did you come, only to say this?
It's not a petty matter for me.
- Neither is it for me!
I have never enjoyed
myself at Mannu's cost.
I know why you're saying this.
- What do you know?!
A girl jilted you and hurt you!
But it does not mean that
all girls are the same!
When the time comes,
I will prove it!
All girls are the same!
Well, I don't want to argue with you!
All I want is for you
to stop meeting Mannu!
Would that make you happy?
I'm not talking of my happiness.
- Will Mannu be happy?
If it makes Mannu happy,
then I will never meet him.
Listen!
I could never understand women
nor explain to them!
I had asked you to understand me
but you have begun to cry.
Well, I love my brothers very much.
If Mannu ever gets hurt the way
I did, then I'll go crazy!
You know I am a boxer,
and I think like one too.
I guess I had a wrong impression
about you.
Wipe your tears.
I forgot your name again.
- Renu.
Renu, don't tell Mannu that I had
come here to discuss all this.
He's my younger brother.
He will feel bad.
And...
And that's all. I'm leaving.
Do what you please.
You needn't touch my feet.
It's indeed very unfair!
Big brother is a boxer.
He can box us whenever he pleases.
What can we younger brothers do?
Well, if a girl and a boy meet,
what's wrong in that?
And suppose
they come home late..
..does it mean they should
get beaten? That's wrong!
Will you remain silent?
- All right!
How can I remain silent?
But why did you get late?
The tyre got punctured.
- Oh, I see!
Get lost!
The tyre got puncture, indeed!
Tell me what happened?
I won't tell anyone.
Please tell me.
Why did you get late?
Shall I?
- Yes.
Let brother come. I'll tell him,
you were asking me all this!
Why involve him?
This is unsporting.
I'll tell him everything.
- You are being rude.
Let brother come,
I'll tell him everything.
Brother, he...
- He...
You keep quiet! You tell me.
This is unfair. Is it right
to go out with girls at night?
But why are you after him?
- I am not.
You were the one who'd asked us
not to get involved with girls...
Hello. Mohan motor garage.
Yes? Renu.
Shall I tell her
that she can't talk to him?
Give him the phone.
Wait! Brother, you had said
that we mustn't talk to girls.
I say, give him the phone!
Hello! Hello!
Yes, it's me.
But I have
some important work here.
What's she saying?
She says that she has important
work and wants me to come there.
You can't go, Mannu!
Why can't he go?! He will go!
May I go?
- Yes.
Hello. I'm coming. Wait for me.
You're gone. Where do I go?
Then what happened?
- I stopped my car.
I disguised myself and went back
to check. What I saw, shocked me!
Renu and the motor mechanic
were in the car!
Renu and that boy?
- Yes.
But why were they following you?
- That's what I don't understand.
They must have had some doubt.
What could be the reason?
Anyway, we must stay alert.
Boss! It's the same car.
So they've reached even here.
It means, they're following you.
Prakash, go to the
house in Versova.
I'll make some phone calls
and join you soon.
And let them follow you.
Okay boss.
It's been so long! Neither is
anyone going in nor coming out!
I think they must be
doing their work at night.
And sleeping till late
in the morning.
You reached home late last night.
Did your elder brother scold you?
Yes.
- What did he say?
No, he didn't say a thing.
He didn't scold you? Not at all?
- No.
I was sure your brother would be
furious that you'd returned late.
Nothing happened. I went home,
ate well and went to sleep.
Really?
- Yes.
In that case, your brother is not
how you describe him to be.
Have you seen a coconut?
- Yes, I have.
My brother is
just like a coconut.
Hard from outside,
soft from within.
A car is coming.
Stay alert.
Renu
- Yes?
Renu!
Are you nervous once again?
- No, I'm not. What do we do now?
Let's go in. We'll get
more information from inside.
Fine, but...
He opened the lock and went in.
So it's obvious that he's alone.
But, Renu...
- Are you so scared?
I'm not afraid for myself
but for you!
He's alone, and we are two of us.
Let's go. - Okay.
Renu, this place looks haunted.
It does seem
as though nobody lives here.
Then where did that man go?
- Where did he go?
What's happening?
It seems as if
somebody is walking upstairs.
What do we do now?
- Let's go there.
Leave us.
- Leave us.
Take them upstairs
and tie them up firmly!
Leave us!
Brother Jaggu! Help us!
Brother Jaggu! Help!
Help!
- Help!
Hello boss!
Good luck Prakash.
- All the best, sir.
I have had both of them
tied in the room upstairs.
Good! Did anybody follow you?
Prakash.
- Yes?
Will you get married?
- To Renu?!
Right now?
- I am ready.
Fetch the registrar. And yes,
we'll need Mr. Kishanchand too.
Anyway, I'll call him.
Leave now, while I go and talk to them.
Okay boss.
I hope you were
looked after properly?
Yes, we were.
Hey, I've seen you somewhere!
Renu! Why did you need
to disguise yourself?
Oh! I understand.
You like the prince
so much that you can't stay...
I hate the very sight of him!
But how can that be?
You will be getting married to him.
She has no intentions of
getting married to a murderer!
Murderer? What do you mean?
Your brother is a murderer!
- Mohan!
Who says so?
- I say so.
Who's he?
Oh! So, he is your lover?
Shut up!
Don't laugh. I can take
your brother to the gallows!
How is that?
I saw him dumping
Lalchand's dead body out of the car.
Mohan!
Mohan.
Your life is over now.
No! Spare him! I promise,
he won't say a word to anyone!
Renu!
- Quiet! Please!
If you want to save his life,
then marry Prakash.
What! Never!
I'd consider it better to die
than to marry that wretched man!
Correct! Don't bother
about his threats!
You will get married
to Prakash tonight itself.
And if you don't agree,
you will be coerced into it.
I give you 15 minutes to think.
By then, even your father
will be here.
My father?
- Yes.
He will come here
to bless the couple.
Understand?
Wretched man!
Now what?
That rogue won't spare me alive!
Please don't say that.
You've got into trouble because of me.
No, Renu. It's my fault.
If I hadn't let you come here,
we wouldn't have got into trouble.
Mohan, is there no way
we can escape from here?
No, we can't.
- We can't?
What are you thinking of?
If we are destined to die,
then let's die together.
But why do you want to die?
What will I do
living without you?
Without me?
I don't quite understand, Renu.
I'd thought you do understand.
I often thought of telling you.
But I couldn't!
And you are saying now
when we are going to die.
Mannu.
Renu.
- Yes?
I don't want to die now.
It's easy to get trapped
but very difficult to escape.
Who are you?
- Me?
Like you, I too have been trapped
in the clutches of these demons!
How?
- What's the use of hearing it?
It's a very long story.
But who are you?
I am Mr. Kishanchand's daughter Renu.
You're the only child, right?
Yes. Help us. This cruel man is
forcing me to marry his brother.
Marry?
I understand.
He was successful once.
And he's playing the same trick again.
I have seen you somewhere.
Me? Where?
I don't remember.
But I have surely seen you.
Surely?
Nobody has seen me
since the last 10 years.
I have been in captivity
since 10 years.
Since 10 years,
no one ever heard my pleas.
And you claim
that you have seen me?
You are crazy!
I remembered! The picture!
Mannu, the picture!
She resembles the woman in it!
- Which picture?
The picture that I'd found under
your brother Brijmohan's pillow.
Brijmohan!
Do you know him?
- He is his younger brother.
Are you his brother?
Yes, you do look like him.
Where is he?
Mohan's Garage. Queen's Road.
Help us. Please release us.
All right, I'll untie you.
I think someone is coming.
Don't worry. The moment I get a chance,
I'll come to untie you.
Come.
This way, please.
Upstairs.
Welcome!
- You here?
How's Renu?
- She is fine.
But which hospital is this?
This is a house, not a hospital.
But they told me that Renu
had met with a car accident.
And that she is in hospital.
Please sit down.
There's no need to worry.
But I don't understand why they
brought me here like this.
We thought your presence was
needed on this joyous occasion.
Joyous occasion?
What are you talking about?
I am getting Prakash
married to Renu.
What! How can that be possible?
I'm sorry but we were
forced to rush things up.
I have called the magistrate.
But I still don't know
what is Renu's wish!
I do. And I also know that
you cannot live without her.
Therefore, I've made arrangements
for you to live with Renu.
What's happening? Where is Renu?!
Renu?
- Yes.
Bring Renu.
She'll be here soon.
You are our guest.
You will be looked after properly.
You will only have to
take a little trouble.
You can't leave from here.
That's no big deal.
You'll get used to it in a few days.
Please be seated.
Excuse me! Is Brijmohan here?
Yes, he is working.
Can I help you?
Could you please call him?
Do hurry. It's urgent.
All right.
Brother!
What's the matter, Jaggu?
Any news about Mannu?
Did you recognise me?
After 10 years...
You must have never thought
that you'd see me in this state.
You must have never even thought
how I spent these 10 years.
Well, never mind.
Come with me quickly.
With you?
- I'm not saying this for myself.
Your brother is in danger.
Manmohan?
What's happened to him?
There's no time to answer. Hurry!
Get the car.
Renu.
- Daddy.
My dear!
Daddy.
These goons brought you too here?
- Yes, my child. Don't worry.
Daddy, they are rogues
and very dangerous!
Yes, now I know that too.
But it's no use now.
It will be in your good
to get Renu married to Prakash.
Never! I will never let
my child marry a scoundrel!
If you love Renu, you'll surely
let the wedding take place.
Never!
Good girls don't go against
the wishes of their fathers.
Your father is going
to get you married.
Never! I won't get my daughter
married without her consent!
You won't?
- No!
Daddy! Daddy!
Leave my daddy!
I say, leave him!
Say yes!
- Don't, Renu!
Leave him!
- Don't, Renu! Certainly don't!
Two gallons of petrol, please.
- Yes, madam.
Two gallons of petrol. Hurry!
- Coming, sir.
I've understood
everything, Kamini.
And today, after 10 years,
I'm glad that I was wrong about you.
Hurry up.
- Yes sir.
You?
What happened?
Rustom.
I'll count three and
give you time to think.
The answer should be positive or
a bullet will be fired... there.
Start thinking.
One!
Two!
- Wait! Say yes, my child.
Or this poor boy will
unnecessarily lose his life.
Don't, Renu! Don't!
Don't, Renu!
- Yes!
Very good!
Take him over there.
Stop crying now
and listen to me carefully.
Some documents are coming.
Quietly sign that documents.
Or this poor boy..
..will be killed.
Mannu.
Brother!
- Beware!
Stop!
Come on!
Hail Lord Hanuman!
Damn you!
Mannu, it's me!
Where am I?
- Mannu!
You betrayed me!
You cheat!
No! Don't!
- No?
Careful!
Stop!
Now who will save you?
- Brother! Let's run!
Sit down, and stop screaming.
Let me put some iodine.
It will be all right.
O' God! What a nasty cut!
It's all because of you.
First, you hurt me and then
soothe it with iodine. Let go!
I am dead!
Sir, can I say something?
- Yes?
I think Mannu and Renu shouldn't be
separated. If you don't object...
If they're willing, no one can stop
the bride and groom from being one!
Why should I object?
- That's right.
Brother, what about me?
What happened to you?
You've got your love.
Mannu too has found his love.
What about me?
Ask her.
Listen... brother wants to know
if you will... marry me.
If you don't marry me, I'll be
left alone. Don't leave me alone.
Tell brother and everyone
that you love me.
Stop it!
She says, stop it!
It means yes.
Yes? Come on!
Hey, leave me!
- I won't!
Shameless boy! You hold a
girl's hand in front of me?
Have you decided?
- Yes.
Are you happy?
- Yes, I am.
Then let's go home.
- Really?
May I bring her along?
- Yes, you may.
Come on.
That's enough, my son.
Go, my dear.
"Always stay together like this."
"United we stand,
Divided we fall."
"If problems are strewn your way
with a brave face, challenge it."
"If huge hurdles block your way,
together move it aside."
"The one who fathoms this
achieves success."
"Move aside."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."
"The honk hoots aloud
so move aside."
"What's mobile here is called a car."