Friends,
we have finally come
with Overlays Clothing haul
The first package has come to us
There is lot of improvement in the brand
and these improvements
will blow your mind
Firstly,
the stiff package
has become shiny and polished
Also, if we talk about the sweatshirt inside it,
this time
they have done amazing work on the material
You get the tag of Overlays
The pricing is written here as
Rs. 1599
You don't have to pay this
You can see, what you have to pay on its website
The sweatshirt is in black colour
Hem at the bottom,
cuffing in the hand,
round neck,
all these things are common
You get fur on the inside
Overall, if we talk about its fabric,
the fabric is like Lalu Yadav
I mean, the fabric is very soft
Mulayam Singh Ji,
don't get angry
If you see at its left chest,
Overlays branding has been done in white colour
But the special thing about this sweatshirt
is its back print
A very beautiful bird
has been designed in multiple colours
whose feathers are very big
And the quality of the print
is also looking very good
It is a bit embossed this time
At the bottom,
Rise Overlays is written here
Simple in the front,
Twinkle at the back
And, it looks amazing
The quality is good
Let's quickly go towards the next
You can see me wearing it, at the back
Alright, the next product has come to us
It is another very beautiful black colour hoodie
The designing is same
You get hem at the bottom
and cuffing in the hands
You get a large hood
and kangaroo pockets in the front
Truly this time,
the material is of very good quality
If we talk about the sizing of the hood,
the hood is quite large
You get lining on the inside
Well, its drawstring
seems very weak
It seems that
by taking out the lays from Overlays,
this lace has been made
which you can eat too
In the front,
you get same white colour Overlays branding
or logo
And that's it
This is the only simple designing in it
Basically,
it is a black coloured solid hoodie
The quality is very good
How am I looking on wearing it,
you have seen this
Let's quickly go to the next product
Alright, the next product has come to us
And it's a very beautiful sweatshirt
Shlok has used many beautiful colours this time
Truly,
I had planned for all these sweatshirts
or this haul a month and a half ago
And a month and a half ago,
we ordered all these products
So much delay
Even if I order clothes from America,
then also it will not be delayed so much
Now, either Shlok's clock is slow
or Overlays has become Overdelays
I don't know this
And this did not happen only with me
Basically, many of you faced this problem
Well, if we talk about this particular sweatshirt,
the material is very good
Hem at the bottom,
cuffing in the hand, round neck,
all these things are common
The quality of the fur on the inside
is very good
On the left chest,
you will get the branding of Overlays here
but this time in black colour
It also has amazing back print
All the beauty lies at the back
Here, you can see,
Overlays is written like this
and there is a purple colour snake
which has flowers on it
Maybe this snake eats manure,
that is why
flowers are coming out of its body parts
Although,
the quality of the print is very good
And it looks amazing
Definitely,
they have not compromised in terms of quality
How am I looking on wearing it,
you can see this at the back
You can see the fitting
I have taken L size
and my height is around 5'11
Alright, next product has come to us
in a beautiful and shiny
packet of sweets
When they launched these winterwears,
then Shlok actually said that
they will make such products
that will give competition to international brands
in terms of quality
and are also at very cheap prices
This has truly happened to some extent
but the problems that the customer had to face
are of next to next level
There is one more problem
I will tell you that later
Well, if we talk about this hoodie,
this whole hoodie is made of fur
You will get to see some off-white in it
and you get black beneath it
You get kangaroo pockets in the front
and hem at the bottom
Everything is similar to a normal hoodie
If you see on its left chest,
you will get to see a metal plate
in which the branding of Overlays
has been done
But if we talk about its upper fabric
or if we talk about its fur basically,
Oh my God,
Truly,
it is very soft,
smooth
and makes you feel very cosy
when you hold it
How am I looking on wearing it,
you can see this at the back
Let's quickly go towards the next
Alright, the next product has come to us
It is another very beautiful sweatshirt
which comes in an amazing colour
i.e. in lavender colour
If we talk about this sweatshirt,
the fabric and quality are same,
everything is same
On the left chest,
you get the same branding of Overlays
which has been done through rubber coating
On the inside,
the fur quality and everything else
is very good
and you don't get anything at the back
It is a solid lavender colour sweatshirt
If I say straight,
if this Overdelays brand
is covering Pan India,
they should be ready for these problems
beforehand
they should not launch the products
so late in winter
because they will surely earn
because all the orders
have already been placed
Those who prepaid for their orders,
I had also prepaid for my orders,
I unknowingly wrote in the community post
that I had not prepaid
but actually,
I came to know afterwards
that I had also prepaid
So, all that money
was stuck for one and a half months
and we did not receive any product
And now what has happened,
I will tell you that later
Well, you have seen me wearing this sweatshirt
Let's quickly go towards the next
We will talk about this further
Alright, next we had ordered a track pant
When we started this haul,
we ordered total 8 products
Till the end,
even after one and a half months,
the result was
that only 7 products were delivered,
they gave refund for one of the product
Well, if we talk about this particular sweatshirt,
its fabric is same
as the fabric of a hoodie
It is as soft as Mulayam Singh Yadav
from the inside as well as outside
On the left side,
you get the branding of Overlays
which is in white colour
The depth of the pocket is good
It is good
It is not very deep
nor it is very small
It has the same poor drawstrings
which could have been better
The quality of the waist is very good
The fur on the inside are same
as hoodies
And definitely,
it is a good pant
Even if you want,
you cannot go for it
You cannot go for it because
it is out of stock
When I thought of making this video,
if it would have been available at that time
then you could have bought it
but you cannot buy it now
Now winter is almost over in our city
and it has started to get warm here
We are wearing sweater in the videos because
winter is still there in some parts of the country
Alright, the next product has come to us
Let's take it out quickly
And it is a very beautiful sweatshirt
It feels like
salary has came when the event is already over
So what is the use now?
This sweatshirt is in sky blue colour
You get hem at the bottom
and cuffing in the hand
You get a round neck
You get the tag of Overlays
The pricing is written here as ₹1599
You don't have to pay this
If you see at its back,
a very good print has been done
What is written?
Overlays Clothing
Dare, Dare, Dare, Dare
To Dream
And a large tiger has been made
It doesn't look like a tiger,
but a Mongoose
It seems that
it has been created with combination of
tiger, snake and mongoose
You will get some flowers on the side
This print is also lightly embossed
And the quality is good
All these things that I say
is difficult for my subtitle writer to translate
We use certain words in Hindi
that are difficult to translate
they face difficulty in translating them in English
How am I looking on wearing the sweatshirt,
you can see this at the back
Let's quickly go to the next
and the last product
When we thought about doing this haul,
basically, we do a series
on our channel
where we review Youtubers merch
This was a part of it
Although,
I was so disappointed
Many people had similar complaints
that their orders are stuck too,
some of them had paid
but had not received the product yet,
or some of them received it after a month
If we talk about this particular hoodie,
it comes with same amazing
lavender colour
You get hem at the bottom,
cuffing in the hand,
kangaroo pockets,
a large hood,
poor drawstrings,
and lining on the inside
On the left chest,
you get the branding of Overlays
The quality of the fabric is very good
The quality of fur on the inside
is very good
You get a very beautiful back print in it too
Overlays is written here
There is a hand
which is holding a flower
It seems that
the Congress's hand
is holding the lotus of BJP
Wow
Mulayam Singh,
Lalu Yadav,
Congress and BJP,
everything is there in it
You get a lot of textography print at the bottom
You also get a barcode at the bottom
Overlays Clothing is written below it
If you loved this video,
make sure to like the video
Subscribe the channel
Follow us on Instagram and Telegram
You will get their links in the description
Bye for now
Jai Hind
Peace
Boom